Chapter 414 – Everyone Blanked Out

Ye Xiu didn’t stop with his progress as he chatted with the stranger, who never lifted his gaze from Ye Xiu’s screen. During the first minute, he was shocked by Ye Xiu’s character’s weapon and class. During the second minute, he was astonished by Ye Xiu’s amazing battle skills and maneuvers.

However, the stranger’s expression didn’t change much the second time. He was already as amazed as he thought he could possibly be. Who would have thought that the person in front of him would have even more in store for him?

“Unbelieveable… this is unbelieveable…” the stranger chanted under his breath while watching Ye Xiu killing a horde of monsters as easily as cutting grass. He soon realized that Ye Xiu’s damage wasn’t very good. However, this was rather normal considering that Lord Grim was only level 50. It was clear proof of Ye Xiu’s terrifying skill.

Soon, the battle ended. The stranger stared in awe at the piles of corpses littered all over the map and the full health bar of Ye Xiu’s character. His face almost twitched in extreme shock.

“Incredible!” He finally squeezed out a word of praise. But then the stranger immediately regretted it because the word came nowhere close to what he wished to say. Unfortunately, he couldn’t find any other word to describe it. He found that not only could his face not express his awe accurately, but his vocabulary was the same as well.

“It was okay.” Ye Xiu responded, “A bit slow though.”

“Of course, you’re only level 50.” The stranger blurted out.

Upon seeing Ye Xiu leave the battleground, the stranger gathered up all of his courage and asked, “Brother, do you have time for a round in the Arena?”

“Hm?” Ye Xiu was startled.

“I’m from the eighth server. My character’s name is Ascending.” The stranger introduced himself.

“F*ck me!” Ye Xiu suddenly cried out, surprising both the stranger and Chen Guo.

“What’s wrong?” Ascending was terrified.

“Nothing, nothing. You go ahead and create a room. I’ll be there soon.” Ye Xiu quickly answered.

“Aye!” Ascending jumped up and ran back to his computer.

“Are you okay?” Chen Guo was still surprised about Ye Xiu’s reaction just now. He was always calm and confident, so why was he did he suddenly curse a moment ago? Was Ascending someone very important?

“I’m so stupid.” Ye Xiu murmured.

“I thought so.” Chen Guo snickered.

Ye Xiu cast a helpless glance at Chen Guo, who just found a rare opportunity to mock him, then he continued, “I forgot that the Arena is cross-server. Aren’t I stupid for forgetting such a basic set-up?”

“What?” This time, Chen Guo was startled.

Ye Xiu shook his head, “And I was counting how many days it would take for the tenth server’s players to reach level 50. Tsk, tsk, tsk!”

“How come you never said anything?” Ye Xiu asked Chen Guo.

“I can be stupid too, can’t I?” Chen Guo was a bit depressed. The Arena being cross-server was basic knowledge among the players. In the end, the top tier professional player forgot about. Chen Guo, an experienced player who had played the game for five years, also forgot about it. Su Mucheng apparently forgot as well. When the three of them were together during New Year’s holiday to play the game, Ye Xiu had mentioned this problem. In conclusion, Su Mucheng didn’t see anything wrong and spent her time with Ye Xiu and Chen Guo worrying stupidly.

This… Did everyone just blank out?

Chen Guo pondered.

Ye Xiu had definitely blanked out; that was obvious. But for she and Su Mucheng to blank out on the exact same issue simultaneously… that was a bit questionable. This was a very basic rule and there was absolutely no reason for all of them to have forgotten about it.

Or could it have been because of something else? Such as a unwavering trust in Ye Xiu from the both of them?

Perhaps it was simply because he said it, the two girls believed it without a second thought. Perhaps it was because he was worried about the issue, so they went along with it and worried about it with him. They had only tried to think up a solution to the problem, but never bothered to check if the problem itself actually existed.

Was this guy… actually that reliable?

Chen Guo was having a bad time believing that this listless guy would actually gain her trust.

It’s probably because of his identity. Chen Guo answered her own question weakly.

On the other side, Ye Xiu was already rushing to the Arena. Then Ascending darted back, “Brother, I got the room. Fixed Field, Arena 5. Room 4689. The password is poiuy. “

“Poiuy? What does that mean?” Chen Guo was interested in the odd password.

Ascending turned and glanced at Chen Guo,”Look at the keyboard.”

Chen Guo looked down. From the right upper corner to the left of the keyboard, the first few keys were poiuy.

“Fixed Field? That’s unnecessary. Let’s go to the regular Arena!” Ye Xiu didn’t pay any attention to the password, but he was unhappy about the mode.

“Ah?” Ascending was stunned.

“I… quest requirement.” Ye Xiu replied weakly. This wasn’t a good explanation at all. A level 50 challenging a level 70 without being in the Fixed Field could easily be misunderstood as contempt against the opponent. Ye Xiu had no disrespect whatsoever against Ascending. It was just that victories in the Fixed Field didn’t count, so it would be useless for the Heavenly Domain Challenge. Then again, Ye Xiu didn’t need this particular victory, so if Ascending insisted, Ye Xiu would be fine with doing it in Fixed Field.

Ascending didn’t mind at all though. ”Wait a sec.” He nodded and dashed back. In a moment, he got a new room in the regular Arena and raced back to tell Ye Xiu.

After seeing Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim enter the room successfully, Ascending sprinted back to his own computer to start the match.

Ascending was a level 70 Mechanic and seemed to be PvP veteran. He rushed forward purposefully the moment the match started.

Ye Xiu didn’t hold back at all. He had refused a match in the Fixed Field, if he still held back, that would be truly disrespectful towards Ascending. As a result, Ye Xiu attacked fiercely and decisively ended the match in 1 minute and 14 seconds.

The match time was a bit longer than usual as expected. 20 levels of level suppression and 20 levels of equipment difference were all too real. Even if Ye Xiu could guarantee that he hit Ascending with every attack, the actual damage would still be reduced significantly.

Still, from a normal player’s point of view, this was an extremely one-sided match. After the first hit from Ye Xiu, Ascending never even got any chance to retaliate until his character died.

“Hey, was that necessary? Aren’t you going a bit too harsh on him?” Chen Guo couldn’t stand to watch.

“I was worried that he would think I belittled him by refusing a match in the Fixed Field, so I thought I’d show him that I really am much better than he is.” Ye Xiu explained.

“Awesome!” Just as Ye Xiu finished his sentence, Ascending sent him a comment.

Ye Xiu’s hands hovered over the keyboard. He wanted to reply, but couldn’t find anything to say. The usual “You’re not half bad either” wouldn’t work at all. Ascending lost this match so completely that Ye Xiu could find nothing to praise him with. If Ye Xiu were to applaud Ascending’s skills, the courtesy would have been so overly untruthful that it would just sound like mockery. After a few moments of thought, Ye Xiu settled on using a smiley face as a reply.

“Shall we try again?” Ascending asked carefully. His diction changed this time. He used “try” after realizing that he might not even get the slightest chance to attack at all.

“Okay.” Ye Xiu agreed, and the two started a second round. Ye Xiu already showed Ascending his true level of skills, so he went easy on Ascending. This time, Ascending lost at the 1 minute and 30 second mark.

“That was really awesome…” Ascending messaged again. This time, he didn’t lose as miserably as last time, but the match was still one-sided.

“It was okay…” Ye Xiu was rather modest.

“Sorry for the trouble.” Ascending texted again.

“Um? No more?”

“Nah, I can’t beat you. The difference between us is too great. I need a long time of practice to reach your level.” Ascending explained.

“Good luck.” Ye Xiu ended the conversation, and both of them left the room. Ye Xiu turned around and spoke to Chen Guo, “See, a smart guy who actually knows the difference.”

“The ‘smart guy’ is back.” Chen Guo saw Ascending running back when she lifted her head.

“If you don’t mind, could I have your contact info? If there’s another chance, I’d like to challenge you again.” Ascending asked humbly.

“Are you in the Heavenly Domain?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Ah!”

“I’ll be there soon. We’ll meet then.” Ye Xiu clarified.

“Oh, oh. Okay.” Ascending nodded. He looked at Ye Xiu and Chen Guo and added embarrassedly “Excuse me.” Then he ran back to his own computer again.

“Heavenly Domain!” Ye Xiu turned to look at Chen Guo. His clenched fists showed his determination. Ye Xiu paid no attention to the little episode of Ascending. As a pro player, meeting another player was nothing special at all. He had gotten used to it a long time ago.

“Hurry up!” Chen Guo answered.

“While I’m still here, I might as well get a few matches done.” Ye Xiu was still in the Arena. He started to enter rooms randomly in search of a suitable match. The regular Arena had two types: Free Field and Level Field . Because Lord Grim and Ascending had a 20 level gap and it wasn’t in the Level Field to cover such a huge level gap, Lord Grim and Ascending finished their matched in the Free Field.

In the Free Field, levels didn’t matter. However, Ye Xiu couldn’t pick on players whose level was lower than his. Thus, after changing the setting on the level limit for entering rooms, he started his conquest.

A conquest without any resistance.

Ye Xiu’s skills ensured that he could easily defeat any player, with or without the 20 levels of level gap. In the Free Field, high level players were primarily picking on the low level players. If a player really wanted a challenge, he or she would go to level limit type arena. In the end, tons of bullies lost miserably in front of Ye Xiu. The 20 levels of difference in levels and equipments were virtually non-existent.. If Glory wasn’t known for its clean gaming environment, a lot of people would suspect that he was hacking.

Still, there were still a large number of people who found this very suspicious. The biggest proof was that strange weapon. It was complete mystery to them. What kind of weapon would change its shape every other second? Would actually having the hack make one that dominant?

While Ye Xiu swept through the Arena, his character’s name showed up again and again on the official report forum. In the discussion forum for PvP, there were mentions of him everywhere. Lord Grim’s fame had finally spread outside of the tenth server and into the entirety of Glory.

As for Ye Xiu, he saw nothing but the waving hand of the Heavenly Domain as he counted his victories.

Chapter 415 – Sensation

After realizing that the issue of the Arena part of the challenge wasn’t actually an issue, Ye Xiu spent the entire day playing in the Arena. In the Arena section of the official forums, many discussions were being held concerning Lord Grim. More and more posts were created as the day went on and quite a few posts were repeated throughout the day. At the same time, there were just as many reports being made in the report section of the forums.

Lord Grim was hacking.

Quite a lot of players believed this was true due to three main reasons.

One, there was a 20 level difference in levels and equipment, yet he was still crushing his opponents like it was nothing.

Two, the weapon in his hands could change forms. This was absolutely unprecedented. He definitely wasn’t switching to different weapons either.

Third, according to the players who were defeated by him, they had been comboed from start to finish. He was being even more precise than machines.

Any one of the reasons above was enough to make a player doubtful, let alone Lord Grim having all three.

This was something Ye Xiu didn’t know about. He was only aware that getting into rooms was becoming easier and easier; so much so that people were now inviting him into their rooms. Moreover, the players who were crushed by him were quite stubborn. They would often have to be crushed four or five times before reluctantly giving up.

Lord Grim’s fame exploded. The tenth server players were all excited seeing this. Very soon, several tenth server players, who had joined the discussion, listed out Lord Grim’s achievements in the tenth server.

As a result, there were now more suspicious areas that Lord Grim could be reported for.

But soon afterwards, the response from the official company caused an even greater commotion from the players.

In the report section, the officials directly released a stickied post telling everyone who reported Lord Grim for hacking that after a careful investigation, Lord Grim was not found to have violated any rules. The officials asked players to stop sending in further reports on Lord Grim. A warning would be issued for the first offense. A temporary ban would be issued for the second offense.

Glory’s report department had a respectable reputation. One is one. Two is two. They were trustworthy and fair. Their handling of Lord Grim’s reports conformed with their consistent style. This wasn’t why the players were in such an uproar though.

They were in an uproar because if the report department officially declared that there was no problem, then there really were no problems with Lord Grim.

This meant that Lord Grim ignoring the 20 level gap and comboing everyone from start to finish was all skill. As for that unheard of weapon…… if it was unheard of, then it was obviously a Silver weapon. This guy actually had a Silver weapon?

Discussions concerning Lord Grim began to spread. They were no longer limited to the Arena. As long as it was a section in the forums, there would be posts on Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu finally grew aware of this. There was one very obvious point that stood out: no matter where he went, the room would have spectators. More and more spectators joined each time. Several characters appeared over and over again. They were clearly following him.

“You’re popular.” Chen Guo laughed. The two quickly thought of why there were so many spectators. Ye Xiu had clearly become famous in the Arena.

It would be weird if he didn’t become famous. Chen Guo muttered. She had watched on the side for a long time and towards the end, she became numb towards the matches. Ye Xiu wasn’t fighting a match in the Arena. He was practically hitting sandbags! Every time he fought, he would attack and then it would be over……

After playing for the entire day, he hadn’t lost a single time.

No, using the word lose wouldn’t be correct. He never experienced any sort of difficulty. As soon as Ye Xiu attacked, the match would be over.

“You’re not tired?” Chen Guo even asked this type of question. In her eyes, playing each match so fiercely and precisely must be tiring.

“Tired? Why would I be tired?” Ye Xiu asked back.

“Fighting each match like that…….” Chen Guo said. She didn’t know how to describe it.

“Oh…… It’s nothing. It’s very relaxing.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo realized that in Ye Xiu’s eyes, these players weren’t opponents, but ants. Those combos were the same as stepping on an ant. It was extremely easy for him, but the problem was that the ants couldn’t fight back. As a result, the ants cried “How strong! How scary!” The God lifted his foot up again and crushed the crying ant.

Videos of the God crushing ants began to appear, one after the other.

The players were all very excited. Such a prominent character hadn’t appeared in Glory for a long time. Those who appeared were quickly noticed by the Clubs and then pulled into the team to begin their career as pro players. Some of them were quickly washed out. Some worked hard to stand firm in the pro scene. Some became true top tier players in Glory.

And Lord Grim? What would happen to him?

There was no need to doubt his skill right? All of the experienced players confirmed this when they watched the videos. He was able to easily crush high leveled experts one after the other even with a 20 Level disparity. In addition, he even had his own self-made Silver weapon. Any of those points would be enough to make Clubs throw out their olive branches!

Some people even began guessing which team Lord Grim would join. Some people even began analyzing which team Lord Grim would fit the best with. After studying his class, discovering that none of his opponents was lower leveled than him, and noticing that he had played in the Arena for a full day, the players quickly concluded that he was doing the Heavenly Domain challenge.

“He’s a talent!” The players all sighed.

“He’ll quickly become a pro player!” Everyone thought.

No one questioned that the player was already a pro player because no pro player had the free time to run to the game, do the Heavenly Domain challenge, and bully a bunch of normal players all day.

The day quickly passed.

The next day came and players went to the websites for all the big teams to see if there was any news of Lord Grim being scouted. However, there was no news.

Afterwards, they went into all the big Glory forums and discovered that Lord Grim was still an extremely hot topic. A few reporters even tried to interview him by finding him in-game, but none of them succeeded.

All of the gossip was focused on Lord Grim.

Every time a gossiper spoke, Lord Grim would always be mentioned.

This was only the first day too.

The second day, the third day, the fourth day……

Day after day passed. Lord Grim’s path didn’t change. Every day, people would chase after him in the Arena to watch him fight. Some even took the initiative to go into battle. All of them ended in defeat. Being crushed by Lord Grim became an event in Glory after the Spring Festival.

Ye Xiu obviously knew of this after so much activity in the past few days, but he didn’t care. He just wanted to complete the Heavenly Domain challenge. If people wanted to line up and fight him, then that was great.

One day, Huang Shaotian’s low leveled account, Flowing Tree, logged into the game and cried a bunch.

“F*ck your sister! You’re PKing with so many people, but you don’t have time to fight one round with me?” Huang Shaotian had asked to fight him several times, but the fight never happened. He resented it greatly.

“It’s for a quest……” Ye Xiu replied. He didn’t remember ever seeing Troubling Rain giving him an invite, but even if he had, Ye Xiu definitely would have refused. Fighting with Huang Shaotian wouldn’t be a one or two minute match and he might not even win either. It would simply be a waste of time!

“I’ll wait until you get to the Heavenly Domain! You wait!” Huang Shaotian said fiercely.

Ye Xiu replied with a cool face and then ignored him.

The sudden appearance of a prominent character gave Glory players a lot to talk about. The atmosphere seemed to be even more lively than during the Spring Festival event. Some people even bought a tenth server account card and ran to the tenth server to personally watch.

There were clearly many bored players.

But there was one thing players couldn’t understand. They were already clear on what Lord Grim was capable of, so why hadn’t any Clubs invited Lord Grim over?

Every old veteran player had their own team they supported. Quite a few even began contacting the Clubs recommending him.

The Clubs didn’t know whether to laugh or cry.

The Clubs weren’t as stupid and slow as the players thought. Early in the first day, they had all received reports. The Club system had a system similar to those in basketball and football. There were scouts, whether they were part time or full time, that went to dig out potential talents. Now that there was a talent that just directly appeared in front of them, not seeing him would be too stupid. It could be said that on the first day, every Club had received several reports on Lord Grim.

A Club had a managing department, a team, a guild, an equipment research department, scouts…… they were split into many departments. Information among them could be shared or withheld.

Lord Grim was Ye Qiu.

Most of the guilds knew. The teams also knew. But the other departments might not know of this.

But in any case, once things got to this stage, with Lord Grim being pushed in front of the Clubs, this information was quickly shared to every department. The secret that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu quickly became known to everyone in the Club.

As a result, the Clubs had to give up on chasing after him. If he was Ye Qiu, then there was different concern.

While the players were just having fun with this gossip, the Clubs had to think of their interests and began seriously pondering over Ye Qiu’s abrupt fame in the game.

With rumors of Ye Qiu creating a team, the Clubs all had a tacit mutual understanding not to let out the news that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu. If the news leaked, it would be hard to say how many eyes would be enamored, how many would be looking forward to it, how many follow along. For the Clubs, not stirring up trouble for Ye Qiu was already quite nice of them. They didn’t have any reason to help Ye Qiu come back though.

Just how much can he do by himself?

The Clubs didn’t dare look down on Ye Qiu, but they didn’t think he could do much alone. This sort of online sensation in game could be achieved by any pro player. After all, pros were in a completely different world than normal players. Ye Qiu might be building up momentum through this sensation. They couldn’t stop him, but they weren’t going to help him. This was what the Clubs all thought.

Chapter 416 – Against the Great Hero

As the team that kicked out Ye Xiu, Excellent Era felt uneasy. At the first Club meeting of the year, this issue was presented at the table for discussion.

This was a Club meeting, so the participants were the heads of the different departments. For the team, both the captain and vice captain, Sun Xiang and Liu Hao, were present. For the guild, Chen Yehui was present. Apart from them, there were the heads of the research department, the logistics department, the scouting department, the public relations department…… as one of the powerhouses in Glory eSports history, Excellent Era had a well developed and organized infrastructure.

This wasn’t the only issue that would be discussed at the meeting. The new years had just passed, so they started off with good news of their business. It was only until the end of the meeting did they begin talking about Lord Grim, who had swept the Glory community in a storm these past few days.

Chen Yehui glanced uneasily at Liu Hao. Liu Hao had excellent acting skills and looked as if this was news to him.

Chen Yehui couldn’t pretend he didn’t know. These were in-game matters and the relationship between Ye Qiu and Excellent Era couldn’t be erased. If he hadn’t noticed this, he would probably lose his job. Luckily, he had given several believable reports to the director about in-game matters and Lord Grim before. Chen Yehui was only worried that the Club would officially order him to suppress Ye Qiu. He truly didn’t have any confidence he could accomplish such a task.

As a result, in the meeting, when the director asked him to explain the Lord Grim and tenth server situation, he stressed how difficult it was to resist Ye Qiu in the game. Whether it was Blue Brook Guild, Tyrannical Ambition, or Herb Garden, all of them had been toyed with by Ye Qiu. As for Excellent Dynasty, under his wise lead, the guild maintained a good distance away from him from the very start, so they hadn’t suffered too many losses.

However…… because of his disturbance, all of the top guilds were having trouble developing in the tenth server. Excellent Dynasty was no exception.

The director wrinkled his brows at Chen Yehui’s conclusion. Their research in the tenth server was an important step in Excellent Era’s plan to rise back to the top, but they had encountered a large obstacle. This obstacle was something they had created too. If they hadn’t kicked Ye Qiu out of the team, Ye Qiu wouldn’t have ran to the game. If Ye Qiu hadn’t run to the game, with Excellent Dynasty’s huge investment into the tenth server, they would have easily gained the upperhand over the other guilds in the tenth server.

“Hmph, no matter how you look at it, he’s still a pro God. Running to the game and making a name for himself is too shameful as a pro.” After hearing Chen Yehui’s description of Ye Qiu’s might in the tenth server, Sun Xiang gave a very rude remark.

“That’s true, but for our guild, such an opponent is truly formidable.” Chen Yehui obviously didn’t mind puffing up Ye Qiu’s strength. It would be good for him if Sun Xiang rushed into the game in anger and dueled Ye Qiu. Even though he knew that the Club probably wouldn’t permit it, with his rash, young behavior, he might just do it in private, similar to what Liu Hao did.

Speaking of Liu Hao, after the previous discussion, he didn’t make any more movements. Liu Hao said that he would help him deal with Ye Qiu, but made no such moves. Chen Yehui wasn’t happy when he thought of this.

“What’s the current situation for the guild?” The director asked.

“It’s pretty much the same as the other guilds. Because of Ye Qiu’s strength, he’s practically monopolized the dungeon records. To the players in the tenth server, Lord Grim and the guild he created is the number one in the server. We….. sigh…..” Chen Guo let out a sigh, “The situation’s a bit complicated. For now, we’ve moved our troops and resources to the Heavenly Domain. In the tenth server, we’ll maintain our characters’ levels and wait to see if there’s any turn for the better!”

“Ye Qiu’s character is unspecialized? And he had a Silver weapon? Is that correct?” The director asked.

“That’s correct.”

“Is there any information on the Silver weapon?” The director’s gaze shifted to the head of Excellent Era’s research department, Qin Yu.

Qin Yu’s expression was quite serious. After thinking carefully for a good while, he began: “It’s quite obvious what this Silver weapon is. It was specially created for an unspecialized player. The design for the different weapon forms is extremely elaborate. The weapon completely solves the issue with an unspecialized needing to constantly switch weapons. Just from this, it’s clear that this weapon is the work of a genius. We’ve studied it for several days, but we haven’t figured anything substantial out yet. This Silver weapon is something that has never been done before, so there’s no way for us to extrapolate what its stats are.

In terms of Glory, Qin Yu was an extremely experienced player. It wasn’t possible for someone without a good understanding of the game nor plenty of experience to become a part of the research department. The responsibility of the research department was studying equipment and to upgrade equipment. But for an unspecialized…… this was a play style that had already faded away before the creation of the Pro Alliance, so the research department didn’t have much information on unspecialized players. As a result, Qin Yu really couldn’t make too much of an evaluation towards this Silver weapon. He could only admit that their department had no idea where to start with this weapon.

“Where did Ye Qiu get such a Silver weapon? Has he ever talked about this with you?” The director asked.

“This…… I don’t think so…….” Qin Yu wasn’t too sure. Ye Qiu was Excellent Era’s captain for seven years and had communicated with the research department many times. For One Autumn Leaf’s Silver weapon, Evil Annihilation, it could be said that without them, it wouldn’t have evolved to such a level. Amongst the countless times they had talked, Qin Yu really couldn’t remember them ever talking about this.

“Then can you be certain that none of the other Clubs made this?” The director asked.

“I’m certain of that.” Qin Yu nodded his head.

There were quite a few people at the meeting. Right now, the majority of them were silent. In reality, many of them didn’t really know about the inside information on Ye Qiu’s retirement. They had no say in the team’s personnel. But as a branch of the Club, they had heard quite a few rumors about Ye Qiu and the Club. The director’s attitude towards the issue of Ye Qiu was clearly a type of vigilant attitude. From this, they were able to get a general feel for the situation. In any case, they wouldn’t say too much. How to deal with Ye Qiu wasn’t really their departments’ matters.

“Keep an eye on Ye Qiu’s movements.” The director turned his head to warn Chen Yehui.

“I understand.”

“The other guilds probably know of his identity too, right?” The director asked.

“Yes.” Chen Yehui nodded his head.

“What are their stances?”

“Retreat……” Chen Yehui smiled bitterly.

“Even Tyrannical Ambition?” The director asked.

Chen Yehui nodded his head.

“Is he really going to rise up so smoothly just like this?” The director looked as if he couldn’t sit still, but quickly realized his current stance. No matter how it was said, Ye Qiu was one of Excellent Era’s great heroes. His current attitude wasn’t suitable to be displayed in front of everyone. At the very least, his expression was making the others tremble in fear.

After regaining his composure, he slowly said: “The rumors are saying that Ye Qiu is planning on creating his own team. If that’s the case, even though he’s certainly a person that will go down in the history of our team, he’ll also become our opponent. We hope that he’ll succeed, but as an opponent, we know better than anyone else how terrifying he is. We have to make proper preparations for him.”

He was clearly trying to save the situation from before. After saying this, the director concluded the meeting. Then, he quietly had the team and guild members stay. These were the people who were going to be at the front lines for dealing with Ye Qiu.

In the game, Lord Grim wasn’t hacking. This was something the officials had confirmed. The players couldn’t understand why such a skilled player wouldn’t be fought for by the Clubs and could only guess why. After several days of fighting in the Arena, Ye Xiu had finally completed all the Arena portion of the Heavenly Domain challenge.

Even though there were a lot of requirements such as how many wins, how many wins in a row, winning in a short amount of time, winning with lots of health left…….

Apart from the number of wins needed, the other requirements were just like the other tests.

For example, for winning several matches in a row, once it was completed, it would change from five wins in a row, to ten wins in a row, and so on.

For health, the first test required a win at 50% health left. After this was done, it would become 60%, then 70%, all the way until winning with no health lost.

Relatively speaking, the health part of the test was easy. After all, it could be accomplished through luck after many tries. Most players were stuck on the winning several matches in a row part. Once a match was lost, all previous progress would be reset. Countless players stamped their feet in frustration at this part. Later, this part became a type of business. Quite a few players relied on intentionally losing to players in order to gain a profit from helping others complete the challenge.

Because of this type of cheating, the rules were constantly being revised. But players would always find some sort of loophole around it. The two sides fought over this ever since the beginning and it was still going on.

As for Ye Xiu, this wasn’t a problem. How many times he won was how many times in a row he won. It didn’t matter if the test required five wins in a row or twenty wins in a row. He would finish it on his first try.

Health, time, etc. Ye Xiu finished each test on his first try. Due to the many spectators watching, Lord Grim had become known as the most efficient player to complete the Arena part of the Heavenly Challenge.

The Heavenly Challenge was what the players called the Heavenly Domain Challenge. They were only sad that they couldn’t record or watch the quest chain part of the challenge. All of Lord Grim’s fighting in the Arena had been completely recorded by the players though.

Chapter 417 – The Level 50 Conflict

Complete!

Not just Ye Xiu, all of the players who were paying attention to Lord Grim knew that he had already finished the Arena portion of the Heavenly Challenge. It wasn’t that the players accurately counted every one of his wins, but rather, the number of wins a character had in the Arena could be easily searched by looking at the character’s info.

After so many days of watching Lord Grim, besides the Silver weapon, they knew of all his equipment from head to toe. The number of wins that Lord Grim had in the Arena could be seen on his character info page.

However, there was no way for them to know how much of the quest chain he had completed. But the players in the Heavenly Domain had already made their preparations. They were ready at any moment to pounce on Lord Grim, the first Level 50 character to reach the Heavenly Domain.

It was true that the quest chain was difficult, but after seeing Lord Grim’s performance in the Arena, the players were certain that the quest chain wasn’t a problem for him. It was only a matter of time.

The players weren’t wrong. It really was just a matter of time. The time it would be quite long though. Chen Guo personally watched as Ye Xiu took a whole three hours to defeat a BOSS.

There was nothing that could be done about it. This BOSS had a passive that let him recover health automatically. Lord Grim’s damage output was very weak because of his level and equipment. With this automatic healing reducing the damage even further, he could slowly whittle it down. He couldn’t make mistakes either because a moment of rest would let the BOSS heal up a bit and destroy some of his previous efforts.

During this battle, Chen Guo was able to witness Ye Xiu’s endurance. For this fight, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim carry a huge amount of mana potions. Once the mana pool hit ten percent, he would begin giving Lord Grim mana potions to drink. Some of these mana potions were instant recovery ones, which were used at the appropriate times. Throughout the long three hour battle, Lord Grim was able to keep his mana pool up.

Of course, this also had to do with Ye Xiu’s control over his skills. If not, with an unspecialized character’s arsenal of 120 kills, if he just randomly threw one after the other out, it wouldn’t matter how many potions he brought. Consuming potions had a cooldown too. This amount of time had to be calculated when using skills. If potions didn’t have cooldowns, then there wouldn’t be a need for learning how to endure; just making sure enough potions were prepared would be enough.

This three hour battle was, without a doubt, the most difficult test for Ye Xiu. After he finished this fight, he couldn’t hide his exhaustion. This was because he couldn’t relax at all during the battle. A single minute of slack could require two minutes to make up for it. Ye Xiu was truly like a machine during this and conducted the battle steadily and precisely for three whole hours.

Even Tang Rou, someone who refused to admit defeat, fell silent after watching the battle.

Tang Rou had come back on the ninth day of the Spring Festival and quickly reached Level 50 as well. Moreover, she was also trying the Heavenly Domain Challenge.

Tang Rou was actually quite familiar with the challenge. In the past, she had helped Chen Guo finish the challenge and had once studied it earnestly. For the sections that tested for a player’s mechanics, even though every scenario was random, Tang Rou had a good mechanical foundation. She might not be as precise and quick as Ye Xiu, but passing those sections wasn’t a problem.

In the Arena, Tang Rou also tried challenging it at Level 50, but she was far from being as clean and decisive as Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu knew very well how significant the 20 level suppression was. Tang Rou didn’t have that experience. When she used a Falling Flower Palm, the level suppression made it so that the opponent would barely be knocked back. The opponent would then use a powerful skill as he was being pushed back. It wouldn’t be an instant kill, but it made it very difficult for Tang Rou. She was far from Ye XIu beating his opponents so easily.

However, with Tang Rou’s mechanical skill, she was probably be considered near unbeatable to playing characters at the same level as her. The 20 level suppression had caught her unprepared in the beginning, but after slowly adapting to it, she was gradually doing better and better. The part of the test that required several wins in a row made her want to cough blood though. After all, Tang Rou wasn’t as knowledgeable as Ye Xiu. When she bumped into a strong opponent, she would sometimes capsize and have to start all over again.

Because of Tang Rou’s personality, she refused to duck away and instead continued to challenge it. Ye Xiu and Chen Guo knew of her stubbornness and were too lazy to try and advise her otherwise. But today, after seeing Ye Xiu’s bitter three hour battle, Tang Rou fell silent.

After all, she was no longer a noob like before. She completely understood how difficult the battle was. She knew that the key part of the battle was the ability to endure. This was something she had learned from Ye Xiu before, but there was no way she was good enough to last three hours like Ye Xiu. And if she couldn’t do this, she would run out of mana. Without mana, the damage output from a Level 50’s normal attacks compared to the BOSS’s automatic health recovery would only end in tragedy.

Perhaps she could do it if Ye Xiu was on the side giving her pointers, but this wasn’t what Tang Rou wanted. After staring blankly for a good while, she finally spoke: “That part looks very hard. I probably can’t pass it.”

“Yeah!” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

Thus, Tang Rou looked at her Soft Mist and saw that she would be stuck on that part of the quest chain. Giving up halfway was something that made her heart hurt very much, but she clearly knew that the obstacle wasn’t something she could clear. Continuing to try stubbornly would be too unwise.

Should she first go to the dungeon and practice her endurance? Tang Rou thought of the training program Ye Xiu had devised for this. She turned her character around and actually planned on heading to the dungeon.

“Where are you going?” Ye Xiu saw her character move and suddenly asked.

“I’m going to try my endurance capability.” Tang Rou said.

“There’s no need to fix this knot at this moment!” Ye Xiu bitterly laughed, “Just pay attention when you practice and you’ll be fine. Improving is a gradual process. It’s not worth it paying so much effort just for this obstacle!”

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist continued to run in the direction of the dungeon as if she hadn’t heard what Ye Xiu said. But when she was about to arrive, she suddenly nodded her head, “True. The obstacle isn’t that important. I’m going to level, while improving.” After saying this, she checked the potions she had in her inventory and rushed into the Level 50 dungeon.

There were many Level 50 dungeons. This was because Level 50 had been the level cap for three years. Leveling to 50 wasn’t that difficult. How was the company supposed to keep the players interested? By giving players all sorts of things to do at Level 50. It could be said that in Glory, players could only truly experience the joy of the game after reaching the max level.

After this, as the level cap increased, more high leveled dungeons appeared, but the Level 50 range still had many classic dungeons or dangerous scenarios that didn’t need to be closed. Once a player reached Level 50, there were many wild maps and dungeons to choose from. The top guilds would naturally have more places to compete at.

However, there were only a few characters that had reached Level 50.

At Level 50, the dungeons wouldn’t only be 5 player dungeons. There were 10 players ones, 20 player ones, even large-scale 50 player ones.

Because there weren’t enough characters, in order to run 10 player and up dungeons, the top guilds needed to party together. The top guilds currently encountered quite a few complications mostly because of the level gap.

The Level 50 dungeons used to be the highest leveled dungeons, so there weren’t any level ranges. Level 50 dungeons could only be entered at Level 50 and above. But just like with the level ranges, lower leveled players couldn’t enter the dungeon and higher leveled teams couldn’t set records.

Because of this, only having Level 50 as the level range was a bit awkward.

Right now, it wasn’t possible for the guilds to form a 50 player Level 50 dungeon team. By the time they could form such a large team, if the first string elites continued to level, when the other guild members arrived, they would already be past Level 50 and wouldn’t be able to compete for the dungeon record. The first string elites were the elites of the elites of their guilds.

It was quite a problem. Should they continue to level or wait for everyone to reach Level 50 and have a large team to advance together? The top guilds began discussing this. And from Level 50 onwards, the same problem would occur at Level 55, 60, 65. These levels were all once the level cap and would all have one level range restriction dungeons as well. At the same time, 5 player dungeons wouldn’t be cared for too much. Whether it was to show the guild’s strength or for good equipment and materials, the larger the dungeon restriction the better. Seven or eight player elite teams could only strut around small dungeons. What was the point in that? Even worse, they couldn’t even show their strength in small dungeons. Wasn’t there Lord Grim’s team still?

But for large dungeons, they believed that Lord Grim wouldn’t be able to compete with them. Guild Happy had only just been created. Apart from the five player team, everyone else was just a bunch of noobs. How could they compete with the experienced teams of the top guilds?

How should they continue? The top guilds obviously wouldn’t discuss this with each other. They planned on their own. And with Lord Grim’s recent upsurge of fame, it seemed like he was about to reach the Heavenly Domain.

“So he’s coming……” In the Heavenly Domain, the top guilds had been watching Lord Grim attentively long ago. In particular, with how much of an uproar he had created with his Heavenly Domain Challenge, even the Clubs had noticed him. After knowing of his identity, no one would dare look down on him anymore.

Chapter 418 – Entering the Heavenly Domain

Entering the Heavenly Domain was an exciting event for Glory players. You have to look at it from Chen Guo’s perspective. Choose a good day, relax, take a bath, pay your respects to those gods of luck, and then enter the Heavenly Domain. But for Ye Xiu, after completing the quest chain, he didn’t look excited at all. He just strolled right into the Heavenly Domain.

Ye Xiu might be calm, but the world wasn’t. Getting into the Heavenly Domain was a major event. The system would publicly announce it. It would be announced to the tenth server, as well as the Heavenly Domain.

This was the first announcement of this kind for the tenth server and another one wasn’t going to happen any time soon. But because the tenth server was full of new players, many of them didn’t really know about the difficulty of the challenge, so they weren’t too shocked. In their eyes, it was just another announcement about Lord Grim.

But for the Heavenly Domain, their response was enormous!

Since the character entering the Heavenly Domain was from the tenth server, the announcement would naturally make it clear which server the character came from. Tenth server. These two words dazzled as brightly as the name ‘Lord Grim’. The old birds of the Heavenly Domain obviously knew that the tenth server had just opened for two months and knew what level they were at. Entering the Heavenly Domain at this time was definitely a record.

Lord Grim’s fame these days was already great enough. Most of them had already prepared for this, so they weren’t surprised. However, there were always a few slow ones. They weren’t aware of Lord Grim and went crazy after seeing that a tenth server player had entered the Heavenly Domain.

The instant that Ye Xiu stepped into the Heavenly Domain, he received who knew how many system notifications. The excited Heavenly Domain players had been waiting for this famous player to arrive for several days already. As soon as they saw the announcement, many of them immediately sent a friend invite to pay their respects, trying to pull him in —– and for all sorts of other reasons.

No matter how friendly Ye Xiu was, it wasn’t possible to answer all of them. The Heavenly Domain had players from all of the nine previous servers. The total population surpassed that of a single server. Everyone knew of Lord Grim because of his recent popularity, so the number of friend invites sent had to be a record. Accepting or rejecting the invites one by one could only be done by a machine.

Ignoring these invites, Ye Xiu first took a look at where Lord Grim was located and confirmed his coordinates. In the game, entering the Heavenly Domain looked like a teleport, but in reality, the servers were doing a calculation. There was no set starting position when going into the Heavenly Domain. But because the Heavenly Domain was created on year five of the game, the level cap had been Level 55 at that time. The Level 55 and up areas hadn’t been created yet, so the random teleport location to the Heavenly Domain was limited to within the Level 55 areas.

Ye Xiu checked his coordinates and looked around him to get a general understanding of where he was.

Even though he was in a Level 55 area and most players in the Heavenly Domain were Level 70, it didn’t mean that the area was empty. The majority of low-level equipment, apart from those with special effects that had a bit of value, weren’t valuable to Level 70 players. However, materials didn’t have levels. Whether it was a piece of self-made equipment using an equipment editor or an in-game piece of crafted equipment, they often used a few pieces of low-level materials. Moreover, the lower the level of the material, the greater the amount of material was needed. As a result, even for Level 55 areas, there were still quite a few players wandering around.

Ye Xiu didn’t seek for these yet. Leveling was still his main goal. However, an only Level 50 Lord Grim couldn’t even enter the Heavenly Domain dungeons. He couldn’t even do any quests. This was also because of his level. Ye Xiu could only grind it out for these five levels and these monsters were also higher leveled.

Of course, a monster that was five levels higher wasn’t a problem for Ye Xiu. However, in the Heavenly Domain, the dangers were never the NPCs, but the players. In the Heavenly Domain, killing someone didn’t need a reason. If you wanted to kill, then go ahead. It was just that chaotic.

It could be said that the Heavenly Domain and the normal server were almost two different games. One was more PvP-oriented, the other more PvE-oriented. Of course, the players could choose and the game wouldn’t force the choice. Moreover, in order to maintain the fun for those who didn’t like the Heavenly Domain, they didn’t stop releasing post-game content in the normal servers either. As a result, there was also a large amount of players who didn’t like the Heavenly Domain and stayed nice and safe in the normal servers to have fun.

But no matter the case, the Heavenly Domain would always be a sort of attraction. Here, the materials and equipment were better than those in the normal servers. No matter what content the game company released, that distance would always be maintained. Thus, quite a few players ran to the Heavenly Domain to get equipment and brought it back to the normal servers to show off their might. These types of players were naturally looked down on up to the point where players unanimously attacked them. The Heavenly Domain players looked down on them. The normal server players hated them. With the general hate for them, there were very few players of this type left.

However, it wasn’t possible to eradicate lowly people. The tenth server might not have anyone like this yet, but that was only because no one had reached the Heavenly Domain. In other servers, as long as one searched the forums, there would often be posts looking to suppress this type of people.

Ye Xiu urgently needed more levels, so after understanding where he was, he immediately began training.

It was true that Level 55 areas weren’t empty, but they weren’t too populated either. Ye Xiu also knew how famous his Lord Grim was right now, so he didn’t want too many people watching him. He took great pains to avoid others and found a place where no one was at to peacefully level.

Just as he began, he suddenly noticed that there were people coming over from a certain direction. Ye Xiu didn’t care too much in the beginning, but he soon realized that they were heading directly towards his position. He immediately took up his guard and hid behind a wall. Then, he moved his head just a tiny bit out to see the two characters heading towards him.

“Ha ha ha, how could you be so scared!” Chen Guo laughed.

Ye Xiu turned his head and looked at her: “I can’t be careless.”

“Trust me. It’s nothing.” Chen Guo said.

“How do you know?” Ye Xiu said. He glanced at Chen Guo’s screen and went speechless.

Sure enough, it was nothing. Because among those two players was Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze.

The two had finally met each other in game. Chen Guo was still a bit excited. No matter the case, she was still meeting up with one of the Gods she respected greatly, even if her respect for the God had gone down a lot after getting to know him better.

“Why didn’t you accept my friend invite!” Chen Guo felt quite good using such a tone towards a God.

“How am I supposed to do that?” Ye Xiu said as he pointed at his friend invites. The system notifications filled up the screen as friend invites continued to be received. The scroll bar was becoming shorter and shorter by the second. The amount of friend invites he was getting kept increasing.

“You’re really popular.” Chen Guo began to sweat.

Ye Xiu was helpless. He cleared away all of the invites.

“You add me first and then I’ll accept.” Chen Guo said, but after no response for a long time. She turned to look at Ye Xiu who just sat there silently staring at his screen dumbly. Chen Guo looked at his screen and saw that his message window had stopped moving. The entire game had froze.

“Frozen……. Frozen?” Chen Guo had a hard time believing it. With today’s technology, the word “frozen” had practically been forgotten by everyone. Today, Ye Xiu had just tried to clear his invites, but the game froze because of it. Just how many invites did he get? There were so many that his computer wasn’t able to handle it in a short amount of time.

“Just wait a bit……” Chen Guo was the owner of an Internet Cafe, so she still had some understanding of computers. It looked like a frozen computer, but it wasn’t actually. The system was trying to clear all the invites and couldn’t deal with his other commands. The clearing was still going underway. It was just that the clearing was using too many resources and seemed like it was ignoring the user.

Ye Xiu could only wait. From Chen Guo’s screen, she saw that Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze had a Battle Mage called Forest Landscape next to her.

Chen Guo had introduced this Battle Mage to Ye Xiu before. When she had left Excellent Dynasty, he had left with her. According to Chen Guo, his mechanics were just a bit worse than hers, which meant that he could really only play in-game. There wasn’t much hope of him being good enough to join the team.

“Look at this guy. His computer froze. Hold on a sec.” Ye Xiu heard Chen Guo talk to Forest Landscape.

“Does he know who I am?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Yes, I told him.” Chen Guo nodded her head. After leaving Excellent Dynasty with Chen Guo, the two had gotten quite close. Chen Guo had already told Forest Landscape of Ye Qiu in private. Forest Landscape was one of Ye Qiu’s loyal fans and was obviously very shocked. He had hoped that he would one day meet with him. Today, after hearing that the God was coming to the Heavenly Domain, he immediately rushed over with Chen Guo. Once he heard that the God’s character was frozen, his admiration for him increased even more.

He really deserves to be called a God! How long had it been since he heard of a computer freezing from Glory. God truly was extraordinary.

Ye Xiu sat there for five minutes. His screen suddenly moved and all of those previous messages were cleared. But Ye Xiu quickly discovered that another flurry of notifications flashed. Players were still sending friend invites. How could Ye Xiu have such a tragedy occur again? He clicked rapidly and rejected all of the invites.

“Forest Landscape.” In-game, Chen Guo introduced him to Ye Xiu.

“IDOL!!!” Forest Landscape blurted out, not waiting for Chen Guo to introduce Ye Xiu.

Chapter 419 – It’s Not That Simple

In reality, Ye Xiu didn’t actually have much experience interacting with his fans. The fact that he was an idol for so many years even with him hiding the entire time was simply a miracle. This type of player could only appear in eSports. Facing an excited fan, Ye Xiu displayed his usual calmness and didn’t appear tongue tied. He acted as if his fan was a normal person and said a simple “Hi.”

“I’m a big fan of yours! You definitely have to return to the pro scene!” Forest Landscape said.

“Of course.” Ye Xiu said.

Forest Landscape didn’t say anything afterwards. Even though he was facing an idol he admired, besides expressing his sincere support, he couldn’t think of anything else to say.

“What are you planning on doing now?” Chen Guo asked. Her voice could be heard twice, both in game and outside of the game, making it sound a bit weird.

“I’m obviously going to level!” Ye Xiu said.

“Let’s party up. I’ll carry you.” Chen Guo said and sent Ye Xiu a party invite.

“You guys carrying me……. might not be faster than me leveling on my own……” Ye Xiu said.

In a party, the individual would gain less experience per monster, but would kill monsters faster. Alone, the individual would gain more experience per monster, but would kill monsters slower. Leveling speed depended on how much experience was gained in a certain amount of time, so whether or not leveling alone or leveling with a party depended on the individual player’s skill and the party’s efficiency.

Ye Xiu was a top God. There was no need to question his individual skill, which was why partying with others might not be faster for Ye Xiu.

“But it won’t be as tiring.” Chen Guo said.

It was true. Whether it was more efficient to level alone or level with a party depended on the circumstances. However, leveling with a party was certainly more relaxing than leveling alone; that was indisputable. Thinking of this,Ye Xiu didn’t persist. Leveling alone was a bit faster, but it wasn’t significant enough to argue over.

As a result, the three partied up. They were just killing wild monsters, so there didn’t need to be any leading or cooperation. It was simply see a monster, kill a monster. Chen Guo and Forest Landscape were veteran players and were bullying Level 55 monsters as Level 70 players. What pressure could there be? Ye Xiu might be low leveled, but with his skill, saying that the monsters were being bullied would be being polite. There was naturally no suspense.

Chen Guo and Forest Landscape had specially come here to help him level and had already decided earlier that they would accompany him all the way to Level 70. As a result, they didn’t have anything else planned and stayed the entire time, killing Level 55 monsters. The Level 55 monsters obviously had some good drops, but because their levels were too high or too low, the chances were low. All it did was make the monotonous grinding slightly more interesting. Though for the two of them, how could accompanying their idol to level be boring? Doing this was very fun for them.

After leveling for an hour, the three chatted for a bit. Suddenly, they saw Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim stop and heard him say: “Someone’s coming.”

“So what?” Chen Guo didn’t understand.

“They’re heading towards us.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha ha ha!” Chen Guo laughed, “The Heavenly Domain really is more chaotic than normal servers, but what’s there to be afraid of? Aren’t you a God?”

Forest Landscape didn’t make known his position, but in his heart, he didn’t think much of it either. PKing in the Heavenly Domain was very normal. Being ambushed by malicious players while leveling was something most players had experienced before. Not only that but they were completely prepared for this to happen. While Ye Xiu’s reaction was somewhat on the cautious side, Forest Landscape also thought that since he was a God, being so cautious for something small like this lowered his image of God a bit.

But Ye Xiu didn’t feel embarrassed at all. He only added: “It’s different.”

“Different? What’s different?” Chen Guo asked.

“In the tenth server, after Thousand Waves Lake, the top guilds stopped bothering us. Do you really think they would just come to peaceful terms with us so easily?” Ye Xiu said.

“That…… usually….. Not.” Chen Guo understood the relationship between guilds quite well. If the guilds weren’t fighting, it didn’t mean that they were at peace with each other. It only meant that the two were equal in strength and didn’t want to make any rash movements. If a guild had a problem, the other guilds wouldn’t feel bad hitting it while it was down. The harder the guild was hit, the better. Was Guild Happy viewed in this way by the top guilds? Chen Guo already had a deep understanding of their situation.

There was nothing they could do at Thousand Waves Lake, but saying that they had completely given up was something Chen Guo highly doubted. During those days, she had been helping Ye Xiu try to figure out what their plans were! It was just that later, the guilds showed no signs of movement. Ye Xiu didn’t say anything either and just left it at that. Now that Ye Xiu brought it up, Chen Guo naturally associated the incoming players to the guilds and immediately said: “Are you worried that they would dispatch troops in the Heavenly Domain?”

“They were without a doubt waiting for this opportunity because if my character was to continue leveling, it would definitely have to enter the Heavenly Domain. But in the Heavenly Domain, I’m only Level 50. They have a 20 level advantage and have an abundant number of troops. How could they let such a good opportunity go?” Ye Xiu said.

“You had already expected this to happen?”

“Yeah.” Ye Xiu replied.

Forest Landscape had heard of Ye Xiu’s deeds in the tenth server from Chen Guo. Hearing the two of them talk, he had a good understanding of the situation. Thinking of the 20 level advantage and that every top guild was sending in their experts to kill him, his image of his God immediately went back up and his respect even increased. He really deserved to be called a God. He pulled the wind wherever he went.

Seeing those players heading straight for them, Ye Xiu stayed on alert, but he didn’t panic. Because he had been on guard since the start, his leveling location had been chosen with this in mind. When they killed monsters, they went through a relatively open map, so that they would discover incoming players early. Seeing that there were only a total of five players heading towards them without any movements elsewhere, it probably wasn’t an ambush. Even so, Ye Xiu had to be careful.

After waiting for the five players to come closer and seeing the guild tags on top of their heads, the three were very surprised.

The guild name on top of their heads wasn’t one from a Club. Because of how the game was set up, guilds could only have up to 10,000 players. However, a team definitely had more than 10,000 fans. As a result, the Clubs would often set up branches in order to accept more fans. These branch guilds often had an obvious indicator to which Club it belonged to. The guild name of the five players in front of them had nothing to do with any of the Clubs though.

“They’re from Justice.” Chen Guo called out the other party’s guild name.

“Hm? Who are they?” Ye Xiu asked. He could tell from Chen Guo’s tone that they had some background to them.

“Heavenly Justice is a player guild. It’s quite powerful. Their guild leader is called Loulan Slash. I heard that he comes from a rich family and used money to create his guild.” Chen Guo explained to Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu hadn’t paid attention to things in-game for a long time, so how could he know of these types of player guilds?

“Oh……” Ye Xiu understood after hearing Chen Guo’s introduction. No matter the online game, the company couldn’t stop people from spending money in order to get stronger. Put some money in and even if you didn’t have the skill, you could get a fully body of powerful equipment, which would be more than enough to bully the majority of players. Calling someone who spent money to get stronger as someone with no skill was wrong. Those who were willing to spend money meant that they at least cared about the game. No matter how bad their mechanics were, they wouldn’t be worse than a noob.

This was why Ye Xiu didn’t discriminate these types of players. It was the opposite for him actually. He was quite envious of them. Using money to get equipment would save a lot of time……

“They shouldn’t have anything to do with the guilds backed by Clubs.” Chen Guo continued. The players from Heavenly Justice soon arrived. They didn’t even look at the monsters around them and headed straight for them. If they weren’t looking for trouble, Ye Xiu could only guess what their goals were. There was nothing he could do. He was too popular!

When they got closer, the five slowed down. But since they were in-game characters, their walking animation was set by the system, so their walking was very ordinary. However, the equipment on them was clearly extraordinary. With Ye Xiu’s experience, he didn’t even need to look up their info pages to know that their equipment were top quality. It had to be known that even in the pro scene, not every character had self-made equipment from head to toe. A lot of their equipment were Orange equipment from in-game. For these types of equipment that could be found in-game, many players had them and definitely wouldn’t be hard to get for someone with money.

The equipment on these five players would definitely make any player in-game envious, especially the one in the middle with the ID Loulan Slash. His character had a Greatsword that even Ye Xiu recognized. This sword was called “Swordpoint”. It was a Level 65 Orange weapon. Even though it wasn’t a Level 70 weapon, it was even used in the pro scene.

This Greatsword had a special effect, which had to do with the character’s Physical Attack and the item hotkey. For every weapon put on a hotkey, the character would have a 10% increase in Physical Attack.

In Glory, there were a total of 12 item hotkeys. In other words, if they were all weapons, the character could have a 120% increase in Physical Attack, which was very powerful. In theory, “Swordpoint” allowed for the highest Physical Attack in the game. The issue of how to self-make the special effect of “Swordpoint” had perplexed the research teams in Clubs ever since the weapon had appeared in game.

TLN: Nom can you update the glossary if there is new terms? Thanks

I can update the glossary after I finish checking a chapter (or an arc). It would be a bit slow though

Chapter 420 – I’m His Boss

There were only things you couldn’t think of, but there was nothing you couldn’t make.

This was one thing the game was proud of. It didn’t matter if their words were just an exaggeration. It was indeed true. As long as you could find the item in the game, it was 100% possible that you could make it. This meant that Swordpoint’s unique special effect could be added onto a Silver weapon. However, even after many years of research, no one had found a way to do it.

“Swordpoint” ‘s unique special effect made it popular in the game and was considered as a top tier weapon for Swordsman classes. Because of its power, it was obviously a very rare drop. Loulan Slash had one, but he probably hadn’t gotten it himself.

“That Greatsword is called Swordpoint. You should know of it!” It wasn’t a secret that Loulan Slash possessed Swordpoint. Chen Guo was still introducing him to Ye Xiu, but she didn’t know that Ye Xiu had already recognized this weapon.

“I know. I already saw it.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh.” Chen Guo didn’t say anymore because Loulan Slash and his four party members were in front of them.

Very soon, a chat bubble appeared over Loulan Slash’s head along with a smiley face: “Nice to meet you :)”

This was one of the most popular ways to chat in Glory. The player used his voice to communicate, but because the character couldn’t show the player’s facial expression, many people liked to use emojis as a replacement.

“Nice to meet you too :)” Ye Xiu did the same and added a smiley face as well.

“Brother Lord Grim, it’s an honor to meet you!” Loulan Slash said directly to Ye Xiu.

“Loulan Slash, it’s an honor to meet you too!” Ye Xiu replied.

“Liar! You just found out.” Chen Guo looked down at Ye Xiu and sent a private message.

“It’s just manners. He probably just found about me too a few days ago.” Ye Xiu quickly replied.

“Tell him you’re Ye Qiu! Then it really would be an honor to meet you!” Chen Guo replied. She was looking forward to see this scene. It would be very amusing to see.

Before Ye Xiu could reply, Loulan Slash continued to speak.

“Brother, reaching the Heavenly Domain at level 50 is unprecedented in the history of Glory! You’re amazing! I wonder which server you used to play on. Perhaps we know each other.” Loulan Slash said.

There was no way a new player who had just started playing on the new server would be able to finish the Heavenly Challenge at Level 50. Even an incredibly talented player like Tang Rou, who had passion, strong mechanics, and a God personally instructing her, couldn’t complete the Challenge.

During the past few days, many people had been curious about Lord Grim’s identity. Every famous player in the Heavenly Domain had been suspected. However, during the Spring Festival event, these characters were all busy in the Heavenly Domain, so the suspicions towards them were quickly dispelled. Then, people began to recall the retired elites, who were perhaps starting the game again.

After greeting him, Loulan Slash began figuring out what server Ye Xiu’s main account was from. Ye Xiu didn’t try to hide it and answered, “I used to play on the first server, but I hadn’t played on it for a long time.”

“First server……” Loulan Slash and his four friends took a deep breath. If he really had started playing when the first server opened, then he was senior of seniors! But there was also another possibility. He had started playing later and had simply chosen to start in the first server.

“Brother, do you have an account in the Heavenly Domain?” Loulan Slash asked again. He felt that someone so skilled must be an experienced player. It wasn’t possible for him to not have a character in the Heavenly Domain and the character must have been famous once.

“Not anymore.” Ye Xiu replied.

“You give it to someone?” Loulan Slash said.

“You could say that!” Ye Xiu replied.

“What’s the name of the character?” Loulan Slash thought if he knew the name of the character, he would have a much easier time figuring out his identity.

Loulan Slash was right. After Ye Xiu told him his old character’s name, it was really obvious who he was.

“One Autumn Leaf.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was excited. This was the moment she was waiting for!

“This name sounds really familiar? Do we really not know each other?” Loulan Slash thought for a while.

But right after the pause, before Ye Xiu could reply, emojis popped up above the heads of all five characters in the other party.

Shocked. Sweating. Surprised. A face that turned black after being struck by lightning. Loulan Slash chose an “unbelievable” emoji and he quickly followed, “One Autumn Leaf? You don’t mean that One Autumn Leaf, right?”

“Is there another One Autumn Leaf?” Ye Xiu laughed.

A moment of silence, this time, there wasn’t any emoji on all five of the characters. They seemed to be lagging and didn’t move at all.

“Are you saying you’re Ye Qiu?” Loulan Slash regained his composure the fastest.

“Yes, that’s me.” Ye Xiu didn’t hide his identity.

“Crash……” Everyone heard a crash, but didn’t know where it caem from. But they could hear someone quickly speak: “GOD YE QIU!!!!!!” He added an emoji as he talked, so everyone knew who had spoken.

He was one of Loulan Slash’s party members and a Battle Mage. As a Battle Mage, admiring Ye Qiu was very common and logical.

Aftera short pause, someone finally awakened and muttered: “Is this for real?”

“It’s real.” Ye Xiu smiled while saying.

“Can you prove it?” Loulan Slash asked.

“I don’t have to prove it. It’s up to you whether you want to believe me or not.” Ye Xiu laughed.

Loulan Slash was startled, but he was right. He immediately followed: “Fine! If you really are God Ye Qiu, then that’s even better! I’ve heard that you want to go back to the pro scene and make your own team?”

“Yes. I’ve thought about it.”Ye Xiu said.

“What a coincidence! I’ve been thinking about building a team for a while and I’ve been preparing as well. But good players are hard to find! God, are you interested?” Loulan Slash asked.

“Then too bad for you. The God has already signed a contract with me already.” How could Chen Guo bear it, seeing a person try to dig him out from right in front of her .She jumped out and pushed Ye Xiu aside, standing in front of Loulan Slash while speaking.

“Who are you?” Loulan Slash hadn’t paid attention to Chen Guo and Forest Landscape after greeting them. These two characters weren’t famous in the Heavenly Domain.

“I’m his boss.” Chen Guo said.

“What boss?” Loulan Slash was puzzled.

“You don’t know what boss means?” Chen Guo looked down on him.

“Investor?” Loulan Slash said in a more professional way.

“Eh…. Kind of…..”’ Chen Guo suddenly lost her confidence because all she did was provide food and shelter for Ye Xiu. She hadn’t really done much else for him. Loulan Slash was quite famous for having money. No one knew what his background was, but there were quite a few rumors saying his family were at least millionaires. In any case, it was a lot stronger than Chen Guo’s background, who only owned an Internet Café.

Having support from someone like this might be better for Ye Xiu. It didn’t seem quite right for Chen Guo to jump out like that. After all, she and Ye Xiu hadn’t officially signed a contract or anything. Even if the guild had already been made in the tenth server, what did that mean? They were still far from starting yet!

Thinking about this, Chen Guo wasn’t sure. She turned around and looked at Ye Xiu, but all she saw was him laughing! Even so, he said to Loulan Slash, “ Yes, she’s my boss.”

Just this sentence made Chen Guo’s confidence come back, even she even straightened her back as if Loulan Slash could see see her. She said. “Did you hear that? That’s what boss means. Do you still need to ask?”

Loulan Slash thought it was a bit suspicious, but this was their first time meeting. He knew nothing about Chen Guo’s background. He heard Ye Xiu admitting it himself, so it naturally wasn’t a good to try and buy a player in front of her. He said “ I see. What a pity!”

He followed: ” Then if it’s convenient, how about we add each other as friends? Later, if anything comes up, we can help each other!”

Ye Xiu agreed and sent a friend request to Loulan Slash. Chen Guo paused for a second because Loulan Slash also sent her a friend request. Of course, Chen Guo accepted too.

Loulan Slash looked around asked, “Are you three leveling?”

“Yeah!” Ye Xiu replied.

“Then we shouldn’t bother you guys any longer. Let’s keep in touch!” Loulan Slash said.

“Let’s keep in touch.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

Loulan Slash turned, carrying his Swordpoint, and left together with the other four players. On the other hand, Chen Guo was in a daze. After a while, she turned around to look at Ye Xiu: “They left just like that?”

“What did you expect him to do?” Ye Xiu asked.

“He should’ve pulled out an empty cheque and then give it to you. Fill in how much money you want and then come with me or something.” Chen Guo said.

“Yeah, what a pity. Why didn’t I meet someone stupid like that?” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s not being stupid. This is your value. That’s how much you’re worth in Glory.” Chen Guo said.

“Sis, he can’t even confirm if I’m Ye Qiu or not!” Ye Xiu said.

“That why I said he’s stupid. He can’t even figure that out.” Chen Guo continued to looked down on him.

Ye Xiu didn’t say anymore. He could tell that Chen Guo had some sort of prejudice towards players who got power through money. She probably thought that they were useless except for being rich. She turned her camera to look in that direction. Loulan Slash’s group had come fast and left fast. They had gone far away enough that their IDs couldn’t be seen clearly anymore.

Chapter 421 – Deceptively Powerful Enemy

Loulan Slash and his group didn’t move very far before starting a fierce discussion.

“Is that guy really God Ye Qiu?” This issue had to be made clear first. The Battle Mage and fan of Ye Xiu among the five of them brought up the topic impatiently.

“We can’t be certain at this moment! But if he really is God Ye Qiu, then the gossip being talked about by everyone would make a lot of sense. Completing the Heavenly Domain Challenge at Level 50, possessing a Silver weapon, no Clubs recruiting him. If he really is Ye Qiu, that would all be very reasonable, no?” Loulan Slash said.

“That’s true……” Another player said, “Especially the fact that no Clubs are recruiting him. I think that proves his identity. With so much commotion around such a talent, even if he’s not genuinely talented, the Clubs could still pull him in and test him. It would pretty much be taking in him in, but at the very least, even if he’s not good, he’d attract a lot of attention in a short amount of time. That would be an amazing opportunity for any Club! Yet no Clubs did things like this. There’s no way the Clubs hadn’t thought of this, which mean that they were being restricted by something. Ye Qiu…… if it really is him, then there’s nothing they can do.”

“If he really is Ye Qiu, his retirement will last at least a full year, which means at the earliest, he could return during the winter split. If they wanted to add him to the team, they would have to wait until then before giving him any consideration.” Another player added.

“You guys have already given it that much thought?” The fourth player laughed, “We still can’t confirm it and even if we could, didn’t you hear the girl? She’s already Ye Qiu’s boss. Ye Qiu also admitted it. It looks like he’s already found a partner to work with.”

“That girl……. I felt like her words weren’t very convincing. My guess is that she’s still not too confident about this cooperation! She wasn’t as calm as Ye Qiu.” Loulan Slash said.

“Then what do we do now?”

“Continue doing what we’re doing. As for that guy over there…… Little Bei, pay attention to him, okay? I feel like you’d be quite interested in doing that!” Loulan Slash laughed.

“Let me! Let me!” Little Bei was that Battle Mage. As a fan of Ye Qiu, interacting with him would be something he was happy to do.

After sending off Loulan Slash, Ye Xiu continued to level. No one talked about what had just happened. Chen Guo wasn’t feeling very calm though.

Even though Ye Xiu had personally acknowledged that she was his boss, what about herself? After discovering that there were these types of competitors out there, she was beginning to hesitate. Loulan Slash’s judgement of her was correct. The current Chen Guo wasn’t feeling very confident…….

She already realized that with Ye Xiu’s skill and position and her small amount of capital, she might not be able to help too much. It could even be said that she would be restricting his development. In the Glory Pro Alliance, every year, the two lowest ranked teams would be kicked, which meant that every year, there could be up to two teams that would be replaced. As a result, there were plenty of people who invested in a team hoping that it would enter the Pro Alliance. Chen Guo was certain that these investors had much more money than she did.

With Ye Xiu’s skill and status, if he had an offer, who would refuse it? But what about her? What type of capital she could afford wasn’t something others knew. She didn’t even know herself. When the time came, she might not even be able to afford the transfer of another pro player. As an owner, being that poor would be a joke. With an investor like her, could she actually help Ye Xiu achieve his dreams?

Chen Guo discovered that she hadn’t been mature enough when she had made the decision on a whim.

Leaving Excellent Dynasty was a small matter.

Not watching Excellen Era’s matches was a small matter.

But wasn’t she overestimating herself saying that she would create a team that would beat Excellent Era?

“What are you thinking about? Please concentrate a bit more!”

Chen Guo woke up with a start. She looked at her screen and saw that Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had moved past her and grabbed a small monster next to her. Launchers were long-ranged attackers. Having a monster so close to her while fighting and not reacting meant that her mind had gone wandering away.

“Oh, I wasn’t paying attention.” Chen Guo gave an excuse.

“Are you thinking about that guy from before?” Ye Xiu asked.

“A bit.” Chen Guo said.

“What were you thinking of?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I was thinking…… that if we’re going to create a team, then our resources are a bit scarce. Seeking for some cooperation with others might not be a bad idea.” Chen Guo said.

“Mm, it’s not a bad idea, but there’s one problem with it.” Ye Xiu said.

“What’s the problem?” Chen Guo asked.

“We’re not familiar with them.” Ye Xiu smiled.

“We just met. Of course, we’re not familiar with them.” Chen Guo said.

“That’s why they added us as friends. Them saying that they would contact us later was because they’re not familiar with us either.” Ye Xiu said.

“Talk with them a bit and we’ll be familiar…….” Chen Guo said, but she also felt a bit grieved. She really wanted to rely on her own power to help Ye Xiu create a team, but she also felt like she wouldn’t be able to accomplish it with only herself. Did they really need to borrow other people’s help? Chen Guo was very conflicted.

Tang Rou was sitting next to the two of them. She wasn’t in the same place as them, so she hadn’t heard their conversation with Loulan Slash. They hadn’t said much, but she had noticed a few subtleties in their words. Tang Rou wouldn’t talk of other’s private matters, but if it was about the team, she felt like she had a part in it, so she joined in: “Who’d you meet?”

“People who appear to have money.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh? What was his purpose?” Tang Rou asked.

“They seem to want to form a team too, so they asked if I wanted to join!” Ye Xiu said.

“Why don’t they join ours?” Tang Rou asked.

“Good idea!” Ye Xiu praised.

Chen Guo listened in astonishment. This sister seemed to have overestimated their strength even more than her!

“How is your dungeon soloing going?” Ye Xiu was only killing wild monsters. It was a very easy task, so he often helped give some advice to Tang Rou on the side.

“It’s a bit slow, but I feel like I’ve improved a lot.” Tang Rou said.

“Mm, for you, leveling isn’t that important. It’s more important to practice your mechanics well!” Ye Xiu said.

“Are you saying that your mechanics have already peaked and you don’t need any practice?” Tang Rou said.

“For now, it really is like that.” Ye Xiu said seriously.

“It won’t be like that sooner or later.” Tang Rou said seriously as well.

“Then I hope I’ll be able to see that day soon.” Ye Xiu said.

“Don’t be afraid if someone embarrasses you first!” Tang Rou said.

“I’m just afraid that won’t have enough time to wait for that moment to come.” Ye Xiu sighed.

Tang Rou was startled by this and also felt a bit melancholy. People couldn’t stop nature from taking its course.

As a result, the three each had their own sorrows. The atmosphere seemed to have frozen up until Chen Guo suddenly called out: “More people are coming.”

“I see them.” Melancholy was melancholy, but Ye Xiu was still going to do what he had to do and was mindful of what was around him. Because the map was spacious and empty, it wasn’t a hard task. He had seen the three heading towards them long ago.

He did the same as before and checked around. There were no other players around them. It was just three of them. Ye Xiu doubted that the guilds would be so arrogant as to send just three players to take him down knowing his identity.

“They don’t have any guild names on them…….” The three players entered their view. After seeing the name above them, Chen Guo started.

“Be careful.” Ye Xiu immediately said. If they didn’t have guild tags, then it was likely they didn’t have any good intentions. In the Heavenly Domain, the top guilds would also have open accounts.

“Understood.” Chen Guo nodded her head and then reminded Forest Landscape: “Be careful.”

The three headed straight for them and the distance continued to close.

From their equipment and weapons, Ye Xiu was able to distinguish their classes.

Spellblade, Sharpshooter, Elementalist.

After seeing these three classes, Ye Xiu’s mind began to turn. Almost instinctively, he gave the three characters an ID. Unfortunately, the three IDs on top of their heads weren’t the ones Ye Xiu was thinking of.

“Run!” Ye Xiu suddenly shouted.

“Run?” Chen Guo was startled.

“No good. Run!” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim slid back with an Aerial Fire and flew out.

Chen Guo also used an Aerial Cannon and asked: “Why run?”

Forest Landscape was confused too, but since Chen Guo was already asking, he didn’t need to say anything. With the movement buff from Neutral Chasers, his movement speed was also extremely quick.

“They might be from Excellent Era.” Ye Xiu said.

“So what if they’re from Excellent Era?” Chen Guo didn’t understand. Hearing the name Excellent Era, she really wanted to rush at them and beat them up.

“Their classes…….” Ye Xiu said.

“Classes?” Chen Guo and Forest Landscape looked at their classes: Spellblade, Sharpshooter, Elementalist.

The two recalled that these three classes were classes that were used in Team Excellent Era. However, determining that they were from Excellent Era with just that? That was a bit too excessive…..

“Even if they’re from Excellent Era, what’s there to be so nervous about?” Chen Guo was still talking.

“I’m talking about Excellent Era, not Excellent Dynasty.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo stared blankly: “Are you saying…… pro players?”

“I can’t be certain, but we’ll know after running for a bit.” Ye Xiu said.

He had been a part of Team Excellent Era for seven and a half years. As soon as these three classes appeared in front of Ye Xiu, he felt familiar with them and had a type of feeling that occurred when one saw teammates. This type of feeling made him even more suspicious of these three characters.

If they were only normal guild players, then three players would be greatly overestimating themselves. But if they were pro players, then three pro players were more than enough.

Three pro players with a 20 level advantage. There was no God in Glory who wouldn’t take this seriously.

The moment they had been waiting for came and in a ferocious manner too……

Chapter 422 – Stay and Fight

Running away to figure out their skill level wasn’t the first time Ye Xiu had done this. The first time he used it was also against Excellent Dynasty’s people. History repeated itself, except this time, it was now in the Heavenly Domain instead of the tenth server, from easy-to-beat Excellent Dynasty players into possibly pro players that Ye Xiu had to respect.

Ye Xiu had chosen the open landscape in order to discover enemies easier, but escaping wasn’t convenient. The enemy could also easily figure out their escape route. However, Ye Xiu wasn’t ready to completely escape yet. He still wanted to confirm his opponents’ identities.

Ye Xiu was undoubtedly the most familiar with Excellent Era’s players. Liu Hao’s Hateful Sword wasn’t able to trick him. The other pros wouldn’t be able to either. Right now, even though they were only running and moving around, every player had small habits that they did. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was using Aerial Fire to fly backwards, so he was able to see what the three players chasing them were doing.

The three players had come for them. This didn’t need to be debated. After seeing them run, the three characters didn’t hesitate to chase after them. The Sharpshooter amongst them turned around and also used an Aerial Fire. While Aerial Firing, the character would turn around in midair from to time to time in order to confirm that he was still moving in the same direction as his target. Ye Xiu saw his movements and rhythm and was now eighty percent certain he knew his identity.

“Wang Ze!” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah!” Chen Guo and Forest Landscape shouted. As former Excellent Era fans, they weren’t a stranger to this name. Wang Ze was one of Excellent Era’s pro players and used a Sharpshooter like the one chasing after them.

“Then the other two are Liu Hao and He Ming?” Chen Guo shouted. Liu Hao and He Ming were Spellblade and Elementalist players on the team. Wang Ze didn’t have a position in the main roster yet. Liu Hao and He Ming were both in the main roster and their skill in the pro scene were widely praised.

“Split up and run!” Ye Xiu didn’t answer Chen Guo’s question and said this.

“Split up……” Chen Guo stared blankly. Forest Landscape, on the other hand, listened and immediately headed towards a different direction.

Chen Guo originally wanted to say that if they split up, they weren’t opponents for the pros. But after seeing Forest Landscape run in a different direction, the three players completely ignored him and still headed straight for Lord Grim and her. Only then did she realize that splitting up wasn’t to drop them off as lures, but rather because Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was their only target. Killing off her and Forest Landscape would just be in passing. They wouldn’t spend any effort to bother with them.

“What do you mean run? Let’s fight them!” Chen Guo suddenly stirred.

“What do you mean fight?” Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry, “Going out and fighting is suicide. Use your brain.”

“Splitting up is using your brain?” Chen Guo disagreed. That type of plan where you guys run first, while I’ll figure something out was something she couldn’t accept.

“Uh, splitting up and running is so that I can focus on myself instead of taking care of you two……” Ye XIu said.

Ye Xiu’s honesty once again made Chen Guo want to cry, but she still persisted: “You don’t need to take care of us! If we die, we die! It’s just a bit of experience. It’s not like we die forever.”

“You’ve bound all of your equipment?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Don’t say it like we’re definitely going to die!” Chen Guo said.

“It was just a kind reminder.” Ye Xiu said.

“Is your Silver weapon bound?” Chen Guo asked.

“It’s too late.” Ye Xiu said.

“Same for me.” Chen Guo said.

“That’s why we can’t die!” Ye Xiu said.

“Definitely!” Chen Guo said.

“Then why aren’t you running?”

“Don’t mind me!!!” Chen Guo fumed. She didn’t need to send an emoticon in game, she could just directly glare at Ye Xiu for him to see.

“Okay okay okay. Then you follow me.” Ye Xiu didn’t persist.

“I know my own limits!” Chen Guo said, “I just wanted to stay and fight, that’s all. So what if I die in game? It’s not a big deal. You can send me as bait and I’d be fine with that.”

“You say you know your own limits. What type of value do you have as bait?” Ye Xiu said.

“You….. Why are you so blunt! Go die!!!” Chen Guo shouted.

“Jump to the rock at 1456, 856.” Ye Xiu suddenly quieted down and his tone turned serious. Chen Guo was a bit confused, but she did as she was told and hastily checked the coordinates. Sure enough, it was a large rock and she ran towards their.

“It won’t be easy to jump on. You have to jump high. Let me see your weight.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo opened up her page. Ye Xiu glanced at it: “Your weight is a bit high. What are you carrying on you?”

“A bit of spare equipment!” The open-minded Chen Guo opened up her inventory and threw out some equipment. Her weight immediately dropped.

“How is it now?” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

“F*ck, so wasteful.” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim used a Falling Light Blade to get to the ground faster and swiftly picked up everything Chen Guo threw away.

Chen Guo was speechless. She was seriously doubting that he was a Glory God.

“Your weight is fine. Go jump. It has to be high. You have to find the right place. Over here.” Ye Xiu said and told Chen Guo to look at his screen, where his mouse pointed to a spot on the big rock.

Chen Guo turned to look at her screen and immediately found the position on her screen. She rushed underneath the big rock, jumped up, Aerial Fired, and then crashed into the rock and slid down…….

“Pay attention to the angle.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo tried again. This time, she didn’t crash into the rock, but she had been too careful with her angle. She missed the rock and failed again.

Looking back, the three were quickly closing in. Chen Guo was starting to get very worried.

“What do I do if I can’t jump on?” Chen Guo asked.

“You’ll be like a clown who the enemy laughs at.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo heard this and got angry. She tried again and this time, she succeeded. She was a bit surprised that she made it on. How did she do that?

“And then what?’ Chen Guo asked after jumping onto the rock.

“Move back. A bit more. A bit more. Yeah. That’s good.” Ye Xiu directed.

This big rock was so big that it was almost like a platform. Chen Guo listened and had Chasing Haze continue moving back. When Ye Xiu told her to stop, she discovered that she couldn’t see what was going on down there anymore.

“And then?” Chen Guo asked again.

“Wait for my order.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo sat there anxiously. Her right hand was on the mouse. Her left hand was on the keyboard. She was ready at any moment to do something complicated. She really wanted to see what Ye Xiu was doing, but she knew that her opponents were already close. What if Ye Xiu’s arrangement for her was very important? As a result, she didn’t dare be distracted and stared at her monitor.

Her line of sight was completely covered by the big rock. She couldn’t see anything. However, she could hear footsteps coming closer and closer, faster and faster. The sounds of a gun firing were getting closer and closer as well. Chen Guo knew that this was the enemy Sharpshooter’s Aerial Fire. Had they already gotten on to the rock? Or were they still below it? Or perhaps they were only a few steps away from her.

But she didn’t dare move. She didn’t know what Ye Xiu was planning. Maybe he was planning on using her as bait and then doing something after that.

Except……. Chen Guo looked around and saw that no attacks came onto the rock. This rock was very big. The Spellblade and Elementalist wouldn’t be able to reach up here. If the Sharpshooter used Aerial Fire, his recoil wasn’t as strong as a cannon, so he wouldn’t be able to reach this height either, unless the Sharpshooter learned the Mechanic skill to directly fly up.

Chen Guo thought about it, when she suddenly heard the loud sound of gunfire. It was continuously firing, which meant that it wasn’t an Aerial Fire, but actual firing. Then, she saw a bright flame rush up. She didn’t have a full view of it, but form the visual effects, it had clearly been done by the opponent’s Elementalist.

If she could still bear to not look at her surroundings, then she wouldn’t be Chen Guo. However, she was still too afraid to move her character, so she looked at Ye Xiu’s screen.

Bullets and magic were flying all around in Ye Xiu’s line of sight. Chen Guo looked at it anxiously for half a minute, but she couldn’t see what the situation was. Once he started maneuvering, his character camera would constantly be turning. Chen Guo couldn’t figure out what his intent was, but she was at least able to see Lord Grim’s health and mana pool. From the looks of it, the situation wasn’t looking too bad.

Chen Guo really wanted to know what she could do, but she didn’t dare bother Ye Xiu right now. Just seeing his screen spin around, making her eyes go blurry, Chen Guo often only realized after several moments later: Oh, that guy just did that type of attack.

Chen Guo, who was unable to see anything clearly, finally discovered a smart method. She started looking at Lord Grim’s coordinates and from there, she could figure out his general direction. However, the coordinates didn’t constantly update and only changed every second. In the end, Chen Guo wasn’t able to get anything out of it.

At this moment, Ye Xiu’s left hand suddenly extended out towards her. He shouted: “Give me your mouse!!”

“Ah?” Chen Guo was startled and let go of the mouse in her right hand in panic.

Ye Xiu’s left hand grabbed Chen Guo’s mouse. His right hand was on the keyboard and he seemed to be moving his character around, while shouting: “Stinger!”

Chen Guo was a bit confused, but hearing Ye Xiu’s shout, she immediately used a Stinger. The, she saw Ye Xiu’s left hand control her mouse, aim in a direction, and throw out the Stinger.

“You can do that?” Chen Guo was frozen.

Chapter 423 – Who Do You Think I Am

“Grenade!”

Chen Guo didn’t have enough time to be shocked, when Ye Xiu yelled this out. She hastily used a Grenade. At the same time, Ye Xiu used his left hand to control her mouse. Her character turned and threw.

Chen Guo couldn’t tell what was happening on her screen, but because it was her Chasing Haze’s attack, she was able to see the result from Ye Xiu’s screen.

The eight missiles that exploded out of the Stinger rained down. Explosions burned all around Lord Grim, but because he was in the same party as Chasing Haze, he wasn’t affected by it. It didn’t matter how many missiles exploded on him. There was nothing to worry about. However, Chen Guo wasn’t able to see where exactly the Grenade had fallen because Ye Xiu didn’t look for the Grenade.

Ye Xiu’s left hand returned to his keyboard. The mouse in his right hand swiftly danced around as the battle continued. The scene constantly twisted and turned. Chen Guo could only watch quietly without knowing what was going on. She didn’t even know if she should have her right hand go back to her mouse.

It couldn’t be said that this was the first time Chen Guo had seen someone use two computers at once. However, normal players could only at most use one computer’s character to follow the other computer’s character in order to gain experience. Ye Xiu, on the other hand, was controlling the other character to attack. Even though Chen Guo was the one pressing the key to use the skill, the attack’s timing and aim were being controlled by Ye Xiu.

In reality, at that time, everything had happened too quickly and Chen Guo had also been shocked. She really hadn’t been paying attention to whether Ye Xiu’s mouse movements had been smooth or accurate.

The next opportunity to see this came quickly though. Chen Guo didn’t know what was happening, but Ye Xiu’s left hand once again grabbed her mouse.

“Satellite Beam!” This time, Ye Xiu shouted out the Launcher’s most powerful move.

Chen Guo was ready. She was already very familiar with how to use these skills. After immediately completing the actions, she looked at where Ye Xiu’s mouse was pointing towards. It was moving very slowly. For a moment, Chen Guo couldn’t tell if it was because he wasn’t very adept with his left hand or whether he was intentionally waiting for some sort of opportunity to appear. Chen Guo only knew that during this instant, the opponents didn’t stop attacking, while Ye Xiu’s right hand on his keyboard never stopped jumping around. What made Chen Guo even more amazed was that after a flurry of actions on the keyboard, his rind hand would even grab the mouse and use a skill……

It didn’t need to be said how fast his right hand was moving to complete what was supposed to be done with two hands with one hand. Under such hasty circumstances, Chen Guo really wanted to know how effective the skills he used were. However, Ye Xiu’s screen was always revolving around so fast that it made her eyes blur. She truly couldn’t see what was happening.

At this moment, Chen Guo saw that the Satellite Beam, which hadn’t been released yet, was about to reach its limit. If the skill wasn’t used now, it would be wasted.

Just as she was about to remind him, the mouse suddenly shot forward and then stopped at a steady position.

With a gentle click, the clouds in the sky split apart and a pillar of light descended towards where Ye Xiu was pointing at. Chen Guo immediately switched her gaze to Ye Xiu’s screen. This time, she was able to see clearly that the Satellite Beam had accurately hit a character.

The target was completely enveloped in the pillar of light. Chen Guo couldn’t tell who had been hit. The pillar of light split into six smaller pillars of light. The other two had to be careful and dodge it. In an instant, sand and rock flew out as the entire area exploded with light.

“Heat Missile!”

After hearing Ye Xiu say this, Chen Guo immediately completed the action. This time, Ye Xiu didn’t wait. His mouse immediately moved and a heat missile shot out from Chasing Haze’s cannon. Chen Guo’s heart thumped anxiously. Just as the heat missile was about to descend, it looked as if it would hit the giant rock. If that happened, it would explode on the rock and the target wouldn’t be affected.

However, the heat missile’s arc just happened to pass by the large rock and then disappear from view. Chen Guo immediately turned her head to look at Ye Xiu’s screen, but Ye Xiu wasn’t looking at the missile. Instead, he rushed towards the target which had been hit by the Satellite Beam.

Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze might not have the best equipment, but they were definitely above average. The three characters being used by Excellent Era had equipment that were only on par with Chasing Haze’s, so being directly hit by such a powerful move like Satellite Beam would definitely hurt a lot. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had rushed forward along with a flurry of gun shots. At this moment, Chen Guo could see who the target was. It was the Sharpshooter.

Sharpshooters weren’t like Launchers that only had long-ranged moves. Apart from gun skills, Sharpshooters also had body skills using the leg as methods of attacking. As a result, Sharpshooters always had a few points into these body skills.

Even if they mainly used long-ranged moves, they also had a few close-range skills, which could be used when necessary for cases like right now, where the opponent had closed in.

However, this Sharpshooter’s legs seemed as if they were like lead and couldn’t get them up. Under Lord Grim’s continuous attacks, he couldn’t use any of his skills. For a pro player, being suppressed to this extent was unsightly.

“Bang!” Lord Grim used a Falling Flower Palm. The unfortunate Sharpshooter crashed into the giant rock and bounced back. Ye Xiu followed up with a Knockup skill. Afterwards, a beautiful performance was played. The Sharpshooter wasn’t able to move away from the rock and soon, a white light shone and he was killed.

“Beautiful!!!” Chen Guo cried out. Though honestly, she had no idea how Ye Xiu had crucified the chaser onto the rock.

Chen Guo thought that the two other opponents would continue chasing and attacking. Her left hand was ready at any moment, while she let go of the mouse in her right hand. She had even moved the mouse a bit towards his side, so he could reach it easier. But then everything suddenly became quiet and it seemed like the battle had stopped.

The Elementalist’s magic could no longer be seen and there were no movements from the Spellblade. The two enemies seemed to have disappeared.

“Could they have all been killed already?” Chen Guo was surprised. Didn’t he say that three pro players was too much? How did he just kill the two of them off already?

Chen Guo didn’t know what was going on, but she was too afraid to move her character. She thought she wouldn’t be able to see anything from her screen and was ready to look at Ye Xiu’s screen, when she suddenly discovered something on her screen. She looked carefully and from the large rock, she saw two characters running farther and farther away.

The rock was big, but it didn’t obstruct too much of her view. After Chen Guo saw clearly who the two characters were, she confirmed that they were the Spellblade and Elementalist that had been chasing them. The two of them seemed to be escaping in a hurry too. Chen Guo scratched her head in confusion, but she didn’t want to be too careless. She thought it might be some pro strategy. However, when the two characters looked back towards them, her heart leaped. What she had thought would happen didn’t happen. The two characters really did just run until they disappeared from view.

“What happened?” Chen Guo saw that nothing was happening, so she asked.

“They ran.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ran?” Chen Guo didn’t understand.

“Yeah, you can’t see it from there?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I can see it! I meant why did they run?” Chen Guo said.

“You’re too amazing. You scared them away.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Nonsense.” Chen Guo said. She wasn’t amazing. The amazing one was Ye Xiu’s left hand. But even so, to scare away two pro players? Chen Guo felt like that was going too far.

“Come down!”

Hearing Ye Xiu say this, Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze jumped down. Ye Xiu gave the equipment Chen Guo had dropped earlier back to her.

“What exactly happened?” Chen Guo continued to ask.

“Ha ha, the synergy between my left and right hand made them feel scared.” Ye Xiu said.

The word synergy had been emphasized by Ye Xiu. Chen Guo stared blankly before suddenly understanding: “Synergy? Did they think that I was……”

“Yeah……. Though let’s hurry up and leave.” Ye XIu said as he moved Chasing Haze away.

…….

“That Launcher was Su Mucheng?” The Elementalist who had already run far away suddenly spoke with a bit of lingering fear.

“Definitely. With that type of control and synergy, who else could that be but Su Mucheng?” The Spellblade replied.

Ye Xiu’s guess had been correct. These three players were Excellent Era pros. The Spellblade was Liu Hao. The Elementalist was He Ming. The two were both using the classes they were adept at and had a 20 level advantage. They even had Wang Ze’s Sharpshooter. Against Ye Xiu alone, they wouldn’t have had any trouble whatsoever.

However, just like how Ye Xiu was extremely familiar with them, they were also extremely familiar with Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng. They had originally ignored the Launcher, especially when she threw out the Stinger and Grenade. They couldn’t tell what she was thinking. It was as if she had just thrown them out randomly. But the Satellite Beam had been too unexpected and directly sent Wang Ze’s Sharpshooter into the abyss. Even if that might have just been a coincidence, the immediate follow up from the Heat Missile had been done so perfectly that there was no way the three could believe that the Launcher was just randomly throwing out moves and praying they would hit.

A Launcher who could coordinate with Ye Qiu so perfectly. Besides Su Mucheng, who else could she be?

Chapter 424 – The Mysterious Chasing Haze

Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng were without a doubt paragons of the idea that 1 plus 1 is far greater than 2. Despite it being a 3v2 and Lord Grim at a 20 level disadvantage, the instant they realized that the Launcher was Su Mucheng, the three thought: We made a mistake…….

After the Satellite Beam directly hit Wang Ze’s Sharpshooter and the six smaller pillars of light trapped Liu Hao and He Ming, the perfectly timed Heat Missile right afterwards made them completely give up any intentions of fighting.

They weren’t matches for the golden duo.

Even though they weren’t happy with it, they still had to admit that rushing in stubbornly would be asking for death.

As a result, Wang Ze’s character was killed, while Liu Hao and He Ming decided to run away.

“SU MUCHENG!!!” Liu hao slammed the table. In that instant, his hatred for Su Mucheng might have even surpassed his hatred for Ye Qiu.

On the side, Wang Ze and He Ming looked at each other. Right now, the three of them were sitting together, so communication was easy to do.

He Ming was about to say something, when they suddenly heard someone humming nearby, startling the three of them. Soon afterwards, they watched as Su Mucheng passed by the the window in front of them.

The three froze.

After a long time, Liu Hao asked absentmindedly: “Who was that?”

“It seemed to be…… Su Mucheng?” He Ming was also lost in thought.

Among the three of them, one of them was in the secondary team, the other was in the main team, while Wang Ze was a substitute. As the lowest position player, he got up and stuck his head the window to see. He looked outside and watched as Su Mucheng walked farther and farther away.

“It’s Su Mucheng…….” After Wang Ze left the window, he was no longer absentminded anymore.

“How could she be here?” Liu Hao seemed to have gotten even more lost in thought. Su Mucheng had clearly been controlling her character in the game. How could she suddenly appear outside of their window? Was she a ninja?

The answer was very simple. It was just that Liu Hao couldn’t believe it. Just before, he had been certain that the Launcher had to be Su Mucheng, but in the next second, Su Mucheng passed by his window. It was as if she were simply stepping all over his face like it was nothing. Did she really just hum and sing happily? Liu Hao was furious!

“If that person wasn’t Su Mucheng, then who was she?” He Ming was a bit more realistic.

No matter how much they thought about it, they couldn’t understand. If that player wasn’t Su Mucheng yet was able to coordinate with Ye Xiu so perfectly, could they have guessed wrong and that player had really just been throwing out random attacks blindly? But those moves were a bit too precise and accurate. They were also chained so perfectly that there was no room for them to retaliate……

“Chasing Haze.” Wang Ze spoke the character’s ID.

“Is that the name of that player?” Liu Hao had fixed his attention on Lord Grim and had ignored everything else.

“Doesn’t that name sound a bit familiar?” He Ming recalled.

“There was a really popular video of her some time ago…….” Wang Ze said.

He Ming suddenly remembered: “The video of that Launcher instant kill was this same character no?”

“What is it?” Liu Hao had been focused on the team during this time, so he hadn’t paid attention to anything in game.

He Ming opened up a browser and quickly found the video. Soon afterwards, he played the video and the three circled around the computer to watch it.

Such a precise and accurate combo definitely indicated that the player was an expert. But it wasn’t easy to say how good the player was exactly because her opponent wasn’t able to show any of his skill. Apart from the very beginning of the match, where he was able to do a little bit, after the first attack, he didn’t even get a chance to struggle.

“At least, his skill isn’t at a pro level.” He Ming was pointing to the Blade Master.

“No sh*t.” Liu Hao said a bit rudely. In the middle, there was a clear opportunity to escape, but the Blade Master wasn’t able to seize it. This type of skill was far from the pro level. There was no need to point it out.

“However, this Launcher’s skill seems to be quite good looking at this short chain of attacks.” He Ming said.

“This video is popular?” Liu hao asked.

He Ming really wanted to say “No sh*t” too, but he would be saying it to the vice captain and didn’t dare do so. He just highlighted the viewcount and said: “See, it’s very high.”

“Has this person ever been contacted by the Clubs?” Liu Hao asked.

“I’m not sure…… “ He Ming said.

Wang Ze stood on one side. He didn’t feel like he was in a position to interrupt them, but the two were missing a very obvious but important detail. Finally, he took up the courage and spoke: “Look at that Chasing Haze’s guild.”

“Guild?” He Ming asked. He pulled open the video and paused on a good still shot of Chasing Haze. He took a look at the guild name and saw that it actually read Excellent Dynasty.

Liu Hao and He Ming stared dumbly.

“Excellent Dynasty…… could it be Su Mucheng’s alternate account?” He Ming guessed.

“The person controlling that character couldn’t have been Su Mucheng.” Liu Hao. It wasn’t possible to immediately appear right outside the window just after playing the game.

“Go into the guild and take a look.” Liu Hao said.

As a result, He Ming logged into his Elementalist, Emotionless Magic. Even though it wasn’t a God leveled account, it was still a pro player’s account, so it gathered a huge amount of attention. As soon as Emotionless Magic went online, the guild chat immediately erupted. But right now, the three couldn’t care about all this. He Ming hastily checked the guild member list, but found no such character. He looked at the video again and confirmed that he had gotten the name correct. Then, he immediately logged out.

Liu Hao was helpless. He could only pick up his phone: “I’ll go ask.”

The call was obviously to Chen Yehui. He would obviously be more clear on the character in-game.

The pros had no idea what was going on, but as soon as they asked Chen Yehui, they were able to get a clear understanding of the situation. Anyone who was a part of a guild in the tenth server knew that this battle was a challenge by Poplar Beach to Lord Grim! Liu Hao was stumped for words after hearing Chen Yehui say this. Afterwards, he asked Chen Yehui on this Chasing Haze’s skill level.

Chen Guo’s skill level and character weren’t bad. In Guild Excellent Dynasty, she had a decent reputation. But because she wasn’t someone who played the game as work like Chen Yehui, no matter how good of a reputation she had, she wasn’t a core member of Excellent Dynasty. Chen Yehui hadn’t had any impression of her until after the video exploded into popularity.

In particular, after knowing that Ye Qiu had played on this character, he knew that the owner of this character had some sort of relationship with Ye Qiu. He had been thinking of some way to exploit her, but then not long ago, she suddenly left the guild at about the same time Ye Qiu created Guild Happy in the tenth server. Seeing this chain of events, it would be hard to say if she had any direct relationship with him, but at the very least, if Ye Qiu played on her account, the two should know each other. This meant that her relationship with him couldn’t be shallow, right?

Liu Hao wasn’t able to contain his emotions after hearing Chen Yehui’s explanation. Right afterwards, Chen Yehui used this chance to ask how the request of killing Lord Grim was going. This question poked right into Liu Hao’s sore spot. Liu Hao replied with a dark tone: “What’s the rush” and then immediately hung up the call.

“This…… she might be someone in Ye Qiu’s proximity.” Liu Hao told his findings to He Ming and Wang Ze.

“Is she someone that Ye Qiu is training?” The two asked.

He Ming glanced at the video again: “She seems to be quite skilled. Maybe the reason why the Clubs didn’t try and recruit her was because she had already tried out before?”

“No. That was Ye Qiu playing on the account. They seemed to have gotten to know each other awhile ago.” Liu Hao shook his head.

“Ye Qiu? So you’re saying that the Chasing Haze in this video is actually Ye Qiu?”

“Yes.”

“If Ye Qiu’s the one playing, then it means that her skill level really isn’t that good, which is which is why she needed Ye Qiu to come out!” He Ming guessed.

“That’s not right either. At that time, the opponent had challenged Ye Qiu. However, Ye Qiu didn’t have a suitably leveled character, so he borrowed it to use.” Liu Hao said.

He Ming’s and Wang Ze’s expressions darkened. This meant that they had no way of knowing how good Chasing Haze really was. If she really was as good as she showed today, then she’d undoubtedly be a terrifying force. They had even mistaken her to be Su Mucheng. How scary was that?

Right now, they were just hoping that it was all a misunderstanding, but even if she wasn’t Su Mucheng, seeing today’s performance, she must have been good enough for Ye Qiu to use as a substitute for Su Mucheng, right? That would mean her skill level couldn’t be much worse than Su Mucheng’s. Could the three of them defeat the duo? They couldn’t log into their pro accounts to use in game, right?

The three uneasily paced back and forth.

He Ming’s character had logged off because he had to log into Emotionless Magic. Liu Hao was stopped there in the wilderness. Wang Ze was at a revive point and was in quite a desolate area.

They didn’t know what to do right now. Suddenly, Liu hao’s character suddenly took damage and his health rapidly went down. Liu Hao had just been thinking of how to deal with Ye Qiu, when he was suddenly attacked. He jumped in surprise and immediately rolled forward, while turning around to look behind him. He saw that it wasn’t Lord Grim. It was a character he didn’t recognize at all. The opponent was probably someone who thought he was AFK, so he attacked. This was the environment in the Heavenly Domain. A 20% experience loss at death was bad enough, but there was also a very high chance of dropping something, which pushed players to PK.

As soon as Liu Hao saw that it was some unknown character, he immediately flared up. If even a nobody tried to bully him, how could he bear it? Liu Hao attacked in a fury as if the opponent had killed his father or mother and destroyed the opponent.

“You’re looking to die! Hmph!” Liu Hao looked down on the character who had just died.

He Ming and Wang Ze quietly wiped away some sweat from their foreheads. It looks like their vice captain was under a lot of pressure!

Chapter 425 – A Difficult Start

Excellent Era’s three players could truly be said to have come in high spirits and returned disappointed. They had originally thought that it would be an absolutely safe and easy battle, but the sudden appearance of another character made them return empty-handed.

The information they received gave them no way of deducing how skilled Chasing Haze really was. For pro players, an opponent they didn’t understand was a very scary thing, especially if the opponent was also at a pro level. They couldn’t be careless. Even though they didn’t care if the characters they were borrowing died a billion times, the problem was, dying again and again with no results would hurt their pride. Unless it was their only option left, they preferred not to shamefully die in order to figure out how skilled their mysterious opponent was.

“I think…….” Wang Ze, who had been too afraid to say anything, saw that the two had completely stopped talking, so he started up the conversation again: “That Chasing Haze might not be that skilled.”

“Oh?” Liu Hao and He Ming both looked at Wang Ze.

“If she really was as good as Su Mucheng, they wouldn’t have needed to run away in the beginning. If they directly contended against us, we might not have the advantage, no?” Wang Ze said.

After Liu Hao heard this, he nodded his head: “You’re right. From what you said, it wasn’t our mistake in thinking that she wasn’t Su Mucheng. But the thing is…… it’s still hard to say how skilled she is. If she didn’t dare to directly confront us, then it means that she’s not as good as Su Mucheng. However, Su Mucheng needs Ye Qiu next to her in order to perform at her greatest potential. Her ability to deal with close-ranged situations isn’t bad, but it’s still one of her weak areas. After all, it’s not the style she’s used to using.”

Wang Ze stared dumbly. On the other side, He Ming followed: “So you’re saying that if you compare this Chasing Haze with Su Mucheng, Chasing Haze definitely has a good synergy with Ye Qiu, but it’s still hard to say how good she is as an individual?”

“Right.” Liu Hao nodded his head.

“But how are we supposed to figure out her skill and have the guild deal with it?” He Ming said.

“We’re being too impatient. The fact that Lord Grim is Ye Qiu is something everyone in the pro scene knows right now. Everyone also knows he’s planning on creating his own team to make his come back to the Pro Alliance. I highly doubt the only ones who are worried about this issue is our Excellent Era. Are the other guilds really just going to sit still and do nothing? I’ll go ask Chen Yehui to switch our accounts with three new ones and look for opportunities. For now, we won’t attack and just observe them.” Liu Hao said.

“If that’s the case, it’d be better if we had more alternate characters to switch to at any time. That way, it won’t be as suspicious.” He Ming suggested.

“As for Su Mucheng, pay attention to her from time to time. In the tenth server, she created a low-leveled account to help Ye Qiu. Who knows what she’ll in the Heavenly Domain.” Liu Hao said.

“Should we use our team’s rules to restrict her?” He Ming made another suggestion.

‘It won’t work. Those rules were always seen with one eye open and the other eye closed. Unless she becomes completely hostile to us, those rules are useless. As for Su Mucheng, I doubt that the Club is willing to cause trouble with her. We can’t offend her!” Liu Hao ground his teeth.

Su Mucheng didn’t have any background support her, but she treated everyone warmly and had good relations with everyone in the Club from top to bottom. After Ye Qiu’s retirement, her relationship with the Club had turned a bit stiff, but she was still a pro player and showed the attitude a pro should have. Whether it be the matches or the Club’s activities, she would still do her best. This wasn’t the reason for her protective umbrella though. Su Mucheng’s protective umbrella was her commercial value.

All of the financial benefits that came out of her such as being a spokesman for their advertisements or being the poster model for their team attire and products were all a large reason for the Club’s wealth. In this area, the three of them combined couldn’t compare to Su Mucheng. The Pro Alliance was being commercialized more and more these days and Su Mucheng was a walking money tree. Unless there was no other choice, what Club would give her up?

Ye Qiu having no commercial was his fatal wound.

“Just take note of Su Mucheng and that’ll be good. First, we need to figure out what exactly is up with Chasing Haze. The guild Ye Qiu created in the tenth server is called Happy. You guys should know that Happy is the name of that Internet Cafe next to our Club. Ye Qiu is currently over there as well. For the guild to be name Happy means that he has a very deep relationship with the Internet Cafe’s people. This Chasing Haze might be one of the Internet Cafe’s people. I’ll get Chen Yehui to send someone over to take a look.” Liu Hao said to the two of them, while thinking about the next steps to take. After pondering for awhile, he felt like he had been a bit too impatient. Right after knowing that Lord Grim had entered the Heavenly Domain, they immediately went to try and kill him. It had been too reckless. How could pro players charge in without knowing the situation?

“Among the three of them, the Elementalist has went offline.” In the game, Ye Xiu and Chen Guo had left their original leveling areas. Chen Guo searched for the three characters’ names and quickly found out that the Elementalist had logged off.

“What’s the point in looking them up? For them, one person having several accounts wouldn’t be unusual. You have no way of knowing if that’s really them playing or not. Don’t bother with it.” Ye XIu said.

“That’s troublesome. Then any character we see might be them?” Chen Guo said.

“It really is troublesome, which is why we have to hurry and level!” Ye Xiu said.

“Right now? Still leveling? Aren’t you afraid that they’ll call more players to look for us? This time, if our opponents send even more pro players, will your previous method work?” Chen Guo said.

Along the way, Ye Xiu explained to Chen Guo why he had done what he had done. Ye Xiu had been making preparations in order to intentionally lure the other side into having a misunderstanding. If it really was a true 1v3, with a 20 level disadvantage, beating three pro players would be a miracle. Chen Guo’s help would honestly be useless. It was like if two grown men were in a fight; a little baby on the side couldn’t be considered as a helper.

Playing on two accounts wasn’t easy for Ye Xiu either. There was no way he could have done it for the entire fight. He had just used Lord Grim to create an opportunity and then have Chasing Haze seize the opportunity to make it seem like Chasing Haze was some sort of expert.

Whether or not they believed that Chasing Haze was Su Mucheng wasn’t a misunderstanding Ye Xiu required. Su Mucheng was someone who was always around Excellent Era’s players. Such a misunderstanding that would easily be seen through. It didn’t have any value. They might be mistaken for a short moment, but Ye Xiu knew that they would quickly see through it. Having the three pro players think that Chen Guo was an expert was enough. Three versus one was something they didn’t need to fear at all. Three versus two, with one opponent being a feared top-tier God and the other being an opponent they knew nothing about. In this type of situation, pro players wouldn’t go out and attack recklessly. No one knew these habits better than Ye Xiu did.

“Then where should we go level?” Chen Guo asked.

“Just follow me.” Ye Xiu clearly had a plan already.

“Excellent Era’s players have already put out their hand. What about the other guilds? If they do the same, then how are you supposed to level?” Chen Guo was thinking about this issue. If all of the Club’s guilds allied together to fight against Ye Xiu, their strength in the Heavenly Domain was far more terrifying than their strength in the tenth server. An issue like not having enough players like in Thousand Waves Lake wouldn’t happen. Here, the Clubs had the strength to topple the mountains and turn the seas to drown Lord Grim with numbers.

Even if Ye Xiu was unequalled, he would still make a mistake eventually after a few tries. A single mistake cost 20% of a character’s experience in the Heavenly Domain. With such an environment, how long would it take him to level?

Chen Guo was extremely worried, but she couldn’t think of any ideas. She could only control her character to follow behind Lord Grim. She turned her head to glance at Ye Xiu. His face was as calm as ever, which made Chen Guo relax quite a bit.

After thinking about it for a bit, Chen Guo thought up a countermeasure: “Right now, you’re really famous. Why not use this opportunity to create your guild in the Heavenly Domain? The Clubs care about their image. With a guild behind you, they at least wouldn’t act openly.”

Ye Xiu heard this and laughed: “They were never going to act openly. In the Heavenly Domain, the top guilds have been operating for a long time. How could they not have many open accounts? Even if they acted secretly, they still have more than enough strength, so the guilds really wouldn’t care. If we ignored that and created one, it would be very difficult for it to remain. I’m only Level 50. I can’t even do Level 55 dungeons and even if I could, who would be interested in playing with a Level 55? I might be skilled, but my current strength isn’t enough to give others any benefit. If they can’t get any benefit with me, why would they go to our guild? Join our guild and also get killed?”

“I’m talking about your identity! You have a lot of fans. They won’t care about that.” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu laughed: “You can say that, but who would believe me?”

Chen Guo stared dumbly. That was true. One of the features of the Glory eSports scene was that no matter how amazing a pro character was, they would still have to rely on Glory’s continent. As a result, pro players couldn’t completely escape from the game. Due to this, there have been many who pretended they were a pro player saying things like “I’m Ye Qiu! I’m creating a guild, follow me!” To put it plainly, this wasn’t the first time such a thing was done. Players had already become numb to these types of words. No one would believe a pro player would come do this type of thing. Later, the Pro Alliance directly set up a rule prohibiting any pro player from doing this.

Ye Qiu might be retired pro player and wouldn’t be restricted by these rules, but no one would be convinced with a casual “I’m Ye Qiu.”

“Then have people with status prove it?” Chen Guo said.

Chapter 426 – To Lose Money Instead of Being Paid

In Glory, it was actually very easy to prove one’s identity. If he just logged into a pro account like One Autumn Leaf, it didn’t matter if the one controlling it wasn’t Ye Qiu or Sun Xiang, the players would at least be convinced that he wasn’t some random person out on the street. The words he said would carry more weight than someone just randomly blurting out stuff in the global chat.

Chen Guo was obviously talking about Su Mucheng. If she had her Dancing Rain log in and say a few words, Chen Guo believed that it would be enough to convince those in the Heavenly Domain. Afterwards, by using the fans’ respect and adoration for their idol, Chen Guo felt like creating a guild would only be a matter of time. Moreover, these fans would certainly stand together with their God and protect him, just like her.

“It’s……. possible, but it’s not time yet.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?” Chen Guo asked.

“Too violent.” Ye Xiu said.

“Violent?”

“Right now, I’m already the target of a multitude of arrows. Fortunately, because the top guilds have been suffering losses at my hands the entire time, they’ll be planning their next moves with a more cautious approach. It would be better to use this opportunity to take things step by step. Your suggestion would instantly cause a huge commotion and force the top guilds to hurry and suppress me. In this type of situation, do you really think that myself and the hundred that have been gathered in one breath be able to compete in strength with these top guilds?”

“You can’t?”

“Even we were only against a single guild, we would still lose very quickly. Would you believe that?” Ye Xiu said.

“No way.” Chen Guo was finding it a bit hard to believe. She felt that with Ye Xiu’s calling power, the number of fans he would gather would be more than enough to compete with a single guild.

Ye Xiu shook his head: “Don’t look down on these Club guilds. They’re all being managed down to a science. They’re on a completely different level than those guilds made for fun. If we pull a huge crowd of players like this, no matter how many players we gather, it’ll be no more than a grassroots organization. It would be enough to fight with guilds created by normal players, but if we’re going against Club guilds, they have a whole bunch of ways to make us collapse.”

Chen Guo thought about it and realized that he was right. She had played for many years and had been with normal player guilds before joining Excellent Dynasty. Even though she wasn’t a core member, she could see how organized the guild was. If Ye Xiu hadn’t said anything, she probably wouldn’t have noticed this. Chen Guo thought about it again and found that she didn’t have confidence either.

“The rich and powerful are rich and powerful because they have inside information. It’s not as simple as having a few God-level characters or God-level players in a team. You don’t want our team to be so short-lived as cause a bit of ruckus for a match and then be done, right?” Ye Xiu continued.

“Mm, then you tell me what you want to do!” Chen Guo said.

Just as she said this, Chen Guo saw several silhouettes flash by. Not waiting for Ye Xiu to reply, she immediately slid her mouse over to these silhouettes, ready to attack at any time. At the same time, she warned Ye Xiu: “There are players again.”

“Don’t be so nervous.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Huh?” Chen Guo looked and when they came closer, she saw that it was the previous Loulan Slash and his group.

Seeing that Ye Xiu wasn’t surprised, Chen Guo suddenly understood: “You asked them to come?”

“Yeah!” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“What are you thinking?”

“We’ll just join them temporarily. What do you think?” Ye Xiu said.

“That sounds like a terrible idea!” Chen Guo immediately blurted out. She didn’t know Loulan Slash and just like many other players, she had a certain prejudice towards players who paid their way to power. In addition, Loulan Slash had thoughts of pulling in Ye Xiu, so Chen Guo didn’t have any good feelings towards him.

“You don’t need to reply so quickly…….” Ye Xiu was speechless.

Chen Guo humphed. Her mind was in a mess. In the end, the great God still needed to ally with rich people like this? Chen Guo was also hoping for Ye Xiu to do well, but she didn’t have the power to help him too much, so she once again became conflicted. It was just like that previous pro match, where she didn’t know who to choose. She knew that she couldn’t help in any pro level battles, but she would still be more than delighted to cheer for them. She just didn’t want to feel like she was nonexistent.

“Hello. It’s nice to meet you again so soon.” Loulan Slash was still in the same five player party. In the blink of an eye, he walked up and greeted Ye Xiu and Chen Guo.

“Brothers, on the way here, have you thought about what I talked about previously?” Ye Xiu was very familiar with the practice in-game. He had only met them once before, but he was already calling them brothers as if they weren’t strangers.

“Are you really Ye Qiu?” Loulan Slash’s tone was very proper.

“I’m absolutely the Ye Qiu you’re thinking of.” Ye Xiu’s tone wasn’t bad either.

“It sounds like you’re implying something?” Loulan Slash said.

“You’re being too suspicious.” Ye Xiu said.

Silence.

“It really doesn’t matter if I’m Ye Qiu or not. Pulling me in will benefit you greatly.” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s hard to say.” Loulan Slash laughed, “I found out that your situation isn’t looking very good.”

“But I’m sure you’ve already made mental preparations for this type of situation. You just don’t know how much preparation you need and whether you can bear it, no?” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo heard the two talking and was feeling a bit confused. She didn’t feel like she should ask either, so she could only quietly send Ye Xiu a message: “What are you guys talking about!”

“I’ll tell you later!” Ye Xiu replied.

Loulan Slash didn’t speak for a good while. Because this was in the game, his expression couldn’t be read. No one knew what he was thinking right now.

“Your team is probably preparing to enter the qualifiers into the Alliance for next season, right?” Ye Xiu suddenly asked.

“How did you know?” Loulan Slash was surprised.

“It was just a random guess.” Ye Xiu said.

Loulan Slash didn’t dig deeper and happily admitted it: “We’ve already registered. Right now, we’re in the process of doing so. I don’t believe we’ll have any problems.”

“Then at this moment, you’re probably going to make announcement soon and attract the eyes of the players.” Ye Xiu smiled.

“Lord Grim really is a huge topic right now.” Loulan Slash said.

“This is a once in a lifetime opportunity.” Ye Xiu said.

“If you really are Ye Qiu, then this opportunity is huge.” Loulan Slash said.

“I am.”

“But I thought God Ye Qiu never publicized himself?” Loulan Slash said.

“I don’t think I ever said I’d help you with that, no?” Ye Xiu said.

“Yes…… having your name is already more than good enough.” Loulan Slash said.

Ye Xiu had finished saying what he wanted to say. Now it was his turn to be silent. On the side, Chen Guo didn’t need Ye Xiu to explain any further and finally understood his intent.

Loulan Slash was planning on creating a team and needed to create a commotion for it. Ye Xiu would be losing money instead of being paid in order to help Loulan Slash use his current popularity.

Lord Grim was currently the most watched character in Glory. Players had already been guessing which team he would be pulled into. If Loulan Slash’s team announced that they had gotten him, his team would immediately attract everyone’s attention. This was exactly what Loulan Slash needed. As for whether or not Ye Qiu would become a member of his team or not was only secondary.

For joining Loulan Slash’s guild, Ye Xiu would have the guild’s protection. However, would they be reliable enough?

Chen Guo thought about it for a bit and suddenly panicked. She couldn’t take the time to type it out and directly glanced at Ye Xiu: “Will this be okay?”

“What?” Ye Xiu carefully covered his headphones a bit to remind Chen Guo.

Chen Guo directly threw his headphones to one side: “If you sell yourself to them, after they’re done using you, they might kick you away. What then?”

“Even if they don’t kick me, I’ll leave. I’m not going to join their team. We’ll be making our own team.” Ye Xiu said.

The words “We’ll be making our own team.” made Chen Guo’s heart soften, but this wasn’t the time to be happy.

“I’m worried about the present! After you join them and he uses your current popularity, if the other guilds come looking for you, he’ll immediately kick you. What then?” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu smiled: “If it was that easy, he wouldn’t be pondering over it for so long. He would have agreed to it immediately.”

“Hm?”

“Burning the bridge right after crossing it would cause their reputation to plummet. They would be attracting everyone’s attention to themselves and then throwing dirt onto themselves…… wouldn’t that destroy their entire purpose for making a commotion?” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah….. that’s…… true.” Chen Guo muddled.

“In addition, afterwards, they’ll pretty much be on the same page as us. There’s no need to cast us away like that.” Ye Xiu said.

“What do you mean?”

“They’ll be creating a team too! Do you really think these Club guilds are only focused on us? It’s not because I’m Ye Qiu. An expert alone wouldn’t make them act. The key reason is because I’m planning on creating a team. They see that I’d be their direct competitor in the future, which is why they’re actions are becoming more and more serious. They’ll certainly have the same attitude towards Loulan Slash too. The Glory eSports scene isn’t like a normal sport. The Pro Alliance is where the battles are seen by everyone, but it’s not the only battle taking place.” Ye Xiu said.

“Understood.” Chen Guo nodded her head. She realized that she had been too panicked. Afterwards, she was feeling very embarrassed. She was always so easy to be startled. Once she heard Ye Xiu’s explanation, she immediately understood. She knew clearly that she didn’t have enough experience, whether it was because she wasn’t looking at the big picture or because she wasn’t looking deep enough or because she didn’t understand the relationship between their circumstances. Owner? Chen Guo began to sweat. If she became the owner of the team, she felt like their team would drop dead before even reaching the door to the Pro Alliance.

Chapter 427 – Too Afraid to Rush In Recklessly

After her doubts were dispelled, Chen Guo waited with Ye Xiu for Loulan Slash’s response. Loulan Slash had been silent ever since Ye Xiu finished speaking without any signs of movement. It was the same for the other four players behind him. Their five characters blended into the background scenery. Only their clothing showed signs of movement, fluttering in the wind.

During these types of moments, Chen Guo was obviously less patient than Ye Xiu. Waiting without seeing any response made her uneasy. She really wanted to shoot a few shots at them and see if they were still going to stay silent.

After waiting anxiously for a good while, Loulan Slash finally began to speak: “I’m going to need more time to consider this.”

“My god. What were you doing just before then?” Chen Guo asked.

“We came to the conclusion that we needed more time to consider it.” Loulan Slash said.

“Why does this have to be so troublesome!” Chen Guo said.

“What are you so anxious for? If you’re so anxious, you can join in!” Loulan Slash laughed, while sending a guild invite to Chasing Haze.

Chen Guo fiercely rejected it. On the other hand, Ye Xiu calmly replied: “I’ll be waiting for your reply.” Then, the five players quietly left just like in their first meeting.

“How is it?” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

“They’re quite cautious. But the more cautious they are, the more we can expect from them.” Ye Xiu said.

“Do you think he’ll accept?” Chen Guo asked.

“I’m not sure. I don’t know to what extent they’ve prepared. I’m guessing that’s why they need more time to consider it.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo turned her camera and watched as the five players left.

Ye Xiu had his Lord Grim look around in a circle, when he suddenly said: “It’s so empty.”

“Do you want an emptier place for peaceful leveling or lively place with everyone attacking you?” Chen Guo asked.

“Loulan Slash found us pretty quickly. Excellent Era’s people found us very quickly as well. Tell me, do you really think the other guilds don’t know where we are?” Ye Xiu said.

“Uh……”

“I’m getting so much focus trying to get one level. I’m really good at getting a crowd aren’t I!” Ye Xiu mocked himself, while having Lord Grim pull a monster to kill.

“If these guilds know where you are, then why haven’t they moved?’ Chen Guo said, while controlling Chasing Haze to help.

“I’m guessing it’s because I’ve been getting a lot of attention recently.” Ye Xiu said, “As guilds, they have to consider the overall player base’s influence. Even if they’re operating in secret, they still have to be more careful. For this type of issue, they hope to eliminate their opponent without any noise, so it’s making it quite difficult for them because of the attention I’m getting.”

“Did you cause such a storm with your Heavenly Challenge intentionally?” Chen Guo said.

“If…… I hadn’t created a storm, it would have been intentional.” Ye Xiu said honestly.

The truth made Chen Guo speechless for a good while.

Ye Xiu’s analysis of the Club guilds were absolutely correct.

In the Heavenly Domain, everyone had a solid base. Whether it was guild members or open accounts, they had plenty at their disposal. For characters without guild tags, even if they passed by Lord Grim, Ye Xiu wouldn’t be able to tell if there was a problem or not. If the guilds wanted to know where Lord Grim was, it wouldn’t be difficult at all. Before Lord Grim reached Level 50 and before he finished the Challenge, the top guilds in the Heavenly Domain had already begun preparing for him.

In the tenth server, it was as if they had come to terms and didn’t make any movements, waiting for this moment. They would use their advantage in the Heavenly Domain to destroy Ye Qiu’s momentum at Level 50.

It might seem empty where Lord Grim was, but as soon as the announcement was made that he had entered the Heavenly Domain, the bustling activity going on underground hadn’t stopped.

The top guilds had been waiting for this day for a long long time and already had their plans made.

Blue Brook Guild, Herb Garden, Tyrannical Ambition, Samsara, Misty Castle, Howling Heights…….. They had set up a discussion group solely for dealing with Ye Qiu.

But while he did the Heavenly Challenge, his fame soared throughout all of Glory. This was something the guilds hadn’t expected. In a sense, they had once again ignored the fact that their opponent this time was on another level.

A God obviously wouldn’t lose to anyone in the Arena. Not only would he not lose, he also had his unique class and strange weapon. Him being Level 50 beating Level 70 players was also a reality. He would naturally attract a lot of attention. These were all easy to think of, but the problem was, the top guilds hadn’t thought about it. It wasn’t that they were unable to think of it, but rather they had neglected it.

Now they were in a difficult situation.

Getting rid of such a popular character would cost them a hand and a foot. They didn’t want the Glory players to begin to discuss: Huh? Who did Lord Grim offend? Why is he being chased after and killed to such an extent in the Heavenly Domain?

On Earth, there was no such thing as an unblockable wall. In today’s generation, gossip could spread like fire for the most random things, let alone something like this.

As a result, until things settled down, the top guilds wouldn’t dare make any rash movements. Only Excellent Era felt like they could make a small movement because they had sent out pro players. However, they had also hit a nail and had to be careful now.

The top guilds hadn’t made any movements yet, but outside in the group chat, their brain cells were exploding all over the ground…….

Lord Grim’s first day in the Heavenly Domain passed by peacefully.

Ye Xiu had killed monsters the entire day. In the middle, he had encountered a few small disturbances, but they were all just coincidences. Whenever players saw the name “Lord Grim”, they would come over to pay their respects. Assassinations, encirclement…… in the end, none of those appeared.

“What are they planning!” Chen Guo felt unsatisfied. She had been worried the entire day, but there were no signs of any movements from the guilds. It made her despise them greatly.

“Isn’t this good?” Ye Xiu laughed.

Apart from this, the customer with the character Ascending had come to Happy Internet Cafe again today. Hearing that Lord Grim had entered the Heavenly Domain, he personally went over to give him his congratulations. Chen Guo watched and understood him well.

On the second day, when Ye Xiu got up, ready to play games, he discovered that his original spot had been taken by three people. The three people were customers too. Ye Xiu was at a loss. He pulled over a fellow employee and pointed there, but didn’t know what to ask.

The fellow employee understood Ye Xiu’s meaning and laughed: “The boss moved those three computers up stairs!”

“Upstairs?” Ye Xiu was puzzled. He looked up to the next floor and didn’t see any signs of Cchen Guo. He turned around, ready to go upstairs, when Chen Guo came out of the elevator. When she saw Ye Xiu, before he could even ask, she said: “Upstairs, Room 213.”

“Room?”

“Yeah! To prevent anyone from bothering you.” Chen Guo said in a serious tone. Ascending had reminded her. This was going to be the base of operations for their team. When they were gaming, she couldn’t have people bothering them.

“You’ve got good prospects for the future!” Ye Xiu gave his approval and immediately ran to the second floor.

Happy Internet Cafe’s second floor was a more luxurious area. It was specious and quiet. The rooms were for customers who didn’t want to be bothered. Their three computers had been put into Room 213. This room was a four person room. The biggest rooms at Happy Internet Cafe were only this big. However, if they were going to develop a team, the team would have much more than four people. Chen Guo and Ye Xiu went up together. She told him her plans to make a special area on the second floor specially for the future team to practice.

“It’s a bit shabby……” Chen Guo said, a bit embarrassed.

“It doesn’t matter. All the teams were like this in the beginning.” Ye Xiu said, but after seeing that Chen Guo didn’t believe him, he added: “In the past……”

As a result, Chen Guo didn’t say anything more. In the room, her computer was already open and she went down to play Glory.

“I was on for a bit. I didn’t see Loulan Slash.” Chen Guo said. She was already beginning to put all of her thoughts into team related matters. Yesterday, she had slept early, so she would obviously be awake sooner than Ye Xiu. But when she went online, without Ye Xiu, she wasn’t sure what to do. She didn’t dare level up Lord Grim for Ye Xiu. The Heavenly Domain was too dangerous. If she leveled him, let alone a pro player, any elite from the top guilds would be enough to delete her. A 20 level difference was something she didn’t have the ability to deal with.

“Don’t worry. Let’s just continue leveling.” Ye Xiu said as he sat down.

“Okay.” Chen Guo nodded her head.

Tang Rou wasn’t here right now. This sister hadn’t received the same treatment as Ye Xiu and still needed to work. Every day, she would sit at the front desk as the cashier just like always. But for her, leveling wasn’t something she was in a rush for. She could spend more of her time reading guides, studying videos, and expanding her knowledge of the game. These types of things could be done at the front desk.

Tang Rou was currently looking at the set of Battle Mage guides Ye Xiu had picked out for her in the beginning, when she heard someone call out for her. When she turned around to look, she saw that there were two customers who wanted to use the computer. She didn’t pay too much attention and after seeing their credentials, she opened up two computers for them. When she returned their credentials to their computers, she saw that the two were looking around as if they were looking for something.

Chapter 428 – Sweeping the Field

“Is there anything else that I can help you two with?” Tang Rou asked.

One of them had glanced at Tang Rou’s screen on the front desk and smiled: “Miss, do you also play Glory?”

“Yes……”

“Is there an expert in this Internet Cafe?” the same person asked.

“Glory expert?” Tang Rou stared blankly.

“Yeah!”

“What would be considered as an expert?” Tang Rou asked.

“Hmm…….you’d probably have to fight him in order to know.” This person smiled.

“Fight with who? You?” Tang Rou asked.

“Any of us!”

“You two are?”

“We came from Grand Internet Cafe.” the other person said.

“Oh, understood.” Tang Rou nodded her head. Even though she hadn’t been playing Glory for too long, she had been in Happy Internet Cafe for quite a while. She knew about some of the things going on between the Internet Cafes.

Glory was currently an incredibly popular game. If you looked in any Internet Cafe, over half of their customers would be playing Glory. Every Internet Cafe would naturally borrow Glory to do some events and pull in customers. For example, the Cafe could hold Glory tournaments or broadcast pro matches like what Chen Guo was doing. These were all done to win the favor of Glory players.

Many of these customers went to the Internet Cafe that they were familiar with and were also quite loyal to it. Just like pro teams or in-game guilds, Glory players also formed their own group for their favorite Internet Cafe. There was a sort of competitiveness between the Internet Cafes. The managers would sometimes lead Glory players from different Internet Cafes to fight each other in Glory from time to time.

The two fellows in front of her had come up claiming they were from a certain Internet Cafe, seeking a Glory expert. These kinds of occurrences had happened quite a few times during her stay at Happy Internet Cafe. Chen Guo and other Glory players called this type of activity Sweeping the Field.

In Sweeping the Field, the majority of the time, players wanted to show off their skill and earn a bit of glory for themselves. It wasn’t rare for the owner of an Internet Cafe to help add fuel to the fire though. It was hard to say if this helped the business or not, but one’s own Internet Cafe winning versus another one was kind of like beating a competitor; it felt quite good.

Tang Rou knew about the Grand Internet Cafe that the two claimed to be from. It wasn’t too far from Happy Internet Cafe and was quite a good Cafe as well. The owner of Grand Internet Cafe also knew Chen Guo, so Tang Rou had seen the owner before. It had been very obvious that the owner was very envious of Happy’s location.

Happy was right next to Club Excellent Era. This location made it a huge attraction to Glory players. The owner of Grand didn’t have as good of a location as Happy, so he had always wanted to beat Happy Internet Cafe in Glory skill to let others know that the Internet Cafe next to Excellent Era was nothing special.

Unfortunately, the owner never got what he hoped for during his several years of fighting. Chen Guo’s business strategy had helped her lure quite a few Excellent Era fans. Players who were fans of a team were undoubtedly big fans of Glory. Their skill level wouldn’t be bad either. Even though no earth-shattering expert had ever appeared, Grand Internet Cafe was the same. None of their customers were exceptionally skilled, so dropping by to play Sweeping the Field would just be laughed at.

As a result, even though Grand Internet Cafe was fighting, they never used such an intense method like Sweeping the Field. Grand usually held tournaments and invited Happy to play. The tournaments had solo, King of Fighting, and team tournaments, making it seem very official. However, after many years of battling, neither side had been able to beat the other. However, if they used a point system like in the pro scene, Happy would have a slight advantage, which made the owner of Grand quite sad.

Grand Internet Cafe sending people to try Sweeping the Field was a first.

Sweeping the Field was a double-edged sword. A successful sweep would give you boundless glory. But if you lost, then it would be very shameful. As a result, anyone who dared to try Sweeping the Field was either very arrogant or had the skill to back it up. Tang Rou was currently sizing up the two of them, when he heard another person say: “Ha ha ha, where’s your boss Chen? I don’t see her anywhere.”

Tang Rou turned his head to look and recognized him as the owner of Grand.

“Boss Ma, it’s good to see you!” Tang Rou greeted. Boss Ma’s full name was Ma Chenyi and he was also a big fan of Glory like Chen Guo. His Internet Cafe and Happy Internet Cafe competed in Glory skill, which sometimes made it difficult to tell if they were business competitors or Glory competitors.

“Oh, it’s Little Tang! Where’s Old Chen?” Ma Chenyi said loudly on purpose and intentionally called Chen Guo ‘Old Chen’. Women were usually more sensitive to age than men. The bad blood between Ma Chenyi and Chen Guo had already spread to every aspect of their lives.

“She’s upstairs. Would you like me to call her over?” Tang Rou said.

“Call her. Of course you have to call her! Hurry up and call her to come down. There will be a good show to see.” Ma Chenyi looked to be in a very good mood today.

“Hold on.” Tang Rou smiled. This boss had personally come to try Sweeping the Field, which meant that this time, he was very confident. Tang Rou knew Chen Guo cared a lot about this. Tang Rou wasn’t worried though. Right now, Happy Internet Cafe housed a God! Who could be more skilled than Ye Xiu? Anyone who could actually match Ye Xiu would be among the Gods in the pro scene. He’d have immediately gathered a huge amount of attention as soon as he walked in. There was no way he’d just be standing there so peacefully.

Upstairs, Chen Guo had just started playing when she received Tang Rou’s text message. Seeing that Ma Chenyi was here to try Sweeping the Field, she immediately became overjoyed.

If this was in the past, Chen Guo would have been quite nervous if Ma Chenyi had personally come to try Sweeping the Field. But now, with Ye Xiu, who could beat him?

“What are you so happy for?” Ye Xiu had been alarmed at Chen Guo’s sudden laugh.

“Someone’s here to try Sweeping the Field.” Chen Guo said.

“Huh?”

“Downstairs.” Chen Guo said.

“Oh, you’re talking about the Internet Cafe!” Ye Xiu had experienced everything there was to experience in Glory. He wasn’t a stranger to Sweeping the Field and quickly understood why Chen Guo had suddenly laughed. With him, trying to sweep away Happy would be like trying to sweep away a mountain.

“Why don’t you come down with me?” Chen Guo said. She clearly wasn’t going to hide anything. She wanted to directly bring in the bullet. She was looking forward to seeing Ma Chenyi’s expression after the two “experts” he had brought were crushed.

“Sweeping the Field……. I haven’t seen it in the two months I’ve been here. Who’s come?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Someone I know well. If you go a bit farther than where you usually buy cigarettes, you might see it. It’s right around the corner over there. It’s called Grand Internet Cafe. Do you know about it?” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu was helpless: “Of course I know. I’ve only stayed here for two months, but I’ve been in this area for many years. I’m just as familiar with it as you are.”

“Oh…… I forgot.” Chen Guo said, “That Internet Cafe has come to try Sweeping the Field. I don’t know what type of expert he picked up to have the courage to do it.”

“Has he come here before?”

“Never. At most, he’s held tournaments between us.” Chen Guo said.

“So it’s like that…… This….. It might be interesting!” Ye Xiu said.

Downstairs, after Tang Rou sent the text message, she was starting to question herself when she saw that there was no reply or sign of Chen Guo! May Chenyi wasn’t in a hurry though. He looked as if he had a card up his sleeve and chuckled: “What’s wrong? Did Old Chen get scared after hearing that I had personally come?”

“Yeah, I’m very scared!” Chen Guo answered Ma Chenyi as she walked down the stairs.

“Old Chen!” Ma Chenyi immediately greeted, “Long time, no see! How was your break? Sigh. Another year has passed in the blink of an eye and you’ve grown older a year again. We’re now in our thirties. Have you gotten a boyfriend yet? Would you like this brother to introduce one for you?”

Ma Chenyi mocked her, though this wasn’t anything unusual between him and Chen Guo. Chen Guo’s resistance to it had gone up just like her resistance to Ye Xiu’s words. The two of them had been like this for many years. Chen Guo’s resistance to his words had already become strong. This bit of trash talk wouldn’t faze her anymore.

“How boring! Do you know how many times you’ve used this script?” She wouldn’t be angry, but she was still going to bite back.

“Ha ha, I’m just here to send you my blessings. Don’t you like Sweeping the Field?” Ma Chenyi laughed. He intentionally stressed the words ‘Sweeping the Field’. He said the words so loudly that even the customers on the second floor could hear them. Many of the customers took off their headphones and had been startled by it.

Those who came to the Internet Cafe often knew what “Sweeping the Field” meant. As soon as they heard this, they raised their heads to look in their direction. When they saw the extremely arrogant Ma Chenyi, they first felt a sense of displeasure and then immediately expected that the Sweeping the Field was a joke.

“How do you want to sweep?” Chen Guo asked calmly.

“It’s simple. As soon as someone beats these two, we’ll leave immediately.” Ma Chenyi loudly shouted.

As soon as these words came out, the Internet Cafe immediately went into an uproar. Sweeping the Field was Sweeping the Field, but there were many ways to sweep. Usually, they arranged a few matches and then looked at the outcome after playing them out. But this guy actually challenged the entire Happy Internet Cafe. This meant that the two that arrived might actually have some real skill. Only someone with such confidence in the two of them wouldn’t be afraid to wage war with everyone in the Cafe.

“Leave immediately? I don’t think we ever talked about coming and leaving.” Chen Guo said.

“Oh? Then what do you want to wager?” Ma Chenyi asked.

Chapter 429 – Meeting the Challenge

“What did we bet last time?” Chen Guo asked.

“It’s been too long. I can’t remember.” Ma Chenyi’s face darkened. Just one look at him and you could tell that he wasn’t too sophisticated of a person. All of his emotions were displayed on his face. He had previously been in high spirits, but as soon as Chen Guo asked this, his face immediately darkened. It was very obvious that he hadn’t forgotten at all. He just didn’t want to think of it again.

Last time, he had lost quite miserably. The crowd was very certain of this.

“It wouldn’t be good if it was like last time, right? We’re still celebrating the Spring Festival, after all. Why not this? 24 Heavenly Domain account cards. One for each class. How about it?” Chen Guo said.

“What are you going to do with so many account cards?” Ma Chenyi was curious.

“What? We haven’t even fought yet and you’re already admitting your loss?” Chen Guo grinned.

“Who’s admitting their loss!?” Ma Chenyi shouted.

“If you haven’t admitted your defeat, then how do you know that the account cards are going to be given to me?” Chen Guo said.

Unsophisticated people weren’t very sharp in battles with words. One just had to look at how Ma Chenyi had used the same script over and over again for several years to know that he wasn’t very skilled in this area. Chen Guo had taken the topic and mocked him with it. For a moment, he didn’t know how to respond. The watching crowd saw him lose his composure and burst into laughter.

Just from this short exchange, Ma Chenyi had clearly lost greatly in the battle of words. He was quite strong as well though and didn’t fall after being mocked. He continued to stand firm and finally had something to counter back with: “What am I going to do with a bunch of account

“You can have something else.” Chen Guo said.

The two were mainly battling for the energy. Their bet was to add hail to the snow. They weren’t actually here for all this. If Ma Chenyi really wanted something, he would be asking for Happy Internet Cafe’s location, but such an unrealistic condition couldn’t be used. The two weren’t going to bet this.

24 Heavenly Domain account cards weren’t cheap, but to these two Internet Cafe owners, it wouldn’t be considered as a large expense. The main reason was still for the energy.

“It’s fine. I won’t bicker with you. Account cards it is!” Ma Chenyi said and then announced to the crowd: “Brothers, in a moment, we’ll have 24 account cards! We have no use for them, so we’re going to be giving them out. If you’re interested, come to my Grand Internet Cafe and help us think of how to give them away.”

“You’re very confident!” Chen Guo grinned.

“Naturally.” Ma Chenyi laughed. After laughing, he suddenly began to think. It made sense that he would have confidence, but how come Chen Guo seemed to be fearless? Something wasn’t right. Where did her confidence come from?

“Is it just these two?” Chen Guo didn’t give Ma Chenyi much time to think deeply and pointed to the two standing beside the front desk.

“Correct.”

‘Okay. Let’s start then. Is anyone here interested in trying?” Chen Guo called out to the Internet Cafe. Ma Chenyi had challenged the entire Happy Internet Cafe, so Chen Guo didn’t need to organize it. She could first pick anyone curious player out there to give it a try.

There were obviously many of these types of players. Even if they weren’t frequent customers of Happy, it was very common for them to run over and give it a try. Many people immediately got up, asking if they could try.

Those who were willing to go up were all max level characters in the Heavenly Domain. When the two logged in, Chen Guo went up to look. One of them was a Blade Master, while the other was a Sharpshooter. They were both very popular classes in Glory.

A room in the Arena was quickly set up. Spectators were welcome, of course. The people who would be watching were obviously going to be Happy Internet Cafe’s players.

“Do you want me to open up a computer for you?” Chen Guo got onto a computer and was also spectating like the other customers. This type of spectating would let them see a more general picture of the match.

“No need.” Ma Chenyi stood behind his two players and was planning on watching the two play from their screens.

The match quickly began.

The first to come on stage was that Blade Master. On Happy Internet Cafe’s side, the challenger was a Witch. Everyone followed the countdown filled with anticipation. For someone to dare challenge everyone at the scene, he must have some real skill, right?

The reality wasn’t too far off. This Blade Master really did have some skill.

Both of the participants were Heavenly Domain players. Unless they had bought their accounts, they wouldn’t be noobs. This Witch player couldn’t be considered to be an expert, but he was still quite good. But as soon as the two sides fought, the Witch never had the advantage and was easily cleaned up by the Blade Master. Even though it wasn’t a full health victory, the difference between the two sides was obvious.

Some of the crowd members who were hoping to watch a comedy show couldn’t say anything. This Sweeping the Field guy wasn’t just talk.

“Beautiful!” Ma Chenyi roared when he saw the word “GLORY” appear on screen. It was once again loud enough for the people on the second floor to hear. He also glanced at Chen Guo to see her reaction.

“Not bad. He’s quite good!” Chen Guo smiled.

“He can play.” Ma Chenyi said.

“Who else wants to try?” Chen Guo asked.

After seeing the match, it was quite easy to see how skilled this Blade Master was. The curious players discovered that they clearly weren’t opponents for him and would be crushed as well. No one replied when Chen Guo asked this question.

“Oh? I thought Happy Internet Cafe had a lot of experts? What’s wrong? Did they all disappear?” Ma Chenyi taunted.

No one knew if he said this on purpose or on a whim, but it really was quite hurtful. Chen Guo also became a bit sad. When she looked around at her customers, there weren’t many who were angry or anything. She also didn’t recognize any of the faces in the crowd.

Chen Guo knew that in the past, the experts that helped her at Happy were huge fans of Excellent Era. Ever since she refused to stream Excellent Era’s matches, many of them were offended and had stopped coming. After that day, many of the faces she was familiar with had disappeared from Happy Internet Cafe.

“Hmph, what’s there to be arrogant for?” Chen Guo hadn’t yet replied, when someone from the crowd suddenly shouted.

Someone who would call out like this would always make others look forward to him. Everyone’s eyes turned towards the speaker. The speaker was looking disdainfully at the two Sweepers.

“With just that skill, how could they be opponents for Lord Grim?”

As soon as he spoke, the entire crowd fell over. This guy wasn’t talking about how amazing he was. He was talking about someone else! With how high and mighty he was talking, it was as if he thought he was the second coming of Christ.

Chen Guo looked at the speaker and saw that it was that guy with the character called Ascending. When he saw Chen Guo look over, he immediately called out: “Boss, Lord Grim! Call him over. That guy will beat these two punks easily.”

“Lord Grim……” When this name came out, everyone was shocked.

In Glory, there were very few players who didn’t know the name ‘Lord Grim’. However, the info that Lord Grim was from Happy Internet Cafe wasn’t something that had spread around. When Ma Chenyi heard this, his expression was as if he had been stepped on. After a long pause, he said: “Lord Grim is one of your people?”

Lord Grim had ignored the 20 level difference. He had a Silver weapon in his hands. In the Heavenly Challenge, he hadn’t lost a single time in the Arena. He had already become a legend. Ma Chenyi finally understood why Chen Guo was so fearless. She was hiding such an incredible expert.

“What? You admit your loss?” Chen Guo laughed.

Ma Chenyi really was afraid because the tales of Lord Grim’s deeds were unprecedented in Glory history. The crucial point was that he had never lost a single round. This was a true Sweeper.

But since things had already gotten to this step, going back on his word would be more embarrassing than losing and then leaving. Ma Chenyi was truly sad. When he recalled how arrogant he was when he walked in, he wanted to slam his head into the wall.

“Lord Grim is just Lord Grim. I’m not scared for you.” Ma Chenyi was afraid, but his mouth was still as stubborn as before. His face already looked like a joke to the crowd though.

“You wish. It’s a pity though. Lord Grim isn’t here today.” Chen Guo said.

“Not here?” Ma Chenyi was puzzled. If he wasn’t here, then Chen Guo shouldn’t have that sort of tone? Why was she still so confident?

“But I never said that Lord Grim is the only expert here!” Chen Guo said.

“What do you mean?”

“See. He’s here?” Chen Guo pointed at the screen.

The Blade Master had just won the match. Even though there were quite a few spectators, most of them were Happy Internet Cafe’s players and knew what was going on, so no one left the room. At this moment, someone suddenly entered and faced the Blade Master.

“Who is this?” Ma Chenyi asked.

“My people.”

“Where?” Ma Chenyi looked around.

“Here.” Someone raised his hand, “Can we start?”

“Start!” Ma Chenyi said fiercely.

The challenger was a Launcher. When the match started, the player immediately began wandering around. The Launcher was a long-range class. In order to win, Launchers had to maintain some distance from their opponent. However, Launchers were a slower class. In order to maintain a high speed, they had to be very skilled with Aerial Fire.

And this Launcher had completely done this. Amidst the sounds of repeated firing, the Launcher maintained a distance away from the Blade Master, slowly killing the Blade Master from afar. This type of strategy leaned on the dirtier side. But whether or not this strategy could be kept to the very end was another question. The Blade Master’s expression was also very patient, waiting for an opportunity to arise.

Chapter 430 – Overwhelming Victory

Everyone was prepared to watch a patient and drawn-out battle, but the momentum suddenly shifted. The Blade Master, who had been looking for an opportunity, was suddenly hit by the Launcher’s strike. No one thought that it was too serious, but the Launcher’s followed up with one attack after another. Layer upon layer of dust from the explosion lifted. The Blade Master was like a struggling boat in a storm, violently bobbing up and down, until it was smashed into pieces.

GLORY!!

The glowing word flashed across everyone’s eyes. Everyone stared with their jaws dropped. They had thought that they were watching a Launcher playing dirty, but then he suddenly comboed the Blade Master until death in one single breath. All of this happened too quickly. The crowd went from thinking nothing of the match to realizing that something wasn’t right to staring dumbly at the already dead Blade Master. They had only just woken up from their dream.

“D*MN!” someone cried out.

“Did anyone record that??” another person shouted.

In the Arena, the system didn’t record the match by default. Someone had to choose the record option for it to work. In addition, the room owner had the right to prohibit recording. Most players didn’t use this right though.

At this moment, when the mention of a recording came out, everyone finally realized what had happened.

The Blade Master had lost. Everyone already knew this result, but how did it all happen? They were all a bit confused and wanted to look back to watch, but they needed a recording to do that. However, when the match started, no one had predicted something like this would happen.

Ma Chenyi’s expression was extremely ugly. In truth, he hadn’t seen the instant the momentum shifted either, but he at least knew that they had lost. He had challenged everyone in the Internet Cafe, but he had already lost after their second opponent. In addition, the loss hadn’t been close. Ma Chenyi still looked straight ahead. He tried hard to not turn his head and look at Chen Guo.

The crowd was unable to recall that brilliant instant the momentum shifted and could only look at the player who did it all. The arrogant person had been stepped on. This would always be something people liked to see. As a result, Ma Chenyi discovered that not looking at Chen Guo was useless. The crowd’s gaze was difficult to bear and his pride was fiercely stepped on.

In comparison, the Blade Master’s expression was more natural. He even stood up and looked in the direction of the opponent he had lost to. The crowd saw this and felt like he was an expert who had seen the wide world. It wasn’t possible to never lose in such a duel. In victory and defeat, he displayed proper behavior and it was the mark of a mature expert.

Ma Chenyi might not want to look at Chen Guo, but Chen Guo was certainly going to look at him. At this moment, she laughed out loud at Ma Chenyi: “Boss Ma, why aren’t you shouting anymore? I’d say this match was even more beautiful than the last match, don’t you think?”

“Don’t be so happy. Say it after you beat both my people.” Ma Chenyi was unwilling to give up until his death, but he no longer had the same confidence as before. In reality, when he heard Lord Grim’s name, Ma Chenyi had already lost most of his hope toward Sweeping the Field. Even if Lord Grim wasn’t there, so what? If Lord Grim had been here, even if he won, when Lord Grim came back, Lord Grim could easily win back their face. The current Ma Chenyi was already in an unwinnable situation.

In the Arena, the Blade Master had already left to spectate the match, while the Sharpshooter entered the room. But the Launcher he was supposed to fight had unexpectedly left.

Just when everyone looked over, the person said: “We’re switching people.”

“Boss Ma, it wouldn’t be fair if you could have two people, while we can only have one, right?” Chen Guo said.

As this was said, another character had entered the match. Everyone looked and saw that it was a Witch this time. Everyone looked around to see who it was. The challenger took the initiative to stand up to let everyone know and then asked: “Can we start?”

Everyone immediately ran back to their seats and this time, they didn’t forget to click the record option.

The match began and was fascinating from the start. The two players clearly preferred to play aggressively. Witches and Sharpshooters had some similarities. Both had close combat skills and also long-range capabilities. Witches could fly on their brooms, while the Gunner classes could use Aerial Fire. These were all unique movement options that other classes didn’t have. The two never paused to stop while they battled.

If they were at close-range, they fought. If they were at mid-range, they fought. If they were at long-range, they still fought. From the start of the match, the battle never stopped for a moment. They moved in all sorts of ways, but they never moved too far apart. The two characters were always in each other’s range.

However, this type of continuous fighting meant that it wouldn’t be a long match. Amidst the dazzling attacks, everyone was easily able to see how the Sharpshooter had been suppressed by the Witch. The Sharpshooter tried to rely on returning fire in order to take back the initiative, but it was to no avail. The Witch cornered him with a few Sweeps and the Sharpshooter no longer had room to move around freely in. The Witch had already prepared an arsenal of magic items to throw down and then ended the match.

GLORY!

The glowing word flashed out.

This time, the crowd wasn’t too amazed. This was because the match had been exceptionally clear. From the beginning to the end, every detail in the match was easy for everyone to understand. The Launcher had suddenly comboed his opponent to death in one breath, which made everyone feel something wasn’t right. But there was nothing to say for this match.

It was clear and obvious that the reason the Witch won was because he was better. Every part of the match was visible. Everyone could understand what had happened at a glance. Not many people went back to watch the recording.

When the match ended, Ma Chenyi had thoroughly withered away. No matter how stubborn his mouth was, Ma Chenyi couldn’t say anything that wouldn’t make him lose face. In the end, he could only quietly say: “I’ll send you the account cards in a bit.”

“You’re going to leave just like this?” Chen Guo laughed.

Ma Chenyi was about to say something, when the Blade Master suddenly said: “No hurry.”

Everyone was startled at this, including Ma Chenyi.

This Sweeping the Field could be looked on as a joke, but the two Sweepers were very calm. They didn’t look as ashamed as Ma Chenyi. The Blade Master continued: “We can’t sweep this field, but the expert you have here really is incredible. We want to ask him for some advice. You don’t mind, right?”

“Of course, I don’t mind.” Chen Guo smiled and then looked towards Ma Chenyi: “Boss Ma, would you like to stay and continue watching the show?”

Ma Chenyi stared blankly, but he felt like this way, his originally very embarrassing situation wouldn’t be embarrassing. His two guys lost in style. With their modest attitudes, the crowd couldn’t despise them.

“Then I’ll stay for a bit longer!” Ma Chenyi nodded his head.

“You two, how do you want to fight? The two from before?” Chen Guo asked.

The expressions of the two moved: “Boss, do you have any other experts? If it’s convenient, let us have a try!”

At this moment, they weren’t the only two who wanted to see any other experts. Ma Cheny,i as well as the crowd, was very curious to see what other incredible experts Happy possessed.

“Okay!” Chen Guo nodded her head and an Assassin entered the Arena room.

Assassins and Blade Masters were both close combat characters. In comparison to the two previous matches, the strikes were powerful and their blades were soaked in blood. Amidst the blossoming blood, the match was still as clear as the last match. Not longer after the match began, the Assassin clearly held the advantage. Seeing this match, if that Blade Master hadn’t crushed the very first match and shown his skill, no one would have thought that he was any expert. It showed just how terrifying Happy Internet Cafe’s experts were.

After the Blade Master lost, the Sharpshooter substituted in. Next up for Happy Internet Cafe was a Striker. Everyone sucked in a cold breath. This Happy Internet Cafe had so many powerful experts!

Ma Chenyi’s expression darkened even further. He had felt that the Blade Master and Sharpshooter that he had were exceptionally skilled. Why else would he be confident in running over to try Sweeping the Field?”

But when he got to Happy, one expert after the other appeared. Seeing their ID and person, none of them were the same. When did they all come to Happy?

Just one of these incredible experts was amazing enough to see in an Internet Cafe. Chen Guo actually had four of them. How many more did she have? Let alone that mysterious Lord Grim with a Silver weapon…

While Ma Chenyi was thinking, the match had already started. No one felt at awe at this match. It was another clean victory by Happy’s expert. After the Striker closed in, he comboed the Sharpshooter into helplessness. This match had been the quickest to end.

At this point, no one cared about who would win or lose, but who would be next for Happy.

After this match, Chen Guo smiled: “Is that good enough?”

“Is that it?” the two asked.

Chen Guo smiled, but didn’t say anything.

“Then can I have a match with the two I hadn’t fought?” the Blade Master said.

“Same for me.” that Sharpshooter requested.

“Sure!” Chen Guo nodded her head.

Without any new characters going up onto the stage, the crowd’s interest had immediately gone down. Happy’s experts were too powerful. These two weren’t their opponents. A match without any suspense wasn’t very interesting to watch.

However, it was still nice to see an expert’s performance. The crowd might not be as interested, but they still watched the rest of the matches. And just like how everyone predicted, these two lost again and again. In the end, each of the four experts won two matches, totaling to eight victories.

Chapter 431 – Pry

“Amazing, amazing……” The expressions on the two Sweepers who had lost eight rounds in a row weren’t as ugly as the crowd thought, which made the spectators view them in another light. The scene they had created had even benefited Ma Chenyi. It didn’t make their loss look as embarrassing.

After observing the matches, next was to observe the experts. However, the four experts seemed as if they weren’t aware they were being watched and simply sat at their own seats without moving. It made everyone feel that they were true experts. Things that everyone else thought was amazing were just trivial matters to them.

The crowd didn’t mind it. The two Sweepers got up and then met with the four experts, giving them their sincere respect. Afterwards, they politely expressed that they should have another match when an opportunity arises and then left with Ma Chenyi. Due to the two Sweeper’s graceful display, the three leaving didn’t seem too shameful. Some people even sympathized with them. Under this sort of circumstance, Chen Guo wouldn’t mock them as they left like villains. Ma Chenyi may have lost this time, but he hadn’t lost face.

Once the three left, the four experts gave Chen Guo a look and then returned to their seats to continue playing. Quite a few curious players wanted to have a match with the four experts, but the four politely refused them. There was nothing that they could do. The Sweeping the Field crisis passed by just like this.

Tang Rou had been operating the cash register at the front desk, so she couldn’t log into the game to watch the matches because her character was still in the tenth server. The Sweeper battles had been done by Heavenly Domain characters and had taken place in the Heavenly Domain Arena.

The normal Glory Arena was cross server, but the Heavenly Domain one wasn’t. The Heavenly Domain Arena could be interpreted as the higher ranked Arena. A player’s win-loss record on the normal server Arena was separate from the Heavenly Domain’s Arena. The two Arenas also had different rewards.

Tang Rou could only watch someone else’s screen. She had originally thought that she was going to go up and battle for this Sweeping the Field, but then she discovered that Chen Guo had no such thoughts.

Tang Rou recognized those four so-called experts. Among them were frequent customers in Happy Internet Cafe and Happy Internet Cafe employees. Tang Rou had been in Happy for a long time and she knew very well that those four definitely weren’t experts. At the same time, she also knew that Ma Chenyi had never seen these four before. Chen Guo had diligently arranged this. Tang Rou had basically figured out what was going on.

“Watch over the place for a bit. I’m going up.” Chen Guo knew that Tang Rou had probably guessed what had happened. She gave her an eye and then ran upstairs.

At Room 213 on the second floor, Chen Guo pushed open the door and her first thought was: the ventilation in this room isn’t good enough. I need to make it stronger.

She hadn’t left for long. How many cigarettes had he smoked? The smoke made Chen Guo cough a bit and she even felt like it made it harder finding Ye Xiu.

“Hm? Did they leave?” Even Ye Xiu’s voice seemed hazy amidst the fumes.

Chen Guo pushed the door wide open and stayed outside of the room. All four computers in the room were turned on. The two screens that Chen Guo could see were stopped on the desktop wallpaper.

“They left.” she said.

“What was their reaction?” Ye Xiu asked.

“They didn’t really have any reactions. They admitted their loss and then left.” Chen Guo said.

“Oh.” Ye Xiu replied simply.

“What are you doing?” Chen Guo asked.

“Looking at the eight matches I just played.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo mustered up her courage. She stepped into the room and sat down next to Ye Xiu. On Ye Xiu’s computer was the match he had just played. However, his studying wasn’t nearly as meticulous as when he studied the pro matches. The recording was played on 2x speed and he wasn’t looking around in different angles either. In the beginning, Chen Guo thought he was looking in the player’s perspective. She wasn’t wrong, but it was in the opponent’s perspective, not his.

“How are these two?’ Chen Guo asked.

“They’re not bad, but they’re still far from being at the pro level.” Ye Xiu said.

“Of course, they’re not at the pro level. Why would a pro player go to an Internet Cafe?” Chen Guo said.

“It doesn’t matter who it is. Did they record it?” Ye Xiu asked.

“They did.” Chen Guo, “Every single match.”

“It seems like my guess is correct!” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“But how did Grand Internet Cafe get mixed up with them?” Chen Guo said.

“That doesn’t really matter, does it? It was just a reason to come over and do this.” Ye Xiu said.

“How did you play these eight matches?” Chen Guo asked.

“Four different styles.” Ye Xiu said, “A normal person might not feel it, but if a pro player analyzed it, he would definitely think that they were done by different people.”

“Excellent Era’s people should be very familiar with you though!” Chen Guo said.

“They’re only familiar with One Autumn Leaf.” Ye Xiu said bluntly.

“Could you be just as proficient with other classes as your Battle Mage?” Chen Guo asked in astonishment. It was true that Ye Xiu was called a Glory Textbook, but this was mainly because he had been playing Glory since the start of the game. At that time, the Pro Alliance hadn’t even been created yet. Glory was still purely an online game. In those days, he was already an extremely popular player and had a lot of influence on the meta. After the Pro Alliance was created, he had used the Battle Mage One Autumn Leaf for around seven years. His nickname of being a Textbook stuck around, but the majority of people knew him as the Battle God.

“Not at all.” Ye Xiu replied, which made Chen Guo relax a bit.

“But they’re close.” These added words from Ye Xiu made Chen Guo stir again. If they were close, then didn’t that mean he was at a pro level with all of the other classes?

“You can’t have that much time!” Chen Guo exclaimed. With 24 classes, if he practiced each class for an hour, he wouldn’t have any time to do anything else.

“Over time.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo nodded her head.

“And of course, talent.” Ye Xiu added.

Chen Guo’s gaze returned to her screen. She didn’t want to bother with him. However, she had to admit that all of these top tier Gods in Glory had to have talent.

“I really want to see their reactions when they see those recordings!” Chen Guo clicked in boredom at the desktop icons.

It had taken her quite a bit of effort to borrow these accounts and organize everything, but she wouldn’t be able to see the results. It was quite depressing to think about.

Club Excellent Era.

After the two Sweepers left Happy Internet Cafe, they apologized to Ma Chenyi.

What could Ma Chenyi say? He had personally witnessed their skill and had thought that challenging the entire Happy Internet Cafe wouldn’t be a problem. How could he know that Happy had so many freaks these days? If he had to blame anything, he would have to blame not scouting out his opponent first and just charging in to try Sweeping the Field.

Moreover, the two might have lost, but their performance made it so he didn’t lose any face. For the loser, Ma Chenyi, this was already quite a good result. It had to be known that when he found out that Happy Internet Cafe had Lord Grim, he felt like dying. But after losing miserably, they were able to peacefully leave. After making such an arrogant challenge, they hadn’t been treated so bad.

As a result, Ma Chenyi thanked the two of them and welcomed them to come and play at his Cafe. The two sides split up afterwards. Ma Chenyi went back to his Internet Cafe. The two walked around for a bit and then slipped into Club Excellent Era.

At Club Excellent Era’s guild studio, when Chen Yehui saw the two come back, he immediately leaped out of his chair.

“How was it?” Chen Yehui immediately asked.

“We did it.” After returning to their seats, the expressions on the two of them finally turned ugly.

“Okay. Come with me.” Chen Yehui had the two follow him. Even though it was his studio, the things they needed to talk about still weren’t convenient to talk about here. The reason was because their opponent was Ye Qiu, Excellent Era’s former God. Chen Yehui could only secretly discuss how to deal with Ye Qiu with his most trusted friends. Lord Grim was Ye Qiu. Quite a few core members from other guilds knew about this. However, in Excellent Dynasty, Chen Yehui didn’t dare tell anyone.

“What’s the situation?” Chen Yehui asked as they hastily headed towards the team.

“There are four experts!” the two said.

“That can’t be right.” Chen Yehui stopped in astonishment. He had even forgotten to walk.

“Both of us saw it.” the two swore.

Chen Yehui hesitated, but then continued walking until they met with Liu Hao.

“We’ve scouted Happy.” Chen Yehui went right to the point.

“Oh?” Liu Hao was quite interested.

Chen Yehui didn’t continue and had his two trusted friends say the words for him.

“Happy Internet Cafe has four experts!” the two immediately said.

“Experts? How good?” Liu Hao was more calm than Chen Yehui when he heard this. A pro player had seen more things, after all. The game had too many so-called experts, but in the pro scene, these so-called experts would just be like fleeting clouds.

“We have recordings.” the two said.

“Let me see.” Liu Hao said.

One of them went to use the computer and logged into an online file hosting service. He had saved all the recordings here. The recordings were quickly downloaded. This person got up and moved to the side: “One Launcher, one Witch, one Assassin, and one Striker.”

“Is the Launcher Chasing Haze?” Chen Yehui interjected.

“No…… all four are male……” When the two were assigned wit this task, Chen Yehui had talked to them that Chasing Haze was important to ask about. But they didn’t even figure out who Chasing Haze was and there were four more experts…….

Liu Hao had already opened up one recording; it was the Launcher match.

Chapter 432 – The Experts Behind the Scenes

Chen Yehui stood to one side and watched carefully with the other two. However, with a pro player like Liu Hao here, the three knew that they didn’t have the qualifications to express their opinions, so they stayed silent. On the other side, Liu Hao had watched until about halfway through, when he suddenly grabbed his phone and sent a text.

As he put down the phone, he rewound the recording back to the beginning and then began to contemplate.

Chen Yehui and the other two looked at one another, but didn’t say anything. Not long afterward, the room to the door was pushed open. The three turned their heads and saw He Ming and Wang Ze walk in. They had seen Chen Yehui call for them and then they went over the videos together.

“Watch this match.” Liu Hao told the two who had walked in.

“Chasing Haze?” He Ming asked.

“First look.” Liu Hao said and then watched the match again from the beginning.

The room fell silent. Liu Hao wasn’t wearing headphones, so the match didn’t have sound. Everyone watched the screen quietly. Once the recording reached a certain spot, He Ming’s and Wang Ze’s expression changed. Chen Yehui and the other two knew that they wouldn’t be able to figure out much from the match, so they weren’t nearly as focused as the three pro players. From time to time, they would glance to see the expression of the three pros. They quickly caught the reason for their change in expression. In the match, it was the moment that the Blade Master exposed an opening and began being comboed to death by the Launcher.

When the match ended, Liu Hao turned around. First, he gave He Ming and Wang Ze an eye before looking at the other three: “Who fought this match?”

“I fought it…….” the Blade Master player replied.

“Do you know where you made a mistake?” Liu Hao asked.

Everyone understood what he was trying to get at because there had been a clear momentum shift during the match. In the beginning, the two sides had been extremely even and it seemed like it would be a battle of attrition. But the tides suddenly turned, and so it had turned out like this. The mistake was obviously pointing toward the moment the tides turned.

However, the Blade Master player shook his head, expressing that he didn’t know.

“The balance of power in the beginning was only a facade. It seemed like a dirty style of fighting, but it actually isn’t. This is a control style. When you find an opportunity, you seize it and turn it into an instant kill. If you don’t understand, you should know who Huang Shaotian is, right? He represents the control style of playing. Of course, it’d be going a bit too far to compare this Launcher with Huang Shaotian. Huang Shaotian’s playing is much better.” Liu Hao said.

This player used a Blade Master, so even if he didn’t like Huang Shaotian, there was no way that he would be a stranger to him. If you wanted to become a Blade Master expert, studying Huang Shaotian was a must. When he heard Liu Hao mention this God, he immediately understood. For a player at his level, he wouldn’t be unfamiliar with different types of playing styles. He might not be able to realize it, but once an expert pointed it out, he could use it to look and could see some things.

“Where’s the other Launcher one?” Liu Hao asked.

The next match was naturally the one against the Sharpshooter. That player immediately came out and pointed at the recording. Liu Hao opened it and everyone began to quietly watch again. Chen Yehui and the other two would glance at the expression of the three pro players from time to time. They couldn’t get much from watching the matches, but they could see quite a bit from the changes in their expressions.

This match was even quicker than the last one. After watching it, the three pro players looked at one another. This time, Liu Hao didn’t speak and looked at Wang Ze to explain.

Wang Ze was a Sharpshooter player, so after seeing Liu Hao’s intentions, he immediately spoke: “Compared to the last match, his play style is smarter.”

Chen Yehui and the other two didn’t dare interrupt and just listened carefully.

“He had mainly been waiting for an opportunity to arise in the last match, but for this one, he took the initiative to create it.” Wang Ze said.

“This has to do with the opponent.” He Ming added, “The previous opponent was a mainly close-range Blade Master. The Launcher has the range advantage, so if he maintained a distance and fought, the Blade Master would certainly begin to lose his patience. Waiting was a good choice. But for this match, his opponent was a Sharpshooter. Sharpshooters don’t have as much range as Launchers, but it’s only a slight difference. It isn’t easy to grasp that difference. As a result, waiting would make him fall from an active position to a passive position, so this time, he took the initiative and created his own opportunity. His decision was correct as well.”

“That’s right.” Liu Hao nodded his head at the two’s analysis, “But the problem is that the two sides have a clear strength gap. Don’t you think that his meticulous planning and playing, depending on the different classes, feels a bit strange?”

“This…… maybe he’s just being cautious or perhaps it’s a type of attitude.” He Ming said.

Liu Hao didn’t say anything and didn’t look at any other match recording. Instead, he went online and took out the match between Chasing Haze and Poplar Beach.

“In this match, Chasing Haze was being played by Ye Qiu.” Chen Yehui said.

“Yes. You’ve said this. However, you can’t ascertain that Ye Qiu really was the one sitting behind the screen controlling Chasing Haze, right?” Liu Hao said.

“Yes……” Chen Yehui nodded his head.

This match progressed a bit quicker. The two sides didn’t really fight much before Poplar Beach was exploded to death. However, after hearing Liu Hao’s control play style, everyone looked and immediately felt that this match was a prime example of the control play style, except that during this match, there were too many opportunities. Chasing Haze didn’t even wait or try to create an opportunity. She simply fought a few exchanges with her opponent and then seized an opportunity that arose and won from there.

“How does this match compare with those two?” Liu Hao said.

“It’s more precise. You could even say that each step was done perfectly.” They had actually discussed this match long ago.

“There’s no way that Ye Qiu is unfamiliar with a Launcher’s control playstyle. Don’t forget that he raised Su Mucheng up by himself. Su Mucheng’s playstyle is another paragon of the control style, though her play style leans more towards synergizing with the team. She isn’t normally a main aggressor, so this type of style isn’t usually seen when she’s in a duel.” Liu Hao said.

“Are you saying that this was all done by Ye Qiu?” He Ming said.

“No….. I’m saying that this type of Launcher style is representative of Ye Qiu’s school of thought.” Liu Hao said, “There must be someone else besides Ye Qiu controlling Chasing Haze. Did you forget that day?”

That day was pointing to the day when the three pros had run to the Heavenly Domain, confident that they would kill Lord Grim. But their two-player duo had scared them off. They had even thought that the Launcher was Su Mucheng.

“There have already been many people who have played on this Chasing Haze.” Liu Hao said, “The true owner of this character is the one that had been in Excellent Dynasty. The one that participated in the All Star Weekend. She’s only a normal player.”

“Yes, she’s Happy’s boss. We asked about it.” the two immediately said. The fact that Chasing Haze was Chen Guo’s account wasn’t something hard to find out about. The two didn’t even need to ask around at Happy Internet Cafe. They had heard Ma Chenyi mention it.

“There’s no need to talk about the true owner. What we want to know is who else the other controller is. Of course, it’s possible that it’s Ye Qiu……” Liu Hao pointed at the video and said, “But it could also be someone else.”

“That’s right…… We also saw that person!” the two Sweepers immediately said.

“What type of person is he?” Liu Hao asked.

The two were suddenly speechless because their appearances were very ordinary. They didn’t have any special air to them.

“Let’s look at the others for now!” Liu Hao felt that this question wasn’t the main point. After closing the online video, he opened up another match recording.

This match was the match between the Assassin and the Blade Master. It was one that went blow for blow, until the scene was splattered with blood. However, after ten seconds, the three pro players quickly changed their view on this because, after ten seconds, it was no longer a close fight, but rather a massacre.

“This is…… a shameless style!” He Ming wasn’t sure, but his tone of voice also had a little hate to it.

The shameless style was something they all knew about. It was usually used by classes with more defense and health. To put it simply, it was an ‘I have more defense and more health, so if we just trade blows, you lose’ style. A player like He Ming who used an Elementalist with paper defense clearly wasn’t suited for this type of style. In addition, it was a style that he hated very much.

The reason He Ming wasn’t sure was because the character attacking shamelessly was an Assassin. Assassins were a class with low defense and health, too, so the style didn’t fit the class.

“Which match is this?” Liu Hao asked the two.

“This is my second match. Wait, no, for me, it was my third match. However, the first match was just against a normal player. I recorded it, but it wasn’t anything of value, so I didn’t save it.” the Blade Master said.

“I don’t think you can consider this match as a shameless style. It’s just because he was certain of his skill that he relied on winning with just brute force.” Liu Hao said.

“Where’s the other match against this guy?” Liu Hao understood the situation. There were four unknown experts and the two brothers in front of him had both fought against each of them for a total of eight matches.

The Sharpshooter pointed to that recording. Everyone watched it. It was quite rough! This Assassin completely ignored the Sharpshooter’s attacks and just brute forced his way to victory. This was his confidence that as long as he closed in, he would be able to defeat the opponent. He wasn’t concerned about the Sharpshooter’s close combat ability and wasn’t concerned that the opponent had the skill to escape.

“The person’s real strength…… is hard to determine. He’s not fighting against someone close to his skill…….” Liu Hao said.

I just hope that the other two don’t play like this……” He Ming said.

Chapter 433 – If I May Be So Bold to Ask a Favor

Striker, Witch.

Everyone watched the four matches with these two characters. The main people discussing were still Liu Hao and He Ming. Wang Ze said a few things too, whenever it was a Sharpshooter match. As for the two Sweepers, they would only be asked for whenever the pros had any on site questions. Apart from that, there was nothing else for them to do.

From these two characters, everyone was able to see their individual styles and could tell that the two were very skilled experts. However, they encountered a similar problem as the Assassin when they wanted to know exactly how good they were: the difference in skill between the two sides was too uneven, so it was hard to measure. They didn’t know if this type of one-sided victory was something the other side could do 80% of the time or only 50% of the time.

This was actually true for the Launcher as well. Even though the Launcher had displayed a clear strategy and style, his opponent wasn’t able to resist, so it was still difficult to precisely determine exactly how good this Launcher was.

As a result, the pros knew that Ye Qiu had four other experts, but their true skill was a still a mystery. These four experts were very strong. Chen Yehui’s people wouldn’t be able to feel them out. However, Liu Hao and the other pros had no way of running over to the Internet Cafe themselves.

Chen Yehui even had to make things worse by saying: “These classes aren’t the classes of Ye Qiu’s dungeon team in the tenth server. In the tenth server, he has a fixed team. Among them is a Launcher, which is probably Su Mucheng. But apart from her, there’s a Battle Mage, a Brawler, a Blade Master, and a Ghostblade. All of them are very skilled.”

Liu Hao’s expression suddenly turned ugly. If that was the case, then not including Ye Qiu’s Lord Grim, he had already netted eight experts? He had only left Excellent Era for two months. How did he do all this by himself?

Liu Hao and the other two pros were already quite worried, but with Chen Yehui and his two men next to them, they couldn’t show it.

“Should we try contact them in game?” He Ming suggested. In order to test for their skill, they needed pro level players to come out. However, pro players couldn’t run to an Internet Cafe to Sweep the Field, so they could only do it online.

“The thing I’m worried about is that Chasing Haze is the same as these guys. We can look for these characters by their names, but even if we meet them, the one playing might not be the expert. Ye Qiu is too cunning. He’s surely taken precautions against the Club digging these experts out, so he’s intentionally hiding them. We know of their existence, but we have no way of finding them.” Liu Hao grinded his teeth.

Chen Yehui listened. His heart thumped and he turned his head to say to his two people: “You two. For now, go frequent Happy Internet Cafe! Try and look for these experts. You shouldn’t need me to tell you how exactly you should do this, right?”

“Understood.” The two nodded their heads.

“Okay. Try to get more information. Find more recordings to get back to us. That way, we’ll be able to know their skill.” Liu Hao accepted Chen Yehui’s plan.

“We can try contact them in-game too! After all, the things you talked about are only a possibility and not a fact.” He Ming said.

Liu Hao nodded his head and then told Chen Yehui: “Find out where these characters are and then we’ll personally meet up with them.”

“OKay.” Chen Yehui nodded his head.

Soon afterwards, Chen Yehui left with his two men. The remaining Liu Hao and the two pros looked at each other and then exposed their true feelings.

Dismay! They were in absolute dismay!

Ye Xiu only had one helper and that was enough to scare the three of them from making any hasty movements, let alone another four. They might not know exactly how skilled these four were, but the two weren’t weak to dominate those two Sweepers. The pro players already had some idea of their level though. If these four helpers were under the lead of a God like Ye Qiu, the three of them definitely wouldn’t win.

“I remember that when we met them…… it wasn’t just the two of them. There was also a Battle Mage with them.” Wang Ze recalled. As a result, the three immediately thought of the experts in the tenth server that Chen Yehui had talked about. There was a Battle Mage among them.

“A Battle Mage trained by Ye Qiu…… would definitely be terrifying……” He Ming muttered.

The three had never been concerned with characters. This was because Glory characters weren’t bound to anyone. Anyone could use the character as long as they had the card. This was why Chasing Haze was such a mystery. She had displayed different skill levels several times, making it so no one had any idea who was behind the character.

They didn’t care who the real owners of these cards were. They wanted to know who the player that displayed such skill was.

For a moment, the room was silent. Liu Hao stared at his computer screen. Who knew what he was thinking.

Meanwhile, in Happy Internet Cafe, after the Sweeping the Field, the customers in the Internet Cafe had returned to playing their own game. The previous commotion had quickly turned into the past. As for those four experts, two of them had already left They were now with Chen Guo and Ye Xiu in a room. Apart from them, there were two other people. The owners of two of the four characters.

“Sorry for troubling you!” Chen Guo poured water for the four of them.

“It’s nothing. Thank you boss.” The four didn’t object. The four of them were quite close with Chen Guo, which was why Chen Guo had asked them for help. Even though they were a bit puzzled, they happily agreed. Afterwards, they couldn’t help be curious and wanted to know what Chen Guo had been up to.

“There’s one more thing I want to trouble you four with.” Chen Guo said with difficulty.

“What is it? Tell us.” The four were quite happy.

“Can you sell me your accounts?” Chen Guo said.

“What?” The four stared dumbly.

“What are you trying to do ?” The four hadn’t gotten their previous questions answered yet and now another thing had come up. The four weren’t willing to sell their accounts. They were all old players. Their characters had been bitterly trained up. They weren’t in need of money either. Why would they sell their accounts?

“Or maybe switch……. I’ll trade the accounts for accounts with the exact same character. Your original equipment, money, materials, quest progress, Arena record, I’ll do my best to match them. I’ll guarantee that besides the character’s name, everything else will be basically the same as before.” Chen Guo said.

“All of those might be the same, but what about our friend? Our guild?” One person said.

“This……. I’ll have to trouble you with figuring that out yourself, but everything I can do, I’ll do well.” Chen Guo said.

The four looked at each other. They couldn’t understand Chen Guo’s intent.” One person shook his head: “Boss Chen, we’ve all been playing at your Internet Cafe for a long time. Our relationship isn’t bad either. We can be considered friends. For a small matter like that, we can help you out, no problem. We didn’t really mind that you didn’t give us an explanation. But now, your offer is really odd. If you don’t tell us the reason for doing all this, we can’t feel comfortable agreeing.”

“That’s right!” Another person nodded his head.

Chen Guo knew that it wouldn’t go smoothly. She turned her head and gave Ye Xiu a death glare.

These four were frequent customers. Ye Xiu had come two months ago, so they recognized him. Right now, he was sitting right next to Chen Guo and looked as if he was the boss. They had been puzzled about this when they first arrived in the room. When a critical point in their discussion had appeared, Chen Guo had unexpectedly looked towards him. The four were filled with doubts. They were currently wondering whether this guy had somehow seduced boss Chen and had now become the owner of Happy Internet Cafe.

But when he spoke, his words made them completely shocked.

“To tell you guys the truth, I’m Ye Qiu.” That person said.

“What?” The four were doubting whether they had heard correctly.

“Ye Qiu! Did you not hear him?” Chen Guo said.

“Which Ye Qiu?” The four were clearly in disbelief.

If this was in a normal situation, Chen Guo would definitely be enjoying this scene, but today, they were discussing serious matters, so Chen Guo didn’t laugh out loud. She just stayed silent, letting the four know they hadn’t heard wrong.

“God Ye Qiu, how could you be here…..” One person said.

“After I retired, I came here to find work.” Ye Xiu told the truth, but the four facing him were all showing an expression that they didn’t believe him.

“I’m planning on using this year of rest to create a team.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah! So the rumors were true!” One person said excitedly.

Another person blurted out: “Did you see our characters and want to buy them to use in the Pro Alliance?”

“You’re thinking too much, brother…….” Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry.

This person had realized this and his face went red.

“Are you really Ye Qiu?” One person was still doubtful.

“He really is. How could I lie to you guys!” Chen Guo said.

“The problem is, you’ve never seen the real Ye Qiu. Maybe he’s tricked you, too.” that person said.

“Then how can I prove I’m him?” Ye Xiu asked.

The four scratched their heads. Ye Qiu had never shown himself to the public, so they didn’t know how they could prove he was Ye Qiu.

“Show a Dragon Raising Its Head?” One person suggested.

“What if he just flukes it?”

“I’d like to see you fluke it.”

“I’m not afraid of ten thousand, I’m only scared of one.”

The four began to argue with each other.

“How about I find someone you guys recognize to do a video chat and have them verify that I’m Ye Qiu?” Ye Xiu said.

“People we recognize? Like who?” The four were puzzled.

“Pro players, of course. Anyone I’ve added on QQ should be fine.” Ye Xiu said.

”

“Wang Jiexi!!!”

“Li Xun!!!”

“Xu Huiliu!!!”

“Su Mucheng!!!”

Their classes were different, so their idols were different. At this moment, their answers were all different.

Chapter 434 – Disappearing Characters

The majority of players in Happy Internet Cafe supported Excellent Era and they really did like Excellent Era players. However, many of the classes that players used weren’t among Team Excellent Era.

A team usually had around 11 or so players. Glory had a total of 24 classes, so a team couldn’t have all the classes. In addition, even if they did, just because the fans supported the team didn’t necessarily mean their favorite players had to be from there.

For example, Team Excellent Era didn’t have any Witches, Strikers, or Assassins. As a result, the Witches liked the great Wang Jiexi, while Strikers liked the famous Han Wenqing. However, because of the rivalry between Excellent Era and Tyranny, Excellent Era fans generally didn’t like Tyranny, so fans who played Strikers wouldn’t like Han Wenqing, but rather Xu Huiliu, a very outstanding player in Team Royal Style.

From this, it could be seen that All Star players were certainly popular, but it didn’t necessarily mean that everyone liked them. First string and second string players also had their own loyal fanbases. For example, the Assassin player’s favorite pro wasn’t the All Star, Yang Cong, but rather Team Void’s Li Xuan. And as it turned out, among the four Excellent Era supporters, only the Launcher liked an Excellent Era player the most: Su Mucheng.

“Okay okay. So these four. Come come come.” Ye Xiu said as he got up. Everyone got up and went over to Room 213. The Internet Cafe computers were fit with all sorts of accessories. As Ye Xiu logged into his QQ, he said: “Let me see who’s one!”

Since things had gotten to this step, the four looked at each other and were already quite convinced that the person in front of them was Ye Qiu.

“No one is on!” But when Ye Xiu said this, the four immediately began to doubt him again.

“Let me see if they’re invisible.” As a result, Ye Xiu clicked on four names from his friends list and sent them each a message.

None of the four replied. The four players behind Ye Xiu didn’t say anything. They had already decided that if there was no video proof, then they wouldn’t believe him. Who knew if this guy had just found four ghost accounts to put up an act!

“Lend me your phone.” Ye Xiu asked Chen Guo.

“You’re going to call Mu Mu?” Chen Guo asked.

“Yeah!”

The call went through. Ye Xiu said a few words on the phone. The four once again began looking at each other, becoming convinced again.

Suddenly, one of the four chat windows on QQ replied and directly sent a video call request. Ye Xiu accepted and then moved away to let everyone see. The face on there was clearly Su Mucheng’s. She waved her hands and smiled at them.

Seeing that no one was replying, Su Mucheng typed: “Hi everyone. I’m Su Mucheng. The person you’re looking at is Ye Qiu!”

“Ah…..” The four were completely convinced now. That Su Mucheng fan was so excited that he didn’t know what to say. Eyeing the headphones on the desk, he was hesitant on whether he should go and grab it or not. But during this moment of hesitation, Chen Guo grabbed it and put it on: “Hey, Mu Mu.” Chen Guo also waved her hands.

Afterwards, the two began chatting. The first three sentences were about their current situation. After five sentences, they began going off topic and after ten sentences, none of the five brothers knew what they were chatting about.

“Everyone……” Ye Xiu could only ignore Chen Guo and looked towards the other four.

The four had only just regained their composure. They were completely convinced. Their expressions of doubt had changed into expressions of excitement and shock towards Ye Xiu. After a moment of silence, one of them finally spoke: “God…… signature?”

“No problem.”

“Let’s leave for now to talk?” Ye Xiu suggested.

“Okay okay okay.” The four nodded their heads. As they left, that Su Mucheng fan looked at the smiling Chen Guo with a face full of envy.

“Hm? What! Done? Wait for me!” Chen Guo immediately called out, when she saw they were leaving. She said bye to Su Mucheng and then stopped the video call.

They returned to the living room. After verifying Ye Xiu’s identity, their attitudes were completely different. They had no idea what to do with their hands and feet. Their favorite players might not be from Excellent Era, but their favorite team was absolutely Excellent Era. It was easy to see just how much they respected Ye Qiu. When they arrived at the living room, at first, they were cautious, but they soon began to open up. All sorts of crazy questions began being asked.

“Everyone, everyone, let’s first talk about the previous matter.” Ye Xiu switched topics.

“There’s no need to talk about that. If it’s to help God Ye Qiu, I have no problem with it.” One of them vouched.

Afterwards, another one nodded his head.

The remaining two were still conflicted. Discarding an account they had put in so much time and effort into wasn’t so easy. It was true that Chen Guo promised she would do everything she could to keep their equipment, items, quests, and even records as close as possible to the original. Their friends list and guilds were a bit troublesome, but they could be dealt with. However, something like a name, which didn’t have any influence on anything in the game, was what was stopping them from agreeing. A different name made it feel like the character was completely different.

Because Ye Xiu and Chen Guo understood this, which was why they didn’t say that it was all the same. They could only quietly wait for their decisions. After a long moment of silence, seeing that the two were still conflicted, Ye Xiu also sighed. He told them all of the difficulties he had come across.

The four listened in shock.

No matter what, a team trying to suppress their former God and captain into the grave was something they couldn’t accept. Their image of Excellent Era crumbled and the four were no longer fans anymore. At this moment, the four hoped that the God would successfully form a team, return to the Pro Alliance, and give Excellent Era a good beating.

“Take it!” The two conflicted players directly put their account cards onto the table.

“Thank you.”

“God, good luck!!!” The other two also took out their cards and said.

“Of course.” Ye Xiu said.

“We’ll definitely support your team.”

“Thank you!”

The four happily handed over their account cards and gave their blessings. Of course, they weren’t going to refuse Chen Guo’s compensation. Chen Guo handled matters cleanly too and immediately went online to search for appropriate cards. The Glory playerbase was massive. Finding four appropriate cards wouldn’t be too difficult. After all, these four characters weren’t anything incredible. However, no matter how easy it would be to find one, there was no way she could be quicker than the four of them handing over their cards.

With the business finished, the four couldn’t help but pay their respects to the God before leaving in satisfaction.

“What do we do with these four accounts?” Chen Guo finally found the opportunity to ask Ye Xiu.

“The best thing to do is not use them.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.” Chen Guo nodded her head. Ye Xiu had already explained to her his thinking. Actually, a big portion of the reason why they asked for these four accounts was to save these four normal players from encountering any trouble. There was no doubt Excellent Era’s people would find these four characters to test their strength. If these four characters were still with those four characters, they would be constantly dying and there was no way they would be able to continue playing the game.

Even though none of this would let Excellent Era reach their goal, the four players would undoubtedly be four pitiful sacrifices. Ye Xiu and Chen Guo felt too bad doing such a thing to them, so they thought of finding a way to acquire these four accounts. Ye Xiu and Chen Guo only had limited resources, so their deal was quite good already.

That night, Ye Xiu continued to power level like usual, while Chen Guo accompanied him. On Excellent Era, they didn’t dare casually provoke them. Excellent Dynasty’s group of players were constantly keeping an eye out for these four characters.

Offline!

Offline!

Offline!

Offline!

All four characters were offline and never went online.

It was an easy task to do, but the people doing them would get annoyed eventually. For Liu Hao and Chen Yehui, they were even more annoyed, waiting for the news. They wanted to know what the skill levels of these experts were.

“How strange! None of these four characters have gone online. What’s going on?” Chen Yehui had waited for the entire night. He didn’t do anything. All he saw was the night getting later and later. He reckoned that Liu Hao was going to sleep soon, so he discussed this issue with Liu Hao on QQ.

“Be patient. There’s still time.” Liu Hao seemed quite calm. The last few times he lost his temper, the results had been quite tragic.

“Do you think…… that Ye Qiu might have predicted we’d do this, so he prepared four one-time use characters?” Chen Yehui wasn’t stupid. He had already guessed the truth.

“It’s possible……” Liu Hao might hate Ye Xiu, but he didn’t dare underestimate him.

“If that’s the case, meeting up with the real players might not go smoothly either.” Chen Yehui said.

“We’ll see when they go take a look around tomorrow!” Liu Hao said.

The night went by. On Excellent Dynasty, there were always keeping an eye for these four characters, but the results never changed.

The next day, the two Sweepers went to Happy Internet Cafe.

“Hm? If it isn’t the two experts?” When the two walked in, Chen Guo immediately recognized them. Internet Cafe customers went in waves. The ones from yesterday might not be here today, so not many recognized the two.

“Boss, you must be joking. Here, we don’t dare call ourselves experts.” The two hastily said.

“Ha ha.” Chen Guo only laughed and didn’t say too much, “Are you going online?”

“Of course.” The two said.

Chen Guo gave a shout and the front desk opened up two computers for them. The two immediately went up: “The brother experts?”

“No.” Chen Guo denied.

“When will they be here?” The two asked after being a bit startled.

Chen Guo saidwith a face full of astonishment: “How would I know! They’re all customers. How could I know who comes at what time?”

Chapter 435 – Whoever Moves First Loses

Chen Guo’s words made the two of them cough blood. Even though those words were very reasonable, the two had some inside information. How could Happy Internet Cafe’s experts be random customers? They had to be inside the Internet Cafe, preparing to create a team with Ye Qiu. This boss was clearly lying to them.

The two were thinking in this way, but on the surface, they couldn’t express that “we see through you.” They could only sigh regretfully: “Then do you know when these brother experts usually come?”

“I haven’t really paid attention to that!”

Chen Guo really looked like she was telling the truth. Who knew how many people had been duped by her like this, not understanding how fearsome boss Chen was. Right now, her expression looked completely innocent , the two spies were suddenly entranced by her. They felt as if this sister couldn’t say anything wrong and they must have made a mistake.

Luckily, the two quickly had reason take over and after regaining their composure, they calmly spoke: “Are the computers ready?”

“Area 14, Number 15.” Chen Guo pointed to where the computers were located.

If the experts weren’t there, they could only wait, while talking with the other Internet Cafe guests to see if they knew anything.

The majority of the people in the Internet Cafe played Glory and there were many like-minded people. If they wanted to, making Glory friends in the Internet Cafe was very easy. However, nowadays, computers were essential to households, so those who came to the Internet Cafe were usually already in a group with three or five other friends. As a result, there weren’t too many who would actively look for friends when they were already with a group of friends.

These two spies had come with a different purpose though, so they were different. After sitting down, the people to the left and right of them were playing Glory. The two quickly logged into the game and looked at their neighbors with a smile. The two took the opportunity to go and chat with them. Unfortunately, the their neighbors weren’t frequent customers of Happy Internet Cafe. They had simply come on a whim. It would be hard to get any useful information from these type of people.

Thus, as the two played Glory, they would look towards Happy Internet Cafe’s entrance to see if those four experts would appear. But after sitting for an entire day, there were no signs of them appearing.

Two of those four fake experts were Happy Internet Cafe employees. If Chen Guo didn’t want them to appear, all Chen Guo needed to do was tell them not to appear. The other two might not be her employees, but because they had already changed to Ye Xiu’s side, as supporters, they would cooperate in earnest.

The two spies weren’t able to get anything out of today. The two couldn’t just live in the Internet Cafe, so when it was time to go, they could only pay the bills and leave.

“Do you know these two?” Meanwhile, Chen Guo had secretly taken a picture of them and gave them to Ye Xiu to look at.

“Of course I don’t know them! If they sent two people who I recognized, wouldn’t that just be asking to be exposed?” Ye Xiu didn’t even look.

“Oh, that’s true……” Chen Guo said, “These two will definitely be coming often.”

“What’s wrong with having two fixed customers?” Ye Xiu smiled.

“With their eyes shifting about, I really want to treat them like little thieves and beat them up.” After knowing their identities, Chen Guo couldn’t like them. Any action they did made Chen Guo want to vomit.

“Don’t be in such a rush. Let them suffer!” Ye Xiu didn’t care.

“What about Loulan Slash! Is there any news from them?” Chen Guo asked.

“There hasn’t been any for now.” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s been so long! Why are they so slow!”

“Slow? It’s only been two days!” Ye Xiu said.

“How is that not slow.”

“This isn’t just about a game. This is a business deal and a gamble. Wouldn’t you want to be careful?” Ye Xiu said.

“Tch!” Chen Guo clearly didn’t care.

The two spies went to QQ and reported the situation to Chen Yehui. There was nothing Chen Yehui could do. In the game, they had watched for an entire day again, but the characters of the four experts never appeared.

In order to be experts, there was no way they wouldn’t be playing a lot. Chen Yehui felt that his initial thoughts were correct. Ye Qiu might have prepared for them long beforehand.

If that was the case, the two spies definitely wouldn’t be able to get anything. Thinking of this, Chen Yehui discussed this with Liu Hao and dispatched more spies. Apart from the two who went to the Cafe like usual, they added more people to keep watch on Happy Internet Cafe 24/7. This arrangement wasn’t difficult for Chen Yehui to do. Their work was done through the game, so if he sent people to go to Happy Internet Cafe, they would be playing the game too. It wouldn’t delay their work.

It was just that there were no results after three days.

In game, their characters had disappeared and the experts from outside of the game were nowhere to be seen.

Chen Yehui was anxious. Liu Hao was anxious. The entire Club guild was anxious.

These past few days, there were no signs from Excellent Dynasty nor any of the other Club guilds. One reason was because Lord Grim’s popularity was still on fire. They really couldn’t make any movements with so many people watching him. In addition, they knew that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, so the Club guilds were very fearful. They wanted someone else to test it out for them and die a few times before they moved.

There was also one other reason. Tyrannical Ambition was a good example of this.

Tyrannical Ambition’s guild leader Jiang You was calm when Ye Qiu entered the Heavenly Domain. Their guild had only gossipped and chatted about it like everyone else and didn’t make any movements. This was because Jiang You was still confident about his previous judgement: there had been some sort of inside conflict when Ye Qiu left Excellent Era, so Excellent Era definitely wouldn’t want Ye Qiu to return. Thus, Guild Excellent Dynasty would definitely go all out to suppress Ye Qiu and they should just wait to watch the show.

As for Tyrannical Ambition, Ye Qiu fighting Excellent Dynasty was simply too good of a show. Both sides suffering would be a delight to see.

Jiang You’s thoughts weren’t complicated or anything. He had talked about it in the tenth server with many other guilds before, so many of the other guilds had this type of thought too. They really didn’t want to move. It would have been so nice if Ye Qiu hadn’t come to play the game. Many people shared this wish.

Thus, if it was highly probable that a guild would stand out, everyone was more than happy to wait a bit.

However, on the first day, Excellent Era had only sent out Liu Hao and two other pro players to move. Their scale was too small. The other guilds hadn’t known about it. As a result, it seemed like Excellent Era was only observing too and couldn’t help but feel a bit worried. These days, the spies in Excellent Era were having a tough time. They were trying all sorts of ways to get information on how Excellent Era was going to deal with Lord Grim.

The peaceful leveling these past few days had made Chen Guo feel astonished. She discussed it with Ye Xiu and after hearing Ye Xiu’s thoughts, she understood that ever since Ye Xiu had stopped the ambush from the three pro players, his plan had already begun.

This was because the Heavenly Challenge had caused his fame to soar, making the guilds unable to do any large movements and were waiting to see what Excellent Dynasty was going to do.

Excellent Dynasty didn’t dare make any large movements either, but the Club behind them helped out by directly sending them pro players. With a 20 level suppression, let alone three pro players, a single pro player would be difficult for Ye Xiu to beat. However, Ye Xiu’s deception had caused Excellent Era to be completely uncertain to how many helpers he had and how good the helpers were. As a result, these past few days had dragged on in this way. During this time, Ye Xiu had come into contact with Loulan Slash. After another contact with each other, Loulan Slash said that he would have his answer today. If Loulan Slash agreed, then Ye Xiu wouldn’t be alone anymore.

“How is it? Do you find it fun?” Ye Xiu laughed, “The top guilds are currently playing a game where whoever moves first loses, but if no one moves, then they will also lose.”

“You really are…….” Chen Guo couldn’t find the words to describe her feelings. Those powerful guilds had been played by Ye Xiu. He had completely figured out their weaknesses and forced them into a tough situation.

However, he also had to have the skill to do so. Without enough skill, how could this situation have happened?

During these past few days, Ye Xiu had went back to the tenth server for one day.

The Heavenly Domain and the tenth server were in different servers, so players couldn’t just switch whenever they wanted to. Right now, the game restricted it so that the player could only switch servers once every day. In other words, since he switched from the Heavenly Domain to the tenth server, he had to wait until tomorrow to switch back.

However, Ye Xiu had used these 24 hours well and with the four players in Happy who had reached Level 50, he formed a team and set records for a bunch of Level 50 dungeons.

Even though his unspecialized wouldn’t gain any experience, four five-player Level 50 dungeon records were now under Guild Happy’s name.

The tenth server Club guilds had thought that they had gotten rid of this devil and had thought that when Lord Grim got to the Heavenly Domain, he would be immediately chased after and killed, so he would never get past Level 50. But who would have thought that this devil would be so evil. Just before he was about to hit Level 51, he returned to the tenth server to set records. How evil! He wouldn’t get any experience in the tenth server and didn’t need to worry about Lord Grim hitting Level 51 while setting these records.

In reality, at Level 50, leveling in the normal server was very quick. This was because starting from Level 50, there were many dungeons available. They wouldn’t need to kill monsters in the wild to level. The dungeons were enough to last for the entire day. Let alone the large scale dungeons, there were 4 five-player dungeons. If they cleared them every day, how much experience was that? 50 to 51 was much faster than 49 to 50. Leveling to 51 in a few days wasn’t a problem.

The reason the guilds didn’t have Level 51 characters was because they had done so intentionally. As long as they didn’t do their Awakening quests, the characters of the 24 classes wouldn’t earn experience either. They had held out so bitterly for so long, but Lord Grim simply came back, waved his sleeves, and left, leaving behind four records under his name.

Chapter 436 – A Wall That Can’t Be Avoided

Lord Grim had already returned to the Heavenly Domain, but the tenth server Club guilds had already suffered heavy losses.

He had returned at Level 50 and left behind four records.

What about when he reached Level 52? He could return to set Level 51-52 dungeon records.

At Level 54, he could set Level 53-54 dungeon records.

And then Level 55, Level 60…… all the way until Level 70.

Lord Grim wasn’t there anymore, but his record-breaking spirit was still there. Were the Club guilds of the tenth server going to be unable to get a single record? If that was the case, they were no different than normal player guilds. How would the tenth server players know how powerful they were?

Speaking of this, it already seemed to be the case.

Whether it was compared to the Heavenly Domain or any of the other nine normal servers, in the tenth server, the Club guilds were undoubtedly at a lower status.

Where did their popularity in their tenth server come from? Firstly, it was directly from their own guild’s players. Secondly, it was by relying on the fame of their Club to attract veteran players that had come to the tenth server to start over. New players occupied the majority of the playerbase on the tenth server, but there were still veterans like Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon who had come to the new server to play. They obviously knew of the Club guilds’ fame. Their name alone was enough to attract them.

After that, their way to spread their name was through dungeon records and first clears. On the level standings, the players from their guilds were at the top.

And after that, there was nothing else.

Their only way to spread their name and prove their strength was through dungeon records. In the tenth server, everyone knew that Lord Grim ruled in this area. The guilds had already admitted their defeat here. Why else would no one challenge Lord Grim’s team? They were always thinking of some way to stop them, not beat them.

Without dungeon records, it really was very difficult for the guilds to widen their influence. In the tenth server, the players only knew individuals and not guilds. Even though Guild Happy had taken all of those dungeon records, the players only felt like it was because Guild Happy had Lord Grim. They might not think that the guild itself was powerful.

The tenth server players already had the same thought in their head: wherever Lord Grim appeared was where the dungeon record would be.

This completely twisted the notion of dungeon records. The records were something that required a team to set, but for the tenth server players, they only thought of a single individual. The record didn’t belong to the team, but rather to Lord Grim.

Even if Lord Grim went to the Heavenly Domain at Level 50, the Club branches didn’t feel any better.

This was because the existence of Lord Grim had already influenced everyone in the tenth server. The legends of Lord Grim were deeply ingrained in everyone’s heart.

From now on, even if the top guilds set a dungeon record, the tenth server players would only have one thought: the reason you were able to set a record was because Lord Grim wasn’t there.

Lord Grim was a giant mountain. No matter how hard you tried to go around it, it would be of no use. The mountain would always stand there, looked up at. If you wanted to replace it, the only way would be to flatten it or create an even bigger mountain.

An even bigger mountain? No guild leader would ever imagine that happening. They were against Ye Qiu! Even in the pro scene, there was no mountain that surpassed him. What could a little group of ants do? Be laughed at?

Flatten him? Just mentioning it made them want to cry. Everyone who had tried to flatten him was now a corpse below the mountain, which only made the mountain even more terrifying.

The poor guilds knew of this reasoning, but there was nothing that they could do. They could only quietly forge ahead. If they wanted to go far away, they would need to go so far that the mountain would no longer be in sight. That way, the mountain would be forgotten.

But at this moment, Lord Grim suddenly came back from the Heavenly Domain and set four records. The mountain had appeared again and it seemed like it would never stop appearing. The guilds finally understood that it was never a mountain, but rather a mountain range that spanned the entire world.

The branch guilds were all crying. They only hoped that their main guild in the Heavenly Domain would hurry up and move, so that there would never be a day when he could return. But did the main guilds in the Heavenly Domain care about the feelings of their tenth server branches? Not one bit. They were currently playing a game of “if no one moves, everyone loses. But whoever moves first also loses”.

Ye Xiu was currently leveling. Chen Guo was accompanying him on her Chasing Haze. Forest Landscape was there, too. The four fake experts were there, too. Chen Guo had already bought four suitable replacements and traded them with the four people. The four people took the accounts, contacting their former friends to add them again, while chasing after their God’s footsteps.

The God was definitely going to create a guild, so the four decided not to contact their guild and would wait for the God to add them when the guild was formed.

These past few days, Ma Chenyi of Grand Internet Cafe had sent over the 24 account cards he had lost in the bet. They were all Heavenly Domain characters. Ma Chenyi wasn’t petty either. He sent over the account cards in the same condition as when they had been bought. None of the accounts had their equipment or money taken away.

Among these 24 accounts, there were seven empty ones. The remaining ones had a few pieces of equipment on them. Chen Guo looked over them and saw that they were very ordinary. She hadn’t made an requirements, so Ma Chenyi obviously wouldn’t send over any amazing accounts.

“It wouldn’t be a problem if we created our guild now……” Chen Guo said. Twenty four account cards was twenty four characters. With those four brothers as well as Lord Grim, Forest Landscape and her, they would even have one extra.

“There’s no hurry. We could have created it a long time ago if we wanted to.” Ye Xiu said.

“I know. I’m just saying. Are you going to use these accounts?” Chen Guo arranged the 24 account cards in a neat pile.

“There’s no need for it now, but there’ll be a time for them.” Ye Xiu said.

“Should I give the Battle Mage to Little Tang?” Chen Guo took out the Battle Mage account card.

“No. It’d be better if she reached here step by step. That way, she’ll be able to get familiar with the Battle Mage skills. If all of the skills are pushed to her in one go, her understanding of them won’t be as deep.” Ye Xiu said.

“What about Mu Mu?” Chen Guo took out the Launcher account card.

“Her? She’s very particular about names. I don’t think she would like this Launcher’s name.” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah, it’s a male character, too.” Chen Guo had looked at this Launcher carefully. The character was male and had a huge face, too. She didn’t want Su Mucheng to use this account either.

“Has there been any news from Loulan Slash?” Chen Guo asked after putting away the account cards.

“Not yet.”

“They said today.” Chen Guo said.

“There’s still a lot of time left today.” Ye Xiu said calmly.

“What if he doesn’t agree? Do you have any backup plans?” Chen Guo asked. In Ye Xiu’s plan, allying with Loulan Slash was a very important step because the fake experts that were currently misleading the enemies wouldn’t last long. There would be a time the guilds would have to move. For example, for Liu Hao’s group, in the worst case scenario, they would have to charge in and perhaps die a few times, but they would at least be able to figure out how many helpers Ye Xiu had at his side. This was something that Ye Xiu didn’t want to see because he didn’t actually have any helpers. He had always been playing alone.

“If he declines…….” Ye Xiu was just about to say something when his chat box flashed. He checked it and saw that it was from Loulan Slash.

Ye Xiu immediately replied, while Chen Guo came over to look at his screen.

“After thinking about it carefully these past few days…….” Loulan Slash messaged.

“Just get to the point!” Chen Guo slammed the table.

Ye Xiu was smiling though: “It’s probably good news then!”

Sure enough, Loulan Slash expressed his approval to working with Ye Xiu.

“I’d be happy to cooperate.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Ha ha, after thinking carefully about it these past few days, we think that a cooperation will definitely be something to be happy about.” Loulan Slash replied.

“What do you plan on doing next?” Ye Xiu asked.

“We’re going to drag you to our guild, of course. Where are you?” Loulan Slash asked.

The two sides agreed on a location and met up. Loulan Slash was leading the same four players from before, giving Chen Guo another reason to despise his ostentatiousness.

Soon afterwards, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim joined Loulan Slash’s guild: Heavenly Justice. Chen Guo listened to Ye Xiu’s arrangement and didn’t join for now. She and Forest Landscape continued to be free.

“If you two have time, you guys should check out the Glory forums and the eSport websites.” Loulan Slash said to Ye Xiu and Chen Guo.

“You’re going to begin announcing your team?” Ye Xiu smiled.

“Yes. Could we trouble you to have a spar with our brothers?” Loulan Slash said.

“You still want to test if I’m real or not?” Ye Xiu said.

“A bit, but more importantly, we would like it if you could measure our skill level and we also hope God could give us a few pointers as well.” Loulan Slash was quite modest. By calling him God, it was already clear that Loulan Slash believed that Ye Xiu was Ye Qiu.

“Ha ha, no problem. What class would you like to play against?” Ye Xiu asked.

“What class?” Loulan Slash stared blankly.

“Yeah, any class is fine.” Ye Xiu said.

“Because you’re unspecialized?” Loulan Slash said.

“No……. it’s because I have 24 account cards of each class with me right now.” Ye Xiu said, while indicating Chen Guo to bring over the stack of account cards.

“So you really are going to use them.” Chen Guo was speechless.

Loulan Slash stared stupidly for a bit and after a brief pause, he spoke: Then let’s go to the Arena and make a room. God, could you give me your contact information. That way it’ll be easy to find you when you switch accounts.”

“Okay.” Ye Xiu nodded his head and the outside of the game, the two added each other on QQ.

Chapter 437 – What Class Would You Like to Play First?

The Heavenly Domain had a huge world and thus had many cities. The experience loss and equipment drop chance was higher here than in the normal servers as well. The official statement was that it was done to increase interactions between players, but in reality, it was to increase competitiveness. In Glory, equipment could be bound. However, from a monetary perspective, binding the item wasn’t good. If the item was bound and one wanted to switch equipment, the player wouldn’t be able to sell his old equipment for money.

This made binding equipment a difficult choice. Choosing to bind the equipment would guarantee safety, but it also meant a loss in money. From the system’s perspective, the system encouraged players to bind their equipment. Bound equipment would lose their value in their market, which meant that the system had taken it back. If the equipment was kept circulating, then the equipment would only continue to lose value with each new one that appeared out in the market.

Loulan Slash took Ye Xiu’s group to the city Sword Shadow, which was where their Guild, Heavenly Justice’s, headquarters was located at. In the Heavenly Domain, guilds could possess a certain amount of territory. Of course, the prerequisites for this were power and wealth. As a result, most player guilds wouldn’t ever think of having their own territory. This wasn’t a problem for Club guilds and Loulan Slash’s guild had money to strengthen their power, so they had a much easier time developing than normal players.

After entering the city, they entered the Arena. For top-level cities, there was practically no difference in facilities inside the city. All the necessary ones were there. The only difference would be the amount of small buildings. Each city only needed one Arena. It was the equivalent of a teleport device.

“How about Fixed Field? The equipment on the account cards I have aren’t very good” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh?” Loulan Slash was a bit surprised. Wasn’t he a God? God’s request seemed a little weak!

“We’re testing skill anyways, so equipment isn’t important.” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s true.” Loulan Slash said. An equipment’s quality could be directly observed. All one had to do was look at the stats. Loulan Slash was looking to test skill level, so equipment wasn’t important.

“What class do you want me to play first?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Battle Mage, of course.” Loulan Slash laughed.

“No problem.” Ye Xiu also laughed. Lord Grim logged out and logged in to the Battle Mage account. He didn’t head toward Sword Shadow City and just went to the nearest Arena. He logged onto QQ, asked for the room number and then joined the room.

Loulan Slash, as well as Chen Guo and Forest Landscape, had both joined to spectate. Seeing Ye Xiu enter with a Battle Mage, the old veterans were all speechless.

How could the equipment on him be called not very good? The Battle Mage was practically naked! No one needed to look at his character’s info page. They could see it just by looking at him.

“Wow, it doesn’t even have a weapon!” Ye Xiu mumbled. The Fixed Field only adjusted for the equipment stats. If his Battle Mage didn’t have a weapon, then he wouldn’t even be able to use his class’s skills.

“I have one here. Just make do with it for now!” His opponent was the Battle Mage in Loulan Slash’s group. His current feelings were a bit complex facing his idol. He had an extra Battle Mage weapon on hand, so he threw it over.

Ye Xiu went over and picked it up: “Dang, it’s a spear! This account is a staff style…….”

The staff-style path of Battle Mages used magic wands, not spears.

Magic wands were weapons with high magic attack. Battle Mages were a class that dealt both physical and magic damage. Staff-style Battle Mages relied more on magic to deal damage. Their main method of attacking was through chasers and was one of the features of a staff-style Battle Mage. Staff-style Battle Mages also had higher attack speed. This was because magic wands attacked at an average speed, while spears attacked at a slow speed. Faster attacks allowed for more Chasers. Ye Xiu’s character was a staff-style Battle Mage. If he used a spear for battle, his magic damage would be much lower. But most importantly, his attack speed would be slower. Attack speed wasn’t a basic stat, so the Fixed Field wouldn’t fix it.

“Does anyone have a magic wand?” Loulan Slash asked. There was an Elementalist in his group. Elementalists usually used magic staffs because of their very high magic attack, but some used magic wands. This was because magic wands not only attacked faster, but also cast faster.

“Mine is bound……” This Elementalist was called Ocean Ahead. He had a magic wand, but because it was bound, it couldn’t be traded.

“It’s fine. A spear will do.” Ye Xiu said. This was the type of air that a God should have.

“Then shall we start?” the opposing Battle Mage said. This was the player called Little Bei by Loulan Slash. His Battle Mage character’s name was called Homeward Bound.

“Start.” Ye Xiu replied. Little Bei confirmed and the two sides began to fight.

Five seconds had passed. Neither side had moved.

Little Bei was waiting to admire his idol’s play. Ye Xiu didn’t know his opponent’s skill. Both sides wanted to see the other side move first. In this small boxing ring, the two sides could see each other, but neither side moved.

The spectators were all friends, so when they started seeing that the two weren’t fighting, they decided to yell at them. Go and fight messages came out.

“Yeah, fight!” Ye Xiu said.

There wasn’t any bad blood between him and Loulan Slash and the two had decided to cooperate together, so the match wasn’t anything serious. Little Bei saw that neither of them were moving and also felt it was funny. Following Ye Xiu’s words, he immediately controlled his Homeward Bound to rush forward.

“Oh oh, not bad!” The two sides began fighting, attack after attack. Ye Xiu had already begun commenting.

“Are you going to be a part of the team’s main roster?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Am I good enough?” Little Bei said.

“Depends on the team.” Ye Xiu said.

“Champion team!” Little Bei said.

“Having a dream is good.” Ye Xiu praised, but he was clearly implying that he wasn’t good enough.

“Then I won’t be nice anymore!” Little Bei shouted.

“Oh, oh? You were still holding back?” Ye Xiu said.

After two minutes, Homeward Bound fell.

“You were holding back?” Ye Xiu doubted.

“Shameless!” Little Bei cried. His corpse sent out a word bubble. This was an in-game Arena, so the settings were decided by the players. It wasn’t like the pro matches, where word bubbles were restricted when one died.

“I thought you were staff-styled. Why’d you use a spear style?” Little Bei was sad.

“You’re too inflexible. Who says you’re only allowed to use one style?” Ye Xiu said.

Ye Xiu said this, but in reality, Ye Xiu really only used a spear style of playing. The difference between the spear style and staff style was that the spear style mainly used physical attacks to deal damage. However, the two styles prioritized different skills, so his damage wasn’t as good. Even so, Ye Xiu was still able to easily beat Little Bei’s Homeward Bound.

The victory had looked easy, too. Loulan Slash and his fellow companions all looked at each other. They had been fairly confident in their skill. To be defeated so easily meant that he really was Ye Qiu. If their skill was that far from a God, then being a Champion team really was just a dream right now.

“Who’s next? What class would you like to fight?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Please use the same class!” The next to jump out was the Elementalist Ocean Ahead.

“Ocean, good luck!!” Little Bei shouted.

“Really?” Ocean Ahead laughed. He obviously knew that Little Bei admired Ye Qiu. With his identity appearing to be true, would he sincerely cheer for him?

“Really.” Little Bei said, “But you’ll still lose anyways. Even if ten thousand people came to cheer for you, it’d be no use.”

“F*ck off!” Ocean Ahead cursed. However, he really didn’t have any confidence because he knew how good Little Bei was. Even if he wasn’t Ye Qiu, his skill was the real deal.

Ocean Ahead was more on the cautious side. After the match began, he pulled open the distance and didn’t hurry to move forward. On the other hand, Ye Xiu’s Battle Mage waved his spear and an Elementalist skill, Flame Explosion, shot towards him.

Ocean Ahead hastily rolled and dodged: “What are you doing? Are you going to fight like an Elementalist?”

Just as he said this, he heard a “Bo!” as he got up from his roll. For an Elementalist, he was very familiar with this sound. It was the sound of a Frost Ball hitting.

So unlucky……. Ocean Ahead thought. He felt that if he had rolled left, he would have been fine. But when he looked to the left, he discovered that a Dark Missile had just flown past him.

How quick! Ocean Ahead was surprised. The opponent had cast three spells one after the other. These low-level spells had a low cast time. His opponent had covered all of his options, so he would have been hit by a spell if he went left or right. If Ocean Ahead had rolled right, he would have been hit by a Frost Ball. If he had rolled left, he would have been caught by the Dark Missile.

“Staff styles will learn lots of Elementalist and Witch skills. Didn’t you know that?” Ye Xiu said. His character flicked his sleeve and a purple shadow came out and wrapped around Ocean Ahead.

Sure enough, it was the Witch skill: Shadow Cloak.

Right afterwards was the Battle Mage skill: Sky Strike. Ocean Ahead was launched into the air. A magic Chaser flew out and exploded. The explosion blasted Ocean Ahead towards the ground. Who would have thought that at this moment, Ocean Ahead would fly back up into the air again.

Impossible!

Ocean Ahead was startled. Sky Strike’s cooldown wasn’t that quick.

But when he looked again, he saw an elemental wave above his head and understood what had happened. The knock up skill that had been used wasn’t the Battle Mage’s Sky Strike, but rather the Elementalist knock up skill: Elemental Power.

“The way this account added skill points is quite interesting!” Ye Xiu mumbled and then went up to combo. Ocean Ahead had been caught completely unprepared. He had originally been planning on being careful, but apart from his initial roll, he never touched the ground again until he fell, defeated.

Chapter 438 – The Opponent Is Too Strong

Loulan Slash’s group were even more shocked this time.

If Little Bei’s Homeward Bound had lost without much suspense, then Ocean Ahead had lost in an almost ugly way.

Being directly comboed to death in the air was something that was rarely seen in the Pro Alliance. No matter how amazing a God was compared to an aspiring pro player without any experience, the gap shouldn’t be that large.

“What happened?” Loulan Slash asked when Ocean Ahead came down from the field.

“His timing is too good. He predicted what I was planning on doing every time.” Ocean Ahead said.

“What you were planning on doing?”

“Yes, he saw through it all.” Ocean Ahead said. Just from this, it could be seen that their skill wasn’t ordinary. They at least understood what went wrong when they lost.

“Little Ye, you go next!” Loulan Slash said in a heavy voice. Whether they won or lost wasn’t something they cared about, but losing two matches in a row so miserably was a bit shameful. Even if their opponent was a God, they weren’t regarding themselves as normal players. Their goal was to become pro players. For pro players to have such a large gap between them, wouldn’t that be a joke?

“Okay.”

The player called Little Ye played on a Grappler called Night Tide.

“Little Ye, good luck!” Little Bei cheered. Night Tide didn’t make any small talk with Ye Xiu like Ocean Ahead before him. He entered the match and the two quickly began fighting.

For this match, Night Tide had completely eliminated his attitude of just playing for fun and giving it a try. He was taking it seriously as if it were a real match.

Grapplers were a class that required to be in a close range to do anything. Ye Xiu continued his previous strategy when he was against Ocean Ahead. He used Elementalist and Witch low-leveled skills to maintain a distance between them, while being prepared to use Battle Mage attacks at any moment.

This match wasn’t as lopsided as the previous two matches. Loulan Slash could finally relax. Little Bei and Ocean Ahead were feeling a bit embarrassed. Night Tide wasn’t any better than them. It was clearly a matter of attitude. If they had taken it seriously, they wouldn’t have lost so easily to the God.

Of course, their unpreparedness was another important reason. In a situation where both sides lacked information, Ye Xiu’s experience as a God was a huge advantage.

Although Night Tide had lost, he had lost in an acceptable manner. After he came down, Loulan Slash personally went up to fight.

There was still one more player in their group of five called Thousand Falling Leaves, a female. Her class was a Cleric and it didn’t seem like she was going to go up and fight. This meant that she was a support Cleric. Fighting 1v1 was pointless.

“God, please instruct me!” Loulan Slash said.

“Sure, sure. In the Fixed Field, your Swordpoint is a bit of a waste.” Ye Xiu said. In the Fixed Field, the stats of each character were adjusted, so both sides were at the same level. Swordpoint converted the item hotkeys into physical attack, but this value would be adjusted, so the two sides’ stats would still be on the same level. As a result, he wouldn’t be able to showcase Swordpoint’s incredible damage.

“We’re testing for skill, no? Equipment isn’t important.” Loulan Slash said.

“Taking advantage of Swordpoint’s power is one way to showcase skill!” Ye Xiu said.

“Mm.” Loulan Slash nodded his head. He had obviously done his research when he chose this weapon. This didn’t mean that he should raise his physical attack to the limit. If all 12 item hotkeys were filled with weapons, then the weight would be too much of a burden. Thus, how many item hotkeys should be filled required a lot of experimenting.

However, in the Fixed Field, none of this mattered. Loulan Slash said a “Let’s start” and then the two began fighting.

Loulan Slash didn’t dare be careless and fought seriously like Night Tide.

“Oh oh…….. You’re okay. You’re a bit better than those three.” Ye Xiu commented, while fighting.

“Thank you!” Loualn Slash replied. But this wasn’t any news to them. They had sparred against each other many times before, so they knew who was better and who was weaker.

“It seems like God is still better though.” Loulan Slash followed. Halfway into the battle, from their respective health left as well as the circumstances, Loulan Slash was in a disadvantageous position.

“I should be.” Ye Xiu laughed.

There wasn’t any twist to this match as it quietly ended. In the end, Loulan Slash wasn’t able to take a match from Ye Xiu’s hands. Four of their players had went up to fight, but all of them had lost. Even though they said that winning or losing didn’t matter, it was still a bit hit to their confidence.

Before, they had only looked at videos, watched match VODs, and then compared themselves to the pro players and Gods. This was their first time fighting against a genuine pro God and truly experienced the gap between them. It wasn’t important that none of them were able to take a match. The important point was that the gap in skill they had felt from these matches wasn’t something that could easily be closed.

At this moment, they lacked the fearlessness of youth that Tang Rou had even when she couldn’t see the gap.

“Again?” Loulan Slash discussed with his teammates, when he heard Ye Xiu ask happily: “Would you like to challenge any other class?”

“Uh……. how about your Lord Grim!” Loulan Slash finally said after discussing with his team.

“Oh, that…… that’ll be even tougher.” Ye Xiu said. He switched accounts and logged onto Lord Grim. The 20 level gap was adjusted by the Fixed Field. Loulan Slash went with the same arrangement as before and each player fought one match.

In the end……. Loulan Slash regretted deciding to fight Lord Grim.

All four of them lost even more miserably than the previous time.

Against the Battle Mage, Little Bei and Ocean Ahead had been somewhat careless. In addition, Ye Xiu’s play style had caught them off guard. Night Tide and Loulan Slash had taken it seriously and did much better.

But for this round, all four of them played very seriously. And before they went up on stage, they did preemptive thinking and planning, but the result was even worse than last time.

Against an unspecialized who had access to the skills of all 24 classes, the four clearly didn’t have the experience nor the decision making to keep up. After returning from losing, the Cleric Thousand Falling Leaves quietly said: “Even if this was a Group Competition, you guys still would’ve lost.”

In other words, the total damage all four players inflicted on Lord Grim wouldn’t be enough to take down his health bar. It could be said that Ye Xiu had won 1v4.

All four were silent. It wasn’t that they hadn’t expected a gap between them. They just didn’t think that it would be so large. Their previous confidence felt naive and arrogant.

“Nice!” Chen Guo didn’t empathize at all with the other side and praised Ye Xiu.

“That’s how it should be.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“That’ll be it for today……” Loulan Slash said. His tone clearly showed how disappointed he was.

Everyone left the Arena and stood outside the entrance. For a moment, neither side talked.

“What’s wrong? With how you guys are, you guys don’t seem like you’ll be competing in the Pro Alliance!” Ye Xiu said.

“With such a large gap, how could we even hope to compete?” Little Bei couldn’t help but say what he was feeling.

“What? Did you guys really think that you could become Champions as soon as you entered the Pro Alliance?” Ye Xiu said.

“That was just a joke.” Loulan Slash said, “But we had always thought that we were good enough to enter the playoffs.”

“And then if your luck was good, you might be able to miraculously become Champions, am I right?” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Uh…… that…….” Loulan Slash felt a bit embarrassed because that really was what they had been thinking. This was because the playoffs was in an elimination format. Sometimes, one mistake could lead to dropping out of the playoffs. Luck was undoubtedly a very important factor in these types of moments. If one’s luck was really good, then winging one’s way to becoming Champions really was a possibility. As a result, they had a lot of these types of dreams when they privately spoke to each other.

“Slow and steady, one step at a time…..” Ye Xiu said.

“If we enter the Pro Alliance right now, what place do you think we would get?” Little Bei couldn’t help but ask.

“Are you the only ones in the team? Do you have any other teammates?” Ye Xiu asked.

“We have six players. One of ours hasn’t been able to come on these past few days, but his skill level is around the same as ours. We’re planning on finding some way to get more.” Loulan Slash said.

“Digging out pro players?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Probably.” Loulan Slash said.

“Which pro players are you looking at?” Ye Xiu asked.

Loulan Slash hesitated. With the team’s preparations at this stage, they already had a list of players they wanted. After their application into the Alliance was completed, they would immediately begin getting in touch with them. However, this sort of thing was more of a secret. Loulan Slash wasn’t sure if he should tell Ye Xiu or not.

Ye Xiu didn’t wait for him to reply and continued: “You’ll definitely need pro players and they must be veterans. Please don’t think of using you six as the main roster. Afterwards, you can find four or five others to be reserve players and then switch them around every match.”

“Uh…….” The five were all sweating like mad. That was clearly what they had been planning.

“In the Pro Alliance, you’re all just people!” Ye Xiu said, “You need to find veterans and from them, you’ll learn a lot of things.”

“Okay……” Loulan Slash replied.

“There’s more.” Ye Xiu said.

The five listened carefully.

“Don’t take today’s matches too seriously.” Ye Xiu said, “It’s not that you guys aren’t good, it’s just that your opponent was too strong.”

The five cried. They even forgot to put out emojis or it.

Chapter 439 – A Strong Alliance

Ye Xiu’s habit of predicting everything was something Chen Guo had experienced many times before, and it didn’t feel like it was strange anymore. However, seeing the dead-like reaction from Loulan Slash’s group, she felt quite delighted looking at their misfortune. Chen Guo couldn’t feel happy about how Loulan Slash was running his operation and felt very happy after Ye Xiu gave them a good beating.

Ye Xiu’s comforting wasn’t very helpful. These five were still in low spirits. They had once been looking forward to it, but after the battle was fought, it all became a nightmare. There was even a bit of lingering fear when they thought about it. They were secretly celebrating that they had only been talking about it amongst themselves before. If they had announced how extraordinary their team would be, then when they entered the Pro Alliance, people would treat them like a joke.

After all, in eSports, most players were young, especially in the pro scene. Loulan Slash’s group wasn’t old either and also had youthful thoughts. They had thought of hiding their true strength and then when they entered the Pro Alliance, they would scare and astound everyone, knocking those pro players from their feet. It would feel great. But now, they finally realized that their thoughts were too naive and ignorant.

When they watched the matches, they hadn’t felt like pro players were a big deal. They could do everything the pros could do; things like hand speed had been practiced until they weren’t a problem. They hadn’t thought that when they fought a real God, it wouldn’t be like how they had imagined it to be. In practice, they could easily reach 200 or 300 APM, but in a real battle, they weren’t able to put it to use. The combos they had practiced so thoroughly had been broken in a few moves by their opponent.

Loulan Slash’s group wasn’t able to escape their crushed morale, but the announcements that they had planned had already begun.

The news first spread through the Glory forums.

In these forums, quite a few discussions concerned Lord Grim. In these discussions, messages popped up pointing out Lord Grim’s circumstances and whereabouts: Lord Grim had joined Guild Heavenly Justice.

Even though Heavenly Justice didn’t have branch networks in the normal servers like Clubs, they were already a huge name in the Heavenly Domain.

In reality, many players felt that once they had reached the Heavenly Domain, the normal servers would be things of the past. Any achievements made in the normal server weren’t worth bragging about. Thus, the long term plans of the Club guilds in the new servers were mainly ignored by the vast majority of players. They only cared about the Heavenly Domain. And here, Heavenly Justice was a rare player guild that had the power to compete with the Club guilds.

On one side was a very famous player guild. On the other side was an immensely popular mystery character. With the two combined, they immediately began stirring up the forum users who were slowly beginning to lose interest in Lord Grim. Gossip immediately began to fly around.

The Clubs quickly received this news. They didn’t even need to look through the forums. For a guild like Heavenly Justice, even though they weren’t considered main competitors, they still had to take precautions against them if they suddenly jumped out. The Club guilds were responsible for their image and the balance of power between themselves. But how could a player guild care about this? They simply did something if they thought it was “cool”, so their movements couldn’t be predicted. For a ticking time bomb like this, the Club guilds would plant a few spies there and gather some intelligence.

Members like these could see guild announcements, so they quickly sent the news to their guilds.

After observing for several days, the Club guilds hadn’t thought that there would be such a result. They hadn’t dared to make any casual movements against Lord Grim with his recent fame. Now that he had joined the famous Guild Heavenly Justice, moving against Lord Grim would be even more troublesome.

The information coming out of the forums was attracting everyone’s eyes and leading everyone’s discussions. This made the Club guilds feel like this was becoming a bigger and bigger problem, but it didn’t stop here. All of the big eSport platforms soon came out with another piece of news: Guild Heavenly Justice’s leader Loulan Slash was planning on creating a team to join next season’s Pro Alliance.

The information being spread in the forums might have just been gossip, but the official announcements from these eSport platforms wouldn’t bring false news.

This piece of news was quickly spread to every place a Glory player might step into.

Loulan Slash was already quite a famous player in Glory. His name alone was enough to attract many eyes. News of him creating a team would naturally receive a lot of attention.

More importantly, with the previous news that Lord Grim had joined Guild Heavenly Justice, everyone immediately understood: that wasn’t Lord Grim joining a guild. Wasn’t that clearly saying that Lord Grim was going to join Loulan Slash’s team? It was no wonder that such a famous expert like Lord Grim hadn’t been scouted out by the established Clubs. He had already been roped in by Loulan Slash.

Many players knew that Loulan Slash was a player with lots of money. However, no one knew exactly what his background was. The amount of news that had been announced wasn’t actually that much. It was just that Loulan Slash was planning on creating a team to join next season’s Pro Alliance and that Lord Grim had already joined Guild Heavenly Justice.

Once the Club guilds knew of this piece of news, the problem would no longer be pondered over only by the guild leaders. This issue had already been thrown to the upper levels of the Clubs.

Facing a team wasn’t something that the guild leaders had the power to create countermeasures for.

In today’s Pro Alliance, every season, the two lowest placing teams in the Pro Alliance would be eliminated. Afterwards, two teams would join the Pro Alliance to fill up the vacancies. The Glory competitive scene hadn’t been around for very long, so they hadn’t reached the point where they could have a complete secondary league. For now, they could only use this type of elimination format.

How did they choose the two new teams to enter? The Alliance had their own way of selection. The Clubs obviously knew what the requirements were. With the season at this stage, it was about time for next season’s team selection to be done. An announcement at this time was quite reliable. Moreover, these Clubs had their channels and contacts. After inquiring about it, they confirmed that this news could be trusted.

The Clubs didn’t dare stay idle facing a team.

In today’s Alliance, a new team didn’t necessarily mean a weak team, especially if was supported by strong investment. With the power of money, it was very possible to directly create a luxurious team. At the same time, they would make the market a mess as well as disrupt the Alliance’s structure.

The new team’s leader, Loulan Slash, was a famous player known to have lots of money. Moreover, no one knew exactly how deep his pockets were. The Clubs had no choice but to be wary, especially since Loulan Slash had somehow pulled in Lord Grim.

The players didn’t know who was behind Lord Grim, but the Clubs knew this very clearly. That was God Ye Qiu. If it wasn’t for his retired status, he would have definitely broken the headlines. Even though Loulan Slash couldn’t use him in the next season, creating a powerful team wasn’t just a possibility with the ability of a textbook and God by his side.

After this news was verified, the Clubs immediately held an emergency meeting.

Ye Qiu alone was something they had to be wary of, but it wasn’t anything scary. However, now that he had actually found a powerful backer, they immediately became uneasy. Some were even beginning to wonder whether Ye Qiu suddenly retiring from Excellent Era was because he had already made an agreement with Loulan Slash.

Loulan Slash planning on creating a team and applying wasn’t something that could be done in a day. Reaching the requirements necessary for applying wasn’t work that could be accomplished in a short amount of time. They wouldn’t be surprised if Loulan Slash had already been planning for a year or two. When did Ye Qiu make an agreement with him? To make Ye Qiu give up on Excellent Era, which he had led for seven full years, and to even make Ye Qiu retire in such a fashion, just how attractive was Loulan Slash’s team?

The Clubs thought too far into it and had come up with all sorts of conspiracy theories for the entire thing. Only Excellent Era knew the inside story behind Ye Qiu’s retirement and as a result were able to keep a clear mind. However, Ye Qiu rising back with such momentum was something they didn’t want to see either.

Moreover, on Excellent Era’s side, through Liu Hao’s and Chen Yehui’s efforts, they had received information the other Clubs didn’t have: Ye Qiu had already netted a group of powerful experts, and it was very likely that this group was Loulan Slash’s team.

As a result, the Club wanted Chen Yehui to gather information on Loulan Slash’s guild and begin analyzing which of those from the guild might be the hidden experts.

Witch, Striker, Assassin, Launcher. Every Heavenly Justice player that used these classes were watched. Club Excellent Era’s experts were currently wondering if they should use an open account and test them out.

The problem was that Heavenly Justice was also a guild with the maximum ten thousand players. If they averaged all the classes, every class would have around four hundred players. With four classes, that totaled around one thousand and six hundred players.

If they went to test them, the amount of work would be too much. Not only that, their movements would be too large. Loulan Slash had just announced that he was going to create a team. If this Heavenly Domain guild suffered an ambush, it would definitely attract a lot of unwanted attention. No Club would want to attract the public’s eye in this way.

They had to think of a way to create a conflict!

Excellent Era was trying hard to think of a countermeasure against the newly rebooted Ye Qiu.

Chapter 440 – Team Feature

All of the Clubs were worried because of this.

Meanwhile, at Happy Internet Cafe, Ye Xiu and Chen Guo were also looking at the news and the discussions that were being spread around by the players.

“They…… were being a bit naive with their team roster, but they’re being pretty mature in hyping the team up.” Ye Xiu commented.

“What do you mean?”

“See, they intentionally broke the message into two parts. First, they announced that I had joined Guild Heavenly Justice through the forums. Then, they released news that they were creating a team through the eSport platforms. But did they ever say that I joined their team? No, right?” Ye Xiu said, “This is to protect them from any form of criticism down the line. If they had said that I had joined their team, they would clearly be lying!”

“But they’re intentionally misleading everyone!” Chen Guo said.

“Obviously.”

“They’ve thought a lot about it!” Chen Guo disdained.

“If they don’t take their time to think, they won’t be alive for very long.” Ye Xiu said.

“How come I didn’t really see any thought being put into their team roster?” Chen Guo said.

“Youngsters are quite naive.” Ye Xiu said, “But if they were thinking about amazing the world as soon as they had began, don’t you think they would put quite a lot of thought into it?”

“Is their skill really not that good or were you intentionally provoking them?” Chen Guo asked.

“Am I really that mean?” Ye Xiu was speechless.

Chen Guo thought about it for a moment before finally saying: “If you were being nice, then was it because you pointed out that their skill wasn’t good enough or was it because you had provoked them to improve?”

“It’s because I pointed out that their skill wasn’t good enough, of course.” Ye Xiu said.

“How are they when compared to me?” Chen Guo asked.

“You?” Ye Xiu’s expression already told her of his reply.

“You’re real nice, aren’t you!” Chen Guo grinded her teeth.

Listening to the news and looking at the drama, this was what Chen Guo did on her computer. Ye Xiu, on the other hand, continued to level. It was a pity that he couldn’t do any quests or dungeons in the Heavenly Domain. Although the experience from wild monsters in the Heavenly Domain was a lot better than they were in the normal servers, his leveling speed couldn’t compare to the players who gained experience through the many Level 50 dungeons. In the normal servers, the players had already reached Level 51. In the Heavenly Domain, Ye Xiu didn’t spend any less time than they had, but he was only two thirds of the way to Level 50.

There was nothing Ye Xiu could do in this Level 50-55 range. No matter how hard he tried, it would be very hard for him to maintain this leveling speed, so he wanted to hurry and get past this difficult leveling range. Especially because the current situation was now stable, Ye Xiu needed to take full advantage of it. After getting past this level range, from Level 55 to 70, the Heavenly Domain would have plenty of dungeons to run and many quests to complete. Leveling in the dungeon was much safer when compared to leveling in the wild and the rewards were much better too.

The sensation outside of the game had slowly trickled into the game. First was Guild Heavenly Justice. When the members had heard that their boss was going to form a team and enter the pro scene, they immediately became extremely proud of themselves. The current guild members of Heavenly Justice would naturally be Loulan Slash’s first supporters.

Because of the number of players in the Heavenly Domain, there were ten global chat channels, which players called, Channel 1, Channel 2, Channel 3, Channel 4…… all ten channels were discussing this news. With a team being formed, the first thing players wanted to know was who the team members would be.

Loulan Slash’s advertising was really quite good and he understood what the players wanted. They had Lord Grim attract everyone’s attention. But after that, they maintained the mysterious atmosphere and didn’t reveal any of their team members.

That evening, on the eSports channel, the creation of the team was the lead story. In the following article, they highlighted a few classes, holding the players in suspension. So far, the players knew which classes would be on the team, but who were the players exactly? It was still a mystery.

The Club guilds were still enduring silently. There would always be teams that would join the Alliance ever year, but this was the first time the team had rooted in the Glory game. In addition, Loulan Slash and Lord Grim were already famous players. The amount of attention the team had attracted was absolutely unprecedented. It would be unwise for the Clubs to stop the waves from flowing. Even Excellent Era wouldn’t dare do such a thing.

They could only wait for the waves to pass. The one thing they didn’t know was that Heavenly Justice had talked about all this before.

“Not a bad job! Of all the teams over the years, you’ve probably done the best.” Ye Xiu said to Loulan Slash.

“It’s not bad, it’s not bad.” Loulan Slash had suffered a large blow in the Arena, but was comforted greatly by their successful marketing.

“Next, I suggest that you slowly release information little by little.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh?”

“With the huge sensation you have created, the teams now hate you to death. The foundation you now have in the game is a clear target for them to suppress you with. But with the amount of attention you have on you right now, they can’t rashly initiate a war with you. Do you understand what I’m saying?” Ye Xiu said.

“So you’re saying that we should slowly release information in order to prolong the amount of attention we get?” Loulan Slash said.

“Correct. The fact that your foundation comes from within game is different from the past teams, so you have to hurry and assimilate your power in-game into the Club guilds’ balance of power and restrict the Clubs from making any large movements. Only by doing this will you be able to develop smoothly.” Ye Xiu said.

“How complicated…….” Loulan Slash said.

“Did you really think that the pro scene was just a competition, match after match?” Ye Xiu said.

“If not?”

“It’s a business.” Ye Xiu sighed.

Loulan Slash went silent for a moment before replying: “How boring.”

“It really is.” Ye Xiu agreed.

“You can’t always do as you like in order to survive in this world. Is it this concept?” Loulan Slash said.

“As long as you understand :)” Ye Xiu sent a smiley face: “Unless you only want to walk freely for a short while. In that case, you don’t need to think about all this.”

“That’s not what I want to do. Our goal is to be Champions!” Loulan Slash said.

“So you have to create a good foundation. Champions aren’t created in one day. Your starting point is very good. Don’t waste this great opportunity you have.” Ye Xiu said.

“Our starting point is good?” Loulan Slash said sullenly, “What I’m worried about is that with all of the attention we now have, our actual skill won’t match this popularity! When we got into the Alliance and the results came out, if it’s too terrible, won’t we immediately lose a whole bunch of supporters?”

“Yes, that’s true. Right now, you only have popularity and attention. If you want to turn this into team fans, then it needs to be done through the team’s performance. But you have to understand that a team’s fans isn’t always gotten through achievements, but through the team’s features.”

“Features?”

“It could be a feature that players can resonate with or a unique feature that no other team has. I’ll give you an example: land. The land your base of operations is located is a feature that many players can resonate with.” Ye Xiu said.

“That counts too!” Loulan Slash began to sweat.

“Of course, City H clearly has a lot of Excellent Era fans. City S, where the All Stars took place, has a lot of Samsara fans. Where do you live?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I live in City B.” Loulan Slash said.

“City B…….” Ye Xiu sent a helpless emoji. It seemed like everything he said was for nothing.

Loulan Slash also understood: “City B already has two teams……”

“If you go, you’ll be the third…..”

“One of them is even Tiny Herb, the Champion team! We will have to try and win over Tiny Herb fans?” Loulan Slash wanted to cry.

“It’s very challenging isn’t it?” Ye Xiu said.

“Too challenging…….” Loulan Slash was already choking.

“Land is an intrinsic feature. It’s a relatively simple one. The others such as ace players or characters are also a type of feature. Among these, there’s actually one class that’s missing. I don’t know if you’ve noticed it or not.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh?”

“Did you watch this year’s All Star Weekend?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Of course!” Loulan Slash said.

“Among the All Star players, not a single player used a Summoner.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh……” Loulan Slash recalled. It was true.

“So if you can push out an All Star level Summoner, you’ll definitely win a lot of Summoner fans.” Ye Xiu said.

“Summoner…… we don’t have one either…..” Loulan Slash said.

“It’s just an example.” Ye Xiu said.

“Hearing God speak, why does it feel like we hadn’t plan enough for our team?” Loulan Slash cried.

“Uh, I’m just giving examples.” Ye Xiu said.

“We don’t have any features!” Loulan Slash said.

“Then you can only decide on your position. You’ll have to know what type of style you want the team to play.” Ye Xiu said.

“………..” The ellipses let Ye Xiu know that Loulan Slash hadn’t had any of those thoughts.

“Right now it’s February. There’s still three more months in this season and then a three month summer break. You’ll have a good half a year to prepare before the season starts again in September. You’ll have to find the correct way to improve yourselves. Bullying normal players in the Arena won’t help you much anymore.” Ye Xiu said.

“D*mn! You even know about that?” Loulan Slash said.

“Know what?” Ye Xiu wasn’t sure.

“You don’t know? Nevermind then…….” Loulan Slash felt a bit embarrassed. After being crushed by Ye Xiu in the Arena last time, they went into the Arena to regain their confidence by bullying normal players. Even though they had won every battle, they still weren’t able to gain back their confidence. When Ye Xiu said it, Loulan Slash thought that God knew about their ridiculous actions.

“It’s not that there aren’t any experts in the Arena. It’s just that it’s too difficult to find them. It’ll mostly be a waste of time. You have to fight with real experts and gain experience. Under harsh conditions, practice your synergy and find your own strategy that fits you. The team’s members can be switched, but if you can maintain the same unique playing style, that’ll be a very valuable asset to your team. This is a team’s feature.”

“A feature again……” Loulan Slash was foaming at the mouth. After talking for quite a while, they came back to same issue.

Chapter 441 – Flood

Ye Xiu’s words gave Loulan Slash some ideas about building a team. Developing one’s own style would take awhile, so his current priority was still advertising and gaining popularity.

Ye Xiu didn’t know if Loulan Slash did this himself or if he knew someone who specialized at advertising. In any case, he had done an exceptional job. His team was gaining popularity from all kinds of information being spread, whether they were true or false. No matter who had done the job, that person had proven himself to be a master at advertising online.

The Clubs became aware of this very quickly.

After making a big entrance that grabbed everyone’s attention, the team was steadily gaining popularity. This team, which was not even in the Alliance yet, already had more attention from the players than some of the lower tier teams.

This team definitely wasn’t inexperienced. Once they came to such a conclusion, they immediately began to be looked down on: with Ye Qiu’s help, even the most inexperienced team would be experienced.

Ye Qiu! He was the source of all their problems. Even back when he was in the Alliance, he was the one of the biggest headaches for every team and every Club.

And he was still giving them trouble despite not being in the Alliance anymore.

The Clubs’ information webs were not as powerful as they believed. Due to this lack of information and that perfect advertising, the Clubs all believed that their sudden rise to fame was because of Ye Qiu. After all, Ye Qiu was extremely familiar with how the Alliance worked. The Clubs were all guessing Ye Qiu’s position in the team. Was he the manager? Or the director?

For less developed Clubs, there were no such positions. This was especially true during the early stages of the Alliance. Besides the owner, the only person who would have any real decision-making power was the team captain. As the Alliance grew, organizations continuously developed and gradually, other positions began having executive powers such as the manager and the director. At this point, the team captain would still have some influence, but he or she would not be the one making final decisions anymore. The team captain’s responsibilities was reduced to the team alone.

With Ye Qiu’s knowledge and experience, Ye Qiu could fill in for any of these positions and would be a very terrifying opponent. In fact, the Clubs felt that Ye Qiu being in one of these positions would be even more difficult to deal with than him competing directly in the matches.

What trick hadn’t Ye Qiu seen in the pro scene? What strategies would work on him? He had been there since the creation of the Alliance. Facing such a formidable opponent, everyone immediately felt like they had a headache.

Loulan Slash maintained the steady growth in popularity and the Clubs were unable to come up with a solution. It was the same in the game. They could do nothing but watch as Lord Grim reached Level 52.

Ye Xiu was still leveling up his character!

To the Clubs, this was a clear signal. This god wasn’t satisfied with scheming behind the scenes. He wanted to step onto the stage with his Lord Grim.

He was already in the declining years for a pro player. Where did he get all of that motivation and willpower from?

Lord Grim’s identity was no secret to the Clubs. Consequently, it wasn’t a secret to the pro players of these Clubs either. Lord Grim was a huge topic among them, especially in places where pro players gathered together.

“What does he want!!!” A pro player yelled in one group chat, opening a new topic.

“Drag him out and ask!”

“Is he still in this chat?”

“Ah! Here he is!” Someone sent a screenshot to prove Ye Xiu was still in the group chat.

“What is he doing? Pretending to be dead?”

“Ye Qiu! Come out come out come out come out come out come out!” Who else but Huang Shaotian would type out so many repeating words.

“Worshiping God…” A few lower leveled pro players greeted Huang Shaotian.

“Who can see if he’s invisible?” The conversion had sped up the moment Huang Shaotian showed up.

“Sister Su definitely has it!”

“She’s not online!” Huang Shaotian started to run the operation of dragging Ye Xiu out.

“Who can see if Sister Su is invisible?”

“Yunxiu definitely can.”

“Yunxiu is online!” Someone shouted out happily.

“Who said my name!” Chu Yunxiu clearly set her name as a keyword, so she was successfully summoned the moment someone mentioned her.

“Is Su Mucheng online?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“Nope.” Chu Yunxiu replied.

“Don’t lie to us! Actually, we’re not looking for her. We just wanted to know how our friend Ye Qiu is doing nowadays.” Huang Shaotian said.

“Why not try mentioning Ye Qiu?” Chu Yunxiu suggested.

“@Ye Qiu @Ye Qiu @Ye Qiu @Ye Qiu @Ye Qiu @Ye Qiu @Ye Qiu @Ye Qiu @Ye Qiu….”

“See? Nothing happened.” Huang Xiaotian answered.

“Try a different keyword.”

“@One Autumn Leaf @One Autumn Leaf @One Autumn Leaf @One Autumn Leaf @One Autumn Leaf @One Autumn Leaf @One Autumn Leaf ……”

“Should you still use ‘One Autumn Leaf’?” Chu Yunxiu wondered.

The conversation quieted down a bit. Parting from one’s own character was always a sad and painful thing. Ye Qiu was no longer One Autumn Leaf. Everyone grieved for him when the topic was brought up.

“Who called me?” In the end, it was Sun Xiang who showed up.

“……” Everyone was speechless. As of this moment, the only ones sending messages were the God level pro players. The other pros had all taken their seats and grabbed their popcorn as they watched the show unfold.

“I didn’t call for you. I’m looking for Ye Qiu!” Huang Shaotian quickly answered the question.

“Ye Qiu? He’s still in the group even though he’s retired?” Su Xiang was curious.

“Careful.” Huang Shaotian warned, “The admin might kick you out.”

“I’ve never seen the admin come on!” Su Xiang retorted.

“Of course, the admin is also retired. Just like you said, he shouldn’t be here.” Huang Shaotian explained.

“Try ‘@Lord Grim’.” Chu Yunxiu pulled everyone back to the original topic.

“Hey! Who called me?” Ye Xiu immediately popped up.

“F*ck me. You were pretending to be dead! Shameless!” Huang Shaotian followed.

“Hi everyone. Long time no see.” Ye Xiu greeted everyone.

Immediately, a huge wall of messages popped up, giving their respects to the God.

“F*ck me! There were so many pretending to be dead!” Huang Shaotian shouted.

“Okay. Done greeting. Bye.” Ye Xiu spoke.

“You only said ONE sentence!!!!!!” Huang Shaotian howled.

“I’m not you…” Ye Xiu began mocking him. The others all responded with an emoji of a person laughing hysterically while hammering the table. A long train of these emojis formed as a result of the fast typing speed of pro players.

“Zhou Zekai! What are you laughing at!” Huang Shaotian saw that even the leader of Samsara, who was known for his quiet personality, was in the train, laughing at him.

“Haha.” Zhou Zekai laughed back.

“Hey! Don’t you dare run away!” Huang Shaotian was almost overwhelmed. After all, trying to make sure that Ye Xiu didn’t disappear while dealing with the train of mockery was no easy task, even for him.

“Here!” Ye Xiu replied.

“What have you been up to recently?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“Leveling up…” Ye Xiu replied.

Another train of hysterical laughter started up. Everyone knew what Huang Shaotian meant, but Ye Xiu’s answer wasn’t wrong. It was a classical example of an irrelevant answer.

“Bastard! Who asked you about that.” Huang Shaotian cried.

“Then what did you want to ask?” Ye Xiu pretended to be confused.

“What are you trying to do by joining that Heavenly Justice?” Huang Shaotian asked again.

“Well, when you’re playing Glory, joining a guild is a very normal thing to do.” Ye Xiu continued.

“Stop pretending to be stupid!”

“Honestly, which one of you would take me in? If there is one, I’ll go immediately. But the problem is that no one will.” Ye Xiu said.

“Come to our Blue Brook!” Huang Shaotian urged.

“Do your words count?”

“No!” This time, Yu Wenzhou answered the question. Because Huang Shaotian had hesitated, the ‘cripple’ had actually beaten him to the reply. Ye Xiu sent an emoji of a person putting his head to the table and hitting the table as he laughed out loud.

“Fight me! One on one! Arena! I’ve been waiting for so long! Let’s see if your unspecialized character is as strong as the rumors say!” Huang Shaotian immediately changed topic in a poor attempt to hide his shame.

“I’m only Level 52. Don’t you feel any shame?” Ye Xiu said.

“Fixed Field.” Huang Shaotian proposed.

“Fixed Field? What can you do there?” Ye Xiu asked. Fixed Field destroyed any advantages in equipment and was a huge disadvantage for a God level account like Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain. A God level character’s power came from their equipment advantage.

“Come on come on come on come on come on!” Huang Shaotian taunted.

“Come!” Ye Xiu replied. A train of shocked emojis followed his reply. No one had thought that the two would actually start a match.

Within a minute, the global chat in Heavenly Domain exploded.

“OH MY GOD! Troubling Rain! At Redwoods Road!”

“Swoksaar spotted in the Entresol!!”

“Cloud Piercer…”

“Windy Rain….”

“WTF! Is this the end of the world? Are the Gods coming to save us???”

Even though everyone had logged in in invisible mode, when their characters stood in the crowded maps, the ID above their heads screamed for attention. Their names were shouted out and all ten global chats went in a frenzy.

That didn’t mark the end of this flood of pro players. Other than a bunch of famous God-level characters, there were also many lesser known pro players who logged in. No pro player escaped the watchful eyes of the players.

“So many fake corpses! I hate you all! Shameless!” Huang Shaotian shouted again in the group chat.

“We’re just here to watch. Which room?” Everyone ignored Huang Shaotian’s complaints and started running a new train of questions that demanded the room number.

“Which room?” Even Huang Shaotian found himself in the train.

“Fixed Field 4. Room 2164. The password and the room number are the same.” Ye Xiu finally answered the question.

In the Arena, Room 2164 of Fixed Field 4, Ye Xiu was doing what Loulan Slash had requested and was giving Loulan Slash’s group a few tips. They had just finished a match and Ye Xiu telling Little Bei of some problems he could work on. Loulan Slash was down in the ring, waiting patiently for Ye Xiu to finish.

Suddenly, a character entered. Loulan Slash looked at the ID, and was shocked to find that it did not belong to anyone in his group. Surprised, he exclaimed, “I set up a password! How…”

“How…” It was then Loulan Slash saw the ID of the intruder clearly.

Troubling Rain?????

Loulan Slash carefully checked the ID again and made sure that there was no mistake. There was no random letter or symbol in the name. This ID belonged to none other than the ace of Team Blue Rain, the Sword Saint Troubling Rain.

Then Loulan Slash heard the person across him start to yell, “Hm? Who is this? Where are you? Where are you? Where are you?!”

In terms of speaking habits, the pro player that people were most familiar with was none other than Huang Shaotian. Why? Because he always talked the most in the Alliance. One important aspect of his speaking style was that he often repeated a single phrase over and over again.

Is that actually Troubling Rain? Is he really Huang Shaotian?

“Hurry up and start.” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim announced in the public chat.

Loulan Slash was at a loss, but obeyed and the match began.

“What are you doing?” Huang Shaotian shouted.

At the same time, the other members in Loulan Slash’s group were all shocked. A crowd had suddenly appeared like a storm. Famous characters had completely surrounded them.

“No way. Are they here to kill us?” Xiao Bei gasped in astonishment.

Chapter 442 – Poor Loulan Slash

Xiao Bei and the others, who were standing outside of the stage, could feel nothing but shock as they watched a flood of names pour in.

The room had a password. Even though the password was simply the room number, the password shouldn’t have been cracked by that many people all at once. Even if that had somehow happened, why were they here?

Loulan Slash’s group had been aiming to be pros from the start, unlike Tang Rou or Steamed Bun Invasion, so they recognized these names. Some of the names weren’t as famous as those Gods, but they still knew these seniors. The entire Alliance only had 200 players in total, so it wasn’t to hard to remember them all. But what really stunned Loulan Slash’s group was that of these 200 pro players, dozens of them had joined their room in an instant. They tried to look for a name that they didn’t recognize, but were unable to find one.

As for these pro players, the QQ group chat had brought everyone together, but there had never been a time where all of them had gathered together at one spot. For a moment, they all felt like it was a new experience and the crowd buzzed with excitement as everyone greeted each other.

“Why are you still here?” Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie asked Ye Xiu when he saw Lord Grim on the list of names.

“Shouldn’t you be sleeping?” Ye Xiu asked back. They even knew of each other’s living habits as a result of being rivals for many years.

“There’s still four more minutes.” Zhang Xinjie replied.

“Are you going to change your mind to see the match?” Ye Xiu was curious.

“No.”

“What a pity.” Ye Xiu sighed.

Other people also realized that Troubling Rain was already in the ring, but the one who stood in front of him wasn’t Lord Grim. They were a bit puzzled, when they suddenly recognized Huang Shaotian’s opponent.

“Loulan Slash? Isn’t he that Loulan Slash?” The people in the crowd began whispering to one another.

Recently, in Glory, there were two important names: Lord Grim and Loulan Slash. Both of them were still only in-game characters. However, based on Glory’s popular search results these past few days, these two names had been searched even more than of some of the God-level players and characters.

Who in the Glory community didn’t know that Loulan Slash was creating a team?

The match had already started, but neither side had moved yet.

Loulan Slash had blanked out in shock from seeing the flood of pro players, while Huang Shaotian was puzzled just like everyone else in the crowd. He was here for Lord Grim, so why was there a Berserker standing in front of him?

“Ye Qiu! You liar!” Huang Shaotian messaged in the group chat.

“Shaotian, go up! Test him out.” The crowd shouted.

“Who is he? Who is he?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“You’ve never heard of Loulan Slash?” Someone asked.

“Hm? Really?” Huang Shaotian cut back to game. His opponent’s ID could be seen quite clearly. It was just that when Huang Shaotian entered the ring earlier, he had only glanced at the name. Upon seeing that it was not the expected “Lord Grim”, he had immediately jumped back to the group chat to vent his anger. His mind hadn’t registered the name “Loulan Slash. Now that he looked back more carefully, Huang Shaotian immediately recognized his opponent.

“Hey! What’s the meaning of this?” Huang Shaotian shouted.

Loulan Slash had no idea how to respond. The crowd of pro players watching made him very nervous. His usual agile hands had turned stiff.

“Why aren’t you talking? AFK? If you’re AFK, how’d you start the match? Is it automatic?”Huang Shaotian continued to chatter.

“I’m still here…” Loulan Slash muttered weakly.

“Start? Start?” Huang Shaotian said.

“Start.” Loulan Slash took a deep breath, trying to calm himself down, but to no avail. He always subconsciously shifted his gaze to the crowd. There, he could see Brilliant Edge, the character of Team Blue Rain’s Yu Feng. He was the All Star Berserker and Loulan Slash’s favorite pro player.

“Let’s go! Here I come!” Huang Shoatian didn’t care if Loulan Slash was prepared or not. After a shout, he suddenly moved. With a Shadow Step, Troubling Rain blurred into six figures, each with a blade aimed at Loulan Slash.

Shadow Step was undoubtedly a very troublesome skill, and it was even more so when used by a top tier Blade Master like Huang Shaotian. But the real headache was still Huang Shaotian’s mouth. Huang Shaotian never stopped moving his mouth as the six shadows rushed towards Loulan Slash.

“I heard that you’re building a new team. That’s pretty amazing you know? Is that the account you’ll be using? Ah! Swordpoint! Luckily, this the Fixed Field! Otherwise, it’s be very scary!”

When the first syllable slipped out from Huang Shaotian’s mouth, six shadows had blurred into existence. When the last syllable came out, the six shadows had surrounded Loulan Slash from six different directions.

Loulan Slash wasn’t even able to gather his thoughts together in time, but as an experienced player, he was still able to react out of instinct. He immediately jumped up and crashed down with a Falling Light Blade.

“Ah! How quick! This is hard to dodge. How unlucky!” Huang Shaotian continued to blabber. It looked as if he really wasn’t going to be able to dodge. The shadows were hit by the shockwave from Falling Light Blade. However, the shockwave only passed through them, making the shadows flicker for a moment.

All of the ones hit were shadows, so where was the real one?

Loulan Slash was completely surrounded. If all of the shadows in view were fake, then where was the real body? He didn’t have enough time to differentiate them apart. At this moment, he could only rely on his experience.

Loulan Slash immediately jumped forward. He believed that the real one must have circled around behind him.

He jumped up and turned 180 degrees in midair, but then a sword light suddenly flashed in front of him.

Too fast!

Loulan Slash’s original plan was jump forward, turn around, and then counterattack with a Collapsing Mountain. He didn’t think that his opponent’s attack would come so quickly. Collapsing Mountain was too slow and would definitely be interrupted. Loulan Slash immediately Guarded and his sword swung up. A metallic ring resonated as the attack was deflected.

“You blocked it? You really do have some skill! But I haven’t gone all out yet. Brother, be careful!” Huang Shaotian continued to chatter. His talking never interfered with his attacks. When he gave the warning, he had already begun moving with a Triple Slash and quickly arrived in front of Loulan Slash.

Loulan Slash rolled away, just barely dodging the attack. When he stood up, his opponent was nowhere in sight.

“On top of your head!” Loulan Slash heard the warning and looked up, but the tip of his opponent’s sword had already stabbed through his head. Loulan Slash was already crying inside. It hadn’t been a warning. It was just Huang Shaotian narrating his moves.

Huang Shaotian was an expert at seizing opportunities. His offense wouldn’t simply end with just that single attack as an unceasing torrent of skills followed. Loulan Slash watched anxiously as the number of combos leaped up. But the more anxious he was, the harder it would be to find the rhthym.

In Glory, combos weren’t guaranteed. They depended entirely on the player’s skill. Thus, in theory, there was no such thing as an unbreakable combo.

In that moment, Loulan Slash could see each attack clearly and knew how to counter each attack. However, his hands couldn’t follow his thoughts. To make matters worse, Huang Shoatian was shouting out the names of every skill he used. The noisiness was disrupting his thoughts and making him feel dizzy. After a while, Loulan Slash began unconsciously thinking of counters for each skill Huang Shaotian named. When a huge mistake suddenly happened, Loulan Slash realized that the skill names Huang Shaotian shouted out weren’t in the same rhythm as his actions. Sometimes, the skill name he yelled out didn’t even match up with the actual skill he performed. What he was saying and what he was doing were two completely unrelated matters.

“Shaotian! Slow down! Don’t be such a bully!” Someone in the crowd typed.

“Shaotian! Why are you so quiet today? Where are your speech bubbles?” Another person shouted.

“This is the in-game Arena! The room shouldn’t be muted, right?” Someone pointed out.

As a result, someone checked the settings in this room. The person came back with a solemn news for everyone, “The room isn’t muted…”

“Poor guy.” Everyone offered their grievances to Loulan Slash.

Because of how the match was progressing, no one really cared about the results of the match. The reason was that Huang Shaotian had taken control of the match from the very start, so they weren’t able to what type of skill Loulan Slash possessed. Of course, his first few responses weren’t bad, but if he couldn’t even do that, then he wouldn’t have any chance in the Pro Alliance.

In comparison, Xiao Bei and the others were all sweating like mad.

Loulan Slash was the strongest among them, but against Huang Shaotian, it looked as if he couldn’t even find which direction he was facing. Against a God, they no longer had any dreams of beating him, but they at least hoped they could put up a fight and not just get tossed around like three legged cats. But watching this match, it looked like they really were just three legged cats. They had a long way to go!

Thinking about this, they all felt a bit disheartened. Suddenly, the clear sound of a dragon’s howl thundered across the stadium. A beautiful circle of swords spread out from around Troubling Rain as Loulan Slash flew through the air.

“Chance!” Loulan Slash’s friends shouted in their minds.

The attack had blown Loulan Slash too far away and was an opportunity for him to steady himself.

Loulan Slash succeeded. He stabilized his position and camera. However, they were unable to celebrate because they discovered that Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain hadn’t chased after him to follow up. This meant that his mistake was an act of mercy. He had intentionally let Loulan Slash get away.

“Any thoughts, brother?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“You’re…… so noisy……” It wasn’t that Loulan Slash had no respect for the God. He was just feeling too unhappy not to spit it out, especially when he was directly asked to say his feelings.

“F*ck! Did Ye Qiu throw you here for me to completely crush your confidence? Are you two even friends?” Huang Shaotian said.

Loulan Slash’s heart tightened. Lord Grim really was Ye Qiu. Even though he had already been convinced, hearing a God say it eliminated any remaining doubts. The appearance of this crowd of pro players must have had something to do with Ye Qiu. What exactly did Ye Qiu want to accomplish??

Chapter 443 – A Berserk 20 Seconds

Huang Shaotian was already about to slice him to death, but Loulan Slash was still unable to free himself from the shock of seeing so many people watching him. During the match, he was unable to focus despite his constant self reminders. These thoughts couldn’t be controlled and he couldn’t help but keep the crowd in mind.

“What are all these people here for?” Finally, in the end, Loulan Slash was able to focus his thoughts.

“God, what are you doing?” Loulan Slash didn’t think about it for himself and directly asked Lord Grim.

“You’re not busy? You still have the time to chat with me?” Ye Xiu replied.

“Ah?”

“It’s a rare opportunity. Don’t waste it!” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah! You found these guys for us?” Loulan Slash felt moved.

“No…….” Ye Xiu explained the misunderstanding, “Huang Shaotian came over to look for me. The others weren’t busy and ran over to watch. I saw a rare opportunity and let you guys have it!”

“Can we fight all of them?” Even though the opportunity had been made in passing, Loulan Slash was still very moved.

“That…… depends on whether they’re willing or not. Give a good performance!” Ye Xiu replied.

A good performance…… Loulan Slash felt upset! He only had ⅕ of his health left and hadn’t been able to give Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain any significant damage ever since the start of the match. Such a poor performance made him look like a complete noob. Would all of the momentum he had gained from his advertising disappear just like this?

“Why aren’t you talking? What are you doing just standing there doing nothing? You’re not my opponent! Give me Ye Qiu!!!!” Huang Shaotian blabbered.

Once the crowd realized that Huang Shaotian’s opponent was someone to be noted, the pro players began discussing amongst themselves. The players they discussed with were from the same team, of course.

“How is this Berserker?” In Team Blue Rain’s group, captain Yu Wenzhou asked the All Star Berserker Yu Feng.

“He wasn’t able to do anything. As soon as the match started, Huang Shaotian suppressed him. His awareness isn’t bad though. He had the right idea in a lot of places, but he just wasn’t able to grasp the rhythm.” Yu Feng replied.

“Yes……. A common weakness among rookies. Moreover, the current environment is only making it worse for him.” Yu Wenzhou said. Let alone Loulan Slash, even these Gods had never been in such an environment before.

“What do you think? On Team Tyranny’s side, Han Wenqing had been quietly watching up until the two sides stopped. Only now did he ask his vice captain Zhang Xinjie’s opinion.

“It’s only been two minutes.” Zhang Xinjie said, “His performance is even worse than most rookies.”

“The opponent’s circumstances should be considered.” Han Wenqing said.

“True…… and the room isn’t muted either.” Zhang Xinjie said.

On Team Tiny Herb’s side, Wang Jiexi thought about it alone. He didn’t have anyone to discuss his thoughts with.

Each of the 20 teams had a few players there and were all discussing amongst themselves while the two weren’t fighting.

Little Bei and the others were feeling somewhat uneasy. After another half a year, they would be a part of the pro scene, but now that they were mingled in with them, they suddenly felt like they were a bunch of children in a group of adults. They couldn’t help but feel weak and helpless. Loulan Slash’s performance didn’t help their morale either. As time passed, they felt more and more cornered.

“I’m going to kill you now and then have Ye Qiu come up! Don’t be shameless!!” Huang Shaotian made a proposal to Loulan Slash. He was here to witness an unspecialized character. He had only patiently fought a match because he realized that his opponent was Loulan Slash. But now that the fight had reached this stage, Huang Shaotian felt that it was enough. He didn’t want to be bothered with him anymore.

Loulan Slash couldn’t refuse him, so he replied with an “Okay.” Then, he raised his Greatsword and his character began to shake with rage. He had used the Berserker skill Enrage and entered a Berserk mode.

The Berserk mode lasted 20 seconds. His strength, attack speed, and movement speed would be greatly increased, but his defense and resistance would be decreased. In normal circumstances, against a stronger opponent, Berserkers would use this skill with cautious. However, Loulan Slash only had ⅕ of his health left. He was clearly planning on risking everything for this one move.

“Whoa! You’re putting everything on the line! How fierce!” Huang Shaotian obviously recognized this skill. He mumbled how fierce his opponent was, but he didn’t say that he was going to run from the fight.

Roar!

After a Berserker turned Enraged, the aura around him would thicken. It looked as if the air around him had transformed into a dense mist of blood. Loulan Slash leaped into the air and pounced forward with a Collapsing Mountain

This skill was extremely tyrannical and in a Berserk state, his skill would have Super Armor. You could attack to deal damage, but your attacks wouldn’t interrupt him.

Huang Shaotian naturally wouldn’t receive the attack directly and jumped back gently. When the Collapsing Mountain crashed to the ground, a shockwave rippled out. Huang Shaotian’s jump had dodged the shockwave with pinpoint accuracy.

“Hu!!” Loulan Slash got up and quickly followed with a Backwards Slash. The heavy sound produced by a Berserker’s sword splitting the air differed from the crisp, clear sound produced by a Blade Master’s.

Under normal circumstances, such a combo would be easy for Huang Shaotian to dodge, but with Loulan Slash’s Berserk state, his attack speed was multiplied. His attack might have hit nothing but air before, but his increased attack speed made up for it now. Huang Shaotian was unable to use a skill in time to interrupt the Backwards Slash and could only choose to retreat.

“Gong!”

Another loud sound reverberated. Loulan Slash grasped his Greatsword with two hands and smashed the ground with an Earth Shattering Slash.

The Enrage skill not only directly increased stats, but it also had another function. In a Berserk state, numerous skills had different effects than when used normally.

Collapsing Mountain had Super Armor. Backwards Slash would have a longer range. Earth Shattering Slash launched quicker.

The instant his sword touched the ground, multiple cracks in the ground quickly formed. Huang Shaotian didn’t have any time to do any careful thinking and hastily jumped again, just barely dodging the Earth Shattering Slash. But following afterwards, Loulan Slash’s left hand swiped across Swordpoint and a blood arrow shot out.

Berserker Skill: Blood Sword.

According to Glory’s class description, Berserkers were bloodthirsty warriors and sacrificed everything for victory. Using their own blood to make their moves stronger was nothing to them.

Blood Sword came out quickly in an artful angle and was extremely difficult to guard against let alone in this type of situation.

Huang Shaotian’s reaction speed truly was exceptional. The instant he jumped, he raised his sword up and blocked the incoming Blood Sword. Under such circumstances, he had actually been able to successfully complete a Guard.

Loulan Slash let out a gasp of admiration. Even with all that he did, he had still been unable to hit his opponent. He could only admit that his opponent was far more capable than him. His little tricks didn’t work on his opponent.

Loulan Slash rushed forward and attacked again twice. The Blood Sword had forced Huang Shaotian to act and this time he was unable to adjust in time. The two attacks connected. However, these two attacks were like little presents and wouldn’t impact the overall situation in any significant way. After these two attacks hit, Huang Shaotian was able to easily escape from any further pressure and was even able to make a counterattack. Even though Loulan Slash was able to avoid it, his Berserk state had ended and he had returned to his normal state.

“Oh? That wasn’t bad!!”

Just when Loulan Slash was feeling sad, the watching pro players gave a round of praise.

The Berserker’s Enrage skill only created 20 seconds of a Berserk state. Defeating the opponent in these 20 seconds obviously wasn’t possible. The most optimal result would be to pressure the opponent, seize the initiative, and bring the opponent into one’s own tempo during those 20 seconds.

Loulan Slash wasn’t able to obtain the most optimal result, but his opponent was Huang Shaotian, after all. Let alone a rookie like him, no Berserker in the Alliance would be able to completely suppress Huang Shaotian during those 20 seconds.

Against a God-level player, pressuring the opponent and dealing some damage, while not receiving any was already quite a good result. Loulan Slash had undoubtedly accomplished this. Unfortunately, Loulan Slash had succeeded with an attack with only a fifth of his health left. With the difference in health and skill between the two, these two attacks wouldn’t affect the overall situation.

“After turning Enraged, you played quite well. What do you think? Aren’t you sad that you only have 20 seconds? Ha ha ha ha, I recommend that you don’t run because you won’t have any chance to wait for your skills to go off cooldown. During this time, I’ll end you!” Huang Shaotian was talking to himself again. He had already began moving when he said “What do you think?” When he said “don’t run”, he had already swung his sword four times. Loulan Slash hadn’t intended to run away to stall for his cooldowns, but Huang Shaotian chattered as if Loulan Slash was.

Gore Cross!

Colliding Stab!

Turn Around Heavy Hit!”

Loulan Slash didn’t run and instead, used low-leveled skills to stall. Without much health left and against a strong opponent, he didn’t dare use any powerful skills because they were easier to interrupt. He had already put his feelings in order. He focused and thought about his actions carefully as he stalled against Huang Shaotian.

Huang Shaotian wasn’t wrong either. Loulan Slash wanted to wait for Enrage to come back off cooldown. But instead of running, he was stalling by defending against his opponent.

Chapter 444 – Round Robin

“Loulan Slash! You can do it!!!”

Upon seeing Loulan Slash’s revitalized performance, Little Bei and the others became all fired up. They jumped out of the corners and shouted wildly in the public channel, cheering for Loulan Slash.

20 seconds….

15 seconds…

10 seconds…

Loulan Slash observed his opponent carefully, paying very close attention to the smallest of details. He fought extraordinarily well during this short amount of time and there were no mistakes. Every attack he made was just right. He neither get hit nor did step into Huang Shaotian’s traps. His only wish was for Enrage to come off cooldown. Other than Troubling Rain’s movements and the cooldown for Berserk, there was nothing else in his mind.

Only 5 more seconds….

In that moment, a spark of excitement ignited in Loulan Slash’s heart. He had survived! He had actually survived this long without taking any damage!

And my opponent is Huang Shaotian! Loulan Slash felt quite proud of himself.

If I can do it once, then I can do it twice!

I have to value these 20 seconds of being in Berserk state. I’ll have to be careful, just like before. If I continue to do this, maybe I can even win?

Loulan Slash’s confidence was reignited instantly.

5 seconds passed in the blink of an eye. Enrage’s cooldown had come off. Loulan Slash knew he couldn’t afford to be reckless. After a few more carefully played exchanges, Loulan Slash saw a chance and activated Enrage!

The air around Loulan Slash shook. His character was engulfed in an eerie crimson light. Loulan Slash felt like he could feel the power and the promise of the skill. It was as if he could feel his boundless strength. In that moment, he felt as if he were invincible.

With a turn of his camera, Loulan Slash was ready to unleash his planned attacks, when suddenly a storm of blades covered the sky in welcome.

No words could describe Loulan Slash’s emotions in that split second.

The icy blade froze all of his boiling ambitions and recklessness faster than he had ever thought was possible. In that next moment, everything shattered into oblivion.

Loulan Slash had lost.

With the reduction in defense due to the Berserk state, Loulan Slash had no chance of withstanding such a powerful attack. He hadn’t even last long enough to see the last strike. Huang Shaotian didn’t need to finish this Formless Phantom Blade either. Right after the killing blow landed on Loulan Slash, Huang Shaotian stopped the frozen sword in his hands with pinpoint precision.

Ice Rain!

Loulan Slash knew the name of Troubling Rian’s Silver weapon. Although the Fixed Field would balance their equipment stats, Loulan Slash could still see the extraordinary icy glare from the frozen blade as his character fell limply. Which did this glare belong to? The sword? The character wielding the sword? Or even further? Like the one behind the screen?

“You’re not bad, but I’m better.” This final sentence was surprisingly short for Huang Shaotian. There were actually no repeated words or phrases.

Loulan Slash felt as if he had suddenly awoken from a dream.

My opponent is Huang Shaotian!

Loulan Slash had the exact same thought just moments ago, when he was doing well. This thought granted him a lot of confidence and ambition. Now, after his dream had being choked into nothing, he had the exact same thoughts once again.

My opponent is Huang Shaotian, the most famous opportunist in the Alliance.

Loulan Slash was still too careless in the most critical moment. That chance that he took to use Berserk, was it really a chance for him? Apparently not. It was a trap through and through.

In front of Huang Shaotian, whenever a chance appears, one always has to consider the question: Is this chance for me? Or is it a chance for him?

“Huang Shaotian! How dominant!!!”

People yelled in the public chat. Because this wasn’t an official competition, most people did not take sides. Aside from getting to know Loulan Slash, everyone was there just for fun. Upon seeing Huang Shaotian win the match, the audience gladly sent their congratulations.

“Hahaha. It’s nothing. Ye Qiu! Where are you? Why aren’t you down here yet! And this brother here, stop pretending to be a corpse. Hurry up and make room! Don’t go and miss the next match! It will really help you improve. Hahaha.” Huang Shaotian replied energetically.

Loulan Slash wasn’t holding the space grudgingly. It was just that after he had lost, Little Bei and the others sent messages in order to comfort him. He had been way too busy replying to the messages that he forgot to step out of the ring. When Huang Shaotian started to taunt him, Loulan Slash immediately left the ring without making any objections.

As a result, Loulan Slash stepped out and Little Bei’s Homeward Bound entered the ring.

“Battle Mage?” Huang Shaotian was confused, “Ye Qiu?”

“Why did you come with a Battle Mage?! Who the h*ll wants to fight your Battle Mage?! I want to vomit just thinking about it. Get your unspecialized out! Unspecialized Unspecialized Unspecialized!!!!!!” Huang Shaotian was mad.

“No……” Little Bei responded meekly, “I’m not God Ye Qiu.”

“Then who are you?”Huang Shaotian was astonished.

“I’m with Heavenly Justice too.” Little Bei spoke.

“GOD D*MMIT!!!!” Huang Shaotian’s patience had finally met its end. He typed non-stop in the public chat, “Ye Qiu! Get down here! Why another Heavenly Justice player? Do you want this senior to kill them all one by one?! There are thousands of them! When will it end????”

There were tons of emoji in the game too. All at once, another long train of “laughing wildly” emojis followed Huang Shaotian’s message.

“It’s a round robin! Shaotian, accept your fate!”

“Yeah! Yeah! This is an RPG after all. The final boss should only reveal itself when you’ve cleared all the levels.”

“Good luck! Shaotian! Everyone is watching! Try not to embarrass yourself!”

“God Qiu, how many levels are there?”

“Five or six! “ Ye Qiu replied calmly as if this situation had nothing to do with him.

“Isn’t that too little! There are ten thousand players in Heavenly Justice! Even if it’s 1%, there still should be a hundred levels!”

“Yeah, yeah. 100 levels! 100 levels!”

“100 levels, no excuses!”

“100 levels +1 no excuses!”

“100 levels +2 no excuses!”

“……”

The number pulled up with astonishing speed. All of these messages were posted by pro players, all of whom possessed nimble hands. In just a few seconds, the message already said “100 levels +50 no excuses!”. No matter how fast Huang Shaotian could talk, he still couldn’t match up to the speed at which the messages were sent. The anger filling up inside of him made him want to cough blood. The shy Little Bei watched, unsure about what to do.

“I say you should hurry up. Look how much time you’re wasting. Zhang Xinjie has already left for bed.” Ye Xiu said.

“What does that have to do with me!” Huang Shaotian shouted.

“He needs to go to bed and so does everyone else here. If you won’t start, all of us are going to go sleep.” Ye Xiu continued.

“Yeah yeah, bedtime.” Everyone agreed.

“You people can get lost! Ye Qiu, you stay!” Huang Shaotian growled.

“That’s no good. We’re all pro players. We have to stand united.” Ye Xiu didn’t need to reply. Everyone had already grabbed Huang Shaotian’s weakness. This guy really wanted to fight Ye Qiu’s unspecialized character.

“F*ck! Why am I so unlucky?” Huang Shaotian was helpless.

“Come come come. Hurry up. Homeward Bound? Ha! I’ll send you home crying!” Huang Shaotian started attacking before he even finished his sentence. Little Bei was totally unprepared. This time, Huang Shaotian was clearly not in a good mood and wasn’t polite at all. After a while, Huang Shaotian felt that the Battle Mage in front of him was similar to Ye Qiu. Both of them were so shameless. Poor Little Bei became a sandbag and was given a ferocious beating by Huang SHaotian to the point that many pro players couldn’t bear to watch anymore, “Isn’t this is a bit too harsh? So brutal!”

“Brutal +1”

“Brutal +2”

“Brutal +3”

“……”

The message soon displayed, “Brutal +50”

“F*ck! Are you guys done yet!!!!” Huang Shaotian fumed. He started to flood the public chat with his angry messages as he beat up Little Bei.

“Oh no! OT!!”

“Your mom’s an accident….”

The pro players cried as the flood of words drowned out their voices. The words on their screens were rapidly scrolling up. Loulan Slash and the others had already turned into stone. Little Bei was a tragic sight to behold, yet Huang Shaotian still had the ability to flood the chat. Just how terrifying was his hand speed and his ability to multitask?

“Room owner! Who’s the room owner? Mute the chat!” Someone finally remembered the ultimate solution and called out constantly in the channel. The pro players who saw it understood right away and joined him. No matter how amazing Huang Shaotian was, there was no way a single person could match the united efforts of so many. Seeing his entire screen filled with demands, Loulan Slash felt his head going dizzy. He didn’t dare delay and muted the chat as fast as he could.

Everyone breathed a sigh of relief, but they soon realized that without the public channel they couldn’t discuss anything together. Watching the match by themselves without any discussion was a bit boring.

“We can continue here!” Someone suddenly messaged.

“Oh! Yeah! We still have here!”

The message came from the group chat in QQ. The pro players turned off full screen for the game. This way, they could watch the match and chat simultaneously with no issues at all. On the other hand, Huang Shaotian definitely wouldn’t be able to switch between chatting and battling at the same time.

“We should have done this earlier!”

After a few chats, everyone turned their attention back to the match.

“This little Battle Mage isn’t that good!”

“It’s because Huang Shaotian is being too fierce! He’s venting out all his anger onto him.

“Poor guy.”

“That’s why he’s a brute!”

“Tsk. Tsk. Tsk.”

“Hey hey! What are you people talk about?” The were a few confused newcomers.

“We’re watching a show. Log into the game.” Someone directed the newcomers.

Consequently, there was another wave of pro players who logged into the game. By the time that second wave found the room, Huang Shaotian had already defeated Loulan Slash’s group.

The pro players finally gathered their thoughts together and stopped horsing around. This was because they saw that Lord Grim, a character with a class that had never appeared before in the pro scene, had finally entered the ring. At this moment, Loulan Slash and the others, finally figured out why so many professional players had decided to gather here. Loulan Slash re-opened the public chat and told everyone so. He hoped that he could see the pro players discuss the match here.

“Mm. It’s about time. Ready to go to bed?” The first one to speak up was Ye Xiu.

“F*ck! I WILL FIGHT YOU!!!!” Huang Shaotian shouted as he unsheathed his sword.

Chapter 445 – The Real Deal

Getting ready to go to bed was just a joke. If Ye Xiu had actually wanted to go to bed, he wouldn’t have gone to fight.

The match began. Huang Shaotian wasn’t sure if the guy he was facing would be so shameless as to ignore the rules and immediately leave the match, so he stabbed forward with his blade. He would fight for as long as he could.

The public chat had been opened up by Loulan Slash again, but after Ye Xiu made the joke, no one followed up with any jeering. Everyone was completely focused on the match.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim jumped in order to dodge and stabbed back. His Thousand Chance Umbrella was only the length of a sword, but with a flip, it suddenly changed into a spear.

Huang Shaotian hadn’t done anything yet, but all the spectating pro players sucked in a breath of cold air.

They had heard about Lord Grim’s Silver weapon. The reports had come from the branch guilds in the tenth server. However, no one there was a worthy opponent for a God, so the information on the Silver weapon gave them a general understanding of it, but no one knew exactly how extraordinary it was.

The Thousand Chance Umbrella’s feature was its ability to transform. This unprecedented function attracted everyone’s attention. They didn’t really care about the actual stats of the Silver weapon. What they wanted to know was how did this weapon transform? How long does it take for the weapon to transform? Was there a cooldown? The guilds had tried to find an answer to these questions, but they couldn’t get a precise answer.

Today, under the watchful eyes of these pro players, the Thousand Chance Umbrella had completed a transformation. Their first reaction to it was: fast!

The transformation from umbrella to spear happened in the blink of an eye. A weapon suddenly elongating could already be considered as a terrifying skill. Huang Shaotian had dodged it, but how many had the reaction speeds and hand speeds like Huang Shaotian?

“If we can’t get a good understanding about this weapon, we’ll definitely suffer the consequences!”

Only a short moment had passed and everyone was already thinking this thought.

In the match, Huang Shaotian had avoided the attack. He had an opportunity to strike back, but he didn’t choose to go for it. He was clearly very curious about an unspecialized character and his Thousand Chance Umbrella. He wanted to see just what kind of tricks it could pull off, so there was no need to rush. No rush at all.

But during the next two minutes, all he saw was Lord Grim use his spear and use the same five low-leveled Battle Mage skills over and over again. There were quite a few times where those five skills were all on cooldown. If he didn’t transform his weapon, he would just be asking for a beating. However, Huang Shaotian also stubbornly waited.

“Is your toy broken?” Huang Shaotian couldn’t help but ask.

The reply came in the form of a Falling Flower Palm.

Huang Shaotian dodged it: “Say something!”

Dragon Tooth.

“Hey hey hey hey hey hey!!!!” Huang Shaotian shouted.

Sky Strike!

“He probably took off his headphones!!” Huang Shaotian thought as he grinded his teeth. However, sound was very important to pro players. How loud or how soft a sound was indicated how close or how far the opponent was. This could all be accomplished in Glory. The Pro Alliance had prohibited talking partially for this reason.

After another minute, Ye Xiu was still using his spear. The crowd was getting a bit tired of it. Huang Shaotian was already at the end of his patience. He clearly didn’t want to show his strength for everyone to see. If he was going to show them a Battle Mage and one that was only using Level 20 and under skills at that, then there would be no point in watching anymore.

Huang Shaotian thought as he cursed out loud. Even though he had his suspicions that Ye Xiu wasn’t wearing his headphones, he also had suspicions that he really was listening, but was just acting as if he wasn’t listening to make him give up on his sound attacks.

Huang Shaotian didn’t mind. Talking while fighting was a habit of his anyways, so he continued to blabber, while he attacked with his sword.

Upward Slash!

The sword arced in a beautiful half circle. After several follow ups, Ye Xiu was finally unable to dodge and the sword launched Lord Grim into the air.

If a pro player launched into an opponent the air and didn’t follow up, then the pro player should feel ashamed for being called a pro.

Huang Shaotian wouldn’t miss an opportunity. His Troubling Rain shot forward like an arrow and slashed across with his sword as if he were going to directly slice Lord Grim into two halves.

“Bang!”

There was no gunfire, but there was the sound of a gunshot.

Huang Shaotian deserved to be called a God. As soon as he heard the sound, he immediately began to dodge. However, without any gun fire, it was hard to distinguish which direction the gunshot was coming from, so Huang Shaotian could only pray for good luck.

“Pu!” A spurt of blood flew through the air. In real life, a single gun wound could be fatal, but in the game, the damage didn’t matter too much.

Huang Shaotian was a bit sad though because his luck wasn’t that good. From where the gunshot had hit, if he had ignored the gunshot, then he might not have been hit by it.

His awareness was too good, which actually made it a weakness. The opponent aimed where Huang Shaotian might have dodged to. Huang Shaotian moved into the bullet’s path and pretty much gifted himself the bullet.

On the other hand, Huang Shaotian was also happy because the Thousand Chance Umbrella had finally began to show its abilities.

Bang bang, bang bang, bang bang!

Rapid gun firing. The Thousand Chance Umbrella had transformed into a rifle. The attacks would come in waves of two or three. It wasn’t like a revolver or an automatic pistol where they only shot one bullet at a time.

From the rhythm of the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s firing, it was clearly a two shot rifle.

Ye Xiu had Lord Grim shoot, while moving backwards. He was using Aerial Fire to kite Huang Shaotian.

“Aren’t you being too naive?” In Huang Shaotian’s eyes, this was a kindergarten level move. Using such a move against a God like him was disrespectful.

Huang Shaotian watched Lord Grim’s movement. He dodged a several bullets and then suddenly used a Triple Slash.

In a single breath, Huang Shaotian completed the Triple Slash, while dodging bullets at the same time.

Afterwards, a sword light flashed out.

The low-leveled skill Sword Draw came out quickly and had a long range too. No expert would give up on such a useful skill.

Huang Shaotian had closed the distance with the Triple Slash. He had calculated the Sword Draw so that no matter where the opponent moved, his opponent would be in his attack range would have nowhere to run.

Thus, Ye Xiu didn’t dodge. The smoke and fire from his rifle was still up in the air, when he suddenly pulled out a Tachi. He raised the sword up horizontally and Guarded against the slash. Right after, he turned his hands over and sent out his own Sword Draw.

Other skills might not matter, but Huang Shaotian felt that if he were hit by a Blade Master skill, then he would lose too much face. As soon as he saw Ye Xiu come out with a Blade Master skill, Huang Shaotian couldn’t help but start to focus. Ye Xiu had blocked his move with a Guard. Huang Shaotian felt like he should be using more high-end skills. He couldn’t use the same Level 20 and under skills as this little unspecialized character.

As a result, against the Sword Draw, Huang Shaotian countered with a Rising Dragon Slash. Troubling Rain was like a firework and he suddenly rose, dodging the Sword Draw perfectly. Following afterwards, he transitioned from a Rising Dragon Slash into a Falling Phoenix Slash downwards.

Lord Grim was cut into two halves, making the delighted Huang Shaotian stare dumbly.

Shadow Clone Technique!

The experienced God instantly recognized it.

However, why hadn’t he seen it? It was because when Falling Phoenix Slash came out, the user would turn around. In that short instant, his camera would turn away from the target.

During that time, Lord Grim left a Shadow Clone for him.

Where was his real body then?

Huang Shaotian had a premonition. Without hesitation, he immediately used a Falling Light Blade. Troubling Rain crashed to the ground like a meteor. Not stopping to pause, he rolled forward. Only then did he turn his camera behind him. Sure enough, Lord Grim had fallen from the air. As he landed, the earth shook around him.

A wall of clapping emojis filled the public chat. That truly was a brilliant exchange.

Only an experienced God like Ye Xiu would be able to grasp the short instant Huang Shaotian would turn around due to Falling Phoenix Slash, allowing him to use a move without the opponent knowing.

And only a nimble God like Huang Shaotian would be able to realize that something wasn’t right and immediately use a Falling Light Blade to avoid Lord Grim from landing an Eagle Stamp on his head.

Ye Xiu’s move was something the onlookers saw more clearly than the person on the spot. Huang Shaotian might not be aware that Ye Xiu had used the Shadow Clone Technique the instant he had a blind spot in his camera view.

On the other hand, Huang Shaotian’s move was something the person on the spot knew more than the onlookers. This was because even though Huang Shaotian had made such a decision, in reality, he hadn’t known that Lord Grim was above him.

Sure enough, a battle between two Gods at the peak was the real deal.

The pro players were extremely excited.

“Boom!” There wasn’t too much noise, but there had clearly been a small explosion.

Where did the explosion come from?

Huang Shaotian was at a loss. The crowd was also at a loss. Only players of the corresponding class were able to recognize the skill: “It’s a Mechanical Seeker!”

Mechanical Seeker was only a Level 5 Mechanic skill. It let out a kamikaze robot, which would move on its own and look for a target.

This skill was within the level range for an unspecialized character to learn, but when had he used it? How did the crowd not see it?

They would have to study the recording to answer this question. After the Mechanical Seeker, exploded on Troubling Rain, Lord Grim immediately followed up. The Grenade that was thrown out seemed to have been flying in the air before he had even landed. This shouldn’t have been a threat, but once the Mechanical Seeker had found Troubling Rain, everything changed.

Chapter 446 – Dying Brain Cells

All attacks had a stun effect, but the amount differed depending on the attack. For example, skills like Dragon Tooth had a stun that could be counted in seconds and were clearly pointed out in the skill description. The majority of skills didn’t mention a stun effect because the hitstun was pretty much instantaneous. It depended on the player’s experience to seize it.

The difference between normal players and experts were clearly reflected in places like these.

Why were experts able to complete combos using a certain chain of moves, while normal players were always easily interrupted by experts using the same chain of moves? It was because experts had a good grasp of the skill’s rhythm. Every time an attack hit, they would always be on point. In theory, true combos that couldn’t be broken existed, but they were too too difficult to perform. No matter how great a player was, the player could only try his best. It wasn’t possible to grasp every attack perfectly 100% of the time.

Ye Xiu’s attack succeeded this time.

Huang Shaotian hadn’t taken the Grenade seriously, but after the Mechanical Seeker exploded, even if he took it seriously now, it was already too late. The brief hitstun, which to most people was nonexistent, allowed the Grenade to hit Troubling Rain’s body.

No matter how fast his reactions were. It wasn’t possible to do anything at this point.

The Grenade exploded and the blast sent Troubling Rain flying. Ye Xiu had clearly calculated this. The positioning created by the explosion was what he needed.

Lord Grim rushed towards that position. Huang Shaotian wouldn’t just let it happen and put up a struggle. However, unfortunately, his movement skills, Falling Phoenix Slash and Falling Light Blade, had just been used and were on cooldown.

If a character could float freely in the air, then being in the air wouldn’t be an opportunity players would chase after. Huang Shaotian didn’t have anything he could use and watch helplessly as Lord Grim met him face on with a Collapsing Mountain, sending him crashing to the ground.

Troubling Rain wouldn’t just fall to the ground like that.

He teched it with a Quick Recover. For an expert at his level, failing a tech was considered a huge mistake.

Huang Shaotian obviously wouldn’t make such a low leveled mistake and his Troubling Rain rolled away.

Quick Recover allowed the character to not get knocked to the ground, but the character wasn’t invincible to the opponent’s attacks.

In a match at this level, an opportunity to counterattack had to be found while teching in order to turn the situation around.

Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain hadn’t even rolled one body unit away, when he leaped into the air. His body spun in the air like a spinning top and moved in a trajectory parallel to the ground. The tip of his sword was raised up above his heads. Numerous sword arcs twisted towards Lord Grim.

Blade Master Level 45 skill: Headwind Strike!

Even though Headwind Strike only moved forward, it enveloped a rather large area. In addition, the sword arcs flying forward were completely controlled by the player. As a result, whether one jumped or rolled, it was very difficult to escape from this sword prison. Ye Xiu didn’t face it head on. He didn’t have Lord Grim stop there either, but instead had Lord Grim retreat back.

Sure enough, the instant he retreated back, Troubling Rain looked as if he extended the sword prison and the sword arcs extended another half a body.

This was a trick or perhaps a flourish used by Blade Masters. By controlling the arcs, they didn’t extend the range to the limit at the start and intentionally held back. Someone not experienced enough would think that he was outside of the range, but then be caught off guard as the sword prison pushed forward and enveloped him.

Ye Xiu obviously knew this trick, so he hadn’t stopped and jumped back. He had dodged it, but it had been a really close one. How much distance was being held back depended on the player. A noob wouldn’t be able to perform the trick. Among normal players, as long as one was able to complete such a move, it didn’t matter how much distance was hidden, it would be enough for one to show off. Huang Shaotian’s Headwind Sword had actually hidden half a body unit. In the entire Glory universe, no one else could do accomplish this.

“Not bad!” Huang Shaotian shouted. His move had dispelled Ye Xiu’s offensive, causing his fighting spirit to rise, especially after knowing that Ye Xiu had begun to show the power of an unspecialized. This was what he had been waiting for. After using Headwind Sword, he didn’t wait to land on the ground and immediately swung his sword. But this time, it wasn’t a Blade Master skill and instead the Spellblade skill: Earthquake Sword.

This low leveled skill wouldn’t do much damage. Blade Masters also weren’t a magic based class either. Earthquake Sword would usually only be leveled only once and was used as a control or combo move. Huang Shaotian had timed this skill well and caught Lord Grim right when he was about to land.

Lord Grim quickly unsheathed a sword and slashed to one side, using a Falling Light Blade to slide diagonally to the ground to avoid the attack.

Falling Light Blade was the move that Huang Shaotian had wanted to use when he had been blasted into the air earlier, but it had been on cooldown for him. Now, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim used this skill in the air as if to taunt Huang Shaotian.

“Shameless!!” Huang Shaotian chattered as he closed in.

Even though he had never fought against an unspecialized before, just from the class’s intrinsic properties, he didn’t need to fight against one to think of a few basic issues.

Unspecialized characters had classes that spanned all 24 classes and undoubtedly possessed a variety of skills. Long-ranged, melee, aerial, unspecialized could use any type of skill. In melee range, unspecialized might use Blade Master or Assassin skills. In long ranged, unspecialized might use Gunner or Mage skills. While moving, unspecialized might drop traps to see if you would fall into one if you fell to the ground.

Right now, the two characters had a bit of distance between them. Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain lost his offensive capabilities and needed to close in. Usually, he would want to find some way of getting close to long ranged classes. As long as he was able to close in, it could said that he would have already won half the battle. But against an unspecialized? If he got close, it just meant that he was no longer in a situation where he couldn’t attack. Next, he still had to face a class that wasn’t afraid to be up close.

As Troubling Rain rushed forward, Lord Grim fired his gun, but he didn’t retreat. If this was any other Gunner class, there was no way they would just sit there waiting for the Blade Master to arrive. But an unspecialized wasn’t afraid. If the Blade Master was up close, then the unspecialized could simply switch from a gun to a sword or spear.

While Troubling Rain closed the distance, Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella continued to fire. Once the two sides were close enough, the umbrella suddenly transformed from a gun to a spear. The sudden change was similar to what Huang Shaotian had done with his Headwind Sword. Huang Shaotian had been prepared though. After all, he was an expert at doing this, so the transformation from gun into spear didn’t cause too much trouble for him. Troubling Rain turned and also made a slash with a sword at the same time.

“Hua!” The Thousand Chance Umbrella flipped open into an umbrella in front of Troubling Rain’s face. The sword hit the umbrella canopy. Then, Lord Grim pushed the umbrella forward and suddenly, all Huang Shaotian could see on his screen was a giant circle. The drawings on the circle looked quite nice and they seemed to be spinning too like a computer screensaver.

“Too shameless!!!” Huang Shaotian shouted as he moved.

This was a commonly used move done by Knights. They would move their shields right in front of your face. The view seen by the player was through the character’s two eyes, so by putting the shield in front of your eyes, the shield would block your view.

“All the dirty tricks the different classes use really aren’t a problem for you!!!” Huang Shaotian cursed as he continued to move. He had to hurry up and get out of this situation. Using the shield to block your view wasn’t done just to play hide and seek with you. The next second, the opponent could send a sword flying towards you. In order to resolve the situation, one had to quickly pull open the distance. Only with distance would it be possible to see the situation. The only inconvenient part about this move was that the user was unable to see how effective his move was because he couldn’t see his opponent’s screen. It was a move that tested knowledge and prediction.

But as an experienced God and hailed as a textbook, knowing every detail of the game was something he possessed.

Ye Xiu already had a good idea of the distance and to what extent his umbrella blocked his opponent’s view. For someone like him who only need to know the skills and tricks of a class, he might even be more precise than top tier Knights. This was because this didn’t require an understanding of the class, but an understanding of the details of Glory.

The instant his Thousand Chance Umbrella opened up, Ye Xiu knew that his “screensaver” had been successful. Huang Shaotian was definitely trying to pull away to get away from the screensaver. But when Huang Shaotian pulled away, Ye Xiu took away the “screensaver”, but instead of taking it back completely, he stabbed forward and his shield turned into a spear.

“F*ck your sister!!!!” Huang Shaotian cried and was caught unprepared. Troubling Rain was stabbed by the Dragon Tooth. This was a skill with a Stun, so the follow ups couldn’t be avoided. A Sky Strike launched him into the air.

“Too shameless!!” Huang Shaotian’s character was in the air, but his mouth didn’t stop moving as he cursed.

A screensaver could be done by Knights, but a screensaver directly into an attack was something Knights couldn’t do!

Knights had a shield in one hand and a weapon in the other. They were clearly separate, but the previous chain of attacks had never been done before in Glory history. Huang Shaotian had to have caught it.

“He’s hurting our brains……” The spectators began commenting.

“Yeah! How are you supposed to defend against those transformations!”

“If it was just a few transformations, then it would be okay. But this thing has too many. It covers all the classes.”

“It can definitely do all of the classes, but what I’m not sure is whether there really is only six types of classes? Are there any small differences within each class?”

“There’s no way it’s just six. Didn’t you just see that shield into spear come out?”

“What a headache!!” The pros were already certain that fighting against an unspecialized would make their heads hurt.

Chapter 447 – Unspecialized Combo

To the spectating pro players, they didn’t actually care who had won or lost this match. In their eyes, Huang Shaotian and his Troubling Rain were simply little white lab mice. It didn’t really matter how they had tussled. Their main focus was on Lord Grim and the weapon that was in his hands.

Huang Shaotian might only be a little white lab mouse, but he was certainly an elite one. With him as a reference, it made it easy for them to see how difficult an unspecialized character was to deal with.

They only discussed a few words, before finally returning their focus back to the match. In a one on one match, it would only last a few minutes. There wasn’t much time for them to freely say what they had wished.

After being struck by a Dragon Tooth and launched into the air with a Sky Strike, Troubling Rain wasn’t able to fall back to the ground for awhile. Lord Grim chased after him and seized this aerial opportunity to combo in a few hits.

There was nothing Huang Shaotian could do. Ye Xiu’s comboing was perfect. If he had tried to get away with something like a Falling Light Blade, he would only be wasting his cooldowns.

As an expert opportunist, he was also very good at being patient. Huang Shaotian continued to chatter as he carefully paid attention to Lord Grim’s attacks.

Skills, angles, timing, weapon forms, length. Every detail had to be noted and it was possible for an opening appear at any time.

This is the difference between an expert and a noob.

Noobs are unable to see through a difference in particulars. Veteran players might be able to see through the difference, but they are unable to seize it. Experts can see through the differences, but might only be able to seize it at times. Someone who is able to seize it often is considered a God……

Ye Xiu and Huang Shaotian were both Gods.

Huang Shaotian watched Ye Xiu’s attacks attentively and resented them so much that his teeth were starting to itch. His voice began to grow louder.

No one was perfect. Even if it was Ye Xiu, there was no way he could do every detail perfectly. However, he was good at distributing his attention. This was because even though some details might not have been performed perfectly, the other side probably couldn’t be able to take advantage of it.

This was how Ye Xiu played. It could even be said that his combos were full of holes. However, if a hole can’t be taken advantage of by the opponent, then it couldn’t really be considered a hole.

His combo didn’t stop however, giving the crowd some time to discuss amongst themselves.

“He’s not going to just get comboed to death, right?!”

“Unspecialized have so many options!”

The pro players went into a discussion. They could understand the reason why Huang Shaotian was unable to escape from the combo. For this to be possible, it had to be an advantage in the classes. Unspecialized characters had numerous skills at their disposal. Moreover, they were all low-leveled skills with quick start-up times and short cooldowns. By using these skills to create combos, the comboing was very flexible and adaptable.

For example, in some cases, a regular class only had one option to continue the combo. If the skill was on cooldown, the combo would naturally stop. Or perhaps if this skill needed a certain set-up to use, then the combo would also stop. On the other hand, unspecialized characters would rarely come into these types of situations because they had so many skills to use. In any situation, they had multiple options they could choose from. Most of the time, the unspecialized could just pick whichever one was most convenient to keep the combo going.

“You can say that in theory, but with 120 different skills, who could create such an unbreakable combo without needing to take time to think?” Someone asked.

The public chat suddenly went quiet. Someone sent out an injured emoji, making everyone start a train of messages again.

Pro players wouldn’t be a stranger to any skill in the game. Because of different amounts of experience, everyone had different understandings of how to use a skill in real battle. Knowing these skills and stringing them all together were two completely different matters though.

“Huang Shaotian, show some more spirit!!!” People began cheering for Huang Shaotian.

This didn’t necessarily mean they wanted Huang Shaotian to win. The more they watched, the more they felt like they needed to study the unspecialized character. They hoped to see more from this match and hoped that Huang Shaotian could force Ye Xiu to reveal more things.

As for what exactly those things were, they didn’t know either because no one had studied unspecialized characters before.

“Shut up! You come down and show some spirit!”

“D*mn, you still have time to look at the chat?? You must not have much to do!!!!”

“You think this is relaxing!?”

The current taunting wasn’t simply there for fun. This type of agitating could be considered a type of trash talk, but it was also being done in hopes of encouraging Huang Shaotian.

“Brother Yu, losing like this is too unsightly! Punish him!!!” Some even complained to Yu Wenzhou.

“Ha ha.” Yu Wenzhou only laughed, but didn’t say anything. He had been watching quietly the entire time and had only talked privately with his teammates sometimes. He hadn’t said anything in the public chat.

“Brother Yu, what do you think of this match?” Some directly asked him. Yu Wenzhou truly was someone worth asking. For one, he was a very experienced and qualified Glory player and two, he was extremely familiar with Huang Shaotian.

“Shaotian is probably going to lose.” Yu Wenzhou didn’t hide and replied.

“Why?” The asker continued to ask. The others stopped what they were doing, waiting for the reply.

“Unspecialized characters have so many options. Experience will be needed to deal with one. But who has experience fighting an unspecialized? That’s why Shaotian probably won’t be able to keep up. Ye Qiu isn’t a noob either. He surely knows this well. Did you guys notice? Not one of his combos are conventional ones. Aside from a Dragon Tooth into a guaranteed Sky Strike, have you seen two skills from the same class being used one after the other?” Yu Wenzhou slowly typed.

Yu Wenzhou might not have been the only one to notice this, but quite a few hadn’t. Everyone listened and took note. Soon, quite a few of them made sounds of them understanding it.

“Huang Shao, your captain is giving you advice. Did you hear it.” Someone took the chance to taunt him.

“F*ck off!” Huang Shaotian wasn’t like Yu Wenzhou and gave a prompt reply.

“Brother Yu, he actually dares to tell you to f*ck off!” That person turned his head to report it.

Yu Wenzhou didn’t take note of these jokes and didn’t reply. He continued to watch the match very carefully.

Huang Shaotian already knew about all of this.

This was why as he watched, he thought to himself, looking for possible ways for these low leveled skills to be used. Once he understood the reasoning, he could then make a prediction. If his prediction was correct, he might be able to break the combo.

If this was during the season, a lot of time would have been taken to study this opponent. But Huang Shaotian was already being comboed up in the air before he began doing this work. It was very likely that he wouldn’t be able to get anything out of it before he died.

As a result, Huang Shaotian wouldn’t hurt his head over this and memorized the previous sequences. He thought about what openings might appear in these sequences and prepared for them. Next, he needed some luck. He needed Ye Xiu to repeat a combo sequence, which would then give him an opportunity. Completely seeing through the possible combinations for the 120 skills while in battle was impossible.

Troubling Rain’s health continued to drop. Huang Shaotian didn’t get discouraged nor did he lose hope. He continued to wait.

When he needed to be patient and when he needed to concentrate, he could still blabber and trash talk. Huang Shaotian truly wasn’t ordinary.

Huang Shaotian often narrated his moves, but unfortunately he couldn’t make any moves, so he switched to narrating Lord Grim’s moves. In order to maintain his style, he was just randomly spouting words. It didn’t matter if the skill being used and the skill being narrated didn’t match. Then, he would add a “Wow! Amazing!” or a “What am I going to do?” or a “Oh no! I’m going to die!” If anyone listened to him, they wouldn’t think he was a hunter waiting for a catch.

Even though he said all this, no one replied. Huang Shaotian felt like Ye Xiu definitely wasn’t wearing his headphones. If Ye Xiu had been pretending in order to make him shut up, with him still blabbering so much, it clearly hadn’t worked! It was possible he had already given up on the plan. And since he’s been so quiet for so long, he probably hadn’t heard him.

“Shameful!!!” As he said this, he began filling the screen with words.

The crowd wailed.

This was the type of style everyone wa familiar with. In the Pro Alliance, voice was prohibited, so only typing was allowed. As a result, Huang Shaotian would do his taunting in the public chat. There was no prohibition today, so he had used his mouth. It was a rare clean chat, but it had suddenly erupted.

As he typed, Huang Shaotian didn’t let up with his waiting.

“Don’t give me a chance! If you give me a chance, you’ll die……”

Everyone thought he was just bragging, but the opportunity actually came!!

After a Striker’s Collapsing Fist, Lord Grim used a Witch’s Shadow Cloak to pull him in. This was a sequence Huang Shaotian had memorized. At this moment, right after the Collapsing Fist, he made his preparations. Lord Grim flung his sleeves and a dark shadow flew out.

Huang Shaotian was able to react. He let out a Rising Phoenix Slash. Troubling Rain looked as if he had stepped on the dark shadow as he pounced towards Lord Grim.

“AHH!!!!!”

That instant, quite a few had shouted at their computers and then the chat immediately burst into astonished emojis.

Everyone had thought that Huang Shaotian would be comboed to death by the unfamiliar unspecialized. Who would have thought that he would be able to turn the situation around and counter attack?

“Shaotian, how mighty!!!” Quite a few began typing.

Chapter 448 – Can You Hear Me?

“Pro players are too amazing!!!” Loulan Slash couldn’t help but exclaim.

Their little group was a bit biased. After being beaten by Huang Shaotian so brutally, everyone hoped to see Ye Xiu win gloriously. They already saw Ye Xiu as one of their own.

They all felt quite happy seeing Troubling Rain being tossed around in the air like a rag doll. However, besides that, Loulan Slash was also feeling a bit disappointed.

The match with Huang Shaotian left quite a deep impression on him. He had played Glory for a long time and had experienced many PvP matches, but none of them had moved him so much like that match.

The sudden retaliation that reversed the situation, the sudden drop from heaven to hell ….… Even though Loulan Slash was the one being pushed around, which had made him very sad for awhile, he had to admit that Huang Shaotian’s finishing blow had been brilliant. He had not only won the match, but he had also devastated his morale.

If this was the Pro Alliance final, an abrupt reversal would feel worse than death. Who knew how long it would take the person to recover?

Thankfully, it had only been an ordinary spar. Loulan Slash wouldn’t feel depressed enough to cough up blood. In that moment, Loulan Slash suddenly had an epiphany. It was no wonder Tiny Herb hated Blue Rain so much after getting robbed of their Champion title. Huang Shaotian’s one-shot-kill style may be very exciting for the onlookers, but to the people at the scene, it was so very painful!

Now, Loulan Slash was a spectator. Even though from his feelings, he hoped that Ye Xiu would win, deep down, Loulan Slash also wished to see Huang Shaotian create such a situation again.

Unconsciously, Loulan Slash had already become enamored with the thrill of the defining strike. He even imagined himself being a similar type of player. This would become the focus of his daydreaming for a long time.

However, Huang Shaotian being stuck in the air the entire time was a bit disappointing, up until the unexpected Falling Phoenix Slash broke Lord Grim’s combo. Loulan Slash immediately became excited and blurted out praise for it. Luckily, he had only said pro player. If he had called out Huang Shaotian’s name directly, he would definitely be looked down on and despised as a traitor by his friends.

Falling Phoenix Slash: The blade rises, the phoenix falls.

Huang Shaotian wasn’t just looking to escape, but also a strong comeback.

“Upward Slash!”

Huang Shaotian yelled as he followed up with an Upward Slash. Lord Grim was launched into midair.

However, Huang Shaotian didn’t rely on the opponent being airborne. Combos didn’t required the subject to be in the air. Being airborne just made it harder for the opponent to break free. An unspecialized character like Lord Grim had a wealth of skills to break free from the combo. For Huang Shaotian, being airborne wasn’t important. What was important was his ability to keep hitting Ye Xiu.

“Triple Slash!!”

Huang Shaotian yelled and used Triple Slash, which was a typical movement option used by Blade Masters to quickly get away or to shrink the distance between an opponent. With Huang Shaotian’s skillful manipulation, Troubling Rain dance around Lord Grim in a triangle. The three slashes all landed on Lord Grim.

“Lunge!”

“Moonlight Slash!”

“Upward Slash!”

“Formless Phantom Blade!”

“Headwind Strike!”

Huang Shaotian yelled out skill names out constantly. The skills he named didn’t match the ones he was using. Huang Shaotian just went on randomly. If the audience could hear him, they would even hear him chanting the casts for mage skills.

At the same time, Huang Shaotian stopped sending messages.

He was very good at multitasking, but facing this powerful opponent, he finally decided to dedicate all his hand speed onto performing.

This was a rare chance that he had fought hard for. He needed to focus to deal as much damage as possible to Lord Grim. If he failed and his opponent found another opportunity to lash back, he would probably never find another lucky chance to reverse the situation.

“Die Die Die Die Die!!!”

Huang Shaotian roared, attacking more ruthlessly than before. His performance, on the other hand, was more cautious than before as well. He needed to try his best to ensure 100% perfection on his performance. It was the only way to ensure Ye Qiu wouldn’t have a chance to overturn the situation.

The blade danced furiously and continuously. In this nonstop wave of attacks, there were other skills that did not belong to the Blade Master. Regular attacks, Spellblade, Ghostblade, and Berserker were all in the mix. These class were all under the general class of Swordman, so their Level 20 and under skills could be learned freely. How one chooses from these skills is completely based the person’s preference. Huang Shaotian had long stopped struggling over which skill to learn and which skill he needed to level up. He had grasped his character’s skill combination a long time ago. He could whip out round after round of combos instinctively. All he needed to do in that moment was to focus, to be fast and steady.

Huang Shaotian knew his opponent did not have the same problem as he did. Ye Qiu’s mind wouldn’t be a slow like how he struggled with the unfamiliarity of the Unspecialized class. Was there anything in Glory that God Ye Qiu, Glory’s textbook, would not know? Among all the combos of Blade Master, there was nothing that was a secret to him. Some of the combos were even created by him.

Huang Shaotian’s performance was undoubtedly incredible. After the unspecialized’s combos, he followed with an excellent combo of his own. The onlooking pro players were surprised by the excellence of Huang Shaotian’s performance and applauded him. However, the one they really wanted to see was Huang Shaotian’s opponent. They wanted to know if unspecialized had ways to forcefully end Huang Shaotian’s combos. If Lord Grim actually died in one breath under Troubling Rain’s constant assault, they would be really disappointed. They would rather watch Troubling Rain die under the constant combos than Lord Grim. At least, they could see more of an unspecialized’s combo that way.

“F*ck!” Huang Shaotian cursed.

He was unable to continue his perfection to the end. He missed.

That tiny mistake would not even be considered as a mistake in front of a regular opponent, but in front of another God…..

Huang Shaotian did not waste time on daydreams. He already started to prepare for Ye Qiu’s revenge. Painfully, facing this Unspecialized, Huang Shaotian had no idea what strange skill to expect.

Despite the numerous thoughts, not even half a second had passed since his mistake.

Thousand Chance Umbrella opened unexpectedly and shot towards Troubling Rain.

“You b*tch!!!” Huang Shaotian was met with another “screensaver”.

“The same move won’t work on me twice!!!” Huang Shaotian yelled out while filling the public channel with the same message. At the same time, his character jumped back, trying to put some distance between himself and the Umbrella as fast as possible.

Despite the intensity of this moment, seeing Huang Shaotian’s messages, many could not help about complain,”What! Huang Shaotian! Could you be a Knight of the Zodiac?!!!!”

“Leo’s Knight of the Zodiac!!!” There were some who knew Huang Shaotian’s astrological sign.

“Lightning Bolt destroy him!!!” Some pro players, who knew of the Knights of the Zodiacs well, shouted enthusiastically.

In the end, Huang Shaotian did not use Leo’s Lightning Bolt. He chose to use the Blade Master level 70 skill: Formless Phantom Blade.

“D*mn! You’re seeking your own death!!!” The pro players cried out in shock.

Without any set up, Huang Shaotian just threw out a Formless Phantom Blade. If Huang Shaotian wasn’t asking for his own demise, then what could he possibly be doing?

“Wait! Ye Xiu is holding a shield, he can’t see it now!” Someone called out as if he discovered a new world.

“He can’t see it, but he can hear it!”

“Hm?”

In this instant, everyone recalled the difference. This was a regular Arena. Originally, Huang Shaotian would be chattering ceaselessly, but he switched to sending messages non-stop half way through the match.

Based on the fact that he voluntarily retaliated, one could see that Huang Shaotian didn’t switch to messages because he was bored, but rather because he figured that the opponent could not hear him.

In conclusion, facing Huang Shaotian’s irritating chatter, Ye Qiu had abandoned his headphones.

His view was currently covered by the umbrella shield, and without a headphone, there was no way for him to know that Huang Shaotian was using a Formless Phantom Blade so shamelessly.

All sorts of thoughts were spinning around in their hearts, but all of this happened in a split second.

While everyone believed that Ye Qiu did not know about Formless Phantom Blade, a silhouette flashed behind Troubling Rain.

Because Lord Grim stayed where he was, still holding an opened umbrella, Huang Shaotian unleashed a beautiful Formless Phantom Blade, ready to crush Lord Grim into nothing.

Everyone sent their prayers in silence and sent emojis of a can’t bear to witness face.

At the same time, Huang Shaotian didn’t realize the impending disaster until he destroyed the elusive figure in front of him with a strike.

Last time, all the combos came in the air.

This time, all the combination of skills came from the back.

“F*ck f*ck f*ck!!! You can hear me!!!” Huang Shaotian roared, trying to shatter Ye Qiu’s eardrums. He also typed this comment into the public chat channel to show how despicable Ye Qiu was.

“Tsk tsk tsk.” The audience signed. This was the classic example of being tricked by one’s own wisdom. Everyone lamented over Huang Shaotian’s demise while admiring Ye Qiu’s persistence. Ye Qiu not only survived under Huang Shaotian’s sound attacks against all odds, he also tricked Huang Shaotian into think that he couldn’t hear anything.

At that time, Loulan Slash felt he needed to speak up to clarify God Ye Qiu’s circumstances.

“He really can’t hear anything. “ Loulan Slash.

“Before he went down the ring, he asked me to mute it.” Loulan Slash was the admin of the room

“Oh….” People murmured in realization.

In the ring, Huang Shaotian, of course, could see the messages posted in the public channel.

“Cheater! You have to tell the participant before you change the rules!!!” Huang Shaotian watched his Troubling Rain fell in front of Lord Grim as he cried out internally. He finally adjusted his view just now. Back attacks were just as troublesome as aerial ones. This time, Huang Shaotian did not last long enough to see another chance to reverse the tide.

“Hm? Were you talking the whole time?” Ye Xiu, who just won, asked in the channel.

In disbelief, no one answered his question.

Chapter 449 – Each With Their Own Thoughts

For a guess at whether or not he could hear or not would decide the match made the crowd somewhat speechless because this was something that would never happen in an official match. Just like Huang Shaotian’s blabbering, in an official match, the rules would be clearly shown.

However, this wasn’t an official match. And against Huang Shaotian, muting voice communication was something that would certainly be supported by the crowd. It was just that Huang Shaotian wasn’t notified of this…….

“Again! Again!!!”

Just when everyone was thinking, Huang Shaotian had already stood back up, shouting for another match.

“F*ck, you’re still going? Go stand in line!”

“Yeah! You should be at the back of the line!!”

“My turn! My turn!!”

A bunch of pro players were eager to give it a try. Many curious pro players couldn’t be satisfied with just watching. Quite a few wanted to personally experience an unspecialized. Soon afterwards, a huge quarrel erupted outside of the ring on who should go up first, but the one thing they all agreed on was that Huang Shaotian had already fought once, so he wasn’t allowed to fight again.

“Roll a dice! Roll a dice! Whoever gets the biggest number wins!” Someone suggested.

“Your mother. There’s over a hundred people. How are we supposed to get them all?” Another objected.

In the beginning, there had only been around fifty people, but later, another group of people arrived. There were even a few strangers mixed in, but no one paid them any heed.

“What do you mean again!!” Lord Grim suddenly typed.

“How could give you guys opportunities to see through me? Ha ha ha ha!”

“Class is over! Bye everyone!”

“God!!”

“F*ck!!”

“!!”

All sorts of curses were used. If this were an official match, they would all be penalized for saying these types of words. But today, they were only in the in-game Arena, so anything went. Everyone took this chance to vent their anger.

But the God did what he said. He ignored everyone’s shouts and directly left the ring. Some even tried to send a request to fight, but Ye Xiu ignored them all and even left the room. There was nothing they could do. If he said he didn’t want to, then they couldn’t force him to.

Loulan Slash’s group wanted to watch some more too, but if God Ye Qiu had decided to leave, then they naturally couldn’t object. They also wanted to fight with some of the people in the crowd, but now even a blind person could tell why they had all come here. If they went up and asked to fight them, then they would probably receive the same words God Ye Qiu used to reject them.

They were just about to leave, when Loulan Slash suddenly received a friend invite. He opened it and looked. The name on it gave him a huge shock: Vaccaria!

Champion Team Tiny Herb’s captain, Wang Jiexi’s Vaccaria.

Loulan Slash immediately accepted and wondered whether he was dreaming or not.

“Hi.” After accepting the friend request, Vaccaria immediately messaged him.

“Hi God.” Loulan Slash replied. If this was before, when he had been a famous money warrior, he wouldn’t have taken pro players very seriously. But ever since he had gotten into contact with Ye Xiu, he had realized that he had been too arrogant. Huang Shaotian’s match with him gave him another unforgettable lesson. Towards God level players, he didn’t dare disrespect them. And the person talking with him was someone who had won two Championship titles in the last three years. His impressive achievements had already won him success and recognition.

Someone like Zhou Zekai might be more popular, but he hadn’t won any prizes yet, so he still lacked in influence.

“Switch rooms and compare notes?” Wang Jiexi replied.

Loulan Slash was overwhelmed by favor from his senior and immediately notified his group. When the rest heard this, they all felt quite excited. After being crushed by Huang Shaotian, they all felt like they had been left ignored in a corner. A God had actually noticed them?

At the same time, Loulan Slash told what had happened to Ye Xiu, asking if Ye Xiu wanted to come too.

“Oh? He’s inviting you guys, so you guys go! I won’t be going.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay, we’ll be going then!” Loulan Slash replied to Ye Xiu. He had already given his reply to Wang Jiexi long ago. Wang Jiexi had already created the room. After the reply came, Loulan Slash called his friends to go over.

As for Ye Xiu, he had already left the room and the Arena, so the Arena invites naturally wouldn’t work anymore.

Huang Shaotian refused to give up. He tried adding Lord Grim as a friend, but the other side closed it without even looking at it. Ye Xiu had received too many friend requests when he stepped into the Heavenly Domain and had already closed off the function.

Ye Xiu couldn’t be contacted in-game, so Huang Shaotian could only spam him in QQ. He knew that Ye Xiu was online, so he didn’t spam it in the group chat. He sent him a private message and spammed him repeatedly. He finally received a reply: “I’m going to block you!”

The instant the other side went online on QQ, Huang Shaotian went into a fury. QQ trembled. He barraged Ye Xiu with video chat requests, voice chat requests, and all sorts of pictures to show his unwavering determination, until Ye XIu finally replied: “So noisy. I’m logging off.’

Afterwards, his image went gray. Huang Shaotian didn’t believe him and continued bothering him for another five minutes without any response, until he finally gave up.

He switched back to the group chat, which was bustling with noise. It was late at night, yet no one had gone to sleep. They were all discussing the unspecialized problem. Some had only just learned of it and hastily asked around on information. They all wanted a recording to watch.

Many of them had obviously recorded it. A few enthusiastic players shared it with everyone. Those who hadn’t seen it immediately downloaded it.

As the character who lost in the video, Huang Shaotian was naturally very sad. But even so, he had also recorded it. He opened it up and began slowly studying it.

“What did you think of it?” On QQ, his team captain Yu Wenzhou messaged him.

“Very difficult to deal with.” Huang Shaotian replied, “The Fixed Field covered up some of his problems though.”

“Nothing could be done about that. His level is too low. If you two had played in a normal match, his Dragon Tooth’s Stun wouldn’t even be able to break past your equipment’s Stun resistance.” Yu Wenzhou replied.

“Yeah, but his combos really are complicated. It’s going to take a lot of effort to study them.” Huang Shaotian said.

“When all is said and done, matches are never decided by a single person.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“But I have a premonition that when he returns, he’ll definitely be a huge problem.” Huang Shaotian said.

“He always was…….” Yu Wenzhou said.

“What a pity. It isn’t possible to find another unspecialized like him.” Huang Shaotian was quite bitter because he hadn’t achieved his goal.

“What do you think of those other people?” Yu Wenzhou asked. He was obviously talking about Loulan Slash’s group.

“Their skill is okay, but they’re too green. They’re a quota team level.” Huang Shaotian replied. A quota team level meant that they were around the same level as the last place teams struggling to stay in the Alliance. In the first half of the season, Team Excellent Era had perished into the quota team realm, making many drop their glasses in surprise.

“Don’t come to a conclusion too early. They still have half a year before they enter the Pro Alliance.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Yeah……. If they get Ye Qiu, then it’ll be a huge help to them.” Huang Shaotian said.

“Don’t forget that Thunderclap without Xiao Shiqin is only at a quota team level.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“But Ye Qiu will only be able to enter midway into the season. He can’t come out in the first half.” Huang Shaotian said.

“That’s why this team will only be able to truly show their strength in season ten.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“What level will Ye Qiu be at then…….” Huang Shaotian muttered.

“That’s hard to say Will a year of retirement make his skills turn rusty or will he return greater than before after a hard earned rest?” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Only the demons know what schemes he’s plotting…….” Huang Shaotian cursed.

Club Tyranny.

The fascinating unspecialized character wasn’t able to move Zhang Xinjie’s unshakeable sleep schedule. Huang Shaotian had only just received the second fight, when he fell asleep on time. However, in Tyranny, Han Wenqing and he weren’t the only two watching. At this moment, Han Wenqing was quietly watching the replay and hadn’t looked for any other team’s players to discuss things with. He hadn’t participated in the pro player group chat’s discussion either.

On his screen played the part where Troubling Rain was being comboed by Lord Grim. Han Wenqing paid close attention to the screen, but his expression didn’t seem too focused. But the moment Troubling Rain turned the situation around with a Rising Phoenix Slash, he immediately rewinded the replay back to where Lord Grim had began the combo with a Dragon Tooth to Sky Strike. He switched perspectives and continued to watch.

Han Wenqing watched again and again. Suddenly, the light in his eyes suddenly blazed. After nodding his head slightly, he closed the recording, shut off the computer, got up, closed the lights, and went to bed.

At Club Excellent Era, Sun Xiang was also watching the recording. He didn’t participate in the group discussion either. Just like Han Wenqing, he also watched again and again, but he watched the entire match. From start to finish, he only watched from one perspective, Huang Shaotian’s. As he quietly watched, his mouth seemed to be muttering something…….

All of the pro players who hadn’t slept were doing the same thing: watching the recording. They might be discussing in a group with everyone or they might be discussing with their own team members in private. Every team, every player was trying to find something from this recording.

Ye Xiu didn’t have one. He hadn’t recorded it. After leaving the match and Arena, he went to level as if nothing had happened.

This made Chen Guo very unsatisfied.

Beating Huang Shaotian had made her blood boil. She had been excitedly waiting for Ye Xiu to challenge every one of the pro players in the crowd and defeat them all. Even though that was a bit of a stretch, but the more of a stretch it was, the more exciting, no?

But after beating Huang Shaotian, Ye Xiu just left. Loulan Slash’s group even went to fight Wang Jiexi, but he wouldn’t even go to that.

“Go! Go! Why not go!” Chen Guo said.

“Because I don’t intend on letting these people get a deeper understanding of me.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 450 – Diligence

Chen Guo didn’t have much of a temper towards Ye Xiu. Seeing that he was just leveling, she wasn’t going to watch that. Chen Guo had remembered the match between Loulan Slash’s group and Wang Jiexi though.

“Why do you think Wang Jiexi looked for them? Could he have seen some talent in them and was looking to pull someone in?” Chen Guo knew about Wang Jiexi wanting to rope in Tang Rou, so she thought of this reasoning.

“No idea!”

“I’ll go investigate.” Chen Guo said.

“If you want to watch the show, just say it. Why make an excuse…….” Ye Xiu disdained.

Chen Guo waved her fist at Ye Xi u and then went to ask Loulan Slash. Chen Guo hadn’t thought much of the money warrior, but after seeing the fight between Loulan Slash and Huang Shaotian, she felt a bit touched and her views changed greatly. It was true that with money, a character could skip through many obstacles, particularly in the equipment area, but she couldn’t ignore his efforts.

Even though Loulan Slash had been a bit distracted fighting against Huang Shaotian in the first half of the fight, later, he let everyone see his efforts. Chen Guo couldn’t help but feel upset at her previous judgement of him. She didn’t need to say it out loud though. Even if she felt regretful, as long as they got along better in the future, it would be fine.

Chen Guo thought like this, so she was also interested in the spar between Loulan Slash’s group and Wang Jiexi. After asking Loulan Slash, he immediately sent her their room number. Chen Guo ran over to take a look and saw that they were currently fighting. This time, because Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim wasn’t holding them back, they had switched to the normal mode. Vaccaria’s equipment as a God-level character gave him an absolute advantage, but at the same time, Loulan Slash wanted to see just how strong this equipment was.

After Chen Guo entered the room, she just happened to see Little Bei’s Battle Mage fall. She asked the rest of them what the situation was and found out that they had already finished their second round. The Elementalist Ocean Ahead had already lost a match.

It hadn’t been long, but they had already finished fighting two matches. It turned out that against Wang Jiexi, they had lost even more tragically than against Huang Shaotian. After all, not only was their opponent far more skilled than them, but their opponent’s character was much stronger too.

After Little Bei lost, Night Tides and Loulan Slash went up one after the other. Neither of them were able to bring about any opportunities before being killed by Wang Jiexi. Their remaining comrade, a Cleric, naturally wouldn’t fight in a duel. They were all feeling somewhat embarrassed after losing four times in a row. They wanted to fight again, but they felt bad to make a request that would waste the other side’s time.

Correct…… after facing a God’s true might, they felt that fighting against him was just a waste of time.

“Ha ha, they lost so miserably!” Ye Xiu floated by just when Chen Guo was feeling sorry for them. Chen Guo turned her head to look at Ye Xiu, who had already turned his head back to his screen. However, he had clearly seen the situation from Chen Guo’s screen.

“They’re not in the Fixed Field. Their characters are still far from Vaccaria!” Chen Guo had seen their equipment already. It was true that their equipment weren’t bad because they had the money, but they still couldn’t compare to pro player accounts. Pro player accounts not only had the best equipment available in the game, but more importantly, they had self-made equipment suited especially for them, especially for a legendary character like Vaccaria, who had Silver equipment from head to toe. This was not just a result of money. It was a result of the combination of money and cutting edge technology.

“Yeah, I’m sure they know that. I just don’t know if the’ve made any preparations.” Ye Xiu said.

“What do you mean?” Chen Guo asked.

“Did you forget? Loulan Slash had been very optimistic about their strength initially! They had never personally experienced the difference in skill and experience and didn’t know how big of a difference it was. However, the difference in equipment is something that can be directly observed. There’s no way they would have thought that they were skilled enough to make up for the clear difference in equipment, no? From their initial optimism, I think that they’ve made preparations for their equipment. The ones they’re wearing right now might not be the ones they’ll be using in the Pro Alliance.” Ye Xiu said.

“So you’re saying that they’ve already prepared Silver equipment?” Chen Guo said.

“Even if they don’t have any right now, they should have at least had thoughts of making up for the difference in equipment, right? If not, then I’ll really be quite speechless towards these arrogant children.” Ye Xiu said.

The match wasn’t over on that side yet. Wang Jiexi actually went another round with each of them. They didn’t do as badly as before, but the results didn’t change. Without the Fixed Field negating the equipment advantage, it would be difficult for them even if Wang Jiexi wanted to lose.

“What is Wang Jiexi thinking?” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

“I thought that was what you were investigating? Why are you asking me?” Ye Xiu asked back.

“I thought you understood these people! You tell me!” Chen Guo demanded.

“He’s probably just testing their strength, that’s all.” Ye Xiu said.

“Testing their strength?”

“They will be Tiny Herb’s opponents in the future. Wang Jiexi never underestimates any of his opponents. He’s looking to figure out Loulan Slash and his group’s skill level.” Ye Xiu said.

“What about now? Can he get a good understanding after two rounds?”

“He’s probably figured out their individual skill by now. As for their ability as a team, I don’t think he’d ask for them to fight him 5v1. He’ll most likely make an excuse like…… yes, let’s have a friendly match in the future or something.” Ye Xiu’s gaze drifted away.

“Ah!” Chen Guo cried out because when she looked back, she discovered that in the public chat, Wang Jiexi was currently discussing with Loulan Slash a time for them to have a friendly match.

“What a god!” Chen Guo looked back at Ye Xiu.

“Yeah, I’m a god, but it’s more like I have good eyes.” Ye Xiu said.

“What do you mean?” Chen Guo stared blankly.

“I saw what they were saying!” Ye Xiu pointed at the screen.

Chen Guo suddenly understood. He had simply looked at what Wang Jiexi was saying. No wonder he hesitated and suddenly shifted his gaze. Chen Guo tried hard not to curse out at him.

In the Arena, Loulan Slash happily agreed to the friendly match. Chen Guo couldn’t help but feel a bit worried though: “Does this count as being duped?”

“Duped? That’s a bit of a stretch. Loulan Slash might be getting probed out by Tiny Herb, but they can also get a taste of the Champion team’s strength. For them, this is a rare opportunity.” Ye Xiu said as he glanced at Chen Guo’s screen. After looking at their chat, he lamented: “Oh, they’ve scheduled it for after playoffs! Tsk tsk, Wang Jiexi ah, Wang Jiexi……”

“What’s wrong?”

“He clearly feels that they’re not any threat to them in the Pro Alliance right now, so he intentionally delayed it. He wants to see if they’ve improved during this time. You could say he’s putting some effort into this.” Ye Xiu said.

“This guy really is……” Chen Guo had seen Vaccaria a lot. But as for the player behind the character, she only occasionally saw Wang Jiexi from reports or interviews. Chen Guo wasn’t his fan either, so she didn’t understand him too well. From Ye Xiu, she was able to get a good understanding of the real Wang Jiexi. She wasn’t sure what to use to describe him.

Chen Guo felt a bit uncomfortable towards him, but she had to admit that he was diligent! He was very very diligent. He was just like Ye Xiu. The effort he put into Glory was something she couldn’t compare with.

After Wang Jiexi discussed matters with Loulan Slash, they left their contact details and then exited the Arena. Once Loulan Slash came out, he sent Ye Xiu a sad face emoji.

“I saw it all.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Hm?”

“From Chasing Haze’s computer.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, you two are together!” Loulan Slash said.

“Yeah.”

“We lost so miserably.” Loulan Slash cried.

“Your skill isn’t as good. Your character isn’t as good. You guys should have been ready for this type of result, no?” Ye Xiu replied.

“We did, but it still doesn’t feel good to lose!” Loulan Slash said.

“You’re going to be a pro player soon. You have to learn how to stand up quickly from defeat and learn from your losses.” Ye Xiu advised.

“That’s the theory, but it’s not that easy to actually put it into practice!” Loulan Slash continued to cry.

“You can do it!” Ye Xiu said.

“Yes! Definitely!” Loulan Slash sent a fighting emoji. After being crushed by Ye Xiu last time, he had received quite a bit of stimulation today.

Soon afterwards, the two went on to do their thing and didn’t talk anymore.

The next day, on all of the eSport platforms, from the Internet to print media, all of them had the same headline: Pro Players Surround Lord Grim, Begging for a Match???

The three question marks sparkled on the media outlets. The content talked about the huge crowd of pro players that had swarmed the Heavenly Domain and then entered the same room in the Arena. They weren’t there to compare notes with each other, but rather there for a single person. In recent times, his popularity in Glory has soared through the heavens. Carrying a transforming Silver weapon and using an unspecialized, which had died out many years ago, the mystery man —- Lord Grim!!!

“Pft!” Chen Guo was eating breakfast as she watched the next. She lost herself as she spat out her food in laughter at the description of “the mystery man”.

“Hey!” Ye Xiu protested.

“Sorry, sorry. Cough cough! It really is…… cough…….” Chen Guo choked.

Tang Rou was in a flurry. She handed Ye Xiu some napkins, while patting Chen Guo’s back.

Their reactions were only on a small scale. At the Clubs, as soon as the reports came out, the pro players were given a furious roar. Those who hadn’t woken up from that were directly flipped out from their nests, especially those whose names had been listed clearly in the reports.

“GOD D*MMIT! WHAT THE F*CK DID YOU GUYS DO!!!” The directors and managers from every team might not have spat out their breakfast, but they certainly forgot themselves in a fit of anger.

Chapter 451 – The Mystery Man

Club Excellent Era. The director hadn’t gathered every team member, but Sun Xiang and Liu Hao as well as the crowd members who were revealed couldn’t escape.

When they entered the meeting room, they saw how dark the director’s expression was. It looked as if it were dripping with malice. After they sat down, one of the team members asked in a meek voice: “What happened?” The director threw the newspaper he had picked up that morning at him.

Some of them had seen the news. Some of them hadn’t seen it yet. The person who had asked the question was called Guo Yang and was a part of Team Excellent Era’s main roster. He played a Qi Master named Qi Breaker. Yesterday night, he had been a part of the group chat and had followed along with everyone else to see the show. Today, his name had been revealed in the news, but he himself didn’t know what had happened. The director was absolutely furious and glared viciously at Guo Yang.

In the eSports newspaper, there were four pages besides the lead story with details, analysis, comments, and a whole bunch of screenshots. It was quite impressive that they had been able to write and print out everything that had happened just last night so quickly.

“What were all of you thinking? Our hated enemy isn’t popular enough right now, so you have to run over and give him advertisement? Am I right?” The director began shouting at them. Even though, he was only facing the few in front of him, he also cursed at the pro players from other Clubs who had been exposed as well.

At Excellent Era, there were four people who had went to watch the show.

Sun Xiang, Liu Hao, He Ming. They had went to watch because they cared a lot about the strength of Ye Qiu’s unspecialized. As for Guo Yang, he was there more as a cheerleader and now, he had attracted the director’s aggro. Who made him go in and act like he didn’t know what was going on?

As an old veteran in the pro scene, he had experienced the director’s shouting many times, especially this season. Their record was poor. Everyone had seen the director like this before. Only Sun Xiang hadn’t. In the past, when he was in Team Over the Clouds, he was considered a jewel. When he came over to Excellent Era, he sat as their ace player. It was his first time in the pro scene being yelled at like this. His expression immediately turned uglier.

“Cough.” Liu Hao cleared his throat as if he were about to say something, when someone knocked on the door. The director turned his head and roared “Enter.” An employee scurried in: “Director, there are reporters outside who want to interview a few players. What do we do?”

News stations which specially covered eSports often had reporters living in cities with Clubs. Yesterday night, they had been busy writing, so now they were here to conduct post-interviews in the morning.

The director had clearly expected this to happen. He waved his hands: “Have them wait a bit.”

“Okay.” The employee left. The director turned his head back and stared at Liu Hao: “What did you want to say?”

“I don’t think this is a random accident.” Liu Hao looked at the newspaper, “Even though we got a lot of attention when we showed up online, after entering the Arena, no one knew which room we had went into. Even if they bumped into it through trial and error, the room had a password. How could someone break in? Moreover, from this report, it couldn’t have been some random person who had chanced upon the room. The intruder had clearly come in with a goal. This was the work of someone’s scheme. We’ve all been used!”

“Who needs you to say something so obvious?” The director barked.

“We hadn’t thought of this at that time.” Liu Hao said helplessly.

“With things having come to this, there’s no use in talking about it.” The director said, “I looked at the news and it seems like Ye QIu’s identity hasn’t been revealed?”

“This…….” Liu Hao hesitated because there was no way he could remember every single detail from last night. Everyone at the scene knew that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, so there was no need for them to mention it when they talked amongst themselves. Did anyone expose Lord Grim’s identity in the chat? He didn’t think so. This may be why the news didn’t reveal Lord Grim’s identity and described him as a mystery man.

But even if he was a mystery man, people would definitely try to guess. As a result, these guesses would be the main topic for today. But it didn’t seem like the mystery man would be much a mystery. With the rumors of Ye Qiu planning on creating a team, most people would guess the mystery man was Ye Qiu.

The few people would question this would be because of one issue: if he were Ye Qiu, it hadn’t been long since he had retired, so why would he create such an uproar and announce that he would come back? Wasn’t he a bit too quick in regretting his retirement? These types of disbelievers also didn’t believe the rumors that Ye Qiu was planning on creating a team.

Speaking of this, the rumors of Ye Qiu’s return was only an inference made in the All Star Weekend, when a Battle Mage had come out and showed a Dragon Raises Its Head. It wasn’t 100% proof that person was Ye Qiu.

“I remember. I think when Huang Shaotian shouted for a match, he mentioned Ye Qiu’s name.” At this moment, Guo Yang suddenly said.

Liu Hao recalled and it seemed to be true. At that time, after Huang Shaotian defeated an opponent, Ye Qiu’s Lord Grim still hadn’t come down, so he shouted Ye Qiu’s name in the public chat. If this had truly been an intentional leak, then such a detail shouldn’t have been missed. Ye Qiu’s name would also create a huge uproar!

All of the Clubs knew that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, but why did no one announce it to the public? It was because they didn’t want to help him cement this identity. Right now, Ye Qiu was one of their competitors. By utilizing the popularity from his identity, a lot of things would become easier for him. This was why they hoped to see Ye Qiu just die away like a nameless soldier. Because he had never revealed himself to the public in the past, it wouldn’t be easy for him to prove his identity.

For Excellent Era, especially their guild Excellent Dynasty, they were extremely nervous of Ye Qiu’s identity being revealed. The revelation would certainly have a huge negative impact on Excellent Dynasty. The guild had old members that had been in the guild for more than five years and many of them were fans of Ye Qiu. If his identity really was revealed by an official and trusted source, it wouldn’t be possible for Excellent Dynasty to go against Ye Qiu. The other guilds even needed to help block this bullet. Otherwise, if Excellent Era didn’t care about their image and popularity and would rather discard everything to be criticized…….

This was why Excellent Era was so worried about this.

The other Clubs were also quite angry that their players would help advertise him and raise their enemy’s popularity.

Loulan Slash’s team had been quite popular from the start. Afterwards, their advertising had only attracted more and more eyes, making everyone look forward to them. They felt like they would be a strong team that would rock the Alliance. Now, Lord Grim had caused another huge sensation, proving their strength again……

Even though the headlines wrote that the pro players had attacked Lord Grim, Lord Grim was already bound with a team. Loulan Slash’s team would have Lord Grim as the team’s ace player and spokesperson.

If Lord Grim was so strong, didn’t that mean the team he was in would be strong too?

And how strong was Lord Grim? From the detailed report of the fight, it described how he defeated Huang Shaotian.

Huang Shaotian! Who was that? To beat him, even if it was in the Fixed Field, would mean he’s an absolutely amazing expert, no?

Who exactly is he? Who is he? Who is he?

The newspaper invited many famous Glory commentators, hosts, and other professionals to give their opinion. Eighty percent of them suspected that he was Ye Qiu. Professionals were professionals. All of them knew what type of fundamentals was necessary to play a class like an unspecialized. Ye Qiu was without a doubt the most suitable to play one.

To the Clubs, Ye Qiu being revealed would also make their popularity go up another level. They weren’t like Excellent Era who had so many worries. This was also one of the reasons Excellent Era’s director was so anxious. These Clubs would certainly be interviewed. If any one of them nodded their heads to the media, the guesses that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu would be 100% confirmed……

“Director…… should we contact the other Clubs and probe their stances, so we can make preparations?” Liu Hao was an expert at currying favor. He had thought of these issues and had come up with a suggestion. The so-called stances were pointing to the other Club’s stances towards how they would reply to the Lord Grim question.

Who Lord Grim is and why the pro players swarmed over to fight with him would certainly be questions that would be asked by the reporters.

Excellent Era’s director thought about this suggestion and was just about to grab the phone, when Wang Sheng from their public relations department suddenly spoke: “I don’t think there’s any need to do that.”

“If this was something that had been planned, then there’s no way they would miss the fact that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, no?” Wang Sheng continued, “In my opinion, revealing information step by step and escalating the speculation around Lord Grim would be a good tactic. They wouldn’t reveal everything all at once, but rather a bit at a time, revealing important details slowly. Lord Grim is Ye Qiu. We won’t say it, but it’ll be revealed sooner or later. If we say it, we can at least take the initiative, but if we wait for them to say it, we’ll have absolutely no control of the situation.”

When Wang Sheng said this, Chen Yehui began to grow anxious. No matter the case, he didn’t want Ye Qiu’s identity to be revealed. Not just in the future, but even now, if the guild players knew that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, their Excellent Dynasty would have a huge wave of deserters.

“I can’t agree with that. If Ye Qiu identity is revealed, the guild will go into chaos!!!” Chen Yehui hastily said.

“Ha ha, this will depend on how we word the statement. Don’t worry Chen, we’ll make sure to consider this when we do it.” Wang Sheng laughed. Their public relations department was responsible for their Club’s marketing. Guild related issues would always be put into consideration.

“Oh? What do you plan on saying?” The director asked. Even though the wording for the statement would be Wang Sheng’s responsibility, the director still needed to know the general picture.

Chapter 452 – Counterattack with the Truth

“D*mn! Excellent Era is too shameless!!!”

In the end, the newspaper reports didn’t cover all of the information. That evening, several more reports came out with more details from the numerous pro players interviewed that morning. The program couldn’t show every single conversation from each pro player. The spotlight would be on the Gods, of course.

With a single exception, as if they had agreed upon it, all of the guilds directly confessed that they had ran over to watch because they suspected that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu. However, none of them said it in a completely certain tone of voice.

“Probably? Playing an unspecialized requires knowledge and proficiency with every class. From what I saw from Lord Grim’s performance, Ye Qiu is without a doubt the number one suspect.” This was what Team Tiny Herb’s Wang Jiexi replied with.

“An unspecialized is a class that cannot be controlled by a single person. But to be able to control one to such a degree, I believe that Ye Qiu is certainly capable of doing so.” This was Team Wang Jiexi’s answer.

“Hm, probably Ye Qiu…… because…… he’s very strong…….” Samsara’s Zhou Zekai.

“At that time, all of the Gods were present. To be able to fight with me to that extent, by using a process of elimination, he would be Ye Qiu.” This was Huang Shaotian’s reply. He was the person who everyone wanted to interview. He was the one who directly fought with him!

“What about Zhang Jiale?” The reporters asked about a God, who had also retired.

“Zhang Jiale? I called him before. He said he wasn’t him.” Huang Shaotian said in a serious tone. He had clearly known that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu long before this, but right now, he looked as if he had only figured it out after fighting him.

“Then what are your thoughts on the match?” The reporter asked.

“I lost. But as a pro player, losing is a very common occurrence, even more so against an opponent like Ye Qiu. More importantly, this match let me see all sorts of different things. Those who haven’t played the game since the beginning probably don’t even know that there is such a thing as an unspecialized playstyle, yet now one appears in front of us. I don’t know if you guys saw the match recording carefully or not. Ah! That’s right! Do you guys have a recording of it? If you want one, I have one. I can go get one for you guys real quick, if you want……” Huang Shaotian spoke frankly with the interviewers.

They didn’t even need to try and dig deeper and they already had so much content to work with, perhaps even too much content. They didn’t know if the space given to them was enough to write it all down. It seemed like they would need to pick out the important words from all of the other excess.

The reporters were always happy to interview Huang Shaotian.

Apart from Huang Shaotian, the other people they needed to interview was of course, Excellent Era.

For Excellent Era, Ye Qiu would always be a topic that would never go away. As long as they were in the Glory scene, Ye Qiu and Excellent Era would always be connected with each other.

Every player was asked why they went to watch the match. Sun Xiang, Liu Hao, and the others who watched it said the same as everyone else. They expressed their suspicions that he was Ye Qiu, which was why they had went over to look.

Afterwards, when they got to the special relationship between Ye Qiu and Excellent Era, Wang Sheng gave a statement.

First, he said how Ye Qiu had still wanted to develop in the Glory scene and how he was very perplexed that Ye Qiu would choose to retire.

Next, he also talked about Lord Grim’s identity as Ye Qiu and how he couldn’t understand some of his actions in the tenth server, especially the conflicts with Guild Excellent Dynasty.

After that, he mentioned Lord Grim’s recent addition to Loulan Slash’s Guild Heavenly Justice. Wang Sheng expressed that he respected any choice Ye Qiu would make and gave him his blessings. However, the Glory Alliance was still a competition, after all. Even though Excellent Era and Ye Qiu would always be friends forever, whether they were in the professional scene or the game, everyone should have a professional attitude. Lastly, he gave Excellent Era and Ye Qiu his best wishes.

“Shameless! Too shameless!!!”

Excellent Era’s spokesperson gave his statement. The eSports channel broadcasted this segment. Chen Guo, who was watching while eating dinner, slammed the table and shouted. Ye Xiu, who had been sprayed all over with food in the morning, immediately took up his guard. He grabbed his bowl and ran far away from her.

“I can’t believe he had the nerve to say that.” Chen Guo was furious at Wang Sheng.

Hiding far away, Ye Xiu took up his bowl and filled his mouth with food: “This is nothing. You really haven’t seen the real world have you.”

“How can you be so calm!” Chen Guo didn’t understand.

“In terms of his responsibilities, I felt like he did quite a beautiful job.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ptui.”

“If you can’t even bear this, you’ll be coughing blood in the future.” Ye Xiu said.

“Hmph, I won’t be so shameless!” Chen Guo said.

“You won’t. But what about your opponents? When the time comes, they’ll spread all sorts of rumors, mixing up truth and lies. And when the reporters look for you to ask questions, you’ll just curse at them and call them shameless?” Ye Xiu said.

“Then what should I do?” Chen Guo said.

“Beat them up in the matches!” Tang Rou interrupted in a determined voice. Chen Guo looked over, a bit surprised. She immediately realized that Tang Rou wasn’t happy about the interview either. She just hadn’t slammed the table like her.

“Mm, counterattack with the truth. No matter how powerful they are, they can’t beat that.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then how are you going to use truth to counterattack this time?” Chen Guo asked.

“By eating dinner peacefully here.” Ye XIu said.

“What type of counterattack is that!” Chen Guo frowned.

“There’s still a long way to go. We’ve only just started.” Ye Xiu said dully.

That night, the interview created a huge uproar.

In these interviews, Loulan Slash’s team may have been mentioned, but only a relatively small amount. Many had already guessed that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu in the morning news, but now the entire pro scene had admitted it. Even though the pros said this and that, they all had the same meaning: he was Ye Qiu, no doubt about it. However, even if you didn’t believe the pros, it was too difficult to actually ask Ye Qiu because everyone knew that Ye Qiu never accepted interviews.

The reports were still busy, hoping to dig even deeper. They wanted to find some way to contact people who were close to Ye Qiu like Su Mucheng. They tried contacting Loulan Slash…… the interviewing wasn’t over yet.

As for the Glory community, the discussions going on amongst them were growing larger and larger.

All of these discussions made Chen Guo quite depressed.

Wang Sheng’s statement expressing how he couldn’t understand Ye Qiu’s actions, how he was perplexed, and then his blessings, made Excellent Era fans who didn’t know the truth very unhappy with Ye Qiu.

After being deceived by Wang Sheng’s statement, they couldn’t that Ye Qiu would betray Excellent Era like that. Their cherished memories of Ye Qiu all became doubts towards him.

These feelings had begun being planted ever since rumors that Ye Qiu was planning to create his own team sprouted. And now, Ye Qiu had ran over to Loulan Slash, who was famous in the game for having lots of money. The players couldn’t help but suspect that Ye Qiu had left for money. At this moment, the discussions online were filled with criticism and hatred for Ye Qiu.

Chen Guo knew the truth and felt angry and sorry for Ye Xiu. She looked at these alone and didn’t call over Ye Xiu to look, up until she couldn’t take it anymore……

She turned around and peeked at Ye Xiu’s screen. To her surprise, he wasn’t playing the game, but rather skimming over these discussions. Chen Guo quietly went over and stole a glance at Ye Xiu’s expression. He looked very calm and relaxed.

“You aren’t going to play?” Chen Guo asked.

“Now? It’s not a good time. Too much commotion. I should avoid making any appearances for now.” Ye Xiu said.

“Avoid for how long?” Chen Guo was depressed. Now that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, Lord Grim would be like Troubling Rain and have crowds of people gathering wherever he went. In addition, with so many angry players, Chen Guo suddenly felt extremely uneasy.

“It won’t be very long.” Ye Xiu grinned.

“What are you planning! Tell me!” Chen Guo could see that Ye Xiu definitely had some sort of plan up his sleeve.

“You’ll know soon!” Ye Xiu said.

“When is soon?” Chen Guo asked.

“Look at the news!” Ye Xiu said.

“News? What news is there going to be at this time?” Chen Guo didn’t understand.

“It’ll be there.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo went over to browse the Internet, but didn’t see anything after checking several big sites.

“Where?” Chen Guo yelled, just as she refreshed again. A new pieces of news really had come out.

Team Heavenly Swords had officially been announced!

“Team Heavenly Swords?” Chen Guo stared blankly. Even though Loulan Slash had already told them about his team, he hadn’t said what his team name was. Heavenly Swords was undoubtedly the team Loulan Slash was planning on creating.

Chen Guo immediately clicked on the news article. With everything all written down already, the news conference for it must have ended a while ago. The spokesperson for Heavenly Swords had stated that their application had taken two days to pass, which was why they had only conducted a news conference now. At the news conference, they also officially announced that their team name would be Heavenly Swords.

Apart from this, another huge announcement had come from Team Heavenly Sword’s spokesperson. The announcement made clear that Team Heavenly Swords had not recruited the former captain of Excellent Era, Ye Qiu.

“This…… this……” Chen Guo suddenly felt dizzy as she stared at the headline.

“See, this is the truth.” Ye Xiu had seen the news too. He stood up and looked at Chen Go with a smile on his face: “That’s not a bad counterattack, right?”

Chapter 453 – Unable to Speak

“You guys…… had it all planned beforehand?” Chen Guo finally understood. Ye Xiu didn’t need to explain anything to her.

It was true that Lord Grim had joined Guild Heavenly Justice, but it had never been said that Lord Grim would join the team. Everyone had only thought that.

Now that Team Heavenly Swords made everything clear, Ye Qiu was in a great spot. With this sudden turn of events, the players would think that they had made a mistake. They might even think that Lord Grim wasn’t Ye Qiu.

“Pretty much. I was really only there as a guest performer to help Loulan Slash publicize his team.” Ye Xiu said.

“Who guest performs like you? The amount of attention you got was even more than their team!” Chen Guo said.

“That’s what happens when you borrow someone else. It’s how you get everyone’s attention!” Ye Xiu said. His QQ made a noise. Loulan Slash saw that he wasn’t in-game, so he went to see if Ye Xiu was on QQ.

“Nice!” Ye Xiu replied: “That was a great press conference!”

“Ha ha ha, too splendid. When those reporters heard that we were going to open a press conference, they immediately gathered there. We prepared the answers to questions relating to you a long time ago. The moment those reporters heard the spokesman say that Ye Qiu definitely wasn’t joining Team Heavenly Swords, you should have seen the expression on their faces! It was amazing!” Loulan Slash said and sent a few pictures of the dumbstruck expressions.

“They really are amazing.” Ye Xiu appreciated them.

“Ha ha ha.” Loulan Slash was very happy. Their plan had gone perfectly. There wasn’t much else to talk about after saying that. It was clear that the reporters were mainly for that one question. First, they asked a few questions regarding the team out of courtesy and then immediately switched to inquiring about Lord Grim.

The spokesperson repeated his statement again and for the questions asking about Lord Grim, he simply replied saying his weapon was a secret and couldn’t be revealed to the public.

“Why did Loulan Slash cooperate with you?” Chen Guo wondered.

“I helped publicize his team. Why wouldn’t he cooperate with me?” Ye Xiu said.

“But if he used your identity as Ye Qiu, he could have gotten even more attention. He could have also pulled in a whole bunch of your fans, no?” Chen Guo’s reasoning was also logical. Even though most people had been angry at Ye Qiu after the previous reports, there were also quite a few who defended Ye Qiu. These few were clearly loyal fans of Ye Qiu and supported their idol unconditionally.

“However, I really wasn’t going to join them. That’s the truth. It would have been seen through sooner or later.” Ye Xiu said.

“But with the way they did things, they’re also just making everything unnecessarily complicated. Lord Grim is you. That’ll be revealed sooner or later too. Doing it this way won’t win much of a favorable impression either, no?” Chen Guo said.

“It’s different. The way they did things is simply a trick to hype up everyone. There will be many chances in the future to slowly dissolve the situation. But if they directly said that I had joined their Team Heavenly Swords, then they would be lying. Once their lie came out, they would provoke a lot of hate from the players and it wouldn’t be easy to dissolve the situation. Loulan Slash wants to be relevant in the Alliance for a long time, so he doesn’t want that type of stain.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh…….” Chen Guo acted like she understood, even though she didn’t. Today, she hadn’t done any fighting in the game, but the several waves of news, made her emotions go up and down all day. It was even more of a thrill than fighting. Chen Guo was now convinced that the competition in the pro scene wasn’t just as simple as characters fighting in matches.

“Are you still going to play today?” Chen Guo asked.

“It’s better not to for now! I’ll be taking a look at the situation after the announcement.” Ye Xiu said. After the Spring Festival, Ye Xiu’s work and rest schedule had been slowly changing to a normal person’s. Before, he had to stay up all night because he had to take up the night shift. But now he only had to focus on the game, it didn’t matter whether he played during the daytime or during the nighttime. With Chen Guo’s frequent shouts, he would probably be heading towards a healthier schedule.

The newly released statement naturally lifted another huge wave.

The thoughts of the players were about the same as Chen Guo’s. All of the news being released today made it so their hearts couldn’t take it anymore.

They had just thought that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, when Team Heavenly Swords clearly said that they hadn’t roped in Ye Qiu.

Just like Chen Guo thought, the players immediately felt that Lord Grim actually wasn’t Ye Qiu.

If Lord Grim wasn’t Ye Qiu, then Ye Qiu’s name didn’t need to be brought into the discussion. As a result, Lord Grim once again became a “mystery man”. Who exactly was he? Everyone began guessing again. This Lord Grim beat Huang Shaotian. He had been acknowledged by the Gods, who had unanimously believed that it was likely that he was Ye Qiu. But he wasn’t actually Ye Qiu. There were only so many Gods in the scene. From the looks of it, it was actually his first time stepping into the pro scene. Was he some sort of immortal that had just come out of closed door training?

When the Clubs saw the reports that night, they were all dumbstruck.

These Clubs were just like the players and immediately felt like Lord Grim wasn’t Ye Qiu. They were suddenly very upset. If he wasn’t Ye Qiu, then why didn’t they try and rope him in? Who told them that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu? Had the pro players made a mistake? After all, no one had personally witnessed Ye Qiu controlling Lord Grim.

Some were completely certain though. For example, Huang Shaotian, Liu Hao, Han Wenqing, Wang Jiexi. All of them had talked with Lord Grim and Ye Qiu directly and were 100% sure about this point. They were having a bit of trouble understanding after seeing Team Heavenly Sword’s press conference.

“I can’t believe he has the balls to lie like that!” Huang Shaotian was dumbstruck and was about to look for Ye Xiu to ask.

Yu Wenzhou quietly thought for a bit before saying: “Maybe it’s not a lie.”

“How could it not be! Lord Grim is obviously Ye Qiu. Hm? Wait a sec…….” Huang Shaotian looked more carefully at the statement and then immediately understood.

“See! Heavenly Sword’s people never said that Lord Grim isn’t Ye Qiu.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“You’re right!” Huang Shaotian recalled Team Heavenly Sword’s marketing from the beginning to end. From the very start, when the news came out that Lord Grim had joined Heavenly Justice, they had never put Lord Grim and Ye Qiu together.

“What a beautiful plan to create hype!” Yu Wenzhou said.

“If it’s just for hype, wouldn’t it be better to reveal Ye Qiu’s identity?” Huang Shaotian said.

“Didn’t you hear the official statement? Ye Qiu isn’t joining their Team Heavenly Sword.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Oh…….”

“The team and the guild in the game are two different things.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“How crafty.” Huang Shaotian said.

“Unless you’re absolutely sure that Lord Grim is Ye Qiu like us, I doubt many will be able to see through the scheme.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“But we can’t prove anything either.” Huang Shaotian said.

“We don’t need any proof.” Yu Wenzhou said, “The people who are having it the most difficult right now is probably Excellent Era. It was lucky they made that statement this afternoon.”

“Ha ha ha, it’ll be a bit difficult, but they didn’t lose anything. They made it clear that even if Lord Grim is Ye Qiu, they would still have a professional attitude, which pretty much means that they regard him first as a competitor and opponent. They will do what they need to do. Even if their opponent isn’t Ye Qiu, they can still do what they like. Even if it’d made clear in the future, it doesn’t matter, no?” Huang Shaotian said.

“That’s certainly true, but their goal was to create an unfavorable public opinion of Ye Qiu. This statement effectively neutralized this.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“A pity. They probably can’t prove that Lord Grim is Ye Qiu either.” Huang Shaotian said.

Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian had already analyzed Excellent Era’s situation well. On the other hand, Excellent Era themselves didn’t react as quickly as the two of them.

They had confirmed that Lord Grim is Ye Qiu. After seeing the news, they were extremely angry at the scheme set up by Team Heavenly Sword and Ye Qiu and had completely forgotten about their statement that afternoon.

After a lot of yelling, Wang Sheng was able to clearly see the word game being played around in these statements.

However, just like Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian predicted, there was nothing they could do. They couldn’t prove that Lord Grim is Ye Qiu!

After thinking about it for a bit, exposing their opponent’s plot and proving that Lord Grim is Ye Qiu wouldn’t really benefit them in any way. Team Heavenly Sword had attracted a huge amount of attention from this. If they jumped out and struck back during this hype, they wouldn’t interrupt it, but instead help them even more.

Even though Excellent Era could attract a lot of eyes this way too, but Excellent Era was an old established team. If they were going to hype things up, they would have to fight with someone of equal status as them. Picking a fight against a new team would make them drop in status. The other side would actually pull themselves up using Excellent Era’s drop instead. If Excellent Era wasn’t even able to see this, then there was no way they would have been able to stay in the Alliance for so many years.

In the end, Excellent Era could only grind their teeth and hold it in. Seeing the forums explode with guessed to this “mystery man” while not being able to speak the truth was truly quite painful.

“We can’t give them another opportunity to attract more attention. Picking a fight would be falling into their trap.” Wang Sheng said.

“Mm, but we can’t have them think we’re idiots. Make another statement, reinforcing our previous statement and that it still holds.” The director slapped the table.

Chapter 454 – To Make a Big Fuss Over Nothing

For this type of disturbance, each side had their own plans. They all had people within the circle, so they knew many inside things. However, Chen Guo wasn’t a part of the circle. This time, she got a taste of what it was like inside.

If this was in the past, she would have definitely jumped out and shouted her support for Ye Xiu. but now, she finally understood the background behind the dispute and the many schemes surrounding it. Fans would dispute to prove what they thought. Would the people being talked about actually care what they said? They might not.

Ye Xiu’s indifferent attitude made Chen Guo even feel as if it were a bit cold-hearted. She wondered how many pro players had this type of inner quality. However, Chen Guo did believe that slamming the table in anger because of this kind of small matter didn’t fit for someone within the circle. Chen Guo acknowledged that this type of ruthlessness and reasoning was needed, but she wasn’t sure if she would be able to learn it.

She hoped that there would be a day Excellent Era would be unmasked and hated how Excellent Era fans could completely change sides in a single night. Their false statement had struck a direct blow to Ye Xiu, but all Chen Guo could see from him was indifference.

Even the hype created from the collaboration between Loulan Slash and him seemed as if it had just been done out of convenience, while giving himself a path to retreat at the same time. Did he actually plan on using this type of disturbance to attack Excellent Era or someone else? No. Not at all.

In reality, those who thought that they had suffered a blow had really just been caught up in the storm. They thought they were the goal, when they actually weren’t.

All Ye Xiu did was take advantage of what he had to help Loulan Slash create some hype for his team.

“What about you? What did you gain from this?” Chen Guo asked.

“Me?” Ye Xiu said without taking any time to think, “Didn’t I already say this before? The more attention Loulan Slash’s guild gets and the more attention Lord Grim gets, the harder it is for the guilds to make any movements.”

Chen Guo suddenly felt dizzy: “So you’re saying, this was all just to continue leveling in peace?”

“Of course!” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

Chen Guo wanted to cry. This type of leveling environment was a given for a normal player. But for a God, why did it have to be so complicated? He led the entire Glory scene into a frenzy, forcing all 20 Clubs to make a move. Millions of players had crowded together discussing and arguing. The media platforms made several headlines in a row…….

Comrades! It was all just a big misunderstanding…….

The truth behind everything was that this God just wanted to level!

Chen Guo didn’t want to be the only person to know the truth. She wanted to share it with the world and wanted everyone to cry along with her.

“I’m going to bed……” Chen Guo swayed back and forth as she walked away.

“Go ahead! I’ll be going to sleep soon too.” Ye Xiu said as if nothing had happened.

Who cares about you!! Chen Guo repeatedly said to herself. At this moment, she suddenly felt that the Clubs were completely correct to hunt him down. He just wanted to level peacefully and in order to do that, he brought the world into chaos. What was this guy made of?

That night, Ye Xiu didn’t go online again. He browsed around the Internet and then went to bed.

The next morning, a few slower news platforms released some articles. Being a bit slow, they had more time to report everything in more detail. However, Chen Guo wasn’t interested in reading them. Once she thought of how much trouble this could bring to Happy Internet Cafe just for Ye Xiu to level, Chen Guo immediately felt weak.

“Are you going to level later you finish eating?” Chen Guo said. She stressed the word level with a bit of a mocking tone.

“Of course.” Ye Xiu spoke as if he hadn’t heard Chen Guo’s tone of voice.

“Will a crowd come to watch?” Chen Guo asked.

“Hard to say. Though if it’s just normal players, then I’m confident I can escape.” Ye Xiu said.

“I hope you succeed.” Chen Guo mocked.

“Thanks. You guys take your time.” Ye Xiu got up and went to the second floor to play.

“What’s wrong?” Tang Rou could hear that Chen Guo’s tone wasn’t right.

“Did you know? He……” Chen Guo said everything on her mind to share her pain and then cursed at him a whole bunch.

“Ha ha ha ha.” Tang Rou couldn’t stop laughing when she heard it, “I think he did pretty good!”

“What’s good?” Chen Guo said.

“Don’t you find it bold making such a big fuss over nothing?” Tang Rou said.

“You’ve been completely ruined by him.” Chen Guo shook her head in disappointment.

“He he.” Tang Rou chuckled. Chen Guo couldn’t find any sympathy from Tang Rou, so she stopped talking about it.

Chen Guo didn’t take it to heart. This wouldn’t stop this disturbance from ending. In reality, the great debate brought about by this had only just begun.

That morning, reporters contacted Excellent Era asking about their thoughts on Team Heavenly Swords denying that Ye Qiu had joined their team.

Excellent Era had already been prepared. They didn’t try to prove that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu and instead, they expressed calmly that it didn’t matter if Ye Qiu joined Team Heavenly Swords or not. No matter what he planned for in the future, Excellent Era would give him their blessings, but would also face him with a professional attitude. As for Heavenly Swords, Excellent Era congratulated them for their success in making it into the Alliance and wished them good luck in the future.

When asked about their thoughts on Lord Grim, who was able to defeat Huang Shaotian, Excellent Era answered that they weren’t scared of any opponent. They didn’t mention Heavenly Swords and declared that they would definitely make a comeback next season to win the Championship.

These sort of words and replies were commonly seen. Apart from this, their words also implied that they didn’t find the new team as a threat and didn’t put them in their eyes.

Besides Excellent Era, the pro players who affirmed that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu were given another round of interviews.

These pro players had all seen Ye Xiu speak in the group chat and then followed into the game to find Lord Grim, so they had been very certain of his identity. However, Team Heavenly Swords declared that Ye Qiu hadn’t joined them. They caught the word play involved in these statements, but none of them jumped out to prove Lord Grim was Ye Qiu because for the Clubs, such an action wouldn’t help them in any way. As a result, everyone just went with the flow. Heavenly Swords could do what they wanted. They weren’t going to get mixed up with them. So as to avoid what happened last time, they sent out their iconic players to act as live promotional signboards.

Some players ran over to look at Heavenly Justice players. After the news came out, Team Heavenly Swords was looked at exceptionally well by many. Some of the more exaggerated analysis claimed that with Heavenly Sword’s strength and resources, they would definitely make a huge impact in the Alliance and might even win the entire Championship as the dark horse.

These discussions made the other Clubs a bit scared. However, they had seen their strength after their fights with Huang Shaotian. All of the pro players at the scene had a good estimate of their skill levels and didn’t see them as a threat.

The reports downplayed one part though. Heavenly Sword’s introduction to scene had cost quite a bit.

As for the “mystery man” who beat Huang Shaotian, everyone knew he was Ye Qiu. Team Heavenly Swords said that Ye Qiu hadn’t joined their team, which was quite a weird roundabout way of saying things.

After the discussions.

Ye Qiu couldn’t formally join now because of his recent retirement, so of course he couldn’t join. But the two sides could have made an agreement for him to join next season.

This was a guess that the Clubs had agreed upon as a possibility. However, all of them simply acted as if they didn’t know this. They laughed over the interviews and didn’t say too much.

There was only one pro player who said things different than the rest: Tyranny’s Han Wenqing. Facing the reporters’ questions, he coldly threw down: “Did Heavenly Swords ever say Lord Grim wasn’t Ye Qiu? Who else could Lord Grim be but Ye Qiu?”

That day, the interviewed players from all of the different Clubs all replied with similar words. Han Wenqing’s reply immediately stood out. Everyone else’s interviews were suddenly thrown to the side and only this reply was reported.

In reality, Team Heavenly Sword’s little wordplay may have tricked most players, but the media reporters were good at these types of tricks and were aware of it long ago. They had already prepared for it. Now that a pro player directly said it, it was as if they had obtained a treasure.

As for the interviews towards Heavenly Swords, they refused to reveal Lord Grim’s identity.

Lord Grim being Ye Qiu instantly became very believable, so the Clubs’ analysis of an agreement and then joining in the future had also been analyzed by the media and reported out.

The credibility of such a statement was extremely high.

Lord Grim had went in a huge circle. In the end, he was still Ye Qiu. Quite a few fans treated the entire course of events as a drama novel. The media wasn’t done yet though. They obtained views from a few reporters, commentators, and normal players.

The view that he would come out of retirement and join became widely accepted. Everyone unanimously believed that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu and had determined him as a part of Heavenly Swords. They were convinced that Heavenly Swords was just saying all of that to make things unnecessarily complicated.

Chen Guo said she didn’t care, but in the end, she couldn’t help but read the reports. The results made her feel dizzy: “Everything just went around full circle. Why’d it return to this?”

“The topic stays hot. The media likes it. Heavenly Swords likes it too.” Ye Xiu said.

“It looks like your identity has been seen through.” Chen Guo said.

“It would have happened sooner or later.” Ye Xiu seemed as if he didn’t care.

“Why does Heavenly Sword refuse to say it? Did you ask them to?” Chen Guo asked.

“They only know that I won’t join them, so it’s better to not say it. You think about it.” Ye Xiu said.

“Think about what! Just say it!” Chen Guo said.

“I’m busy! BOSS!” Ye Xiu called.

“What?” Chen Guo flew over when she heard this.

Chapter 455 – Scrap Picker

Boss!

This was a word that would make any Glory player’s heart leap. Moreover, this was the Heavenly Domain. A Heavenly Domain boss was on another realm compared to one in the normal server. Chen Guo also knew that Ye Xiu could only level in the wild, which meant that this was a wild boss.

The Heavenly Domain was similar to the normal servers in this sense. Wild bosses would randomly spawn someplace every week. But the difference was that wild bosses would only spawn once a week, which meant that every wild boss would spawn a maximum of 52 times a year. The unique equipment and material dropped from this type of boss would undoubtedly be rare and precious.

The top guilds naturally watched for these types of bosses with great attention. At the start of every week, in all of the Level 55 to Level 70 areas, the top guilds would dispatch scouts to wander around randomly 24/7. At the same time, they also bought information on the boss’s coordinates from players who didn’t have the strength to kill one but had found one.

Every time a wild boss spawned, it was likely a huge war would erupt. Lower leveled bosses were a bit better. Normal players had a chance to snatch one. After all, apart from Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, everyone else in the Heavenly Domain was Level 70, so they had a high level suppression. In addition, even if they weren’t experts, they were all experienced players. Killing a low-leveled boss with friends wasn’t too difficult.

As for high leveled bosses, those would always fall into one of the top guild’s hands. One reason is because high level bosses spawn in high level areas. With everyone in the Heavenly Domain being Level 70 players, most of them played in high level areas. High level areas weren’t as empty as the Level 55 area Lord Grim was in. As a result, if a boss spawned in a high level area, many players would notice it and there was no opportunity to hide it and kill it.

The second reason was because high level bosses were strong. No matter who fought them, they wouldn’t be easy to kill. The longer it took for one to die, the more likely the chance someone could run over to kill steal it. The only ones who could fight to the end with such risks were those with strength.

Thus, for high level bosses, normal players wouldn’t dream of snatching one. But Level 55 bosses had more hope.

“What type of boss?” Chen Guo rushed over to Ye Xiu’s computer while asking. Her eyes were already fixed on his screen. Ye Xiu’s line of sight only exposed half the screen. Something was clearly blocking the other half. From the exposed half a screen, numerous players battling a single boss could be seen.

“This one is…… Wilderness Escort! How could one appear here??” Chen Guo didn’t ask about Ye Xiu’s blocked line of sight and first identified the boss. The Wilderness Escort wore a large felt cap, a pair of leather boots, a corset. His tanned face gave the look of a rough and uncouth male. He was the Level 65 Wilderness Escort of the Eastern Wilderness. However, this place was the Level 55 Chalk Town. The wild boss here should be the Evil Mayor Chalk.

“He was clearly summoned here!” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh!” Chen Guo immediately understood. As the number of players in the Heavenly Domain increased, a wild boss spawning once a week wasn’t enough to satisfy everyone’s appetite. Many players who had played for several years hadn’t even seen a wild boss yet. As a result, in one update, Glory released a “Boss Summon”. As rewards for some quests or for killing a boss, there was a chance to obtain an item to summon a boss. This item could be used at any time and any place outside of a dungeon in the Heavenly Domain. As the name implies, the item summoned a boss for everyone to kill.

This type of item was equivalent to a boss, so it was obviously rare as well. Apart from this, these items couldn’t be traded. As a result, when players who didn’t have the strength to kill the boss happened to obtain this item, they would find a way to contact the top guilds. The player would summon the boss, the guild would kill it, and it could be considered as selling a boss. The price for selling a boss would obviously be much greater than selling information on a boss’s coordinates. With this item, one could find a place with no one around and then kill it in secret.

The people in front of them right now were clearly trying to kill it in secret.

Level 55 areas were without a doubt the most empty places in the Heavenly Domain. They were currently located in the corner of a Chalk Town. If one didn’t wander deep into the town, there was no way they would find this place.

Coincidentally, Ye Xiu wanted to find a place to level with no one around, so he chose Chalk Town. After wandering around, he happened to bump into this place.

The Wilderness Escort was a Gunner though as a boss, it wasn’t any particular class. If you did, you would definitely suffer. If you thought it was a Sharpshooter, he might just send you a Spitfire skill.

“What are you doing? Are you going to try and steal it?” Chen Guo noticed that Ye Xiu’s movements were a bit strange. He only half his screen looking at the situation, which meant he must be hiding behind a window in some room.

“That would be too lacking in principles.” Ye Xiu said, “I’m going to pick up scraps.”

“You….. don’t you feel ashamed!!!” Chen Guo heard this and almost fell over.

Picking up scraps was a term used in the Heavenly Domain because the Heavenly Domain players had a high chance of dropping items when they died. Thus, in a large scale conflict, there would always be players who would do this. They would wear cheap equipment and charge into the battle without any fear. However, don’t make this misunderstanding, these players weren’t a suicide squad to attract attacks. Their target was the equipment that dropped when players died!

This type of activity was called picking up scraps, while the players who did this were called scrap pickers. Scrap pickers were hated by others and if one appeared next to them, they wouldn’t hesitate to kill them. A boss fight was a prime opportunity for scrap pickers. There would always be casualties against a boss.

But what type of person was Ye Xiu! He was a God! Right now, he was camping in a corner waiting to pick up scraps. Such shameful behavior made Chen Guo give him a good scolding.

“Shh!” Ye Xiu actually turned his head and reminded Chen Guo that she was being too loud.

“Do you want to come too?” Ye Xiu whispered.

“Uh……” Chen Guo hesitated. In reality, she didn’t mind picking up scraps when she had the chance to. The only thing she couldn’t accept was that a God like Ye Xiu would do such a task. After all, he used to be her idol once too. Her image of him being shattered was very painful for the fans!

“What…… can you pick up from this?” After hesitating for a bit, she still went to sat next to Ye Xiu. She opened up the game, while telling Tang Rou: “Little Tang, help me log out.”

Room 213’s four computers were arranged with two rows back to back. Chen Guo and Tang Rou had been sitting next to each other. Chen Guo wanted to pick up scraps with Ye Xiu, so Chen Guo was going to switch spots to make it easy to communicate with each other.

“They’ve probably made preparations for this type of summoning. Have there been any accidents?” Chen Guo continued.

“Hard to say. I’ve been watching them for awhile and they might not make it.” Ye Xiu said.

“You…… can you be even more shameful?” Chen Guo was depressed.

“Sigh. If only my level wasn’t so low. I could wait for them to wipe out and then pick up the boss too.” Ye XIu sighed.

“You can’t kill it?” Chen Guo asked.

“It’s a Heavenly Domain wild boss that’s 14 levels higher than me! No matter how good I am, there’s still a limit.” Ye Xiu said.

“What a pity.” Chen Guo muttered. She had logged into the game on this side. She looked at Ye XIu’s screen for his coordinates and then immediately headed over there.

“Hm. Do you want to contact Loulan Slash?” Chen Guo suggested. In the Heavenly Domain, stealing a boss wasn’t looked down upon as much as stealing monsters. Even though there were fewer bosses, that was exactly why people were fine with it. Under normal circumstances, sitting on the side watching others fight without attacking them was already considered quite nice. If you couldn’t kill it, who cares if you saw it first or summoned it, it was time for other people to try.

Most directly stole it away. Usually the Club guilds were the ones who were nice. The Clubs had to care about their image. Even though stealing bosses wasn’t considered as anything bad in the Heavenly Domain, for the Club guilds, it would be bully. Even though they had strength, when they encountered normal players, they had to let them try first. It was quite depressing for them actually.

There was only on the surface though. Underneath, there would definitely be something going on. If they didn’t, then why would the Club guilds go through so much trouble to make so many wild accounts?

“I was thinking that too, but they’re not online!” Ye Xiu sighed.

Chen Guo had just gotten online. When she looked at her friends list, she also saw that Loulan Slash and his group wasn’t there. As for Chen Guo’s original friends, they were all from Excellent Dynasty. The group of people sent over would be from Guild Excellent Dynasty, so they were a no go.

“If you use my account, can you kill it?” Chen Guo asked.

“Solo…… the problem is time! This isn’t like the tenth server, where no one goes to the high leveled areas. Killing the boss would need three hours without anyone noticing. That isn’t very likely.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was helpless. That wasn’t a possibility. Let alone others, but the team in from them would definitely come back if they wiped out.

“Is picking scraps the only thing we can do?” Chen Guo wasn’t happy.

“Uh……” Ye Xiu hesitated.

“What are you thinking?” Chen Guo could see that he had some sort of plan.

“From a scrap picker’s perspective…….” Ye Xiu had only finished halfway, when a message was sent in the global chat: “Chalk Town, coordinates 45, 74, a Wilderness Escort!!!”

“Wow! Who did this!” Ye Xiu shouted, “He was just about to say what I wanted to. This is something a professional scrap picker would do.”

Chen Guo saw a string of emojis appear after the message on the global chat. She was speechless. She could imagine that a storm would erupt soon. When this message appeared on the global chat, the team killing the boss went into chaos. Two rays of white light shot out as two players perished.

Chapter 456 – Not a Bad Hiding Place

There were originally fifteen players who had gathered to hunt the summoned Wilderness Escort.

In terms of preparation, this team was more than enough to kill a Level 65 Wilderness Escort. Ye Xiu didn’t know what type of accident had happened, but when he arrived, he saw that the situation had already devolved into chaos. Under the Wilderness Escort’s frenzy, the Cleric was frantically healing left and right, but to no avail. The situation couldn’t be rescued. When Ye Xiu got there, they only had 12 players left. The number fifteen had been calculated by Ye Xiu based on their classes.

“Need help?” When Ye Xiu saw that the other side was in a crisis, he had even asked if they wanted help.

“No need!!” The other side were facing the enemy, so it wasn’t possible to tell how many had yelled it out.

Thus, Ye Xiu quietly left, walked around in a circle, and then slipped into an empty room, becoming a scrap picker.

And now, when the message appeared in the world chat, Ye Xiu immediately knew that he wasn’t the only one hiding there.

This other person was undoubtedly a scrap picker too because if he had cared about the BOSS, then there was no way he would have announced it to the world. This type of work was something a scrap picker would like to do. Scrap pickers loved chaotic battles. It didn’t matter if you were killing a BOSS or PKing because of a BOSS. In any case, if there were battles and dead people, there would be scrap pickers.

Ye Xiu understood this sort of shady business. He wasn’t the one to do it though. He had

planning to telling Chen Guo about it, when someone else beat him to it.

“It seems like this corner might not be safe!” Ye Xiu sighed. He had Lord Grim move backwards and begin observing the surroundings to see if there was anyone else on the lookout as well. Only now could Chen Guo see that Lord Grim was in an empty room, next to a window looking at the others outside fighting a BOSS.

“Is it going to get chaotic real soon?” Chen Guo said.

“Yeah!” Ye Xiu constantly moved his camera around, but from out his window, apart from the BOSS, there was no one else he could see.

“Where should I hide……” Ye Xiu mumbled. Outside of the window, a white light flashed and another player died. So far, only six players remained. In addition, the Cleric had already fallen. In a chaotic situation, if the situation couldn’t be saved, the aggro would eventually fall onto the Cleric. Once the Cleric fell, the attempt to kill the BOSS could be considered over.

“You’re still not running?” Ye Xiu saw the remaining six players continue to struggle. But after watching for a bit longer, he understood their intent. They wanted to pick up the items their comrades had dropped after dying. After picking up all of the items dropped on the ground, the six immediately ran away. As expected, these were experienced players. Once they saw the announcement in the global chat, they figured out that there were scrap pickers hiding nearby.

Scrap pickers had their own styles of scrap picking.

Some risked their lives. They charged straight into the battlefield, not caring for their life, and picked up as many items as they could. These types of scrap pickers would certainly die on the battlefield, but they didn’t care about the experience loss. They only wanted to see if they could pick up some good equipment.

Apart from them were scrap pickers who wanted to pick up items, while staying alive. These scrap pickers were more cautious and wouldn’t charge into the battlefield. This was because once you entered the battlefield, it didn’t matter if you were there to steal the BOSS or pick up equipment, your opponents wouldn’t be nice.

“What a patient guy!” Ye Xiu saw that the hidden scrap pickers still hadn’t moved out yet even though the other side had already picked up their equipment and left.

At this moment, the six players were preparing to escape, but the Wilderness Escort wouldn’t let them go so easily. As the group ran and the Escort chased, the Escort would move away and then scrap pickers would have to follow along.

Ye Xiu didn’t hurry and move. He continued to have Lord Grim stay by the window, observing the surroundings. Just as he predicted, when the six players moved away along with the Wilderness Escort, players scurried out from the corners of the streets, rooftops, and rooms.

Ye Xiu sweat like mad. He had thought that there was only one person hiding, but in reality, there were actually so many of them waiting.

These scrap pickers seemed to have a tacit understanding amongst themselves. Either that, or they didn’t know there were others around. None of them seemed too surprised though nor did anyone seem to have any enmity with each other. Everyone had the same thought and immediately chased after the Wilderness Escort.

Ye Xiu still didn’t move. He waited another long while, but didn’t see anyone else come out. If he didn’t move out now, he wouldn’t be able to follow them, so he immediately had Lord Grim chase after.

“Despicable!! How despicable!!” Chen Guo disdained as she chased after with her Chasing Haze. The Heavenly Domain was very big, but luckily, Chen Guo had been accompanying Ye Xiu these days with leveling, so her character wasn’t too far away and it wouldn’t take her too much time to catch up. She constantly glanced at Ye Xiu’s screen for his coordinates up until they bumped into each other at a street.

“Over here.” Ye Xiu said. Chen Guo followed behind him.

“Did they all die?” Chen Guo asked.

“Six ran away. The BOSS is still there.” Ye Xiu said.

“And us?”

“See the opportunity and act.”

“More like see the opportunity and pick scraps!” Chen Guo said.

“Depends on the situation.” Ye Xiu said.

“How come I don’t see the BOSS?” Chen Guo couldn’t see the Wilderness Escort. Ye Xiu couldn’t see it either, making Chen Guo quite puzzled.

“I know where! I’m bringing you to a good hiding place.” Ye Xiu said. Not long after, he brought Chen Guo to outside a wall.

“Jump over.” Ye Xiu said. His character jumped over and used a Rotor Wing to directly hop over. The wall wasn’t that tall, so it wasn’t hard to get over. Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze jumped and used an Aerial Fire. Her character leaped over in a beautiful arc. While in the air, she heard Ye Xiu cry out “Oh wow.” When she landed, she stared dumbly.

“A good hiding place?” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

“Of course. See, just look at how many people are hiding here…..” Ye Xiu said. When he looked around, there were already five people there. When the two flipped over the wall, the five were startled at first, but then one quickly raised his sword.

Chen Guo also reacted quickly. Her Chasing Haze lifted up her cannon towards the other side. One of the people among the five shot forward like an arrow between the two of them. His body turned left and right with his arms in a cross position to the two sides.

“What’s he doing? Is he trying to shoot out a laser?” Chen Guo didn’t understand.

Ye Xiu laughed: “He wanted to move his arms in an X position to tell us to not fight, but he messed up.”

Chen Guo understood. Some Glory people liked to show off their skill and would make small poses from time to time.

“You two, stop talking!!!” The person with his arms in a cross position was very embarrassed. Seeing that the two were still chatting, he immediately tried to shush them. Following afterwards, he gave each of them a team invite.

At the same time, the person who had just wanted Ye Xiu and Chen Guo to be quiet shouted in surprise: “Ah! Lord Grim?”

“What?” A bunch of wide eyed emojis popped up and the others crowded around them.

“Don’t use emojis! Use the party chat!!!” The person whispered.

Ye Xiu and Chen Guo looked at each other and then accepted the invite. Then, he heard the person say in a low voice: “Don’t talk and don’t use the public chat. Talk in the party chat!”

The speaker was called Sparse Fragrance. He was the person who had made the stop pose, but messed it up. This person was the party leader, a Blade Master. Blade Masters really were popular classes in Glory. Everyone else in the party were also Blade Masters.

“What are you doing?” Chasing Haze asked.

No one cared about her though! Everyone was crowded around Lord Grim!

“Wow! It really is Lord Grim!!”

“Are you God Ye Qiu?”

“Can I touch you?”

Ye Xiu sent out a sweating emoji. No one really noticed though. As they talked, they opened his character page to admire his equipment. But apart from the Silver weapon, the other equipment made the Heavenly Domain players want to vomit.

“Big bro, are you really Ye Qiu?” Even Sparse Fragrance was asking! As long as one was a Glory player, everyone knew about the drama going on.

“You guess.” Ye Xiu replied.

“I don’t think you are.” Sparse Fragrance said in a very confident tone.

“Why?” Ye Xiu said.

“Would God Ye Qiu stoop so low as to pick up scraps with us?” Sparse Fragrance replied.

“Ha ha ha ha……” Chen Guo typed, while looking at Ye Xiu to see how he would reply.

“I’m Ye Qiu!” Ye Xiu said.

“Tsk…….” Sparse Fragrance didn’t believe him at all.

“Tsk tsk tsk tsk!!” Everyone followed along. Chen Guo was laughing so hard she couldn’t straighten her back.

“How did you guys get here?” Ye Xiu didn’t mind. He cared more about this question. He had chased after the entire way too and when he discovered that the Wilderness Escort had stopped, he felt like this was a good hiding spot. However, if they came from the front, they would have alarmed the Wilderness Escort, which was why they had looped around and jumped over the wall. He was moving at the same speed as the other scrap pickers and didn’t see any of them jump over the wall, so the others had clearly gotten here some other way. Ye Xiu couldn’t understand.

“He, there’s a small hole there. If you crawl through, you can get in. But since the grass is blocking the way, most people wouldn’t know.” Sparse Fragrance said in a delighted tone.

Ye Xiu was speechless. He may be known as a textbook and God of Glory, but he had no idea there was a dog hole covered by the grass.

Chapter 457 – Professional Scrap Picking

Ye Xiu couldn’t understand why they were so happy about a dog hole, even though it was something he didn’t know about. He had previously seen the group from outside the window and had thought that the scrap pickers were peaceful with each other, but now from the looks of it, these five players all recognized each other. They had partied together to pick up scraps together. If not, how could they have all decided to go into this hiding place through a dog hole?

Nowadays, players knew to make preparations against scrap pickers. It didn’t matter so much for players in a conflict, but for an activity like fighting against a wild BOSS, players would often specially dispatch troops to be on the lookout for them. One reason was to prevent others from causing trouble. A second reason was to prevent scrap pickers from mixing in.

The team from before was an exception. They didn’t seem to be a team with any sort of background. Their main team only had ten or so people. Where would they get the extra manpower to do all this? Thus, they simply went forward with it and found an empty place to kill it as fast as possible.

But the situation had changed now. With the announcement of the BOSS’s location in the global chat, the top guilds would soon arrive along with a bunch of scrap pickers. Finding a good hiding place was extremely important. They would strike when the moment was right. If there was chaos, there would be items to pick up. If there was none, then because they were hidden, they could easily retreat.

Sparse Fragrance’s group denied the possibility of Lord Grim being God Ye Qiu through Ye Xiu’s actions. Towards the so-called mystery man, they just looked at him for a bit, but didn’t gossip too much. They were here to pick up scraps and they didn’t want any accidents to happen.

“When the opportunity comes, we’ll rush out and go pick up items. Don’t hold back each other!” Sparse Fragrance was mainly saying this to Ye Xiu and Chen Guo. The rest were a part of the same group, so they naturally had a tacit understanding between each other long ago.

“Then give me a spot!” Ye Xiu said. It was a bit crowded for seven people in this room. In particular, the five took up the places where the outside situation could be seen. There wasn’t any space for Ye Xiu.

“Give him a spot.” Sparse Fragrance seemed to be this team’s leader. After speaking, someone moved back two steps and let Lord Grim take the spot.

“F*ck, my area! Move aside!” Sparse Fragrance realized that there wasn’t any space for him. After shouting for a bit, he snatched a spot next to Lord Grim.

The Wilderness Escort was still wandering around outside. Before a summoned BOSS was killed, it would wander around for eternity.

“There’s still no one here yet.” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s far. You’ve got to give people some time! Who strolls around here everyday! The Mayor Chalk of Chalk Town has already been killed this week.” Sparse Fragrance said. He was saying that this area’s wild BOSS was already gone this week, so the top guild’s hunting teams had already left this place.

“You know quite a lot!” Ye Xiu said.

“Of course. Scrap picking requires information.” Sparse Fragrance said. A despicable activity like scrap picking sounded like an honest profession coming out from his mouth.

“Then how much longer do you think we’ll have to wait?” Ye Xiu asked.

“From the time the announcement was made, I’d say half an hour or so. So now, it’d be around ten more minutes!” Sparse Fragrance continued, “A Level 65 Wilderness Escort! There’ll be quite a fight for it. The more chaotic the better!”

Ye Xiu understood after hearing this. They weren’t expecting to see the BOSS show off its might because with a top guild’s strength, killing a Level 65 BOSS wasn’t a problem. They hoped to see a struggle between different groups fighting amongst each other for the BOSS. A huge mess like that was perfect for scrap pickers.

“Did you send out that info?” Ye Xiu asked. Even though the name didn’t match with anyone in the group, there was something called a trumpet.

“No.” Sparse Fragrance said.

“Then that means there’s at least one other scrap picker that we don’t know of.” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s why we hid in a good place, so we can carefully observe the situation and strike when the opportunity arises!” Sparse Fragrance spoke in a serious tone.

“What if he also comes in through the dog hole?” Ye Xiu asked.

“There’s no need to talk about that.” This time, Sparse Fragrance didn’t mess up and through poses made from various attacks, he was able to make a sword sliding across a throat movement.

“Oh, then I really got lucky didn’t I? I didn’t get cut by you.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“How dare you!” Sparse Fragrance answered.

This guy! Ye Xiu muttered to himself. This guy had definitely noticed his name when he came in, which was why he had jumped out to stop his comrade. Someone who could beat Huang Shaotian wasn’t someone five normal players could hope to beat.

But afterwards, he pretended that he just noticed the name Lord Grim, concealing their initial plan to kill them. However, he accidentally exposed it……

“This other scrap picker probably isn’t simple.” Ye Xiu said. After this person sent out the message, he still hadn’t appeared. Could he have also waited to see if there were any other scrap pickers? Ye Xiu thought.

“Who cares about him. In any case, we’re all here to pick up scraps. Just don’t attack each other and pick up as many good items as you can. Even if he isn’t a simple guy, he should understand this reasoning.” Sparse Fragrance’s tone suddenly changed.

“Really? Do you have any other specific plans?” Since there wasn’t anything to do, Ye Xiu thought he might as well chat with them.

“In this current age, scrap picking isn’t easy. For example, those people who just charge into the battlefield and pick up items until they die can’t be considered professionals. Nowadays, there’s a certain amount of skill involved and you have to understand the situation clearly before moving out. If it’s too chaotic, then the players can’t distinguish foe from friend and just attack whoever they see. With bullets, magic, sword light flying around, you can’t pick up anything. If it’s too stable, then the experts on the guild will simply kill you before you mix in with everyone. So that’s why you have to pay close attention to the situation. If you’re asking if I have a plan, then of course I don’t have one. I’m also waiting for a certain scenario before I make any decisions.”

Ye Xiu was quite amazed at Sparse Fragrance’s scrap picking theory. It really showed that there was a master in every trade! Moreover, when he heard that there needed to be a certain amount of skill, Ye Xiu looked at their five Blade Master team composition and asked: “In reality, you should have six people, no?”

“Good eye! You really do deserve to be called an expert! You even guessed that!” Sparse Fragrance gasped in astonishment, “In reality, we’re six people. But we’re missing one today, so it’s a bit troublesome!”

“No problem. When the time comes, I can help you guys and substitute in.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh?”

“I’m an unspecialized, so I have Blade Master skills.” Ye Xiu said.

“But you only have Level 20 and under skills” Sparse Fragrance said.

“It’s enough.”

“How could that be enough. Do you know what we’re planning on doing?”

“I know. It’s the Six Sword Formation. Do you know who came up with the Six Sword Formation?” Ye Xiu replied.

“Correct. And I’m Ye Qiu. Didn’t I tell you guys that?” Ye Xiu said.

“Tsk!!” Sparse Fragrance hadn’t replied back, when two of the other players in his group booed.

“He really is Ye Qiu…..” Chen Guo interrupted.

“You even brought a cheerleader!” They continued booing.

“What a sin!!” Chen Guo sighed as she looked up towards the sky. Such a despicable act really did destroy his image. There were so much support for Lord Grim being Ye Qiu, but as soon as they saw Lord Grim was scrap picking, they immediately denied this possibility. From this, it could be seen what the popular consent towards this type of activity was. It had to be known that these people were professional scrap pickers. Even they denied the possibility that Ye Qiu would stoop so low as to pick up scraps.

“Okay then!” Ye Xiu was also silent for a good moment, “To tell you the truth, I know a lot about the Six Sword Formation. In any case, you five won’t be able to do it with just yourselves. You might as well let me try.”

“Do you really think you can do it?”

“It’s not like you guys have any better options right?” Ye Xiu said.

Sparse Fragrance thought for a bit and then said “We’ll see!”

At this moment, one of the other players among the group suddenly asked: “If you say you’re Ye Qiu, then is she Su Mucheng?”

“Ha ha ha ha, how funny! How could I be Su Mucheng.” This was in the game. Outside of the game, Chen Guo directly grabbed Ye Xiu’s arm and continued to laugh: “Ha ha ha ha, he actually thought I was Su Mucheng.”

“Hurry up and let go. If you keep pressing on my arm, I’ll walk out.” Ye Xiu hastily tried to shake her off. His hand was still on the keyboard. When Chen Guo grabbed his arm, she made it so his arm was pressing the forward button. He almost walked out of the room.

Ye Xiu obviously couldn’t type in this situation, so he had to say it out loud. The others in-game could hear him. After a moment of silence, Sparse Fragrance spoke: “Well, it doesn’t matter. In any case, you’re an expert, so let’s act accordingly!

“Okay.” Ye Xiu approved.

Afterwards, there wasn’t much to say, so everyone just sat there in silence. Chen Guo had went scrap picking before, but it had always just been done because she was passing by. She had never done something like guarding a BOSS and waiting for an opportunity to pick up scraps. It was both a fresh and despicable experience.

“There are people coming! No one say anything or use word bubbles!!” Sparse Fragrance reminded everyone. If scrap pickers were discovered, they would be killed on the spot.

“Yes!” Everyone replied. Outside, amidst frantic footsteps, someone shouted: “Over here. F*ck, how’d it get here.”

It was a bit off from the coordinates announced in the global chat.

“The other guilds will be here soon. Let’s hurry and find a spot to lure the BOSS away.” Another voice said.

“No need. There’s a spot here. If you can send the BOSS into it, then you can get it stuck there. From there, killing it will be easy and if outsiders don’t especially look for it, then there’s no way they’ll find it!”

“Oh? There’s a place like this?”

“Yeah! Right over there!!”

“The place they’re talking about…… is where?” Ye Xiu whispered to everyone in the party. In that instant, the seven didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. Why did it sound like the spot those people were talking about was where they were?

Chapter 458 – Maximum Precision

“Not good!!” Sparse Fragrance cried. Their hearts leapt into their throats as they turned around to look towards the dog hole hidden by the pile of grass.

“Hurry up and run!” One person suggested.

“There might be people outside!” Sparse Fragrance seemed to be calm facing the crisis like a general. But his next words exposed his true feelings: “We’re so dead…….” It wasn’t that this guy was calm. It was that he had completely given up.

“Dead? Isn’t there still time to log off?” Ye Xiu was the real calm one facing the crisis.

“Oh oh, I forgot about that. Everyone, hurry up and log off!” Sparse Fragrance hastily said.

“I won’t send you off then!” Ye Xiu said.

“What?” Sparse Fragrance was just about to log off, when he felt like something was wrong with this statement. He immediately let go of the mouse: “You’re not logging off?”

“I’m not in a hurry……” Ye Xiu really was calm facing this crisis as he had Lord Grim look up at a 45 degree angle.

“For a height like this as well as a Level 65 boss’s resistance, in order to send it flying in, they would need to coordinate very well.” Ye Xiu came to this conclusion after carefully looking at the room.

“Oh?” Sparse Fragrance stopped the other four from logging off. Lord Grim was an expert, so he felt like they should put some hope into him.

“So if they want to send the boss into here, the easiest way would probably be to use a ground sweeping attack and send the boss flying through the dog hole.” Ye Xiu said.

“What?” Sparse Fragrance couldn’t understand what Ye Xiu was trying to get at.

“We can block it from coming in.” Ye Xiu said.

“Big bro, if they flip over the wall to get in, then we’ll all be exposed.” Sparse Fragrance said.

“Bro, if you look through that crack in the wall, you’ll see that no one is going to flip over the wall!” Ye Xiu replied.

Sparse Fragrance immediately understood. He immediately peeped out of the crack in the wall and sure enough, no one on the other side looked like they were planning to flip over the wall. When Ye Xiu had jumped over the wall, he had to go around in a circle. Ye Xiu had been afraid of alarming the boss when he did this, but these people didn’t have that problem. The boss had already been lured by them. These people had to hurry. As soon as they came up with the plan, they immediately began carrying it out.

“Listen carefully!” Ye Xiu said in the party chat.

There was no longer anything that could be seen from outside of the crack in the wall, but on the other side of the dog hole, all sorts of battle sounds could be heard.

“How are we going to block it?” Sparse Fragrance wasn’t sure what to do.

“If you’re familiar with your skills, you can do it.” Ye Xiu had Lord Grim move towards the dog hole.

“But if we block like this and the other side knows there are people in here, won’t they come in and kill us?” Sparse Fragrance thought about it for a bit and still felt like they should hurry up and log off.

“So don’t let them know. You have to make them think that it was their mistake.” Ye Xiu said.

“How are you supposed to do that?” Sparse Fragrance was still at a loss.

“Just watch.” Ye Xiu sent a smiley face.

“Get ready to log off at any time.” Sparse Fragrance warned.

On the other side of the wall, battle sounds could be heard more and more clearly. Only the Wilderness boss could make such loud gunfire. The attacks from the players were all mixed up, but Ye Xiu still listened intently and grasped information from these noises. The most direct information came from the players’ voices though.

“Pull it here, pull it here!!!!”

“Cleric, don’t heal so much! Be careful, don’t let it OT.”

“If I don’t heal, then they’ll die.” The Cleric objected.

“Increase the aggro! Don’t just run! Can you run faster than a bullet?” The brothers responsible for pulling the boss were scolded. The outside situation could be figured out from these shouts. The players had aggroed the boss and then impatiently ran over here. However, the Wilderness Escort was a long-ranged fighter! No matter how fast you ran, attacks would follow. As a result, the Cleric had to keep healing, but the pullers only ran and didn’t continue establishing aggro. It wouldn’t be long before the aggro switched to the healer.

“Stupid, just have the Cleric stand over here……” Ye Xiu couldn’t help but say, “Which guild are these guys from?”

“I couldn’t really see it clearly! Did anyone else see it?” Sparse Fragrance replied.

The others didn’t know either. They could see that there were people there from the crack in the wall, but the crack in the wall gave them a very limited viewpoint. If the player didn’t stand at a certain spot, then the name and guild tag on top of his head couldn’t be seen. As a result, no one saw where these guys came from.

“Pay attention to that side and whether or not there are people coming to flip over the wall.” Ye Xiu instructed.

“Understood.” Sparse Fragrance immediately had two of his people continue watching, while he continued to focus on the dog hole.

Outside, the gun sounds grew near and nearer. The Wilderness Escort was getting closer and closer to the dog hole. Suddenly, they heard a shout: “F*ck, OT!”

“Cleric, hurry up and go over there!”

“Long ranged……. He can shoot me from there……” The Cleric wanted to cry.

“You’re all dead! Move that way a bit.”

Amidst the flurry of footsteps and attacks, Ye Xiu was listening for the gunfire of the Wilderness Escort. He needed to know how much longer it would take for the Wilderness Escort to arrive.

It’s close. It’s getting closer and closer……

Ye Xiu could tell. These people weren’t bad. In the end, they were able to lure the boss to the dog hole.

“Get into position!” Someone emphasized.

“Ready!” Someone suddenly shouted.

After the sounds of several skills being used, a “Bang!” echoed. A single skill could clearly be heard.

Falling Flower Palm! Ye Xiu quickly determined. He immediately went onto his stomach and pushed down the pile of grass. From his viewpoint, he could see a black shadow about to fill up the dog hole. Ye Xiu didn’t hesitate. While laying on his stomach, he sent an attack into the dog hole.

Besides Ye Xiu, no one else knew where his attack was going towards. Chen Guo and the others waited nervously. They couldn’t see what was going on. However, Chen Guo had an advantage! She turned her head and looked towards Ye Xiu’s screen.

It looked like Ye Xiu had only sent a normal attack towards the Wilderness Escort, but soon afterwards, a “Crash!” boomed. Dirt from the earthen wall shook free. The grass near the the dog hole trembled. Outside, a voice could be heard: “Again!”

Their first attempt had clearly failed, but Chen Guo couldn’t tell if it was because of Ye Xiu or not. She didn’t know what effect Ye Xiu’s attack had accomplished.

“Move to the sides!!” Ye Xiu typed. His Lord Grim jumped up and rolled away from the dog hole. The others didn’t react in time though. A barrage of bullets whistled through the dog hole. Two people were hit by them.

“What’s going on!” The two people hit were scared out of their minds.

“Get up! Be careful.” Ye Xiu replied as he went back over to crouch down.

Outside, sounds of skills being used could be heard. After a short while, Ye Xiu once again heard a Falling Flower Palm.

He lay down and attacked.

Ye Xiu’s actions looked very simple. Outside, they could hear a depressed voice say “Again.”

“I don’t understand……” Chen Guo watched as Lord Grim dodged another round of bullets.

“What don’t you understand? I just need to slightly change his movement path so he hits one of the walls. That way, he won’t be able to get in.” Ye Xiu said.

“I understand this, but I don’t understand how you accomplish that!” Chen Guo said.

“That’s a really hard question……. The only answer I can come up with is that it’s because I’m Ye Qiu……” Ye Xiu was helpless.

“……” Chen Guo was speechless. The other side were going for their third attempt. This time, Chen Guo didn’t look at Ye Xiu’s screen. She paid attention to what Ye Xiu did that instant.

“Bang……” The ones on the outside thought that it was because they were making mistakes, which was why they kept on trying again. The skill responsible for blowing in the boss was the Battle Mage’s Falling Flower Palm.

Ye Xiu began acting when heard this sound.

Lay down, push down the grass, align his viewpoint with the dog hole.

Attack. To Chen Guo, it just looked like Ye Xiu was randomly attacking….

But she soon discovered that Lord Grim’s attack wasn’t a stab, but a flick.

Chen Guo was surprised. Because stab skills were point and click attacks, while slashes were sweep attacks, which required mouse movements to accomplish.

Lord Grim’s attack belonged in this category. However, Chen Guo couldn’t see any movements from his right hand.

Outside, a furious “AGAIN!” could be heard. This time, Chen Guo didn’t look at her screen and watched Ye Xiu’s right hand.

“Bang!” When Falling Flower Palm came out, his right hand twitched. Chen Guo stared with wide eyes.

After clicking……

So small!! Chen Guo finally saw the movement, but she didn’t dare call that a movement because Ye Xiu’s right hand didn’t really move. After he clicked, Ye Xiu’s right hand just looked like it trembled.

A tremble……. Chen Guo put her right hand in front of her. When she tried doing the same as Ye Xiu, her movement was much larger than Ye XIu’s!

Does that even count as a movement???

Chen Guo suddenly realized that it was possible because for a dog hole that was only big enough for a person to squeeze into, in order to let out a sweep attack with the desired result, the action done had to be extremely precise. If the movement was too large, the weapon would hit the wall and the attack might not come out.

Even though it was only a normal attack, it was an extremely precise one.

Chapter 459 – Mistakes

Outside, there was another “Again!” The same person always said it. Judging from his tone, they could hear that he was getting more and more anxious.

They had already failed three times and were getting ready for their fourth attempt.

Chen Guo stopped looking at her screen and watched Ye Xiu’s right hand attentively.

I’m right! It’s just a tremble!

Chen Guo confirmed. Under her watchful eyes, every time he attacked, there would be a tiny tremble in order to make a small swinging motion.

“Too scary…..” Chen Guo muttered. After ruining his image with doing a shady business like scrap picking, he immediately followed with incredible microing worthy of a God. Chen Guo didn’t know what to think of him. She wasn’t sure if it was because this God was too twisted or if she liked to be conflicted.

While Chen Guo was figuring out what Ye Xiu was doing, the leader outside was completely furious.

“What the f*ck are you guys doing!! How can you guys not do something so simple???”

He could no longer calmly say “Again!” and was now beginning to whip them into shape.

This was already their sixth failure. None of them realized that someone was making them mess up from inside the dog hole. All they saw was that when the Wilderness Escort went flying towards the hole, the Wilderness Escort would always hit a wall. In short, their angle was always slightly off.

The Battle Mage responsible for using Falling Flower Palm was sweating like mad. He clearly had the largest responsibility among everyone.

“Standing Foolishly, go there. Peaceful Justice, come here!” The leader had already lost confidence in this Battle Mage and had someone take his place.

As these shouts came, the sounds of battle never stopped. The Wilderness Escort wouldn’t stop for them. He quickly got up and attacked. The players had to deal with him.

After failing six times, the players responsible for sending the Escort flying into the hole didn’t dare be negligent. They carefully adjusted the Wilderness Escort’s position before launching him into the air.

Paying attention to the timing and position, the newly switched Battle Mage unleashed a Falling Flower Palm, hitting the Wilderness Escort.

In order to reduce the difficulty, they moved the Wilderness Escort as close to the dog hole as possible.

The Wilderness Escort flew like a bullet into the dog hole. The boss had high resistance, so the Blow Away effect from the Falling Flower Palm wouldn’t be too effective, but it was enough to send it through the dog hole. If not, they wouldn’t have chosen a Battle Mage to do this task.

After the boom from the Falling Flower Palm, everyone went silent. They stared at the flying Wilderness Escort and only sounds of him and the earth rubbing together could be heard.

“IN!!!” Seeing the Wilderness Escort’s head enter the hole, the Battle Mage Peaceful Justice turned ecstatic. He was just about to shout this out, when the Wilderness Escort’s shoulder knocked into a wall. His body went askew and he popped out of the hole.

Seventh failure!

Peaceful Justice swallowed his words back into his stomach.

“F*CK!!!” The leader’s rage was about to reach its peak.

“Can you be more careful!!” The leader roared. He couldn’t say this was an easy task, which was why he had been able to endure the first three attempts, but seven failures was too much.

The others didn’t wait for him to speak again and immediately went for their eighth attempt.

Inside the room, Sparse Fragrance was so shocked he didn’t know what to say. They weren’t able to see Ye Xiu’s minute movement outside of the game, so their shock towards this was a bit different than Chen Guo’s.

Besides the shock from Ye Xiu’s movements in the dog hole, they were shocked that Ye Xiu had caused them to fail seven times already without the other side knowing.

Ye Xiu’s covert actions made them respect him even more!

After this next attempt, they could only hear the other side’s fury. The other side had stopped shouting “Again!” They all snickered, thinking that the other side was about to collapse from anger soon.

Suddenly, there was a “Bang!” The sound of a Falling Flower Palm.

They were all startled by it.

But Lord Grim’s movements didn’t slow down. He immediately did his previous sequence of actions again. But this time, Lord Grim didn’t send out an attack.

While everyone stared in astonishment, Lord Grim rolled to the side, avoiding the incoming bullets. In the chat, he typed: “They messed up……”

Everyone immediately understood.

They were all Heavenly Domain players and knew that stuffing the boss through the hole wasn’t an easy task even without anyone making them mess up.

With Ye Xiu’s words, they now knew that Ye Xiu had even been paying attention to this. He was even judging whether the opponents would mess up or not in case he didn’t need to act.

But at the same time, they also noticed that the previous Battle Mage’s skill must have been quite good. He hadn’t messed up the previous six times. As for the new one, it was only his second attempt and he had already made a mistake.

They thought about it for a bit and felt like it made sense. The other side wasn’t here to practice. In order to finish the task as fast as possible, they would obviously send out their best first. Unfortunately, this Battle Mage suffered an unjust wrong by Ye Xiu’s hands. The others saw that he was trash who couldn’t succeed after six tries and directly substituted him without giving a reason.

After failing eight times, roars of rage filled the outside.

He couldn’t be blamed for not having any patience. There just wasn’t any time for patience. They had gotten to their destination slightly earlier than the other guilds. If the other guilds arrived, even if they stuffed the Wilderness Escort into the hole, it would be pointless.

What he feared came true. As they began getting ready for their ninth attempt, someone suddenly shouted: “Herb Garden and Excellent Dynasty have come.”

“F*ck!” The leader was depressed, but he still ordered: “Everyone, hide in a corner. Have one team head in the other direction and have them see you run away.”

This was their last hope left. However, even he didn’t think their opponents would be so easily tricked by this. Right now, everyone was still looking for the boss. It wouldn’t be any trouble for them to split up their troops.

“This is probably our last chance!” The leader shouted. For this last attempt, he didn’t express his impatience. He hoped his calmness could raise their morale and let them succeed this time.

“You can do it!!” The surrounding players encouraged them.

The players responsible for this task had their morale boosted.

“We have to succeed……”

Ye Xiu and the others could hear how serious his tone was.

“I feel so sorry for them…..” Chen Guo sympathized.

“……”

The others used ellipses to express their sympathies as well.

They began their ninth attempt. Skills began being unleashed one after the other, clearer than any other time. Treasuring this final attempt, besides the players responsible for this task, the other players kept silent so that they wouldn’t disturb them in any way and prayed for their success.

“Bang!”

In the end, the final skill used was the Falling Flower Palm.

Everyone gripped their mice tightly. Whether they failed or succeeded depended on this.

They failed…….

The Wilderness Escort knocked into a wall in the hole and wouldn’t go through. It struggled up and open fired.

Roars of rage echoed through the air!

However, no one denounced the players responsible for sending the Wilderness Escort into the hole. These players were their team’s best players.

They couldn’t blame these nine failures on their skill. It was an issue of luck.

“Increase the DPS!!!”

An order came out. They would now try to kill the boss.

“They’re coming!!”

Inside the wall, the ones responsible with observing the outside through the crack in the wall found that more troops were joining the scene.

“Oh! They’re busy!”

Outside of the wall, a weird voice could be heard.

They didn’t know who it was, but they at least knew that others had arrived. As professional scrap pickers, Sparse Fragrance and the others had never participated in the struggle for the boss, but they had been a part of the shady business involving this. One minute they might be allies. The next minute they might be at each other’s throats.

The team who had failed to stuff the boss into the hole weren’t in a good situation. Don’t look at how these players had found the boss first. Because they were the first ones to find the boss, they were destined to fail. The first team to find the boss would have a certain advantage over everyone in damage dealt. The distribution of boss drops depended on whichever team did the most damage, so the first team would be everyone else’s first target.

“It’s just a Level 65 Wilderness Escort. I’m surprised you would actually go to the trouble of personally leading the team, Dawn.” The weird voice continued to speak.

“Is he famous?” Ye Xiu asked the others.

“Icy Dawn! One of Blue Brook Guild’s Five Great Experts!!” Sparse Fragrance was astonished that Ye Xiu didn’t even know this.

“Oh, one of Blue Brook Guild’s!” Ye Xiu said.

“Blue Brook Guild, Herb Garden, and Excellent Dynasty. It’s about to get rowdy.” Sparse Fragrance was very excited. As a scrap picker, the larger the scene the better, the more experts the better. More experts improved their chances of picking up better items.

“A wild boss……” Ye Xiu lamented. Even though he hadn’t played the game in many years, he knew the value of a wild boss. It was a resource the top guilds needed to fight for. It couldn’t be shared. Winner takes all. Thus, everyone scrambled for it. Even if it wasn’t useful for them, if it was useful for their enemy, then it was also their weakness. The influence of this could directly affect the pro scene.

Chapter 460 – High End Setting

Because of how the Heavenly Domain was set up, the value and importance of many things were vastly different from the normal servers.

In the normal servers, the competition between the guilds for the dungeon records were life and death battles. They were mainly sought after for the achievement. Through achievements, the guilds could prove their strength. Through strength, the guilds could grab the attention of new Glory players and turn them into their members and their team’s supporters. This was the value of dungeon records.

As for the Heavenly Domain, the idea was different.

In the Heavenly Domain, it couldn’t be said that there weren’t any noobs. After all, you could directly buy a Heavenly Domain account card and directly skip the normal servers to this high end server. However, most of the Heavenly Domain players had gone through the normal servers and completed the challenge.

These players had all played Glory for a good amount of time. From playing the game and watching the pro scene, they already knew very well which guilds had Clubs backing them. For these players, the Clubs no longer needed achievements to attract their attention. For them, the names of these guilds were huge gold-lettered signboards.

In addition, the top guilds in the Heavenly Domain were fundamentally stable. They didn’t need to do much to prove their existence.

In the Heavenly Domain, everyone still competed for dungeon records, but these weren’t done to prove their strength. After taking down a dungeon record, the system rewards were what everyone cared about. It was just that once a record reached a certain point, trying to break it was very difficult.

For the Heavenly Domain’s dungeon records, you can’t look at just the team composition.

The dungeon records here stored countless famous names. These were characters from the pro scene.

Pro players and accounts were not restricted from competing in the game. This was something the Glory Alliance had put in great effort to fight for. The famous speech made by the Alliance’s chairperson at that time was still enjoyed by today’s players.

In that speech, the chairperson enthusiastically promoted a huge benefit in relying on the game’s competition: pro player interaction.

No sport had the same level of pro player interaction as Glory did.

Football, basketball, F1, or even any other eSport may have huge amounts of fans, but for those fans, pro players are a higher level of existence. Normal people would have a hard time ever meeting them.

But in Glory, with the game as the foundation for the competition, the distance between pro players and normal players could be closed through the online platform. In the game, you might be able to run into your worshipped pro idol or you might have the chance to team up with your favorite pro player, dungeon, and kill the boss together.

The core idea raised from this speech truly aroused a huge number of Glory supporters. At that time, Glory had only just pushed into the Heavenly Domain. In order to promote this type of setup, pro players would undoubtedly attract many fans, so they didn’t have any problems with it either.

The game company accommodated for this feature by allowing pro players to play freely in the Heavenly Domain.

In the early years, the dream the Alliance chairperson had imagined came true. Speaking of this, at that time, pro players were the first bunch of characters to reach the Heavenly Domain. Normal players truly were able to play with pro players frequently. However, as Glory developed, the player base rose and the maps expanded, pro players became more and more popular. That initial dream was rarely seen now.

Pro players not running over to the game to play wasn’t something the Alliance restricted. It was just that the pro players were too afraid to log into their accounts.

With so many people gathering around to watch, the pro player wouldn’t be able to really do anything in the game. The crowd watching was only one aspect. In reality, the pro player would even sometimes be attacked. The attackers might want the pleasure of fighting against a real pro player or they might be attacking for the equipment on the pro player. There were all sorts of reasons. As a result, with how popular Glory was, that beautiful dream had already faded away.

Today’s pro players would only come on to challenge the hardest dungeon records. Because of this, the Heavenly Domain’s dungeon records were set by the pros.

And the reason they set these records was for the resources given by the system’s rewards.

Resources.

In the Heavenly Domain, the top guilds competed for resources.

The dungeon records were for this. The wild bosses were for this.

For the pro scene, the value of materials were far greater than the value of equipment. If one really wanted an equipment that dropped from in the game, it wasn’t too hard to get it. Self-made equipment were the high end equipment the Clubs pursued. And in order to create equipment, materials were necessary.

The production of materials in Glory spread throughout the game’s activities.

The levels of these materials weren’t the important point. Their rarity was what determined the material’s value.

The unique materials dropped from some wild bosses were very precious. Every year, these wild bosss only spawned up to 52 times. If the material was necessary for research of a self-made equipment, then there were only 52 chances to fail every year. And that was under the scenario where one obtained the necessary material every time.

How could this type of material not be valuable? And how could equipment made by this type of material not be powerful?

The Level 65 wild boss Wilderness Escort dropped a unique Revolver, Wildfire. In a normal players’ hands, this weapon alone would be extremely valuable. But in the pro scene, this Level 65 weapon wouldn’t be looked at.

However, these equipment might be used while researching self-made equipment, though its uses were quite narrow. For example, Wildfire could only be used for Gunner weapons. The less uses there were, the lower the need. Its value would obviously be lower as well.

But no matter how low its value was, as long as it was unique, it would always be more precious than those uncommon materials that could be found in dungeons. As a result, it still had to be fought for. Even if a team didn’t have any Gunner classes and there was no value of this gun to them, it could still be used a bargaining chip. No matter how useless it was to them, it would be a weakness to whomever needed it. The competition in the pro scene extended down into the game in this way.

“Fight! Why aren’t they fighting!!!” Sparse Fragrance couldn’t control himself as he typed out in impatience.

“The Wilderness Escort isn’t considered that valuable. The items it drops are fairly limited in use. How will the guilds deal with this……” Ye Xiu pondered.

“Can you see anything from that hole?” Sparse Fragrance asked Ye Xiu.

“I thought you were more familiar with that hole than I was…..” Ye Xiu replied.

“I’m just more familiar with going through it……” Sparse Fragrance said. He lied down on his stomach and stuffed his head into the hole to see if he could see the outside situation. Although the battle outside didn’t stop, it was still just Blue Brook Guild’s players dealing with the Wilderness Escort. A large scale PK wouldn’t just have this miniscule amount of movement.

“He won’t be discovered by doing that right?” Chen Guo said.

“No. There’s grass covering up the hole outside.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then wouldn’t that mean he won’t be able to see anything?” Chen Guo said.

“There might be a few cracks between the grass…..” Ye Xiu said.

“How despicable…..” Chen Guo was speechless.

Outside the walls, Blue Brook Guild’s Ice of Dawn couldn’t really do much. They had the chance, but who would have thought that their luck would be so bad and they would fail nine times before the competitors arrived. Their numbers were lower. Against another top guilds, in a direct fight, they would certainly lose.

The person talking to him was from Herb Garden. He was called Mugwort. Dawn of Ice recognized him. Mugwort was quite a famous figure in Herb Garden. In an activity like this, there would certainly be a fight, so the top guilds wouldn’t just randomly send some troops over to charge in. There would definitely be someone with reputation to lead the team.

The one leading Excellent Dynasty was called Dreamland, a famous expert from there and a core member of the guild. The people leading teams would always be these types of people.

“Ha ha, you two are pretty slow!” Dawn of Ice shouted to these two leaders.

“This place, he he, I think I know what Senior Dawn is trying to do!” Mugwort said. Club guilds understood the system quite well. The guild leader, the secondary guild leader, the team leaders all had their own purpose. They weren’t just placed there randomly because they knew each other well or because they were skilled. These were true core members of the guild with their own specific duties.

Ice of Dawn was one of Blue Brook Guild’s Five Great Experts. It was hard to say how skilled they were in the game, but in terms of responsibility, their importance in Blue Brook Guild wouldn’t be low. Compared to Mugwort’s and Dreamland’s status in their respective guilds, he would be considered a bit higher and someone at a Senior level.

“Really?” Ice of Dawn half-heartedly remarked. His line of sight was towards these two opposing guilds and not the dog hole behind him. At this moment, a familiar “Bang!” boomed. The sound of a Falling Flower Palm.

“What!!” This sound startled Ye Xiu.

Sparse Fragrance, who had his head in the dog hole, shot out like a bullet. He rolled backwards all the way until he crashed into the wall. In the chat, he spammed: “F*ck f*ck f*ck f*ck!!!!”

“What’s wrong……” Ye Xiu immediately went down to the dog hole to take a look and even he stared in shock.

Chapter 461 – A Traumatic Experience

Even the great God was astonished. Chen Guo turned her head towards Ye Xiu’s screen and saw the Wilderness Escort’s face staring back.

The Wilderness Escort had been stuffed in, but he wasn’t able to go completely through the dog hole because Sparse Fragrance had blocked his path. Falling Flower Palm’s Blow Away effect wasn’t strong enough against the boss, so it just stopped there unable to move any further.

As a result, the Wilderness Escort had half of his body stuck in the hole. Chen Guo could see the Wilderness Escort twisting and turning strangely and then the sounds of rapid gunfire.

“What is he doing……” Chen Guo stared.

Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry: “He’s trying to get up…… but he’s stuck in the hole. Does this boss know what that even means?”

“You don’t know this?” Chen Guo asked back.

“How would I know?” Ye Xiu was helpless. He knew some information on the Wilderness Escort, but he didn’t know about this sort of specific data similar to how he didn’t know of the existence of the dog hole.

“They’re probably going to try and push the boss in. The boss isn’t very smart right?” Chen Guo said.

“Hm or maybe……” Ye Xiu said.

“Could they want the boss to stay stuck there?” Just as Chen Guo finished saying this, the sounds of gunfire echoed again.

“He’s still trying to get up……” Ye Xiu was helpless.

When the Wilderness Escort got up, it would randomly fire and also let out a shockwave. Now that it was stuck in the hole, it couldn’t get up, but the random firing could still be done. However, the Escort couldn’t move his arm in the hole, so it could only fire at his own feet.

“Someone’s running this way!!”

At this moment, the two players responsible for observing the outside situation nervously reported.

“There’s nothing we can do! Log off!!!” Sparse Fragrance cried.

“Don’t be in such a hurry. Wait here!” Ye Xiu said, while having Lord Grim let out a Falling Flower Palm. With a bang, the Wilderness Escort was pushed out.

“What are you doing!!!!” Sparse Fragrance shouted. This would undoubtedly expose them.

“Wait for me here!!” Right as Ye Xiu said this, the others watched as Lord Grim slipped out from the hole. They stared dumbly for a moment, before suddenly realizing that he had slid out using a Sharpshooter skill.

After failing to send the Wilderness Escort into the dog hole nine times, they accidentally got it in on the next try. It made Ice of Dawn feel like God was playing with them.

With the other guilds already there, sending the Wilderness Escort into the hole was completely pointless. It was just that the players had done the same set of movements so many times that they inadvertently did it. The Battle Mage looked as if he were about to make a big gamble when he shot out the palm. Who would have thought that this strike would actually send the Wilderness Escort into the hole.

It hadn’t gone all the way through, but no one thought much of it.

After all, this had only been done accidentally. The Battle Mage hadn’t been very careful with his move and hadn’t paid attention to his position. As a result, even though the angle had been extremely accurate, the distance wasn’t optimal, so it made sense it would only stop halfway.

Following afterwards, the Wilderness Escort fired his gun from the hole directly towards the players outside.

Everyone outside and inside had been amazed at this strange scene. Just when everyone was astonished at this sight, the Wilderness Escort fired shots a second time trying to get up and then suddenly slipped out.

Even if the boss had been coded to be able to crawl out from the hole, it should be able to slid out so perfectly right?

“There are people inside!!!” Someone immediately shouted. Just as someone was about to go run inside and check, there was a woosh and sure enough, someone slipped out from the dog hole. That someone got up smoothly and shouted: “Everyone, don’t panic! It’s me. It’s me.”

“It’s me. It’s me.” was quite an arrogant thing to say. It was as if everyone should recognize him.

However, no one felt that he was arrogant once they saw the ID on top of his head. Everyone was surprised: It’s him!

Lord Grim. In recent times, he was an extremely popular character. Rumors even said that he was God Ye Qiu. The debate on whether or not he really was him was still going on.

Blue Brook Guild’s Ice of Dawn and Excellent Dynasty’s Dreamland had all sorts of feelings arise.

They had finally met in the Heavenly Domain.

These two had similar thoughts.

Ice of Dawn once gone with Changing Spring as well as the other great experts of Blue Brook Guild to try and save the situation in the tenth server. He could be considered as someone who had competed with Ye Xiu before, but had lost. They had practiced bitterly in order to set a dungeon record, but their efforts had been pointless.

When the great experts returned to the Heavenly Domain, they came back dejected and depressed. At that time, they had even felt somewhat grateful for Poplar Beach. When Poplar Beach challenged Lord Grim, he became a huge focus in the guild. The guild leader had personally led experts to support him, but he returned in embarrassment.

After that, they quickly found out that Lord Grim was actually Ye Qiu. This information had been personally confirmed by Blue River and others. Even though right now, the media were obfuscating it, they had a hard time doubting it.

From a psychological perspective, if he really was God Ye Qiu, then that would be great.

From that point onwards, they knew that even though they had avoided competing with him in the tenth server, how could a person like God Ye Qiu not make any movements in the Heavenly Domain?

Especially after the Thousand Waves Lake campaign……

Ice of Dawn hadn’t participated in that battle, but Changing Spring had personally led the troops. Ice of Dawn was well aware of his own status. From then on, the resistance towards Lord Grim in the tenth server had disappeared. They began preparing for the arrival of the God in the Heavenly Domain.

At that time, they had analyzed as an unspecialized, he could only come at Level 50. They would have a 20 level advantage and a huge numbers advantage as well. Defeating him wouldn’t be a problem!

But then, when Lord Grim actually arrived, Changing Spring gave the order to sit and watch.

Changing Spring had said that there wouldn’t be any pressure, but when he actually came, they were told to sit and watch.

Ice of Dawn didn’t look down on this order. He even felt a sense of relief.

It was true that with a numbers advantage and a 20 level advantage, even if he was a God and an unspecialized, taking him down wouldn’t be a problem. Ice of Dawn had felt this was true at that time as well.

However, when Lord Grim actually arrived, Changing Spring’s orders weren’t wrong either.

The first order was a fight. The second order was to avoid first.

These two completely contradictory plans were both very reasonable.

In reality, his interactions with Lord Grim were very shallow. He had only lost once in that dungeon record competition. He wasn’t like Blue River, who had to toss and turn with Lord Grim the whole time. However, that single loss had left a huge shadow in Ice of Dawn’s heart. Because only they knew how hard they had worked for that low leveled dungeon record.

Limit!

Even though it was a low leveled dungeon, they had done it to their limit.

Their limit had been completely broken without any effort. The sense of defeat in that instant was something outsiders wouldn’t be able to understand.

This was where his trauma came from.

Lord Grim’s next actions hadn’t been personally experienced by Ice of Dawn, but Ice of Dawn had paid attention to them. He had even noticed Blue River’s wavering.

Ice of Dawn admired this old friend greatly. He felt like his friend’s wavering had been a show of his resolve. Ice of Dawn could completely understand him.

It wasn’t that they weren’t trying hard. It was that their opponent was too terrifying!

Ice of Dawn couldn’t help but think of his traumatic experience in that low leveled dungeon and how hard he had worked.

When Lord Grim was in the tenth server, the guilds had watched him with great care. They had paid attention to Lord Grim’s movements.

But when Lord Grim stepped into the Heavenly Domain, their guild wasn’t the only one watching. The entire Heavenly Domain was watching.

He truly deserves to be called a God!

Ice of Dawn thought. A God’s Heavenly Challenge should be that eye-catching.

Afterwards, he began playing tricks one after the other. Lord Grim’s fame had began in the tenth server to the Heavenly Domain all the way to the entire Glory scene.

Pro players began watching him. The media began reporting on him, calling him a mystery man or whatever. All sorts of guesses, information, rumors, and drama flew around.

His fame seemed to have reached the entire world.

It even seemed as if Blue Brook Guild had forgotten their original purpose for watching him.

It’d be best to just keep watching like this!

After Ice of Dawn looked through all these news reports, he even had this type of thought. Today, without any preparation, Lord Grim suddenly popped out from a hole in front of him.

“Ice of Dawn!”

Ice of Dawn was startled. It seemed as if someone was calling his name.

“Haven’t we met before?” He heard the same voice continue.

He knew who was talking.

“I’ve been to the tenth server before.” Ice of Dawn replied.

“Yeah, I have a pretty good relationship with your Blue Brook Guild too! Would you like some help?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Ah?” Ice of Dawn stared blankly.

“Let’s ally with Excellent Dynasty and get rid of Herb Garden first!” Ye Xiu said.

It was Herb Garden’s turn to stare blankly. Following afterwards, the leader Mugwort laughed: “You think everything will go as you say?”

Lord Grim had already walked forward. Ye Xiu shouted: “Excellent Dynasty, stand with me! Didn’t you hear the news? I’m Ye Qiu!”

Chapter 462 – To Catch a Band of Thieves, Catch the Leader First

The first person to almost fall over hearing Ye Xiu’s words was Chen Guo. Her complicated and conflicting feelings instantly grew even further. However, as someone who had broken away from Excellent Era and as a fan of Ye Xiu, Chen Guo was looking forward to what would happen next. She stared at Ye Xiu’s screen and even had the urge to grab Ye Xiu’s headphones.

In game, everyone on scene froze.

Lord Grim was Ye Qiu. This was an issue that was still being debated, however, most views pointed towards this. As normal players, they might not have much authority to say anything, but they were free to choose whichever side they liked.

To choose to believe or not to believe.

Ice of Dawn was a believer. Thus, at that instant, his emotions surged. He quickly realized what these words entailed.

This was as if Blue Rain’s Yu Wenzhou or Huang Shaotian appeared in front of them and told them to take down Herb Garden. Even if Ice of Dawn were alone, he wouldn’t hesitate to jump into the flames and do as he was told.

When these words came out, Mugwort’s expression immediately changed. Of course, in the game, the others could only see his character and not his actual face.

As for Excellent Dynasty’s players, when Lord Grim suddenly slid out from the hole, they were already in conflict.

Was Lord Grim really Ye Qiu?

This topic was without a doubt discussed the most intensely in Excellent Dynasty. The guild leader, Chen Yehui, saw this, but it wouldn’t be easy to stop them. He could only send a few of his trusted subordinates and have them lead the direction of the discussion. He wasn’t trying to prove that Lord Grim wasn’t Ye Qiu, but rather to destroy Ye Qiu’s image among Excellent Era players.

He had thought of doing this a long time ago, but he was always too afraid to do so. Up until now, using the Club’s public statements as a base, he used those as arguments to being carrying it out now.

However, using this chance to tarnish Ye Qiu’s image in Excellent Dynasty had only just begun. There hadn’t been any significant effects yet! Excellent Dynasty’s players were still relying on their own judgement to make a decision. Some of them firmly believed that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu. Some didn’t believe it, while some weren’t sure.

At this moment, Lord Grim leaped out in front of them and yelled out an “I’m Ye Qiu.”

Truthfully……… if he really was Ye Qiu, they weren’t convinced that he would be so direct. This was because although Ye Qiu was a God, he had never shown himself outside of the game. Fans knew very little about him. Otherwise, why would Chen Guo be so conflicted? She had her own thoughts on how this God would act, but his actions were inconsistent with her own thoughts, which was why she was conflicted.

Excellent Dynasty’s team leader Dreamland was one of the guild’s core members. When Lord Grim suddenly jumped out, claiming that he was Ye Qiu, and then gave an order, for a moment, he was unsure of what to do. Dreamland had his own thoughts on whether or not Lord Grim was Ye Qiu though. But at this moment, he was leading the team for Excellent Dynasty. Even if Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, if he carried out his orders, he would be blindly following his idol and perhaps not working in the guild’s interests.

What were the guild’s interests right now? It should be to first kill off Blue Brook Guild because Blue Brook Guild already had the damage dealt advantage on the Wilderness Escort. It didn’t make sense to cooperate with them and put an end to Herb Garden who was in a similar situation as them!

Thinking of this, Dreamland immediately typed out a message in the team chat, ordering everyone to stay put for now.

While he was typing out this message, a few Excellent Dynasty players had already started running towards Lord Grim. When the message came out, they were suddenly at a loss again.

Dreamland was having a huge headache. He immediately went to ask Chen Yehui for advice.

Chen Yehui was also very startled when he received this message. Was Ye Qiu finally using his identity as a weapon?

Chen Yehui regretted that the person he had sent to lead the team wasn’t his own trusted aide. However, since Dreamland was someone who had the power to lead a team, Chen Yehui also had a certain understanding towards him. This person understood the importance of working in the guild’s and the team’s benefits. At this moment, he probably had made his own decision already and didn’t listen to Ye QIu’s orders yet.

Thinking of this, Chen Yehui relaxed a bit. As he replied to Dreamland, he reminded himself to cleanse those who held different views. Excellent Dynasty’s core members had already tried to rope in as many non Ye Qiu fans as possible. In the beginning, Chen Yehui didn’t think that they would make any difference because he hadn’t thought Ye Qiu would actually come to the game to fight with them. Facing this type of situation, he should have cleansed them all long ago. Chen Guo was upset! Why hadn’t he done this earlier?

Chen Yehui was very careful with his reply to Dreamland. Dreamland was currently neutral. If he directly talked bad about Ye Qiu, it might have the opposite effect. Anyone could see Ye Qiu’s impact on Excellent Era’s achievements. Making them flip sides with just a few words wouldn’t be that easy. It wasn’t a good idea to do it at this time either. In Chen Yehui’s eyes, Dreamland wasn’t a reckless, brain-dead fan. Thus, his following command was to let Dreamland weigh the situation and give priority to the guild’s interests.

Give priority to the guild’s interests!

In Dreamland’s eyes, Lord Grim’s orders wouldn’t be working in the guild’s interests!

Dreamland hadn’t said anything the entire time. Besides the few in Excellent Dynasty who had slipped away in the beginning, no one else had moved. And once the ones who slipped away realized that their actions weren’t aligned with their team, they immediately returned. From this, it could be seen that such discipline in a Club guild was something that players guilds made for fun didn’t have.

Was no one in Excellent Dynasty as fan of Ye Qiu’s?

Seeing how some of them had run off, there were definitely fans!

However, when Ye Xiu blurted out an “I’m Ye Qiu’, some of them wavered.

It was similar to how Chen Guo almost fell over. Ye Xiu’s actions didn’t fit with their image of God, which was why they hesitated. The initial few saw that everyone wasn’t moving, so they began to waver too.

“Why isn’t anyone moving?” Ye Xiu said. Lord Grim walked over as if he were going to stand with Excellent Dynasty.

“Uh……” Dreamland wanted to say something, when Lord Grim suddenly stopped.

Dreamland was startled, when suddenly a shout could be heard. He turned his head. Lord Grim was now amongst Herb Garden’s troops.

Shadow Clone Technique!

What’s going on?

Dreamland was at a loss. Then, he saw Herb Garden’s Mugwort in the air. He wasn’t doing this himself. Lord Grim, who had suddenly moved next to him, had done it.

How was this done? Dreamland didn’t know. He hadn’t seen it in time. When he turned over, all he saw was Mugworts flying out as well as a bunch of shouts from Herb Garden’s players as they surrounded him and began to attack.

“Take him down!!”

Mugworts fell in Blue Brook Guild’s territory.

Ice of Dawn was also startled, but after hearing Ye Xiu suddenly say “Take him down”, he suddenly woke up with a start and also shouted a “Take him down!!” Blue Brook Guild’s players immediately surrounded Mugworts.

Mugworts might be a top player in the game, but there was no way he could fight against an entire group of experts. His Quick Recover had been done beautifully, but his hopes had already withered away.

Too careless!

He had seen that Dreamland wasn’t siding with the self-proclaimed Ye Qiu and was just about to tease him, but who would have thought he would suddenly sneak attack like that…….

Against a group of wolves, Mugworts only had half his heath left. He knew that he wouldn’t be able to be saved. He could only turn his head hatefully and see the same result for Lord Grim.

The results were disappointing though.

Ye Xiu hadn’t gone in on impulse. He had calculated everything beforehand. Before sending Mugworts flying away, he had already determined an escape route. When Mugworts looked back, Lord Grim had already run away.

“Beautiful!” Ice of Dawn praised. He ordered his subordinates to go to Lord Grim’s side to block the incoming Herb Garden players.

“To catch thieves, first catch the leader!” Ice of Dawn laughed as Mugworts fell. On paper, the number of players on Herb Garden’s side was about the same as Blue Brook Guild’s, but without a leader, it would be a one-sided defeat.

“You’re right.”

Ice of Dawn heard Lord Grim give a praise as well. Afterwards, he discovered that he was suddenly in the air as well.

What’s going on?

Ice of Dawn wasn’t sure what happened.

“Did I press jump?” Ice of Dawn looked down at his keyboard. His left hand was far away from the jump button.

After that, he heard a ton of angry shouts. Didn’t he just hear this sound before? It sounded very similar to when Lord Grim had been surrounded by Herb Garden’s group.

“Take him down!”

Then, he heard another shout he had heard before.

Ice of Dawn fell to the ground. He had even forgotten to use Quick Recover. When he looked up, he saw a bunch of “Guild Excellent Dynasty” tags……

Ice of Dawn suddenly understood what had happened. He was just like Mugworts. He struggled to adjust his camera, but he wasn’t even able to do that. As a mage class with only cloth armor, he died even faster.

There were now two teams without heads.

Excellent Dynasty’s players instantly understood what was going on.

“KILL!!” Everyone shouted.

But kill who? Who had they decided to kill?

Chen Guo had her mouth wide open as she stared at Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu was as calm as ever.

Chapter 463 – This Chapter Doesn’t Have a Title

Chapter 463

The dead Ice of Dawn didn’t hurry and revive. He only wanted to cough up blood right now.

Ally with Excellent Dynasty first and get rid of Herb Garden?

It was true that Herb Garden’s Mugwort had been the first to die, but right after that, he got killed. Why didn’t you inform me beforehand?

The sad Ice of Dawn became a ghost, floating around as he watched the following battle that ensued between the three guilds.

Herb Garden’s players pounced towards Blue Brook Guild. Blue Brook Guild’s players charged at Excellent Dynasty. Originally, they had wanted to rescue their senior, but their seniors had died so quickly. There was no point in rescuing them, but the conflict had already erupted.

But without anyone to lead them, Blue Brook Guild and Herb Garden didn’t have any specific strategy in mind. They simply fought with revenge on their minds. As long as the person in front of them didn’t have their guild’s name, they would immediately attack.

“You really are…… too despicable!!!” Chen Guo watched with wide eyes for a good half a minute before she blurted this out. Her voice didn’t carry any hints of delight. The word “despicable” wasn’t enough to describe her feelings.

Especially after seeing Ye Xiu open up Pandora’s Box and then immediately hide behind Guild Excellent Dynasty.

Chen Guo had thought that after taking down the two guilds’ heads, Ye Xiu would also go and take down Excellent Dynasty’s Dreamland. But he didn’t. With this, Excellent Dynasty still had their leader and held the advantage. However, she didn’t even have time to complain when she realized that this wasn’t actually the case.

The guild in the worst situation was Blue Brook Guild.

The Wilderness Escort’s aggro was still on them. After killing Mugworts, they had now aggroed Herb Garden as well. In addition, by attacking Excellent Dynasty, they established their aggro, too. Fighting against three enemies at once wasn’t something that Blue Brook Guild had intended, but it was already too late to regret their decisions.

After Blue Brook Guild, the guild in the second worst situation wasn’t Herb Garden, but rather Excellent Dynasty.

With Dreamland leading Excellent Dynasty, their formation was very stable. However, they couldn’t keep up with the chaotic fighting. This was because Lord Grim had sent the two enemy seniors to their deaths at the start. It had been such a surprise that the two seniors weren’t even able to leave behind any words before they were surrounded and killed. Lord Grim had established the greatest aggro.

Herb Garden and Blue Brook Guild didn’t have any specific strategy in mind and were attacking purely based off of emotions. The majority of them wanted to rush at Lord Grim and kill him. Of course, Lord Grim was now hiding behind Excellent Dynasty.

Excellent Dynasty’s players didn’t stop him.

This was because Lord Grim hadn’t attacked their senior Dreamland, but had killed the other two guilds’ seniors. It was obvious whose side Lord Grim was on.

He really is Ye Qiu!!!

Excellent Dynasty’s players grew excited. As a result, without any second thoughts, they protected Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, stopping the incoming aggression.

This was clearly another decision based off of emotions.

Even though Excellent Dynasty’s team had a leader at their head, they didn’t have an appropriate strategy set either. From a strategical perspective, they weren’t any different from Herb Garden and Blue Brook Guild.

Something’s not right!!!

Excellent Dynasty’s Dreamland quickly realized that the situation wasn’t looking good. Although the heads of the other two guilds had fallen, Excellent Dynasty was now burdened with both guilds attacking them. Dreamland didn’t know what to do in order to stabilize the situation.

In terms of strategy, everyone was acting on impulse.

In terms of tactics, even though Blue Brook Guild and Herb Garden didn’t have anyone leading them, the groups were still in formation.

In large-scale battles like these, teams were the unit of measurement and each team was made up of groups. Each group would have a group leader. Right now, the two guild teams were only missing their team leader who coordinated the groups. However, each group still had their group leaders commanding.

In other words, the two guilds were no longer whole entities, but they still had countless small entities battling. If it was just one on one, Excellent Dynasty would have certainly won because of their advantage as a whole. But with two guilds attacking them, there were too many small entities, leaving them with a numbers disadvantage, giving Dreamland even greater pressure.

After all, he was just an expert in-game. His ability to lead wasn’t at a pro level. If not, he might be able to beat the many with only a few.

Pro level…….

Dreamland immediately thought of one person, who was at the top even among the pros.

Dreamland turned around frantically and quickly found Lord Grim’s position. He was just sitting amidst their troops in the back and looked like he was just there to cheer them on.

Dreamland was quite fast at weighing the situation. It could be said that Lord Grim had created their current predicament, but right now he was in a safe spot outside the battle. In the area where the battle was taking place, players from the three guilds were rapidly falling.

Was Lord Grim really helping Excellent Dynasty or did he have another motive?

Dreamland didn’t go and consider whether or not Lord Grim was Ye Qiu. He was only thinking about Lord Grim’s movements and he suddenly felt uneasy.

If Lord Grim had truly wanted to help Excellent Dynasty, the amount of help he was giving them was far from enough!

Uneasy, Dreamland retreated until he reached Lord Grim. Soon afterwards, he sent an invite over to him. However, the system quickly notified him that Lord Grim was already in a party!

He was already in a party!

This notification immediately aroused Dreamland’s suspicions even further.

“What are you trying to do?” Dreamland blurted out.

“Picking up scraps!”

Three simple words struck like thunder. Dreamland was immediately taken aback.

Picking up scraps…….

As a person who frequently led teams, Dreamland obviously knew about this. Dreamland had a lot of experience with scrap pickers.

But it was the first time Dreamland had encountered such a high-end scrap picker.

Normal scrap pickers were more passive. They could only wait until a good opportunity appeared. But Lord Grim? He wasn’t waiting. He took the initiative to create the opportunity. This was completely raising the concept of scrap pickers to another level. Such a scrap picker was no longer just picking up items at his convenience……

“Just like I expected!” Chen Guo slammed the table and shouted when she heard Ye Xiu say “Picking up scraps.”

She had noticed that after Lord Grim killed the two seniors and escaped, Excellent Dynasty’s situation wasn’t looking good. She felt like Ye Xiu wasn’t helping any one guild. She had already made some guesses towards Ye Xiu’s plan and Ye Xiu had helped prove it to her.

“You’re really good at picking up scraps!” Chen Guo said.

“Of course. You have to work hard to pick up scraps, too!” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo didn’t know how to assess this. He said he was here to pick up scraps and he really was going to. Plus, he was making such a big commotion for it. He really deserved to be called a Glory textbook. He was a God even at scrap picking.

Dreamland now knew the truth, but he didn’t immediately attack Lord Grim.

For one, he didn’t think that he was Lord Grim’s opponent. After all, Lord Grim had rolled his way through Level 70 players for the Heavenly Challenge.

Secondly, Dreamland was still weighing the pros and cons. He could kill Lord Grim, but it wouldn’t stop him from suffering any less casualties.

What made Dreamland’s head hurt was still how he couldn’t control the battlefield.

With Lord Grim’s movements, not just Herb Garden and Blue Brook Guild, but even their Excellent Dynasty’s players considered him as one of their own.

His poisonous actions couldn’t be cleared away with just a few words. By the time he finished speaking, everyone would already be dead.

Dreamland didn’t forget that they were there for the boss. With their current situation, how could they have any chance of killing the boss? The conflict with Blue Brook Guild and Herb Garden was completely pointless and it was simply the perfect situation for the scrap pickers to do their dirty work.

“Retreat!” Dreamland ordered after thinking for a while.

Excellent Dynasty’s players were startled.

“Retreat?” Quite a few questioned his order.

“How could we have any chance of killing the boss in this situation?” Dreamland wouldn’t mention scrap picking. He simply reminded them what their objective was.

Everyone quickly woke up. They realized that their struggle had been completely pointless!

Excellent Dynasty’s players prepared to retreat, but Blue Brook Guild and Herb Garden continued to act on impulse. Seeing Excellent Dynasty retreat, they believed that they had the advantage and immediately began fighting even more intensely.

Dreamland was very sad. By retreating, he boosted their opponent’s morale. Blue Brook Guild and Herb Garden were missing a rational brain behind them right now. Not having a leader to guide them hurt Excellent Dynasty in the end.

Dreamland didn’t forget Lord Grim. He was planning on making an ambush to send Lord Grim to the enemy troops and have him experience Mugwort’s and Ice of Dawn’s fall. But when he looked over, he realized that Lord Grim was extremely devilish. He had previously been sitting there watching the show, but now that the situation had changed, he began to move, not giving him any chance to do so.

“How are things going? How are things going?”

At this moment, Sparse Fragrance and the others were very anxious. Hearing the shouts and curses outside, they were feeling tormented. They had only just met Ye Xiu. How could they have so much trust in him? Hearing how chaotic it seemed outside, they were doubting whether Ye Xiu was intentionally not telling them any information and picking up scraps for himself before talking.

“Be careful when going out from the hole.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Got it!” Sparse Fragrance and the others had been impatiently waiting for awhile now and lined up to leave the hole. Sparse Fragrance was the first to come out. When he turned his camera around, he saw the chaotic fight outside and immediately turned elated. As an experienced scrap picker, Sparse Fragrance quickly discovered the valuable equipment scattered across the ground and hastily rushed over.

And at this moment, a gray shadow suddenly rushed down from a rooftop on another side.

Chapter 464 – Deception

Sparse Fragrance glanced in the direction that gray shadow was heading towards and immediately knew that this shadow had the same goal as him: the equipment scattered on the ground. As a professional scrap picker, it wasn’t his first time encountering this sort of scenario. Sparse Fragrance hastily used a Triple Slash and rapidly rushed his way over, moving faster than that gray shadow.

Sparse Fragrance delightedly shifted his mouse to click on the equipment, when several people suddenly warned him in the party chat. Surprised, he saw his screen shake and his character flew away.

Sparse Fragrance hastily turned his camera around to see how his enemy had sent him flying. However, he didn’t get his answer. All he saw was the gray shadow land on the ground and toss the equipment into his bag.

“F*CK!” Sparse Fragrance cursed. Quickly, he saw the name of the gray shadow who had snatched the equipment first: Deception.

“It’s Deception!!!!” The others in the party chat shouted.

“You guys know him?” Chen Guo had slipped out from the hole as well. Compared to these professional scrap pickers, she was clearly more reserved. She wasn’t like Sparse Fragrance who eyed the scattered equipment and immediately pounced towards it like a hungry tiger. As the last one who came out, she had seen Sparse Fragrance get sent flying away. In the beginning, she find anything special about the shadow, but after hearing everyone else shout his name, she looked over and noticed that besides his name, he didn’t have a guild affiliation. This meant that he most definitely wasn’t a part of one of the three guilds there.

“You’ve never heard of him? He’s an extremely fierce scrap picker.” The other party members introduced him to Chen Guo.

Chen Guo was new to the scrap picking industry and had never paid attention to it. Hearing their tone, this person was probably a very famous character in their industry.

“How fierce?” Chen Guo asked. Then, she saw Deception suddenly dash out. He lifted his ninja blade and shot out a blood arrow. Following afterwards, a person fell. This person seemed to have dropped something, but before anyone could see it clearly, Deception had already tossed it into his bag.

“What?” Chen Guo wasn’t able to wrap her head around what had just happened. But Deception didn’t stop there. He wandered through the chaotic battle and wherever he roamed, the gold coins glinting on the ground as well as the equipment scattered around disappeared. Whenever he waved his hands, a blood arrow would shoot out and a player would die. Around ten seconds later, the ground had become much cleaner. Four people had already fallen to his ninja blade. They had been killed instantly without a trace.

Not just Chen Guo, but even the people fighting in the battle had only just realized what was going on. And when they saw the ID on top of his head, the players of the Three Great Guilds immediately focused their attention to him.

As players who frequently participated in team activities such as killing bosses, they weren’t a stranger to this name.

Deception was a scrap picker who caused a headache to every guild team.

This person wasn’t in any guild nor had anyone ever seen him in a team. He worked alone and came and went as he pleased.

Compared to normal scrap pickers, this person had a goal. He wasn’t like normal scrap pickers who would only look for dropped equipment. He would even look at the players fighting in the battle and kill them for their equipment. Deception wasn’t just a scrap picker, he knew how to loot.

The amount of damage this scrap picker had dealt to the guilds were even greater than normal scrap pickers. This was because he was an expert and was an expert at sneak attacks and one hit kills. His outstanding looting and assassinations sometimes even changed the outcome of a battle. For example, a team might be killing a boss and although the battle was difficult, they could definitely beat it. But then Deception would arrive to pick up scraps and the equipment scattered on the ground wasn’t enough for him. He would see that the equipment on the tank in the team looked good and would look for an opportunity to assassinate him.

When the tank died, if the tank didn’t drop the equipment Deception wanted, then he would shake his head and leave. But without a tank, how was the team supposed to take down the boss?

In a scenario like this, how could he not be more troublesome than a normal scrap picker?

Thus, after seeing the ID on top of his head, a barrage of attacks suddenly erupted. All sorts of skills flew towards him like a storm.

Consequently, tragedy struck.

The three teams of the three guilds weren’t immune to each other’s damage. When they attacked, they wouldn’t hesitate to aim for others at the same time. After all, the teams were enemies of each other. If they could kill Deception as well as their other enemies simultaneously, it would be killing two birds with one stone.

A wave of sword light and artillery fire swept over the field. A huge hole appeared in the crowd. Corpses piled on top of each other on the ground and countless equipment glittered in the sun. Sparse Fragrance and the others began drooling. However, in an area that had just been under concentrated fire, even if they had another ten of them, they wouldn’t dare rush over to pick up equipment.

Sparse Fragrance and the others were very depressed. Suddenly, in the empty space, a shadow broke through the earth. Deception had once again appeared in front of everyone. No one was able to respond in time as all of the equipment scattered among the pile of corpses was picked clean.

“Underground Tunneling Technique! Amazing!”

Chen Guo heard Ye Xiu praise.

Chen Guo obviously knew what the Underground Tunneling Technique was. It was a Level 35 Ninja skill in which the user went below the ground to ambush the target. That was what the skill was supposed to be used for, but a person could use it creatively. Deception had used this skill to avoid the attacks. He quickly unleashed the skill, hid underground, and escaped from the storm. After jumping out from the ground, he immediately picked up all of the items.

As a scrap picker, up until now, Deception had looted quite a few items. Even if he died and half of what he had picked up was dropped, he had already done an exceptional job.

The people of the Three Great Guilds were naturally extremely furious. Seeing Deception in the middle of the empty space, they immediately fired another storm of attacks and turned him into ashes……

But no matter how fierce your attacks were, it wasn’t possible to get such a result. Their attacks had only hit a shadow clone.

Where was his real body? Everyone began searching for him.

“Here!!” Someone shouted. Everyone once again saw another blood arrow fly forward. But when this person fell, his body didn’t drop anything. The Heavenly Domain might have a high drop rate, but it wasn’t guaranteed.

“Pauper!” Seeing the players of the Three Great Guilds pounce towards him, Deception actually complained and sent a sad face on top of his head. At the same time, he leaped up and swiped with his ninja blade and stuck into a wall. In the air, he bent his body and his two legs stepped onto the ninja blade. He jumped again and grabbed the ninja blade out from the wall back into his hands.

This was one of the features of the ninja blade. The hilt had a long rope attached to it. By using the ninja blade as a foothold on a wall, the Ninja could jump again. Then, using the rope, the Ninja could take back the ninja blade. There was also the ninja blade’s sheath, which was hollow. At certain moments, it could be used to stay airborne a bit longer.

Ninja blades could be used by other classes too, but many of its functions could only be utilized by a Ninja. In addition, many Ninja skills required ninja blades as a weapon.

“This Ninja is pretty good!!!” After seeing Deception throw down a “Pauper!” and flip over the wall, Ye Xiu praised him again. The players of the Three Great Guilds saw that Deception was about to leave with a whole bunch of items and weren’t going to just give up like that. Any class which could go over the wall went over the wall. For this Deception, the Three Great Guilds suddenly allied together.

Climbing the wall and looking around, hm, he’s not a part of my guild, let’s just attack him. No leader! In the end, it came down to the two guilds not having a leader. Excellent Dynasty had one, but with the other two guilds fighting chaotically, Dreamland couldn’t tell everyone to not resist, so everyone began fighting amongst each other again.

“What do we do?” Chen Guo looked across the ground. There were still lots of equipment lying around!

“Pick up scraps!” Ye Xiu said. He had his Lord Grim jump into the air. He raised his Thousand Chance Umbrella above his head and with a click, the umbrella canopy was retracted. The joints connecting the eight umbrella bones turned into four long ones. “Shiu shiu shiu shiu” as they rotated. Like a helicopter, Lord Grim flew in Deception’s direction.

“Where are you going?” Chen Guo was surprised.

“All the good stuff has been taken away by that guy. I’m going to go take them back.” Ye Xiu said.

“You call that looting? That’s called dropping!” Chen Guo said.

‘Yeah! I’m learning from him!” Ye Xiu replied.

Chen Guo thought about it. It was true. Deception wasn’t a scrap picker who simply picked up equipment. He would even take the initiative to make a move. It hadn’t even been a minute yet and he had already killed several players from the Three Great Guilds.

“I’m going too!” Chen Guo wasn’t that interested in picking up scraps and felt like Ye Xiu chasing after that guy would be more interesting. She hastily headed over towards where Ye Xiu was moving.

“Be careful. That guy isn’t so simple.” Ye Xiu said.

“I can see that.” Chen Guo said. To make these players from the Three Great Guilds to go into a rage like that clearly indicated how extraordinary he was. It hadn’t yet been a minute since he arrived and although the Three Great Guilds were a bit in a mess with two of the guilds not even having a leader, to be able to accomplish such a feat showed how he wasn’t any normal expert.

It was more obvious when one compared him to Sparse Fragrance’s group. They were in a group of five, yet they didn’t dare jump into the fray. They were all very careful with every step they took and ran over when they saw a good opportunity. How could that even be compared to the uproar Deception had created?

Chen Guo now understood that even for something despicable like scrap picking, different players had different styles.

Who exactly was this Deception? Chen Guo wondered. She knew that Sparse Fragrance’s group might know, but she reckoned that they didn’t have time to answer her. She also had to hurry up and move too, so she didn’t have any time to ask either. Thus, she called for Tang Rou: “Little Tang, could you help me look up someone using these three keywords: Glory, scrap picker, Deception?”

Chapter 465 – Pursuit

Tang Rou wasn’t too busy, so when she heard Chen Guo’s request, she immediately looked it up.

Glory, scrap picker, Deception (荣耀、拾荒、毁人不倦). Apart from the first search term, Tang Rou had trouble getting the other two terms correct.1 Finally, she got the information she wanted and read it out loud.

Not just Chen Guo, Ye Xiu also straightened up to listen. Unfortunately, the results didn’t really give them any new information.

A lone operator, a ruthless scrap picker. The information on him could be summarized with these two phrases. Most of the comments were angry complaints and curses from players who had their equipment stolen by him. Besides that, a few people thought Deception had an interesting personality and wrote some random romantic fanfiction stories of him. Tang Rou hadn’t even read the first sentence, when Chen Guo stopped her.

“It’s just a bunch of random nonsense.” Chen Guo remarked.

“Ha ha, how mysterious.” Ye Xiu commented.

“Can we catch him?” Chen Guo had almost reached the coordinates Ye Xiu had given her. She could even see Lord Grim now, but she couldn’t see Deception.

“Of course. That guy has so much stuff on him. How fast could he run?” Ye Xiu smiled.

“But I don’t see him. Do you know where he is?” Chen Guo looked towards Ye Xiu’s screen. There was no sign of Deception there either. Ye Xiu’s movements were extremely quick. He had chased Deception right after he jumped over the wall. Chen Guo had been closely watching Ye Xiu’s screen the entire time, but Ye Xiu had never seen him.

‘He’s close.” Ye Xiu was certain. Lord Grim also stopped.

“How do you know?” Chen Guo was still heading over.

“Based on his movement speed, he won’t be able to escape from my field of view.” Ye Xiu said confidently. His camera kept on turning, observing his surroundings.

“So you’re saying he’s hiding?” Chen Guo asked.

“Yeah. We have to hurry and find him.” Ye Xiu said.

“What’s the hurry?”

“He’ll be out of combat soon. If he logs out, what can we do?” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh!” Chen Guo immediately understood.

In Glory, you couldn’t log out while in battle. Turning off the power or forcefully quitting could still be done, but your character would simply sit in the game for awhile and you would naturally be turned into paste. Because of this, it would be better to hide and wait until you were out of combat before logging off. There wasn’t any problems with doing that.

“Where could he be hiding…….” Chen Guo had arrived and she looked around as well. The streets were empty. Ye Xiu could also see what was above on the rooftops from his position and there wasn’t anyone there. The only possibility left was that he was hiding in a room somewhere. This was what made town maps troublesomes. There were too many places to hide. When Chen Guo fought in these maps, she really didn’t like playing a game of cat and mouse.

‘257, 186’s room. Go check it out.” Ye Xiu looked around and then suddenly spoke.

“Hm?” Chen Guo looked in that direction.

“There’s no noise, which means there aren’t any monsters there. From the looks of it, he’s probably in somewhere in that direction.” Ye Xiu said.

“Are you afraid of startling a snake in the grass?” Chen Guo asked.

“Not at all.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.” Chen Guo said. Chasing Haze immediately rushed towards it as she fired her cannon. Chen Guo didn’t dare be careless. Deception wasn’t any ordinary expert.

“Careful!!” Ye Xiu suddenly warned as Chen Guo charged forward.

Chen Guo was an experienced player too. No matter the danger, it was a good option to immediately roll. She chose a random direction to roll in and just as she was about to ask what was going on, Chasing Haze was suddenly launched into the air. Deception had popped out of the ground from underneath her.

Underground Tunneling Technique!

Chen Guo immediately understood. Her random roll wasn’t able to dodge his sneak attack. Remembering how everyone who Deception had acted against died, she started getting a bit nervous. But the damage done by the Underground Tunneling Technique wasn’t anything to worry about.

“There’s no need to be afraid!”

Chen Guo muttered. After playing Glory for so many years, she had a good amount of experience with every class. She was able to tell from the damage taken that Deception’s attack power might not even be as good as Chasing Haze’s. Thinking of this, she became more confident. She prepared to launch a counterattack and give him a good beating, but even if Deception’s attack power wasn’t good, his movements were extremely quick.

Chasing Haze had only just been launched into the air by the Underground Tunneling Technique. Deception turned his back on her and threw his two hands back…….

Chen Guo immediately recognized this pose. It was the Ninja skill: Neck Bind Technique!

Chen Guo didn’t think that Deception would be able to use a Neck Bind Technique so quickly. She had originally been planning on counterattack, but now her only thought was to hurry up and widen the distance between them. However, she was too slow. The rope on the ninja blade wrapped around Chasing Haze’s neck. With a pull on the rope, Deception dragged Chasing Haze down and she crashed into the ground.

The damage wasn’t very high, but Chen Guo was able to tell their difference in skill from this combo.

But Chen Guo wasn’t someone who was afraid. After suffering two attacks, she began to get annoyed and thoughts of fighting back with all she had begun to rise up in her mind. Neck Bind Technique was a grab skill and couldn’t be Quick Recovered. However, Deception didn’t seize the opportunity to follow up with another attack. Instead, he turned around and began to run.

Chen Guo immediately had Chasing Haze get up. She lifted her cannon onto her shoulder and was just about to fire it, when she saw a black light shoot towards. A whoosh and Chasing Haze was stunned. A blood spurted out from her head. Deception had seen Chasing Haze get up and attacked with a Shuriken, which hit Chasing Haze’s head.

Shuriken was a Level 5 Ninja skill. It wouldn’t do much damage, but targets hit by one would be stunned. Chasing Haze was hit and as a result, wasn’t able to attack. Her body froze as she watched Deception run away.

“I”M GOING TO KILL HIM!!!!” Chen Guo roared. She wasn’t like Tang Rou, who would express her feeling with her actions. Whenever Chen Guo got angry, she would use her mouth to express her feelings.

“Kill who?” Tang Rou heard that things were getting exciting. She took off her headphones and ran over to watch.

“Don’t worry. I’m here.” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was on the side! He wasn’t just waiting there doing nothing. It was just that the exchange between Chen Guo and Deception had been too quick. From the Underground Tunneling Technique to the Neck Bind Technique to the Shuriken, it had only been a short amount of time.

Chen Guo heard Ye Xiu speak and then saw as his Lord Grim descend from a rooftop, cutting off Deception’s escape route. In mid-air, he unsheathed his sword and swung down in a beautiful arc.

Deception reacted quickly and immediately stopped. The blade light fell one step behind Deception.

‘God, your aim sucks.” Chen Guo remarked after seeing Ye Xiu miss.

“Are you stupid? This is called a prediction.” Ye Xiu said.

“Predict what?” Chen Guo asked.

“He predicted my attack and dodged it. This guy has some skill.” Ye Xiu said. Lord Grim had already landed on the ground. He stood in front of Deception, blocking his path.

Deception wasn’t just going to stand there stupidly. After dodging the Sword Draw, he immediately ran diagonally. Seeing Lord Grim blocking him, he threw Shurikens. Instead of just a single one, he threw three of them.

This could be considered a hidden attribute for Shurikens. More than one Shuriken could be thrown at a time. In theory, it was similar to the Blade Master’s Shadow Steps, which relied on the player to use its full potential.

Deception threw the three in a triangular formation and the angle was quite good. But with Ye Xiu’s skill, three Shurikens was nothing to him. He didn’t stop moving and just before the Shurikens hit him, he used a Z-shake, twisting in between the gap within the triangular formation.

Deception had clearly been a bit overconfident. He thought that the three Shurikens would be enough for him to safely pass by him, but who would have thought that his opponent would go right through them. It was only until Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella transformed into a Priest sickle did Deception realize what had happened.

His reactions were quick though. Deception rolled backwards and Lord Grim’s sickle missed. Deception leaped up and turned around in mid-air. He raised his two hands towards his head and formed a hand seal.

“Flame Cut?” Ye Xiu laughed. Deception was truly alarmed when he heard this.

Ninjas were a physical and magic hybrid class. One unique aspect of their class was that when Ninjas cast skills, they didn’t need to wait for the cast to finish before using the skill like an Elementalist. For Ninjas, in order to use a skill, it required a certain set of movements and these were hand seals.

The faster the player’s hands, the faster the hand seals would be completed, and the faster the cast time. The cast speed depended on the player, which was something Elementalists didn’t have.

Deception was clearly very familiar with his hand seals. His hands moved in a blur. Even he couldn’t see the seals clearly. Who would have thought that his opponent would be able to see through his skill from these hand seals.

However, since things had already gotten to this step, should he cancel his skill? Deception didn’t overthink it and immediately unsheathed his blade. The ninja blade swung in a blazing arc towards Lord Grim.

Chapter 466 – Unconventional Methods

The flames blazing out from the ninja blade crashed down. Even though the opponent had already seen through his move, Deception was clearly very confident in his technique. The faster the seals the faster the move came out. So what if the opponent knew?

What could he do?

A glint of cold light!

Brief and rapid, a fleeting flash.

The flames arrived at an empty spot on the earth. Lord Grim, who had just been standing there, was nowhere to be seen.

Deception tensed up. He immediately turned right and the flames followed along with him. From a straight chop to a horizontal slash, a wheel of flame whirled around Deception.

The process sounds complicated, but it was very quick. If it wasn’t quick, Flame Cut’s flames would have extinguished and it wouldn’t have been possible for him to do so many movements.

However, this slash still missed. As soon as Deception turned around, he saw Lord Grim leap backwards, just barely dodging the Flame Cut.

Once the skill finished, the flames went out. The two didn’t move. Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze had finally arrived and saw the two staring off, neither side acting. She turned her head to look at Ye Xiu and discovered that Ye Xiu had an unprecedented look of concentration. This really was the first time she had seen Ye Xiu like this. Ever since they had met, he had always played Glory in a casual manner. But today? Was this scrap picker actually giving him this much pressure?

Chen Guo remembered that even when he fought against Huang Shaotian, Ye Xiu hadn’t been this serious.

Chen Guo didn’t dare say anything. Chasing Haze stood on one side, quietly observing the two of them.

“If I didn’t have so much stuff on me, you wouldn’t have been able to dodge.” Deception suddenly spoke. His voice sounded very stiff as if he weren’t good at speaking.

“If I hadn’t known you had this much stuff on you, I wouldn’t have done what I did.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“There’s no point talking any further!” Deception suddenly said and then quickly slashed again with his blade. This time, he didn’t use any skill, just a normal attack.

Ye Xiu had prepared for this long ago. He immediately had Lord Grim dodge and also swung his word. He also didn’t use a skill, just a normal attack.

In an instant, the two blades met. As if they had a tacit understanding with each other, the two only used normal attacks. Normal attacks didn’t have any cool visual effects, but their movements were extremely quick and their characters looked as if they were just a blur in a storm of sword light.

Chen Guo was shocked. This was her first time seeing such a fight. Not only were their blades quick, but their pathing was quick and the two constantly switched positions. Luckily, the equipment on the two characters were completely different. If not, Chen Guo wouldn’t have been able to tell who was who.

Deception’s equipment was gray and ragged. They clearly weren’t high grade equipment. Speaking of this, very few scrap pickers wore their best equipment when scrap picking. This type of activity was extremely risky and ended ninety percent of the time in death. Wearing a set of top equipment might increase your survivability a bit, but if you died, then it would be a disaster.

However, even if Deception’s equipment weren’t top quality, they were still a set. As for Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, Chen Guo wanted to cry. His character was also a blur, but Lord Grim was like a rainbow. He was so colorful, it made people want to vomit. He didn’t look imposing at all.

He might look weaker, but Chen Guo was very confident in Ye Xiu’s skill. However, the two were moving too quickly. Chen Guo wasn’t able to see what the situation was. But because of where she was located, she could simply look at Ye Xiu’s screen. By taking Lord Grim’s health and comparing it to Deception’s health, wouldn’t that be an accurate indicator of who was winning?

But after watching for awhile, she realized that their health bars were decreasing extremely slowly. This meant that despite their intense fighting, the amount of damage they each dealt was very limited because both sides had difficulty hitting their opponent.

Moreover, as they fought, they moved towards a certain direction. It had only been a short while, but there was already a gap widening between Chen Guo and them. She wanted to help, but with how they were fighting, she didn’t know how to help.

“Hey, do you need help?” Chen Guo couldn’t help but ask.

These words were like a turning point. The two blurs suddenly split apart. Deception quickly turned around. His two hands formed a seal in front of his forehead. His hands moved in a blur. In any case, Chen Guo didn’t have the skill to figure out what type of skill Deception was going to use next.

Deception quickly finished the hand seal and slashed out. This time, the ninja blade was no longer a flame, but flowing water. As soon as the ninja blade came out from the sheath, it split into multiple streams, sweeping towards Lord Grim.

At this point, Chen Guo recognized the skill. This was another Ninja skill: Hundred Streams.

Just like the name implied, this was actually a crowd control skill with low damage. The streams chased after Lord Grim and lifted him up. As they rose, they formed a water prison with Lord Grim locked inside.

Chen Guo instantly understood!

The two weren’t actually fighting. Deception had wanted to run away, but Ye Xiu was stopping him. Now that he found an opportunity, he unleashed a Hundred Streams. The water prison formed by Hundred Streams could last up to thirty seconds. It wasn’t possible to break it from the inside. It locked the movements of the target inside. In other words, if no one from the outside helped break you out, you would be stuck there for thirty seconds.

Chen Guo was outside of the water prison, but the water prison couldn’t be broken through that easily. By the time she broke the water prison, Deception would already be gone. Should she fight with Deception, while attacking the prison? Chen Guo began to sweat. She didn’t have any confidence fighting Deception, let alone attacking the prison at the same time.

But in any case, she couldn’t just sit there.

Chen Guo fired towards Deception. To stop an opponent from escaping, melee classes were better than long-ranged classes. Chen Guo wasn’t as skilled as Deception either and wasn’t good at doing this sort of thing. She couldn’t feel happy about this at all.

I won’t be able to block him, but what if I just make it so he can’t run?

Chen Guo’s mind suddenly stirred. There was no time to think about it too carefully, so she immediately blurted out: “If you’re smart, don’t run!!!”

“It doesn’t matter. He won’t be able to escape anyways.”

Deception wasn’t the one to answer her. Chen Guo was slightly startled. A rainbow blur rushed towards Deception. And at this moment, Chen Guo hadn’t finished her attempt at trying to block Deception!

“What?” Chen Guo was confused. She turned her head to look. The water prison formed by the Hundred Streams was still there, but there was no one inside. Ye Xiu had clearly escaped from the water prison’s grasp.

Right! That could happen……

Chen Guo thought, but she was still confused. Why had she thought that Lord Grim had certainly been captured by the water prison?

Someone helped her ask this question.

“Impossible!” She heard Deception shout.

“What’s impossible?” Ye Xiu replied.

“How did you know I would use Hundred Streams!?” Deception said.

Chen Guo immediately understood.

Why had she thought Ye Xiu wouldn’t be able to avoid the Hundred Streams? It was because the Hundred Streams had been done to near perfection.

Deception clearly knew that his opponent was extremely experienced after using that Flame Cut. Even though the Ninja’s cast time was much faster than a mage’s, if the hand seal was seen through, then it meant he would lose the initiative and the chances it would connect would be much lower. As a result, he chose the instant they split apart to complete a Hundred Streams. During that entire time, Lord Grim had been behind him, so there was no way he could have seen Deception’s hand seal. And there weren’t any sound effects either, so there was no way he could have figured out from listening.

This type of situation had made Chen Guo think that the Hundred Streams would certainly connect, which was why she began to think ahead. But Lord Grim had unexpectedly dodged the water prison. Deception obviously couldn’t understand.

As for Chen Guo? She quickly understood.

Who was this! The Glory Textbook! God Ye Qiu of hundreds of battles. Things that normal players couldn’t do could be done by Ye Qiu. Who cared if how fast you were. More importantly, your thoughts have been completely read by him. No matter how fast you were, if your opponent knew what you were going to do, then it didn’t matter.

“Ha ha, your skill level isn’t bad. I also used a bit of an unconventional method.”

Chen Guo heard Ye Xiu explain.

Unconventional method?

Chen Guo wasn’t sure. At this moment, Ye Xiu had already begun fighting with Deception again.

“An unconventional method? What is it?” Deception shouted.

Ye Xiu only replied with a smiley face.

What was the unconventional method? Chen Guo was also curious, but seeing the two fight like that, she didn’t dare ask. However, she began paying attention to see if there was anything unusual Ye Xiu was doing.

She quickly figured it out.

“F*ck! You’re shameless!! You’re looking at my screen!!” Chen Guo jumped up.

When it wasn’t convenient for his Lord Grim to catch what Deception was doing, Ye Xiu would turn to look at Chen Guo’s screen. He didn’t look the slightest bit ashamed at his actions.

Chapter 467 – This is an Opportunity

Despicable!

This time, Chen Guo really did look down on him. What textbook? What God? What idol? None of them could stop Chen Guo’s disdain towards him.

Peeking at someone one else’s screen. What shameful behavior! On an online platform, you might not have the chance to peek even if you wanted to, but they were in an Internet Cafe. In an Internet Cafe, this sort of behavior was common. Groups of friends would sit together to play Glory. As a result, they would shift their eyes around like little thieves. Every time Chen Guo saw this, she would always feel the same: dirty, extremely dirty!

Chen Guo already felt dirty enough following a God to pick up scraps. Seeing how shameless he was being, Chen Guo almost couldn’t bear it. In order to win, he wouldn’t hold back anything!

“You really don’t feel any shame!!” Chen Guo didn’t care about bothering Ye Xiu anymore and began shouting in his ears.

“Stop moving around randomly! You’re blocking the screen!!” Ye Xiu was still looking at Chen Guo’s screen.

Chen Guo swiped her mouse and turned her character’s line of sight away.

“Shameless, shameless!” Chen Guo continued to criticize him and asked Tang Rou: “Isn’t he too shameless?”

“Hm? Really?” Tang Rou was actually doubtful.

Chen Guo worried. Tang Rou was only a person! She had been too careless, letting her play with Ye Xiu. Now she no longer had any sense of justice when watching Glory. How could she be so nonchalant over such shameless behavior?

“Isn’t peeking at someone else’s screen immoral?” Chen Guo wanted to bring Tang Rou back onto the right path.

“But…… you do it too?” Tang Rou said.

“Ah…… that’s just everyone playing together. That’s not related.” Chen Guo laughed.

“Isn’t he playing right now too?” Tang Rou asked.

“Uh……” Chen Guo was stumped.

After thinking for awhile, she realized that she had thought wrong. She had been replacing Ye Xiu with the image of the idol she had in her mind. If others peeked at someone else’s screen or even if she did it herself, she wouldn’t feel bad. It was fine as long as they weren’t using it as an advantage in a fight.

But what about Ye Xiu? She had always treated him as a perfect God. As a result, when Ye Xiu acted in this way, she would immediately be unable to bear it. In other words, she cared even more about Ye Xiu’s image as a God than Ye Xiu himself.

Was she being too harsh?

Chen Guo suddenly thought of celebrities from other areas. Common mistakes made by normal people would turn into huge news by the media if these celebrities did this type of mistake. Public figures seemed to have been burdened with a strong sense of responsibility by society. Was acting like this because Ye Xiu had been hiding behind the curtains the entire time? Was it because he didn’t want to feel restricted from the spotlight being on him?

Chen Guo thought as she quietly returned her camera angle back to where the two were fighting.

“Hey!” Chen Guo called Ye Xiu, telling him he could look.

“Thanks!” Ye Xiu replied and immediately turned his head to look. His nonchalant look as if he had done nothing wrong made Chen Guo angry.

Show restraint! Patience! He’s just playing the game. If we were in a guild war and I had this opportunity, I probably wouldn’t let it go either…… Chen Guo reminded herself.

“Your little trick is of no use.”

Chen Guo heard Deception speak and suddenly felt the urge to smash her computer on this guy’s head. Your opponent’s trick was of no use? What do you mean no use? It’s not like you’re looking at my screen. Why are you so happy that I’m restraining myself! Was this some sort of brilliant tactic?

During this time, Deception rolled away. He threw the long string in his hand and ninja blade turned into a flying blade. The attack range grew longer and could be retracted as well.

Lord Grim stepped to the side. He moved up and brandished his sword. His mouse clicked on the ninja blade flying at him and blocked the attack. This was truly a brilliant move. If this was any other time, Chen Guo would have stars in her eyes, but now, she restrained herself from cheering.

Using this opportunity, Deception once again pulled away from the conflict. Having stuck for this long, Deception was clear that pulling such a distance away from Lord Grim wasn’t an easy task. This was his chance to escape.

Deception was just about to run, when a cold light flashed and Lord Grim chased after him. However, Deception had already figured out the length of his opponent’s weapon. His ninja blade had only been just enough to reach him, which meant that a sword wouldn’t be able to hit him.

Who would have thought that this sword light would actually flash in front of him? Deception looked carefully in surprise. His opponent had actually thrown his sword.

Deception thought this was an accident. What type of attack was that supposed to be?

His ninja blade had a string attached to it, so he could pull it back when he threw it. Normal weapons could be thrown too, but once you threw it, it was the same as discarding it. He would actually drop his own weapon in order to make such an attack?

Deception couldn’t understand, but he couldn’t miss the opportunity. As a scrap picker, once he saw an item, it had to be picked up. This was the fundamental essence of the profession.

Deception swung his blade and knocked it down. It was the same as what Ye Xiu had done. He was ready to pick up the sword after it landed on the ground. But when he looked at his opponent, his opponent’s hands didn’t stop and continued to charge at him. He had another thing in his hands.

What is he trying to do?

Deception was at a loss. His ninja blade had already knocked down the sword. At the same time, he heard a “Ka!” The thing in his opponent’s hands seemed to have picked up the sword. And then…… and then the sword didn’t drop and continued to fly towards him.

Deception couldn’t dodge in time and was hit by the attack. It didn’t do much damage to him though. Just as he was about to continue running away, he was suddenly launched into the air. He spun around in midair as his head crashed into the ground.

“Circle Swing????” Deception shouted in surprise.

“That’s correct!” Ye Xiu said.

“You you…… what class are you? What’s with your weapon?” Deception could speak quickly too.

“I say, aren’t you reacting a bit too slowly?” Ye Xiu was shocked.

Deception checked Lord Grim’s character page: “Level 52? No class???”

“Ah?” Ye Xiu was surprised. He thought his opponent had known about this long ago.

“There’s no info on your weapon…… this is…… a silver weapon?????” Deception was still shouting.

“Brother, do you not read the news?” Ye Xiu was lost in thought. He even stared blankly towards Chen Guo. Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze wasn’t far from them. She could obviously hear the two of them speaking.

This Deception clearly didn’t know who Lord Grim was.

“What news?” The guy even asked.

“Brother, it’s been all over the place recently. I can’t believe someone from Glory doesn’t know! I’m very surprised.” Ye Xiu said.

“…….” Chen Guo was speechless. This type of introduction must make the other person want to roll his eyes. Don’t you feel embarrassed talking about yourself like that? It was the truth though.

“Who are you?” Deception asked, when a bunch of shouts could suddenly be heard.

“Over there!”

“So it turns out those two were partners!”

“Don’t let them run!!!”

Ye Xiu quickly turned his viewpoint around to look. The troops from the Three Great Guilds were charging towards them. He and Deception had been fighting with each other for too long. The Three Great Guilds had been in chaos in the beginning, but as time went on, they finally realized that they had been set up by Lord Grim into a pointless fight.

Once they regained their composure, they asked their superiors for instructions on what to do. Their superiors slapped the table and cheered in response!

Why hadn’t the guilds acted against Lord Grim yet! It was because his fame was too high right now. Chasing and killing him would attract too much attention. The Club guilds cared about their image. If they were going to chase and kill someone, they needed a reason others could accept. They had to be especially careful for a public figure like Lord Grim.

But now, he had come out and killed two of their guild’s captains and caused a huge fight to break out. This could be used a reason. In addition, Lord Grim was seen to be together with Deception.

Deception could be considered famous as well, an extremely infamous figure. Everyone who had their equipment stolen by him all wanted him dead.

The top guilds had noticed him and had initially tried to pull him in. After all, they could all see that Deception was an expert. One of their missions as Club guilds was to discover experts, rope them in, and then send them to the Clubs.

But this Deception seemed to never come out. His friends list was closed. Whenever they happened to bump into him, let alone negotiate, if he didn’t steal your equipment, you got lucky. In the end, the Club guilds tempered themselves and made preparations. Whenever there was an activity, they would guard against his scrap picking. Whenever there was a chance, they would try to get close with him. But up until now, it’s said that anyone who has tried to get close to him has died. Of course, the top guilds wouldn’t admit this. Letting this type of news spread was too shameful.

Seeing Deception and Lord Grim together, the core members of the top guilds seemed to have a sudden realization.

They were a set!

Lord Grim had sowed discord. Deception had picked up the scraps. These two were working together!

“KILL!!!”” The Three Great Guilds swarmed. Their numbers had even increased.

They finally had the opportunity to chase and kill Lord Grim. Moreover, this was also another opportunity.

Because of Deception.

After reporting this situation to their superiors, the top guilds immediately made a decision: whether or not they really were together, they were to kill them both in one bite.

“Record! Record the two of them together!!” The orders came down.

Chapter 468 – I Can’t Stand Being Ignored

“Hurry up and run!” Ye Xiu immediately warned Deception when he saw this scene. But when he turned to look, Deception had already run off.

“Where’s your code of brotherhood! You didn’t even tell me you were running off.” Ye Xiu ran while scolding him.

When Deception heard this, his movements clearly slowed down for a second. What is that supposed to mean! I’ve been trying to run away the entire time. If it weren’t for you, I’d have escaped a long time ago…

“Don’t let them escape from combat!!” The guild players were experienced. Once they escaped from combat, they could simply log off. With today’s technological progress, logging off was very quick. Don’t count on the character sitting there waiting to die. If you were still in combat though and you force quit the game, your character would stay in-game to be killed.

The order came down. The long-ranged classes fired a barrage of missiles. Even though not all of them hit, whether or not one was considered in-battle didn’t depend on how much damage one took. The system had its own way of deciding it.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim and Deception had been fighting for awhile, so they were already in a combat status. Even if they wanted to log off, they wouldn’t be able to. Seeing how careful and meticulous the guilds were being, it seemed like they would need to give up their hands and legs in order to escape.

Chen Guo was nervous as well. Hearing Ye Xiu’s warning, she immediately ran away too. But she quickly remembered that she wasn’t in combat. Those guilds were only focused on Lord Grim and Deception. She was being regarded as a passerby.

Chen Guo was furious. Seeing that no one was paying attention to her, she directly let out a powerful skill.

The Three Great Guilds were too tunneled onto Lord Grim and Deception. They were busy attacking and recording. Suddenly, a flash of light appeared before their eyes. The experienced players were overwhelmed with shock. They looked up and looked. Sure enough, it was the Launcher’s Satellite Beam about to crash down onto them.

The Satellite Beam shot down. The wind from the shockwave blew across the surrounding character’s equipment. Those who were enveloped by the light naturally took a huge blow from the Satellite Beam. Chen Guo continued and the large beam split into several smaller pillars. The players didn’t dare be slow. They scattered away and their formation went into a mess. Chen Guo had taken her revenge and was delighted. Following afterwards, Ye Xiu helplessly said: “You’re still playing? Why aren’t you running?”

Chen Guo could re-activate the skill one more time. But with the skill already raining down on them, how could the guild players not notice her? All sorts of attacks were being thrown at her. Ye Xiu’s warning was just done as an act of kindness. In this situation, with Chen Guo’s skill level, she was basically a sheep throwing herself into a pack of wolves. Chasing Haze wasn’t even able to take two steps, when the barrage of attacks crashed down on her, turning her into a corpse.

“You really…… died like that?” Ye Xiu criticized.

“Hmph, I wanted to do that!” Chen Guo spoke like that, but her first reaction was to check her inventory. She would certainly lose experience and money, but importantly was her equipment……

“F*CK!” Chen Guo erupted. She had lost two pieces of equipment. Her hands were empty, indicating that her weapon had dropped.

Weapons were valued the most by players.Whenever anyone invested money into equipment, their first choice would be to invest in a weapon. However, the system considered the chances to drop the weapon as any other piece of equipment. Not only did Chen Guo drop two pieces of equipment, she had even dropped her weapon. Her luck was too tragic.

“Tsk tsk tsk tsk.” Ye Xiu shook his head repeatedly.

“As if I care! It felt good doing that.” Seeing the look on Ye Xiu’s face, Chen Guo continued to speak bravely. But this time, these words really were just words. Her decision to use Satellite Beam was completely done on impulse. It hadn’t been a decision based on rational thinking. Afterwards, not a single person was close to dying, while she herself was killed. Being killed would have been fine if not for her Level 70 Purple Rose Flower Cannon dropping. Chen Guo really wanted to cry.

“Don’t cry. Don’t cry. If the old doesn’t go, the new won’t come.” Ye Xiu actually consulted her using this saying.

“Who wants to cry.” Chen Guo continued to speak bravely, but her actual emotions had already been sold out. The current Chen Guo was so sad she had even forgotten to revive as she stared at her corpse. Her equipment had already been stolen away.

“It’s just a Rose Flower Cannon. Though……” Ye Xiu was just about to analyze the equipment’s value in order to comfort Chen Guo’s anguish, but when he turned his head to look at her, he immediately stopped.

From his perspective, a Rose Flower Cannon was nothing. But for a normal player, any Level 70 Purple weapon wasn’t easy to come by.

Purple lettering meant the equipment was very rare. Level 70 was also the max level. Very few of these would become outdated, so even Level 70 Blue equipment were valuable. For a core member of a top guild, a Level 70 Purple equipment might not be much. This was because they had the guild’s resources to pull from. A ten thousand player guild had who knew how many parties that could be formed. The chances that one of these parties would get an equipment was very high and the core members would have priority over these equipment.

Normal players had it a lot more difficult. It required them to grind a certain dungeon many many times. Even if the equipment dropped, it might not fall into their bags. They could be bought on the market, but with how rare these equipment were, the market prices wouldn’t be low.

If Chen Guo really wanted to, it wouldn’t be difficult for her to buy a Purple equipment with some money. But Ye Xiu had been with her for two months and knew that Boss Chen was very proper. She would never use real money in the game.

For this type of player, a Purple weapon was a huge loss and was enough to make one’s heart ache.

Her heart ached, but there was nothing she could do. This was because the Heavenly Domain had another different rule than normal servers: Heavenly Domain equipment couldn’t be bound. If Heavenly Domain equipment could also be bound, everyone would bind their good equipment and there would be no reason to worry. If that was the case, how could scrap pickers exist? Any equipment obtained in normal servers could be bound though. However, these equipment were all considered low quality goods in the Heavenly Domain. Apart from disassembling them for some equipment that had value, even scrap pickers didn’t like picking them up.

Seeing the bitter look on Chen Guo’s face, Ye Xiu didn’t look down on Chen Guo’s loss.

“What else did you drop?” Ye Xiu asked.

“My head equipment also dropped.” Chen Guo said. The head part didn’t have to be a hat. It could also be a scarf or a mask or a hair accessory. There were even lollipops and cigarettes. Glory had all sorts of different types.

Ye Xiu also knew about the head equipment Chasing Haze dropped. It was a hairband. Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze had a ponytail just like Chen Guo in real life. With this hairband gone, Chasing Haze’s corpse had her hair scattered everywhere all over the ground. Ye Xiu restrained himself from mocking her and nodded his head: “Don’t worry. You’ll find another cannon and hairband.”

“Hm?” Chen Guo suddenly woke up from her anguish.

“What are you planning on doing?” Chen Guo felt like something was about to happen.

“I’m about to go scrap picking.” Ye Xiu said. Lord Grim stopped and turned around.

“You’re crazy. Do you think you’re some sort of…….” Chen Guo wasn’t able to finish, when Lord Grim turned back and began running away again.

“You….. you…..” Chen Guo was at a loss.

“I was just looking back for a second to see if they had a lot of Launchers among them or not.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why don’t you take care of yourself first! There’ll be more equipment in the future. It’s nothing.” Chen Guo said as she had Chasing Haze revive.

Apart from the equipment, she also lost experience and money. After her experience dropped, don’t look at how she was still Level 70. In reality, her stats had been reduced. All of her equipment stats would be reduced as well. Not letting the player’s level fall was to prevent players from taking advantage of it. It was done so that the player wouldn’t be able to purposefully drop in level to finish level restricted quests or dungeons. Reduce stats, while not reducing the level was something that made the players furious.

“You worry about yourself. I’m about to pull off something huge.” Ye Xiu rolled up his sleeves as he spoke.

“How about you escape first before talking…….” Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu’s screen. There were no longer just players chasing from behind, but players were blocking them from the front too. The guilds finally had an opportunity. A single team was enough to take down a Wilderness Escort, but to kill a boss like Ye Qiu, the more players the better.

“Oh! Excellent Dynasty, Excellent Dynasty is good!” Ye Xiu said.

“What’s good?”

“Excellent Dynasty will have more Launchers.” Ye Xiu said.

“You…..” Chen Guo stared blankly, “No need. It’s better if you escape. It’s just a Rose Flower Cannon. I can easily buy it if I need to. But what will we do if your Silver weapon drops?”

“There’s where you’re wrong. To tell you the truth, there’s no need to worry about a Silver weapon dropping. Your equipment needs time to obtain, but a Silver weapon? If I can make one, then I can make a second. Do you know how many of One Autumn Leaf’s Evil Annihilations there are?” Ye Xiu said.

“I don’t know……”

“Three! Apart from the one One Autumn Leaf has equipped, there are two others. These two are for research purposes. If one breaks, another one will be made to make up for it.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then with what you’re saying, if Silver weapons weren’t valuable, they would be everywhere?”

“Of course not.” Ye Xiu said, “Some of the extremely rare materials restrict how many Silver weapons there can be. But the one I have in my hands right now is only Level 45. It hasn’t reached that level yet. Plus, while I upgrade it to 70, who knows how many times I’m going to break one, so don’t worry. This is still incomplete.”

“Oh…..”

“Then again……. I should still get to know the person who killed me.” Ye Xiu said.

“Let’s just hope it’s not so many that you won’t be able to remember them all.” Chen Guo said.

“Ha ha ha! Speaking of this, there’s one such person in front of me! See that ninja bro? He’s not very focused when he’s running. He’s always peeking at me. I think he really wants my Silver weapon.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 469 – A Way Out

Ye Xiu’s tone of voice wasn’t polite at all and he spoke loudly too. Chen Guo heard it. Deception must have heard it too. Deception had nothing to say after being seen through. He simply made a humph.

“I say. Where are you running?” Ye Xiu asked. The two had been running for awhile. Ye Xiu had been following behind Deception the entire time, but he was unable to see through this guy’s intentions.

“How much of a burden are you carrying?” Unable to get Deception to reveal his intentions, Ye Xiu switched topics.

Deception continued to stay silent and do his own thing. Suddenly, he heard a gunshot from behind him. It was coming from somewhere very close too! Deception was someone who had been doing this for awhile and had some skill in judging distance from the surrounding sounds. He immediately rolled. When he turned back to look who had shot it, he saw Lord Grim with his gun pointing straight at him!

“What are you doing!” Deception was furious.

“I thought you couldn’t hear me.” Ye Xiu said.

“……” Deception really wanted to kill him, but it wasn’t the right time to do so. The troops chasing after them had started to close in. The gunners were all firing rapidly at them. One group from the front had also arrived. The situation was looking quite grim.

Deception didn’t plan on wasting time on Ye Xiu. After moving forward a few steps, he switched directions and leaped onto a rooftop.

“Bro, isn’t your plan a bit too low-leveled? Aren’t you afraid of an ambush?” This time, Ye Xiu didn’t follow him. Lord Grim stood on the street and asked Deception.

Deception didn’t reply. He jumped up and swung his ninja blade at the wall. Crouching down, he used the blade in order to jump again.

“Attack your enemies, when they’re halfway across the river. Have you ever heard of this saying?” Ye Xiu was still talking and Deception was still ignoring him.

“This theory applies to climbing walls too.” Ye Xiu continued.

Deception still wanted to ignore him, but suddenly, he saw a flash of light from the corner of his eyes and immediately knew something wasn’t right. He didn’t dare continue climbing up. He rolled backwards and watched as a Satellite Beam descended from the sky, right where Deception had just been. The stream of air caused by the Satellite Beam made Deception roll farther than normal. When he landed on the ground, he used a Quick Recover to steady himself. Although the attack hadn’t hit him, he had still suffered from some of its effects. If he wasn’t so skilled, he would be lying on the ground right now.

“Not bad.” Ye Xiu praised. The several smaller pillars after the main Satellite Beam began heading towards him, but he was able to easily dodge them and escape.

“Where are you going to jump next?” Ye Xiu dodged, while asking Deception.

“If you’ve got any suggestions, hurry up and say it!” Deception was annoyed. After the Satellite Beam, he could see that there were people standing on the roof. Even though there weren’t many of them, a certain level of skill was necessary to get up onto the roof in the first place. These few players were more than enough to take him down.

Deception swept the surroundings. The escape routes he eyed already had enemies guarding them. Deception was somewhat sad. This wasn’t his first time scrap picking and he had more fruitful pickings before. He had never seen such a huge operation either. Why was it like this today? Had he picked up something extremely valuable?

Deception had swift eyes and hands. He had already seen what equipment he had picked up, but he didn’t remember anything too special. Seeing all of these pursuers, he was starting to doubt himself. He couldn’t help but look at his inventory again. However, there really was nothing that shocking.

“There are escape routes everywhere. It just depends on whether or not you have the ability to go through them.” Ye Xiu said.

“Can you stop with your bullsh*t?” Deception was worried! The two groups on the side were defending their place and their routes in front and behind were blocked. They were trapped.

“I’ll show you how to do it.” Ye Xiu said. Right as the Satellite Beam finished, his character charged forward towards Deception’s previous escape route.

Deception was startled, but he didn’t have any time to think too much and followed after him.

Lord Grim didn’t wait to get near the wall before he jumped. The players on the roof weren’t just going to sit there and watch. They sent out their attacks at him.

Lord Grim opened up his Thousand Chance Umbrella above him. “Ka ka ka!” It began spinning with the Mechanic skill: Rotor Wing. He even made some drifts while in the air to dodge the attacks.

Deception was sad!

What type of demonstration was that? He just flew up there with a Rotor Blade. I’m a Ninja. How am I supposed to use a Rotor Blade?

Deception didn’t have any other choice though. He jumped up again and used the ninja blade to climb. An Elementalist on the roof flicked his sleeves and his staff pointed towards him.

Deception was about to jump away to dodge, when he heard several shots of gunfire. Blood splashed out from the Elementalist as he stumbled, unable to finish casting his magic.

Deception was delighted. He quickly climbed up. He turned to look at Lord Grim. But the scene in front of him was something he never would have imagined.

Lord Grim had used Rotor Wing to fly up, but he wasn’t able to find any opportunity to land. Rotor Wing’s skill was at the end of its duration too. The guy had used a Gatling Gun in order to help Deception out, while using the bullet’s recoil to slide in the air.

After interrupting the Elementalist’s casting, the bullets swept across the other players and they lost their balance. However, the recoil from the firing caused Lord Grim to move away from the rooftop.

In any case, this was a huge opportunity for Deception to break through.

Deception was very confused. Seeing Lord Grim move farther and farther away, he doubted Lord Grim would sacrifice himself to save him.

“What are you hiding for? It’s not like you’ll die!!” Someone suddenly roared. This person clearly saw that they weren’t blocking well enough and warned them not to care about the opponent’s damage and make sure they didn’t land on the rooftop.

The guards on the rooftop suddenly woke up. It was just that dodging when you were attacked was a habit already. The better the expert, the more it was like so. They were Heavenly Domain players as well as part of the top guilds, so they obviously had this sort of habit.

As a result, once Deception finished his jump, he took out his blade and wanted to beat them away, while he was on the rooftop. However, the Launcher completely ignored Deception’s attack. He took out his handcannon and used the low leveled Launcher skill Swing to trade blows with Deception. It didn’t matter if he took a lot of damage for doing this as long as he was able to send Deception back down.

“Not good!” Deception could tell the situation wasn’t looking good, but it was too late to change attacks. He could only pray his luck was good today. Suddenly, he heard the sound of a sword slicing through the wind. A silver light came crashing down in front of him. Lord Grim had used Falling Light Blade.

“Join my party!”

Deception heard him yell as a party invite popped up.

Without hesitating, Deception immediately clicked accept. He prayed he wasn’t too slow.

He knew that this Falling Light Blade could resolve their current situation. However, if he didn’t accept Lord Grim’s party invite and the damage wasn’t negated, this Falling Light Blade would send him flying too. He would fall back onto the streets.

Did I succeed?

In that split second, Deception wasn’t sure if he had accepted the invite faster or if Lord Grim’s sword had arrived first.

He saw the sword hit the ground. The shock wave from the Falling Light Blade immediately spread outwards. That Launcher was the first to be hit by it and fell tumbling to the ground. He immediately used a Quick Recover. Although he didn’t get knocked down, he lost the opportunity to block them.

And Deception?

Deception was standing firmly on the rooftop. He had joined the party before the Falling Light Blade hit.

“You’re pretty quick!” Deception heard Lord Grim say. After using a Falling Light Blade, Lord Grim did a roll and then immediately went after the Launcher.

Deception suddenly realized something. Just before, that guy had used Gatling Gun and was pushed away from the roof. How did he get here so quickly?

Deception turned his head to look and saw another Lord Grim behind him, falling to the ground.

“Shadow Clone Technique!” Deception was a Ninja, so he obviously recognized this skill.

Lord Grim used Shadow Clone Technique to instantly move close and then used a Falling Light Blade to quickly fall onto the rooftop. While doing this, he also sent over a party invite……

Deception wasn’t a noob. He was very clear how difficult it was to pull off such a string of inputs.

“There are escape routes everywhere. It just depends on whether or not you have the ability to go through them.”

Deception suddenly thought of Lord Grim’s words. It could be said that he could do all this because of his access to skills from different classes. However, by looking at what he had accomplished with those moves, forcing his character to stay in midair for a long time wasn’t something any normal player could achieve either.

“Who is this guy?” Deception wondered, when he heard him shout: “If you just stand there, you’ll die. Hurry and help me.”

Deception hastily moved away. Sure enough, someone was already heading to his location and attacking him. Deception was surprised. To think he would get distracted at such a critical moment!

When he looked ahead, he saw Lord Grim sticking close to the Launcher, who could do nothing to fight back.

“What are you doing?” Deception couldn’t understand his actions. Why wasn’t he trying to escape? Why was he fighting with the Launcher?

“I’m going to pick up scraps!” After saying this, Lord Grim sent out a Striker’s Front Kick and kicked the Launcher down from the rooftop. Following afterwards, he went down and struck the finishing blow.

Chapter 470 – Scrap Picking and Playing with Lives

Deception was stunned. If he hadn’t heard the sound of an attacking coming at him, he would have probably frozen in place.

What was their current situation? There were enemies on all four sides. It might even be too late to run away and yet this guy still wanted to pick up scraps? The problem was that this guy said he was going scrap picking, but his actions didn’t seem like scrap picking at all. What was scrap picking? Taking advantage of a chaotic situation to pick up dropped equipment. This was scrap picking. Deception taking the initiative to attack targets was already considered beyond scrap picking. But this Lord Grim directly grabbed a full health character to kill him and then pick up his scraps. Was that even called scrap picking? It was more like stealing.

Deception cursed silently. But when he looked left and right, he discovered Lord Grim that Lord Grim kicking down the Launcher might be the only way to escape. This escape route required the Launcher to be knocked down.

Thinking of this, Deception immediately felt like his motive to pick up scraps was simply done in the passing. His real intention was to kill off the Launcher to create an escape path. Deception thought about this as he rushed past this breakthrough and leaped down. When he looked down towards the streets, he immediately turned to stone.

Below, Lord Grim really was trying to kill that Launcher! The Launcher wasn’t an obstacle anymore to them. Once you hit him down, why would you waste your time killing him?

Was he really going to go scrap picking?!

Deception felt like there had to be some sort of scheme around this. Before he landed, he checked the Launcher’s equipment.

A character from a top guild wouldn’t have bad equipment, but that was only relative to normal players. Even though Deception didn’t have such a mountain to rely on, but he was able to prosper quite well through his scrap picking business. The equipment from these ordinary guild members weren’t good enough to make him drool.

When Deception landed on the ground, the Launcher’s equipment had already been thoroughly checked two times. However, with his two experienced eyes, he didn’t see anything very valuable on the Launcher’s body……

“Hurry up and help me! You’ll profit too!”

Right when he was puzzled about the situation, Lord Grim suddenly interrupted his thoughts.

Could it be in his inventory?

Deception suddenly reacted. He could only check the equipment being worn on the Launcher, but he couldn’t see what was in his inventory. The items in his inventory also had the same chance of dropping.

Because of this, Deception didn’t hesitate and brandished his ninja blade.

Ye Xiu completely crushed this Launcher. The various skills being used made the opponent’s head dizzy. It didn’t matter that his damage output was extremely low. Lord Grim’s level was low and his equipment was low-leveled too. Against a Level 70 character, the damage done would be very low. Under this sort of scenario, Ye Xiu might have the advantage in skill, but he could only kill him in so much time.

However, Deception was different. He started with two high-leveled Ninja skills, coordinating with Ye Xiu’s combo.

“Not bad! Be careful above you.” Ye Xiu praised and reminded him.

Deception lifted his head up and saw the players, who used to just be guarding the rooftops, come jumping down. Deception was worried! He felt like still trying to kill someone in this situation was a bit crazy.

But the items dropped by this guy must be very valuable right?

Thinking of this, Deception couldn’t bear to just leave, but how was he going to deal with all of these dumplings?

“Faster!” Deception heard Lord Grim shout. Then, he saw him rush forward and send out a Falling Flower Palm towards a player on the left. This player turned into a cannonball, crashing into two others.

Afterwards, he turned around and fired an Anti-Tank Missile. The players on the right side were just about to land on the ground, but instead, they landed on the missile and immediately went flying away.

Just like this, using a melee skill and a long-ranged skill, he used the descending players as toys. These players were unable to dodge in the air. Not a single one of them were able to close in on them and were all sent far away. Those who failed their Quick Recover rolled about on the ground.

“You still haven’t killed him yet?” Ye Xiu had returned and immediately criticized Deception for still fighting with the Launcher.

Deception was also somewhat sad. He had come out to pick up scraps, so he wasn’t wearing very good equipment. As a result, his damage output wasn’t very high either. Hearing Ye Xiu complain, he suddenly remember that he could use the equipment he had picked up.

Thinking of this, he quickly found equipment that would increase his damage output and wore them. His damage output immediately increased greatly.

“Yes, good good.” Ye Xiu watched the Launcher’s health drop and expressed that he was satisfied. Deception was already completely focused on the task though. When this Launcher died, his items would drop out in an instant. Deception was confident that with his ability as a scrap picker, he would be the first to pick up the items. At the very least, he didn’t believe the other side, when he said “You’ll profit too.”

“Hurry hurry hurry! They’re about to surround us!” Lord Grim hurried over to help, complaining while attacking. Sending the dumplings flying away would only buy them a few seconds of time. All of them quickly got up and charged forward at them again. Ye Xiu had no way to send them all flying again. The two were truly in a difficult situation. They hastily tried to kill off the Launcher, while dodging the incoming enemies’ attacks.

A forest of spears and a rain of arrows descended onto them. The two skipped about like two little monkeys. They were about to be surrounded, but the Launcher was at critical health. Just a bit more and he would die.

The chasing guild players didn’t know the truth behind why Ye Xiu and Deception were fighting with the Launcher. They just thought he was being a brave hero and sacrificing himself in order to stall for time. Everyone felt very moved and couldn’t bear to watch the Launcher actually dying.

“Cleric! Cleric!” Everyone in the group shouted.

In this sort of many against few scenario, Clerics tended to follow a bit behind everyone else. Hearing an urgent call, a Cleric appeared. Seeing the situation, he knew what to do and rushed forward to heal the Launcher.

“Bang!”

But then there was an explosion and the explosion blasted the Cleric flying away. There was even a knife stuck in his forehead.

“Cleric, heal yourself!” Ye Xiu said in a low voice.

“Troublemaker! You’re looking to die!” Deception held his knife-tossing position.

The two characters turned back and made the decisive blow.

“Pu!”

Deception’s ninja blade swung down. Lord Grim’s spear thrust forward. Both hit at the same time and blood spurted out from the Launcher’s body. The Launcher fell and with a “hua”, equipment jumped out from his body. Deception immediately focused and his mouse moved so fast, even he didn’t know where he was pointing at when he picked them all up.

“I got them!!” Deception was excited. He delightedly turned to look at Lord Grim, when he realized he was suddenly gone.

“Are you waiting to die?”

Lord Grim’s voice unexpectedly came out. Deception immediately turned to look and saw that he was already five units away.

How could he be so fast? Unless he didn’t pick up any equipment?

Deception was surprised and opened up his inventory. Earlier, he had only cared about picking them up and didn’t check to see what he had gotten.

When Deception saw what he had gotten, he immediately felt disappointed.

A pair of shoes dropped. It wasn’t bad, but it was far from what Deception was expecting. It wasn’t anything worth dying for.

“Could he not have even tried?” Deception thought and turned around to look. The Launcher’s corpse was still there. Deception took note of his name.

“Over here!”

Deception was still thinking about equipment, when a voice suddenly came. Another group of players were in front of them and had blocked their path.

Deception didn’t think and immediately turned his body to jump towards a wall. Before, that street had people guarding the rooftops. But here, they shouldn’t have had enough time to make any arrangements yet right? Deception doubted they would have made preparations for the entire town.

But when he looked, he saw a greatsword smashing towards him. Deception reacted extremely quickly and raised his ninja blade.

This wasn’t a Blade Master’s Guard. The system didn’t help out in any way. It was entirely the player.

It could be said that this was technically an attack, but the target wasn’t the opponent, but rather the opponent’s sword. This sort of attack could be considered a guard. If it was successful, the opponent’s damage and knockback could be reduced.

Guarding in this way was even more difficult than attacking. After all, if an attack missed, it wouldn’t matter much, but if a guard missed, then the player would take the full brunt of the hit. But in this situation, Deception didn’t have any other choice but to guard. His mouse moved and his ninja blade went out in a swift arc, hitting the greatsword.

“Dong!” Deception wasn’t hit by the greatsword, but he couldn’t jump onto the roof either. Because of this attack, he had to land back onto the street.

“I say, is your memory that bad?” Lord Grim’s voice floated over.

Deception was startled. Could there be people here too? Just how big of a net had these guilds constructed?

“Don’t only think about the roofs. Over here.” Lord Grim called. He moved into an empty room. Without stopping, he directly went through a building and jumped out from a window.

Deception rushed forward and was just about to jump out through the window, when he saw a shadow leap into the building. Deception hastily raised his blade, but he quickly recognized the name on top of the shadow: Lord Grim.

“Ha ha ha, there’s even more people over there.” Lord Grim laughed, but the news he gave wasn’t anything to laugh about.

Chapter 471 – Each to One Side

Deception didn’t delay and ran out through the door, but when he looked left and right, he saw that there were already people on the two ends of the street. The two rooftops were also dangerous. His character was still in battle, so he couldn’t log off. Deception had no clue what to do. It felt like today was going to be the day he died. Thinking of how killing off that Launcher had been a huge waste of time, if he hadn’t wasted time there, would he have been able to escape?

Deception was somewhat annoyed. His most important goal in scrap picking was to escape alive. In order to do this, he had to be content with what he had and couldn’t be greedy. Many scrap pickers were in situations where they could escape, but died after trying to pick up an eye-catching piece of equipment.

Different from scrap pickers who traded their lives for money, Deception wanted both his life and money. However, this time, it looked like his streak of never dying was about to end. Who knew how much equipment from his inventory he would drop.

“Don’t block the entrance!”

Deception was trying to figure out his future plans, when he heard Lord Grim grumble and also exit from the building.

“What a scene!” Lord Grim looked around left and right and mumbled to himself.

The enemy guild players hadn’t arrived too quickly. Their main goal was to create a perfect encirclement. Catching a turtle in a jar would only be a matter of time.

“From the looks of it, I feel like that street over there might have fewer people.” Lord Grim went back to the window.

Deception wanted to cough up blood, but he didn’t want to die either, so he ended up following Lord Grim back into the building. Then, he saw Lord Grim rush to that window, but not go through it.

“What are you doing?” Deception couldn’t understand.

“Get ready!”

“What?”

“Go out!” Lord Grim shouted. Deception saw him throw a grenade and then go out the window.

The blinding light from the grenade covered for them and because Deception was in the same party as Lord Grim, he wasn’t affected by it. He also jumped out through the window as well.

“Go!”

A word flashed in the party chat. Outside the window, people who were hit by the explosion lay on the floor. Lord Grim had charged forward to a nearby street and jumped onto a rooftop.

Deception didn’t dare delay. The small grenade didn’t have a very large explosion radius. It had only knocked down the small group of players outside the window. The others behind them had already come chasing after them. Deception was too afraid to even run forward and made a roll. Even so, he was still hit by a few attacks. Fortunately, he didn’t take any significant damage.

Deception drank a potion and also leaped up, using his ninja blade to climb up the wall.

This rooftop wasn’t very high and Deception quickly reached the top. When he looked back, the streets were filled with people. Long-ranged classes were firing continuously at them. Deception hastily flipped onto the roof to dodge these attacks.

“Why didn’t we jump here earlier!” Deception realized that there weren’t any ambushes waiting here.

“Just because there aren’t any now doesn’t mean that there weren’t any before.” Lord Grim replied and then continued forward.

After a short pause, Deception came to a realization. When Lord Grim had leaped out of the window previously, the area close to the window might have been empty, but there were people waiting out on the rooftops. As a result, he immediately returned back through the window to let them think that he wouldn’t come this way. This way the enemies on the rooftop were lured down. But then he came back again and threw a grenade outside the window, giving them a pathway to the rooftops.

By going in and out, he had actually made so many calculations. Deception was naturally amazed.

The area in front of them was completely empty. The enemy’s encirclement was now behind them. As long as they paid attention to any stray pursuers and avoided getting trapped again, they would successfully escape.

However, after seeing where Lord Grim was running, Deception creased his brows: “Isn’t that way a bit roundabout? This way seems better.”

“Oh? It sounds like you’re familiar with this area?” Ye Xiu heard Deception speak and replied back.

“Yeah.” Deception didn’t say anything more.

“If we’re going to run away, then that way is better, but I don’t think I ever said we were going to run away did I?” Ye Xiu smiled.

“Then what are you planning on doing?” Deception was puzzled.

“Didn’t I say it already? I’m going to go scrap picking.” Ye Xiu said.

“You……. You’re crazy!” Deception stopped moving.

“What? Isn’t this a good opportunity to go scrap picking?” Ye Xiu asked.

“If it’s our scraps, then it certainly is a good opportunity.” Deception said dryly.

“Woah, you have a sense of humor.” Ye Xiu was astonished.

“You can go and kill yourself!” Deception threw out and then left Lord Grim’s party. The pursuers behind them were getting closer. There wasn’t any time for him to just stand there. Deception went towards the path he considered as the best escape route.

“You’re missing out on a big opportunity!”

When he jumped onto another street, Deception heard that guy shout from behind him.

Deception didn’t say anything. He gave a disdainful face emoji. He knew Lord Grim could still see word bubbles at this distance.

Wilderness Town, top of an abandoned building.

Excellent Dynasty’s Chen Yehui, Blue Brook Guild’s Changing Spring, and Herb Garden’s Arisaema. These three guilds had gathered together. Killing a boss or attacking a scrap picker, none of these tasks required guild leaders to personally watch over. However, for pursuing Lord Grim, even with the guild leaders personally leading the campaign, they still weren’t able to complete the task.

The guild leaders didn’t dare be negligent in the Heavenly Domain. These three guild leaders were from the three guilds in today’s conflict, so they had received the information the fastest. They had acted quickly too. The troops in Wilderness Town mainly consisted of their three guilds.

As for the small conflict over the Wilderness Escort, it was just a small matter for these guild leaders. There would always be friction between the guilds. It would be abnormal if there wasn’t a conflict over a boss. This was nothing to be worried about.

“He really is Ye QIu. He can even survive in this type of situation.”

It wasn’t possible to see the entire Wilderness Town on the second floor of this small building. The one speaking, Arisaema, had received the news from his subordinates. When he said this, Arisaema really wanted to see Chen Yehui’s expression. For Excellent Dynasty, the name Ye Qiu was a very sensitive subject.

“Oh? He really is Ye Qiu?” Chen Guo replied dully.

“Ha ha.” Arisaema laughed. Lord Grim was Ye Qiu. Their Herb Garden was certain of this and he doubted that Excellent Dynasty wouldn’t know. But from the looks of Excellent Era’s statements, they clearly wanted to limit the number of people that knew this.

These sorts of public statements expressed the attitudes of both Excellent Era as well as Excellent Dynasty. It was just that these statements could only influence their fans’ opinions towards Ye Qiu but they couldn’t change them. As a result, for Excellent Dynasty, dealing with Ye Qiu was a difficult task. They needed a completely good reason to do so. Obscuring Lord Grim’s identity was obviously a good method.

Is there anything I can utilize among these? Arisaema thought to himself. In addition, he believed he wasn’t the only one thinking about this question. Chen Yehui himself was being cautious too.

“They split up!”

Changing Spring suddenly said. He had just received news from the front lines.

The speed at which Chen Yehui and Arisaema got their news wasn’t any slower than him. Before Changing Spring could finish, they also got the news.

“We can’t let Deception go that easily. For the outside world, Deception is the main target. Lord Grim is simply implicated with him.” Chen Yehui said.

“Ha ha.” Arisaema laughed. Sure enough, Excellent Dynasty was very worried about chasing after Lord Grim, but Chen Yehu wasn’t wrong. Even for their guilds, chasing after the Glory star Lord Grim put huge pressure on them. Deception’s appearance was an opportunity. They couldn’t let this opportunity go away so easily. They had to bring these two down together.

Deception is heading towards the north, Lord Grim is heading towards the west.” Changing Spring said.

“I already have troops on the north side. Deception won’t be able to escape.” Arisaema said confidently. Honestly speaking, Deception wasn’t a big threat to them. No matter how great of an expert he was, with his lone wolf personality, he might injure their guild, but it wouldn’t hurt their foundation. The top guilds were more forgiving towards him because they had thoughts of roping him in.

As for Lord Grim, they had already experienced his abilities in the tenth server. In addition, with his identity, he was an even bigger player than they were. This was the type of player the top guilds placed great importance on.

“Lord Grim’s goal seems somewhat strange. What is he trying to do going west?” Changing Spring wondered.

Wilderness Town was on the southwest corner of the Heavenly Domain. Towards the west was the map’s end. In the game, this was an impossible to climb over mountain range. This mountain range covered the entire Heavenly Domain’s western boundary.

“Pull back the encirclement. Trap him at the foot of the mountain. Let’s see what he can do.” Chen Yehui said.

“I’ll take care of the north.” Arisaema said.

“I’ll take the east.” Changing Spring said.

“Then I’ll take the south!”

In order to make things easier to command, the three guilds didn’t mix together. This time, the three were working hand in hand and had made the appropriate arrangements. The three guilds had their work clear-cut. Their goal was to pursue Lord Grim and take his head.

Chapter 472 – Ninjutsu · Disappearing Body Technique

To the north of Wilderness Town was a flat wasteland with nowhere to hide. However, a river which snaked through the entire Heavenly Domain flowed from the mountain range. Dive into the water, follow the flow, and escape shouldn’t be too difficult.

Deception made a living as a scrap picker. He naturally had experience running away and had even decided where he should get back onto land.

Whoosh!

A gray shadow zoomed through a window from the second floor straight down to the streets. After rolling, he leaped up and stuck his ninja blade into the wall. Using it twice, he jumped up onto the top of the wall. He pulled on the rope in his hands and the ninja blade returned. The entire set of movements flowed perfectly. Not a single sound could be heard. In covert operations, Ninjas were better than Assassins at hiding and had stronger attacks than Thieves. Deception had a solid understanding of his class.

Deception didn’t immediately go down after jumping up onto the rooftop. He looked around left and right first and then crawled quietly forward. Below on the streets, he could hear the sounds of hurried footsteps. Deception didn’t move and listened carefully to their voices.

“Don’t go onto the roof!”

This was what Deception hoped would happen, but reality didn’t turn out as he hoped. All of a sudden, the whirring of rotor blades could be heard. There was nothing he could do. He immediately rolled backwards and his character slid down the wall. Midway, he stabbed his blade into a crack in the wall and swung back. His character flipped in the air and then he put his back to the wall underneath the cornice. If one didn’t look up, it would be difficult to see him.

This wasn’t any normal technique. This was a Ninja skill, Ninjutsu · Disappearing Body Technique.

However, in order to get underneath the cornice, a certain amount of imagination and mechanical skill was needed. What places the Disappearing Body Technique could or couldn’t be used, whether or not the desired effects could be reached, all of this depended on the player. The ability to hide with the character’s back to the wall without falling down was a type of support given by the system.

Because it was a skill, it had a duration limit. At max level, this status could be held for 30 seconds. How many levels this skill should be skilled up depended on the player to decide. For Ninjas, this skill was undoubtedly an important feature of the class, but every player had their own play styles, so there were quite a few who played it as a battle class. For these types of players, just one point into this skill was good enough.

Deception was in the middle. The skill wasn’t at level one but it wasn’t at max level either. He could sustain this state for 20 seconds. In this type of situation, he felt like this was good enough, unless these players moved abnormally slow. After going up onto the roofs and seeing that there was no one there, if they decided to dally around, then Deception would be exposed.

Seeing the skill’s timer turning, Deception listened carefully to the sounds up above on the roof. However, amidst the noisy whirring of rotor wings, it was very difficult to hear them.

Once the rotor wings stopped whirring, movements could be heard from up on the roof. The sounds were all over the place though and he couldn’t tell how many people there were.

Soon afterwards, several shadows leaped down from the roof.

“One, two, three……. Nine, ten……” Deception counted. An entire team of players had come down. Deception held his breath. Luckily, no one in the team looked back. The team split into two groups of five, heading in separate directions.

Deception let out a sigh of relief. He watched as the two groups moved farther away. There were no movements from up above either. He still had three seconds of his Disappearing Body Technique left. Deception used this time to quickly flip up onto the rooftop.

Cha!

A person was standing on the rooftop. Fortunately, his back was facing towards him. Under the Disappearing Body Technique, Deception’s movements didn’t make any noise when he landed. This person didn’t notice him.

They had actually left one person there.

Deception was extremely sad. If this wasn’t the game or the Arena’s sudden death mode, a slice across his throat would be enough to kill him off silently. Unfortunately, it wasn’t possible to kill off his opponent in one move. With his current equipment, it would take him at least a minute to kill him.

He couldn’t turn back either. There were certainly more pursuers coming after him there. Helpless, Deception could only continue forward. Exposed was exposed! It was just one person. It’s not like he would be trapped right?

Deception didn’t dare waste any more time. After a short moment of hesitation, he immediately moved. He threw out the string attached to his ninja blade. The string intersected and directly latched onto the person’s neck. He straightened his back and directly threw him onto the streets below.

He executed a clean Neck Bind Technique. He didn’t wait to see how that person would respond and immediately rushed forward onto the street below.

It turned out that over on this street, another team had slip up to the left and right directions. They were currently moving apart! The instant they received the news, they turned their heads back and saw Deception. Without hesitating, the two headed back to pincer him.

How unfortunate! If it wasn’t for that guy on the roof, he would have gone through without anyone knowing.

After passing through two streets, he looked forward. There were people on the roofs!

Deception was depressed. He hadn’t even escaped the people behind him yet and there were already people in front. His path in front was blocked, so he flipped a coin and turned right.

It was hard to avoid escaping in a complicated manner. However, Deception hadn’t changed his general direction. His goal was to get to the river north of the town.

He ran crazily towards the street’s east entrance. The pursuers were right behind him. The ones on the roof didn’t jump down and instead chased after him along the roofs.

Deception wasn’t wearing good equipment and he had a lot of stuff on him. The effect of the weight on his movement speed was somewhat of a disadvantage. He had mainly relied on hiding in order to get this far. A straight running race like this was not good for him. Before, he had run at around the same speed as Lord Grim, which meant that Deception’s running speed had decreased to a Level 50’s speed.

This street was a bit too long. At his speed, he might not even make it out of the street. Deception observed his surroundings and saw an empty building in front of him. He immediately rushed into it. After going through it, he discovered that the building didn’t have a window!

Deception hastily headed back. The instant he got out of the door, he nearly brushed shoulders with the enemies. These guild players weren’t ordinary and immediately attacked him when they saw him. Deception reacted quickly and rolled along a wall, dodging the sword.

But right after finishing the roll, he saw a grenade float in front of him. Deception hastily rolled to the right. The explosion injured him a bit, but it hadn’t affected his movement speed.

Currently, Deception wasn’t afraid of losing health. He was afraid of the after effects of the attacks. For example, a stun or a grab or a blow away wouldn’t give him any opportunities to live.

Deception got up and saw ten or so people pounce at him.

Deception could only jump onto the roof. This was where he had come from. He really didn’t want to go backwards. But going back now would be to move forward later. At this crucial moment, he had to backtrack to advance.

Deception went back, but soon discovered his step back was trash enough. This street used to be empty, but now there were people there.

In addition, they had blocked the east exit which he had originally been moving towards. Deception could only turn around and head to the west. He saw several empty buildings and wanted to go through them, but he was conflicted. The same situation as before might happen and the building might not have windows. It would be the same as going into a death hole. Seeing the pursuers beside him, with this distance, if he went in he wouldn’t be able to get out.

The pursuers were getting closer and closer. The gunners hadn’t stopped shooting at him. Deception’s pathing in order to dodge these bullets had greatly affected his movement speed. On the other hand, the pursuers behind him were moving in a straight line. Due to this, it was only a matter of time before he would be surrounded by them.

With the distance between them, he might not even be able to successfully flip over a wall. He could only make a gamble!

Deception clenched his teeth and rushed into an empty building on the left side. As soon as he went in, he saw a window! His hopes resurged. Just as he was about to go through the window, he suddenly had a thought.

This window was so obvious, of course……

Deception suddenly moved back a step. He jumped and threw a ninja blade at the wall. He swung up and went into a corner above the entrance like a spider. Disappearing Body Technique.

Right as he finished jumping, shadows appeared at the entrance and characters went into the building. Without hesitating, none of them stopped and rushed out through the window.

One, two, three…….

The pursuers all went through this route. Deception counted and counted anxiously.

Hurry, hurry!

Deception counted as he urged them to move forward. Before, he had been annoyed at how fast they were running and now he was annoyed at how slow they were. His Disappearing Body Technique only lasted 20 seconds. Once those 20 seconds were over, he would drop down. Twenty seconds should be enough. Deception had made the calculations before he did this.

But the moment of excitement never came. He heard a worrying voice. In the direction of the window, he heard someone say: “Did he come through here?”

“No, I didn’t see anyone come out from here!”

There were people watching outside!

Deception immediately understood. If he waited there, he would certainly die. His only choice was to break through with force.

He quickly cancelled his Disappearing Body Technique and immediately landed on the ground. At the same time, someone came into the building through the door. Deception’s brandished his blade and stabbed it into this person’s head as he fell. Then, he landed on his shoulders and pulled out the blade. His character shot out from the door like a bullet.

Ninjutsu · Bird Fall!

Chapter 473 – Difficult to Find Escape Route

Ninjutsu · Bird Fall!

After having just bumped into some bad luck, Deception whooshed out through the door. His character moved like a shadow, leaping directly over the incoming players’ heads. This time, his actions were completely unexpected. None of them had made any mental preparations. Deception landed on the ground and rolled forward. Without pausing, he got up and jumped up onto the rooftop.

The pursuers on the streets were in complete disorder and only realized what had happened after a short moment of confusion. They quickly turned their heads and saw the shadow of Deception drop towards the neighboring street.

The guy had run away again!

The players were furious. All of them recognized Deception. Some of them had even had their equipments stolen by him before. No one had any good feelings towards him. Although the guilds had never organized a group hunt for him, the players had privately organized their own hunting group before, but they had never been able to catch him.

Deception and Lord Grim were on two completely different ends of the spectrum for the guilds.

From the guild’s perspective, a lone soldier like Deception would never be able to injure their guild’s interests as a whole. No matter how annoying he was, it was just like an ant biting an elephant. However, while Deception caused trouble, there would always be a few inside the guild who would have their interests injured by him. Even though the top guilds could easily make up for the damage Deception did to them, there were many players who still detested him.

Lord Grim was the opposed. Lord Grim’s actions didn’t do any direct damage to the individual members of the guilds. However, the pressure he put out suppressed the guild’s strength as a whole. For example, in the tenth server, Lord Grim’s brilliance made the playerbase understand that he was an expert who didn’t care about the top guilds. This type of situation affected the top guild’s development greatly, but it was difficult for the individual members of the guilds to feel anything.

In the end, only an opponent like Lord Grim could make the entire guild act. Deception was simple a complimentary gift attached to him. However, in terms of execution, most of the guild members wanted to abuse their orders to carry out their private interests. They didn’t need any encouragement from above to kill Deception. They were more than happy to do the task.

“Is there anyone on East and West 8? Deception is heading in that direction!”

Against Deception, many of them were sincerely cooperating together.

“We’re there, but we don’t see Deception!”

“What?”

“He’s on the rooftop! He didn’t jump down!!”

The players who had just climbed up immediately saw Deception hiding in a place out of view from the others looking up from the streets.

“North and South 4, seal off the intersection between roads 47 and 48!!!”

“North and South 4 here, but we only have five people……”

“He’s on the rooftop. If you can delay him, that’s enough!!!”

Information continued to be passed around. Everyone reported Deception’s whereabouts and concentrated their strengths into encircling him.

There were all sorts of ways to communicate with each other. The temporary channel set-up by their guilds could only be used by people in their guilds. However, those in the alliance needed a way to communicate with each other as well. In game or out of game, as long as they could send information back and forth amongst each other, it didn’t matter. For a while, the people in charge of receiving and sending out information were extremely busy.

“Are the people at the people at the intersection ready? Deception is almost there!!”

The pursuers on the rooftops saw that they were almost at the end of the street and hastily urged them.

“Ready!” They were already in position.

“He’s here!!”

The five players at the intersection suddenly saw a shadow drop from a rooftop. The party leader gave a shout and skills were released in that direction. However, they soon realized that something wasn’t right. Wasn’t this shadow a bit too small?

“It’s not a person! It’s a piece of equipment!” Everyone instantly figured it out, but in that short instant, the real shadow landed. However, the five were still in their ending animation for their skills though! Just like this, Deception broke through.

“Deception broke through the blockade and is heading north towards North and South 4.” Even though it was shameful, the five made their report as they chased after him.

“Is there anyone at North and South 4? The target has just crossed intersection 48! No one can block at 49, 410, 411.” Someone shouted.

“Received! I’ll be at intersection 410 very soon!”

“We already see the target and are chasing after him. East and West 9, coordinates AX又，AX又.”

“East and West 11 is being reinforced. Coordinates 默又, 默又.”

“We’re at North and South 12. Do you need our help? Coordinates, 巛，巛.”

The nearby players reported their positions and their coordinates. Their chase after Deception was very active.

But the guild leaders of the three guilds were speechless at their situation. They didn’t mind everyone being so enthusiastic to kill Deception, but the important thing was, their other chase was the complete opposite.

Their main goal was still Lord Grim, but there was no news from the chase for Lord Grim in the past five minutes. He hadn’t left the Wilderness Town, but he had already escaped from their pursuit.

Against Deception, it was a chase. Against Lord Grim, it was a search. News about Lord Grim came about every two minutes about having not found him yet.

Five minutes! That was more than enough time to be out of combat, but they knew that lord Grim was still online. He had escaped, but hadn’t gone offline. This meant he didn’t care about them at all. The three were uneasy. The news telling them “he’s not here, he’s not there” made them extremely annoyed. And then when they looked how active Deception’s chase was, it was obvious how they were feeling.

“What is this guy planning on doing?” Besides the moment Lord Grim and Deception split up and deciding not to let Deception escape, they never mentioned Deception’s name again. Their attention was on Lord Grim.

The three were conflicted.

Lord Grim had already escaped from their eyes. They thought he would immediately log off and were originally disappointed and angry, but who would have thought he wouldn’t logout. However, they soon felt uneasy. After all, logging out was the safest and most efficient method. If he wasn’t going to log off, then it meant there was something he still wanted to do.

Ye Xiu hadn’t even done anything yet and he was already making these three guild leaders feel uneasy.

They still hadn’t found any signs of Lord Grim, yet all they were getting were information about Deception. The more the three looked at the incoming news, the angrier they got.

“What’s going on? They can’t even kill off Deception?” Chen Yehui was the first to curse. The more impatient they got over Lord Grim, the more unsettled they became. Poor Deception had become their outlet to vent their anger.

“Nine Heroes, Golden Fragrance! How come there’s still no news from you two??” Chen Yehui reprimanded two players in his guild.

“We’re guarding the south side…..” Nine Heroes and Golden Fragrance were Excellent Dynasty’s core players and Chen Yehui’s trusted aides.

“What are you guarding for? There’s still no one after five minutes! Hurry up and move. Go look for him.” Chen Yehui roared.

“Do we look for Lord Grim or Deception?” Nine Heroes carefully asked. He was a bit confused. In the beginning, the guild leader was criticizing them for not catching Deception yet and then he switched the topics to him and Golden Fragrance, complaining how they weren’t working hard. Then, he told them how there was still no sign of him after five minutes, talking about lord Grim again. Finally, he told them to look for him…… Nine Heroes felt like the guild leader’s thoughts were a bit jumbled.

“LORD GRIM!!!”

“Understood……” The two hastily told their troops to move out and look around. After shouting at these two, he picked out more names to instruct. The group leaders who were scolded yelled at the party leaders inside their groups. The party leaders immediately urged their party members. In Excellent Dynasty, everyone from top to bottom was given a yell. No one dared to be negligent again. They looked around and searched. A portion of them went over to help out the other chase and quickly kill off Deception.

Chen Yehui found Deception extremely annoying. It was like when you were working hard at something and there was this house fly buzzing around you all the time.

Deception was ready to run as if his life depended on it along one road, but he soon encountered a strong blockade. He wasn’t going to kill himself to do so though Deception was just a bit tougher than before. In places where he would have ran back, he now chose to break through them with force. Yet even so, he still hadn’t escaped from the pursuit. Deception’s current goal was the north exit, but he was getting farther and farther away from it. He was being pushed to the foot of the mountain on the west side. Once he got there, his options would be more limited. They originally needed to surround him on all four sides, but if they trapped him there, they would only need to surround him on three sides.

“Is there anyone at intersection 24! Is there anyone there!!” The communication once again started. Deception had already been forced to this position.

“Here.” Someone replied. This was Excellent Dynasty’s Golden Fragrance. After being yelled at by Chen Yehui, she and Nine Heroes led their teams around. They just happened to have gotten here and received this message for help.

“Deception is heading towards your direction.”

“Okay, give him to us!” Golden Fragrance was one of his guild’s core members, so her thoughts were more from an upper level perspective. Her attitude towards Deception was the same as her superiors, but now that they had bumped into each other, she wasn’t going to let it go. After being yelled out by her guild leader, she was quite panicked too! They only had two targets for this operation. It wasn’t easy to find an outlet to vent her anger. Now that an outlet had come to her, she was going to play around.

“Spread out!” Golden Fragrance led more people than the others. Her group wasn’t made up of just three or five people. Right now, the ten players under her were ordered to completely spread out, leaving intersection 24 empty.

“Tell me the target’s coordinates.” Golden Fragrance requested.

“Coordinates 又,又.” Someone replied. He was clearly still chasing after Deception. Deception wasn’t having it easy either. Everywhere he went, he knocked into a bee’s nest. He had never gotten out of combat. If he could, he would have logged off long ago. Why would he still struggle? Right now, the north side was completely blocked off. His only choice was to run south. In front of him was an intersection. After having been on the run for so long, he knew there would soon be people rushing to block the intersection, but it seemed unexpectedly quiet this time!

Chapter 474 – Ninjutsu – Shadow Dance

Deception wasn’t stupid. The guilds weren’t foolish either.

Golden Fragrance wasn’t the only one to try hiding on the sides, waiting to make an ambush. Deception had seen this sort of scenario, where the intersections looked very sweet, four times already. This was now Deception’s fifth time seeing this scheme.

However, this time, there was one thing different from the previous four attempts.

Golden Fragrance had more people!

Deception took up his guard. He didn’t rush straight towards the intersection. Instead, he went onto the rooftops and prepared for the unexpected. When he landed on the roof, he was suddenly caught off guard. In that instant, fifteen people appeared at the intersection.

Their encirclement tightened around Deception. It looked like he had a way out behind him, but the pursuers from behind were getting closer and closer by the second. From the start to the finish, he had never been able to escape from the pursuers.

“Let’s see where you run now!” Golden Fragrance stepped forward and shouted aggressively at Deception. She didn’t have any enmity towards Deception. It was just that she hadn’t been able to find Deception and wanted to seize this gift to vent her anger.

“Hmph!” Deception coldly humphed. Without saying anything more, he looked around and calmly observed his situation.

Fifteen players. They had already completed the encirclement. It was his first time encountering this sort of situation. Moreover, his opponents had plenty of experience. Their encirclement had layers. The gap between the layers had calculated the distance his Shadow Clone Technique could reach. Deception wouldn’t be able to rely on this technique to escape.

There was no easy way out.

Deception immediately realized this. He knew that this time he was truly in a dangerous spot. If he didn’t force his way through, he would certainly die!

It only took him the time for a single breath to come to this conclusion. Golden Fragrance’s words had only just finished, when Deception suddenly rushed forward. His target was Golden Fragrance.

To capture a band of thieves, first catch the leader!

Although taking down the leader wouldn’t change the situation significantly in this situation, if he wasn’t able to break through, bringing down the leader along with him was still decent.

With his blade glinting in the light, Deception arrived extremely quickly.

But Golden Fragrance wasn’t a core expert of Excellent Dynasty for nothing.

Seeing Deception rush at her, she immediately raised her hands and fired.

Three Anti-Tank Missiles shot out towards Deception. In an instant, the smoke and light from the explosion engulfed the area.

“Careful!”

Someone on the side warned.

Golden Fragrance didn’t have time to react. All she saw was a streak of blood fly out from her.

Assassin skill: Cut Throat!

How did Deception get behind me? It wasn’t hard for Golden Fragrance to figure it out. His only way to do so was Shadow Clone Technique. However, she hadn’t seen him used even though he had been right in front of her eyes.

Every skill had a sign before it was used. When Shadow Clone Technique was used, the character would shake slightly. Everyone knew Ninjas had this technique, so everyone usually looked for this sign, yet Golden Fragrance hadn’t seen it.

This was because Deception’s hands were extremely quick! The faster the movements were done, the shorter the sign. This didn’t have any limit.

For a Launcher, being closed in on was very bad. However, Golden Fragrance wasn’t too alarmed because she wasn’t the only one fighting.

Her character turned around and used a Swing, the Launcher’s knock-up skill.

Deception had retreated a long time ago though. Cut Throat had simply been an attack done in the passing. His main goal was to break through the encirclement and escape. If he wasn’t able to escape, then he would fight.

After retreating from Golden Fragrance, Deception turned around and leaped up. He flipped in the air and flew above two players blocking the path in front of him. He just hoped these two players wouldn’t react too quickly.

Of these two players blocking the path, one was a Sharpshooter and the other was a Blade Master. Unfortunately, their reactions were very fast.

The Blade Master leaped up and used a Falling Phoenix Slash in an attempt to slice Deception.

There was no other option for Deception. He slashed with his ninja blade to guard against the Falling Phoenix Slash.

Clank!

This guard was only a type of attack versus attack. It wasn’t an actual defensive skill. Whether or not the attack hit the opponent’s weapon depended on the player.

Deception had only used a normal attack, while the Blade Master had used a Falling Phoenix Slash.

Thus, he was only able to reduce some of the damage and wasn’t able to block the Falling Phoenix Slash’s momentum. The blade light continued to descend rapidly. Deception put his ninja blade in front of him and could only watch as he was cut down.

This was the difference between a normal guard and the Guard skill.

The Guard skill could completely negate the opponent’s attack, while a normal guard only blocked a portion of the damage.

Deception was hit to the ground by the Falling Phoenix Slash. When the Sharpshooter jumped up, he made a roll backwards.

This roll made Deception very sad. When he landed, he made a forward roll to avoid the Blade Master, but was now right in front of the Sharpshooter’s gun.

These two were clearly experienced veterans. This sort of coordination completely removed all of Deception’s options.

The other players were also closing in. There were a few waiting outside too in order to guard against a Shadow Clone Technique.

How troublesome……

The instant Deception landed on the ground, he immediately rolled backwards.

Behind him was the enemy leader, Golden Fragrance.

After all, Golden Fragrance was a Launcher. Seeing Deception roll towards her, she jumped back.

But at the same time Deception rolled back, he suddenly disappeared.

“Not good!”

Golden Fragrance realized, but Deception had already dug back up below her feet.

Ninjutsu – Underground Tunneling Technique!

A streak of blood flew out from Golden Fragrance’s body.

But the attacks weren’t done yet. After using the Underground Tunneling Technique Deception put his two hands together in front of his head and formed a hand seal.

“This is…….” Golden Fragrance could see him clearly, but she couldn’t tell what seal he was forming. The hand seal was finished in an instant. Deception’s body suddenly flickered as if he were going to use a Shadow Clone Technique. But the movements made after this flicker were much greater than the Shadow Clone Technique. It looked as if he spread out in all different directions.

Golden Fragrance instantly knew what was going to happen.

Unfortunately, that was all she could do.

After Deception flickered, he suddenly spread out. Suddenly, countless shadows of Deception appeared. The shadows ran in all different directions causing everyone’s eyes to go blurry. Blood began flying out continuously from Golden Fragrance’s body.

Ninja Level 70 skill, Ninjutsu – Shadow Dance!

“Spread out a bit more! Don’t let him escape the circle!!!!” Golden Fragrance immediately ordered.

Shadow Dance’s attack made several shadows appear. After finishing the skill, the character could freely choose which shadow to go to. With so many shadows around moving in a blur, it was impossible for them to know where he would go. If they didn’t widen their encirclement, it was very likely that their prey would use this chance to break through.

When everyone heard this order, they widened the encirclement, while attacking the shadows.

The clones from the Shadow Dance and the clone from the Shadow Clone Technique was the same. They could be destroyed with an attack. The difference between these two skills was that the clones of the Shadow Dance could move around and had higher health.

People tended to choose the shadows which weren’t moving.

This was because each clone in the Shadow Dance had to be manually controlled by the player. As a result, most of the time, the player wouldn’t be able to move every single clone. Some of them would just stand there.

But they soon realized that there weren’t any! There weren’t any clone which weren’t moving!

Deception could unexpectedly control all of the shadow clones. Such a level of mechanics was already a pro level. As players in a top guild like Excellent Dynasty, they had seen many things. However, whether it was in-game or in the Arena, they had never seen a player able to control Shadow Dance to such a level.

With no clones sitting still, they could only attack randomly. But the shadow clones moved faster than normal under the Shadow Dance. With so many shadow clones flickering around, none of them could follow them and were unable to properly seize one.

The skill had a time limit though. Just go rampant! You won’t be able to run away anyways.

They had the numbers advantage. The weren’t afraid.

Golden Fragrance initially thought like this, but after awhile, she suddenly realized something wasn’t right.

Wasn’t her health dropping a bit too fast?

Shadow Dance was typically used as an AoE attack. But right now, it seemed like Deception was only focusing on her. The dancing shadows were not only obscuring everyone’s view, but also attacking her.

Because of how a player’s skill greatly affected a skill’s effectiveness, it was difficult to tell a skill’s effects. Using Shadow Dance as an AoE attack was simple. But using it as a single target attack wasn’t impossible, but it required much more skill to accomplish.

Deception was undoubtedly doing it in this way. He had controlled all of the shadows to focus fire on her. Due to this, Golden Fragrance’s health was dropping rapidly. She originally hadn’t been worrying about it, but now such a thought had risen in her head.

“Am I really going to die?” Golden Fragrance was scared. She hastily called out: “Cleric!”

There team of fifteen would obviously have a Cleric. The other players really hadn’t noticed her situation, but after hearing her call for a Cleric, they suddenly realized that Golden Fragrance was already at such low health.

The Cleric quickly dashed over. Just as he was about to heal her, a shadow passed by him and interrupted his casting.

“Use an instant one!” Golden Fragrance was furious.

Chapter 475 – What Enmity Do You Have with Launchers?

There were two types of Cleric heals. One type was a heal over time and had a cast time. This was what players commonly referred to when they said heal. This type was split into three different kinds, small heal, great heal, holy heal. The longer the cast time, the greater the heal. The casts made by Clerics were different from Ninja hand seals, which would be improved with better skill. For these casts, the only thing that could be done was to press the skill faster. The cast time could only be decreased with the character’s spirit attribute and certain equipment.

The other type of heal was an urgent rescue type. This type of heal was called cure and was split into three different kinds: small cure, great cure, holy cure. Cures didn’t have a cast time and were considered instant casts. However, they had very long cooldowns and it wasn’t possible to only rely on these to recover health. As a result cures were mainly used in emergencies, while heals were the ones mainly used.

When to use the three different kinds of heals and the three different kinds of cures was one area which determined a Cleric’s skill level.

The Cleric in Excellent Dynasty looked at Golden Fragrance’s health and didn’t see it as too dire. Moreover, they had the numbers advantage and his safety should be ensured. Thus, he had been planning on healing Golden Fragrance with a holy heal. Who would have thought that Deception’s Shadow Dance would interrupt him.

Golden Fragrance was in a panic and urged him to hurry, so the Cleric hastily prepared to cast a cure, but before he could do so, one of Deception’s clones pounced at him. Under the combo, the Cleric remained in a stunned state, unable to cast the cure. Deception had turned Shadow Dance into a multi target skill. He was planning on giving Golden Fragrance a good beating.

But with the attacks from Shadow Dance being split between the Cleric and Golden Fragrance, Golden Fragrance was no longer in as much pressure. When she looked at her health, she felt like she had been a bit too panicked. No matter the case, it wasn’t possible for a single skill to instantly kill a same-leveled character, even if Shadow Dance was solely focused on her.

After drinking a health potion, Golden Fragrance arranged everyone’s position using the team channel. Shadow Dance couldn’t kill her, but Deception might simply be trying to use the chaos to escape.

Once Golden Fragrance calmed down, the entire team was no longer in as much of a panic as before. Shadow Dance’s attacks hadn’t been aimed at them, so their movements weren’t affected. All of them were Glory veterans, so they understood what this skill did and immediately went to the positions Golden Fragrance arranged.

Deception had been paying attention to his surroundings the entire time. This had been his only plan. If everything went well, he would have been able to escape. Initially, when he saw the enemies fall into disorder, Deception felt excited and carefully looked for an opportunity. But then the enemies quickly calmed down and moved into a tough formation, not giving him any opening to escape. On the other side of the street, the pursuers from behind were about to arrive.

It’s over……

This time, Deception had no more tricks left. He would never have imagined he would be unable to escape in such a large map. What type of drug did these guys eat today?

Shadow Dance soon ended. Deception hadn’t been able to find any opening. After landing on the ground, he directly headed towards Golden Fragrance.

Ninjutsu · Bird Fall!

Shadow Dance was one of the few high-leveled skills which didn’t have a long landing animation after using the skill. As a result, Deception was able to directly chain it with a Bird Fall. Falling from the sky, he stepped on Golden Fragrance.

Just when she was thinking he would be unable to do anything after finishing with the Shadow Dance, who would have thought she would eat such an attack. Golden Fragrance’s head crashed to the ground. Her pose looked very embarrassing. Under everyone’s gazes, she had trouble keeping up appearances.

“KILL HIM!!” Golden Fragrance hissed. As a girl and an expert among girls, one of Excellent Dynasty’s core members, Golden Fragrance was used to getting attention everywhere. When had she ever been bullied by someone like this before? She didn’t have any enmity with Deception, but she instantly had some now.

“Ha ha ha ha ha…….”

At this moment, the sounds of someone laughing could be heard, a girl’s laugh. And in this team, Golden Fragrance was the only female there. But how could Golden Fragrance laugh in this situation? Even Deception was surprised by the sudden laugh. He thought she had gone mad. However, when he checked again, he felt that something wasn’t right. The voice was a bit quiet and unclear. It wasn’t from nearby.

“What are you laughing for? You’re going to expose me!!” Following afterwards, another voice could be heard, though this voice was much more clear.

“Isn’t this Excellent Dynasty’s Golden Princess? Isn’t it funny seeing her on the ground eating dirt?” Someone said. The voice seemed to be stuttering. The Glory veterans knew what was going on. Some other person next to the person playing was speaking, so the voice wasn’t too clear.

“Who is it!” Golden Fragrance asked angrily.

Golden Princess was a nickname people gave her behind her back in Excellent Dynasty. It didn’t have any positive connotations to it. It was mocking her, saying she was like a snobby princess.

The surrounding Excellent Era players looked at each other. They looked around, but didn’t know where the voice was coming from.

“How embarrassing. I’m very sorry for bothering everyone.”

The clear voice could be heard this time. A figure suddenly came around the corner of the street, dashing at them, while speaking.

“LORD GRIM!!” Everyone cried out in fear. With a shout, the encirclement around Deception broke apart and headed towards Lord Grim. The players around Golden Fragrance were all of the upper level in the guild. They knew who the guild attached the most importance to. Thus, when as soon as they saw Lord Grim, they immediately switched targets and forgot about Deception.

An opening!

Deception was pleasantly surprised at first seeing a sudden opening, but when he turned around, he figured out the reason for the opening. It was because everyone had turned to surround Lord Grim. He suddenly felt an empty feeling in him.

He finally understood why the guilds were pursuing him so crazily in this Wilderness Town. The main reason was because of him. Because he had gotten involved with him, he was brought into the storm as well.

Lord Grim……

This time, Deception took note of his name. As for Lord Grim, he was instantly surrounded.

Lord Grim suddenly did a roll. When he got up, he turned around 180 degrees and fired his gun. His character began flying backwards with a smooth Aerial Fire. The entire movement was completed in a single breath.

However, this wasn’t enough to break out of the encirclement. The players’ attacks had already arrived, when Lord Grim suddenly turned into smoke.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Deception was caught off guard. He was unexpectedly unable to figure out where Lord Grim had gone.

“You’re so slow. I’ve been waiting here all day.” Lord Grim suddenly spoke.

“Waiting for what?” Deception was at a loss. When he turned around, Lord Grim’s real body was already next to him.

“A scrap picking opportunity!” As he spoke, Lord Grim swung his hand. Deception was looking at him from behind and didn’t know which knock-up skill he had used, but Golden Fragrance had been launched into the air.

The sudden laugh to Lord Grim appearing next to him had all gone by too quickly, so quickly that Golden Fragrance had only just climbed back up.

“A scrap picking opportunity? You’ve been following me the entire time?”

“Why would I follow you? You’re not my target.” Ye Xiu said.

“What target is there for scrap picking?!” Deception cried. He suddenly noticed that Golden Fragrance and that previous guy who had been killed for nothing happened to both be Launchers……

“What enmity do you have with Launchers?” Deception had a sudden realization.

“Nonsense! I have a good relationship with Launchers.”

The two were talking, but they weren’t just standing there. After Ye Xiu launched Golden Fragrance into the air, he used a Delivery Gun to send Golden Fragrance to Deception. As he rushed forwards, he fired attacks at the airborne Golden Fragrance as if he were dribbling her like a ball.

Deception was also hurrying way. It was just that he felt a bid sad at this opening because this opening had been made by the enemies ignoring him.

“A helper, old friend. See, I’ve saved you again.” Ye Xiu said.

“What do you mean again?” Deception kicked Golden Fragrance to Lord Grim like a ball.

“How mean! If it wasn’t for me last time on that street, you would have died in some corner in the street!” Ye Xiu said.

Deception immediately recalled. That time, he had tried getting over a wall, but had been blasted down by someone. Later, Lord Grim created an opening for him to get through. The heavens knew how hard he had been working to escape from the pursuers. There had been something going on every minute. That small scene felt like something from a long time ago. He really hadn’t thought about it.

“I helped you kill off that Launcher from before. I’ve paid you back for that time.” Deception said.

“It’s the same this time. Just a bit more! Good! Success!”

Golden Fragrance had already turned into a corpse. But this time, Deception didn’t go and steal equipment. This was because his situation was already burdensome enough. He didn’t want to add any more weight to him.

Ye Xiu’s hands weren’t any slower than his either. The items were instantly picked up by him. In the blink of an eye, Deception couldn’t help but shudder because that item had Orange lettering!

Could it be an Orange equipment?

Deception was astonished. He had never picked up an Orange equipment in his career as a scrap picker before.

Chapter 476 – Chen Guo’s Resentment

Self-made equipment practically only belonged in the pro realm.

In the Heavenly Domain, an Orange equipment was already considered an extremely rare equipment.

Anyone who possessed an Orange equipment wasn’t any ordinary player. The probability that they survived in a chaotic situation was high. Deception couldn’t be compared to an ordinary scrap picker. His eyes were sharp and venomous. Whenever he moved out, he would usually have a clear understanding of the situation in front of him. He would notice the equipment on every player and their health. Compared to a normal scrap picker, he was more selective. Even so, an opportunity to one shot one kill an expert with an Orange expert was extremely rare. As a result, even if he really wanted it, he rarely got the chance.

Deception refused to call grabbing and mercilessly killing the target like what Lord Grim did as scrap picking. This was stealing.

“What dropped?” Everyone wanted to know the answer to this question. Deception wasn’t an exception.

“A lame necklace.” Ye Xiu said.

Lame!!!

No matter how lame it is, it’s still an Orange equip! Did you think I didn’t see it?

Deception had a very strong urge to give him a stab, but he stopped himself and calmly asked: “It seemed like an Orange equip?”

“Yeah! Trash.” Ye Xiu said.

“What do you want?” Deception’s voice was trembling a little bit.

“I want a weapon.” Ye XIu said and then added: “You want a weapon, right?”

“What?” Deception was confused about question.

“I wasn’t talking to you.”

Ye Xiu was obviously asking Chen Guo. From the start, he had been very serious. He had really been planning on helping Chen Guo get back her dropped weapon. He didn’t even feel ashamed to ask Chen Guo which Excellent Dynasty Launcher had good equipment.

After all, Chen Guo had been in Excellent Dynasty for a long time. The guild leader and core members might not recognize her, but she certainly recognized them. She pretty much knew which guild members had what dazzling equipment. Right now, Ye Xiu was like a bandit, asking her who had good equipment. Chen Guo suddenly felt like a villain.

Her resentment towards Excellent Era wasn’t fake. It had been very painful seeing her weapon drop too, but she didn’t feel too happy getting it back by stealing from someone else. Excellent Dynasty’s members were all normal players too. Excellent Era might have kicked Ye Qiu out of the Club, but that had nothing to do with these players. It’s not like they knew the truth. They would still jump out and support Ye Qiu. If they were to take out revenge on Excellent Era, it definitely couldn’t be done by acting against the normal fans.

Chen Guo was going to refuse to answer him in the beginning, but after she thought about it again, she suddenly blurted out a name: Golden Fragrance.

Golden Fragrance was already one of Excellent Dynasty’s core members now, but when Chen Guo had joined Excellent Dynasty, she still wasn’t one yet.

At that time, she was also just a fan who liked Excellent Era a lot. She was a very ordinary guild member.

She was a lively and outgoing girl. People tended to like her. Golden Fragrance was very easy going. She would go with whatever team was there wherever she went. Everyone was happy to have her join. Any equipment she wanted went to her.

Even though Chen Guo was also a girl, but she had turned independent early in her life. She was on the older side too. Outside of the game, she was an owner, while in-game, she had the air of a big sister. She also liked Golden Fragrance and happily welcomed her. In particular, Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze and Golden Fragrance were of the same class. Of everyone she had played with, she had played with Golden Fragrance a lot.

This didn’t really mean much.

But once she regarded everyone else’s welcome as a given, it was quite immature of her.

There were many girls in the guild who also played Launcher. They were clearly influenced by Su Mucheng.

As a big sister, Chen Guo gave them an appropriate amount of care. In a dungeon, she would give priority to the other younger sisters.

In the guild’s fixed dungeon teams, the distribution of items was done by the team captain. This was something everyone agreed on.

No one objected to Chen Guo’s actions of taking care of the younger ones. Golden Fragrance, who everyone took care of, snatched a piece of equipment that she had the right to take. The good-hearted team’s preferential treatment gave her unwarranted qualifications. It was certainly an eye-opener for Chen Guo.

Chen Guo wasn’t like Ye Xiu who could just laugh and not think much of it. At that time, she called out to Golden Fragrance for her to give her an explanation.

But Golden Fragrance didn’t even bother properly discussing with Chen Guo. She just cried and privately told countless players her sorrows and gain their sympathy. In the blink of an eye, Chen Guo turned into a tyrant in the team in other players’ eyes..

This description fit well with Chen Guo’s personality. Golden Fragrance’s actions were a huge success.

With Chen Guo’s personality, there was no way she could do the same, running to others and crying. In the end, she challenged Golden Fragrance to a duel.

This was how the men decided on issues, but Chen Guo liked it. She was too lazy to go into a verbal battle with a younger sister. Even though duels weren’t absolute, they put an end to the matter. It was a very common way of deciding on issues.

But for this manly method, Golden Fragrance actually found men to participate in the duel for her. This girl, who hadn’t been in the guild much longer than Chen Guo, was used to having this sort of princess treatment.

Chen Guo obviously wouldn’t retreat from any opponent. It’s just that the players Golden Fragrance had found were experts in the guild. Chen Guo went forward in battle, but lost.

Chen Guo wasn’t someone who couldn’t take a defeat. If she lost, there was nothing she could say. No matter how arrogant or condescending the opponent was, she would bear it. Chen Guo wanted to leave the guild, but she felt unwilling to. By being with a Club guild, she would have the opportunity to play with her idols. Many people had joined the guild for this reason.

Chen Guo’s support for Su Mucheng and Ye Qiu triumphed over her resentment over that little girl.

Chasing Haze stayed in the guild as Golden Fragrance continued to play the part of a princess in Excellent Dynasty. Golden Princess wasn’t a nickname Chen Guo had come up with. Who knew when this nickname spread. Chen Guo really liked it. She felt that it suited her well.

In Excellent Dynasty, there were quite a few who were annoyed by Golden Fragrance. However, the number of people who liked to spoil her were a lot too. Just like this, she move her way up to becoming a part of Excellent Dynasty’s core.

Core members were vastly different from normal players. Core members could be considered as employees of the Club and surrogates for the team in-game. When Chen Guo initially joined, she also wanted that status so she could get closer with the team she supported.

At that time, when Golden Fragrance became a core member, many people in the guild objected. This girl was a spoiled brat. Chen Guo really couldn’t understand how people could like such a girl…..

Is being a spoiled brat an art form?

Chen Guo thought it was because of this, but she wanted to vomit whenever she thought of it. Being a spoiled brat was something boss Chen could never learn.

It had been several years since this. But Chasing Haze had always been in Excellent Dynasty and Golden Fragrance was a name that could never be erased. Chen Guo had to admit that even though she lost, she wasn’t willing to accept it. She could never see Golden Fragrance in a good light. Even though Chen Guo hear that she was no longer like the princess from before and that she took care of others like a big sister, Chen Guo just felt like it was obvious. As a core member, why would she need others to give way to her? With her status as a core member, this was already a given.

Today, Ye Xiu suddenly asked her which Launcher in Excellent Dynasty had good equipment as if he were going to take it. Chen Guo originally didn’t want to say it, but her mind whirred and she blurted out Golden Fragrance’s name.

There were lots of Su Mucheng fans in Excellent Dynasty and thus, there were naturally many Launchers. More than one core member was a Launcher. Golden Fragrance’s equipment couldn’t be considered the best among them, but if her items dropped, Chen Guo wouldn’t feel bad. She would actually feel quite good.

Thinking of this, Chen Guo felt somewhat ashamed. She felt like she was being petty. But after seeing Lord Grim wandering around and seriously looking for Golden Fragrance, Chen Guo immediately turned hopeful. She realized that this was a dream of hers. She really wanted to see the look on the Golden Princess’s helpless face after being bullied. This mission was something Chen Guo felt that Ye Xiu could accomplish.

Chen Guo had been thinking like this the entire time. On the other hand, Ye Xiu was only carefully looking at her, but not moving. He waited a very long time until Deception had been caught. His movements were like a pros. Deception was hitting Golden Fragrance under the team’s protection without any retaliation. He even ended it by kicking her face into the dirty. Such a scene made Chen Guo extremely happy.

Petty is petty! Why be so kind? It’s not like I’m a saint. That instant, Chen Guo let go of her morals.

However, her laugher revealed Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. Chen Guo had went closer to Ye Xiu’s screen to admire Golden Fragrance’s embarrassing pose and then burst out into laughter.

“I didn’t get a weapon, just this lame necklace.” Ye Xiu reported his results to Chen Guo.

“Not bad, not bad.” Chen Guo was very satisfied. Her goal wasn’t Golden Fragrance’s equipment. She just wanted to see Golden Fragrance eat sh*t.

“Do you have some sort of thing between you two?” Ye Xiu clearly saw something.

“Uh, it’s a long story!”

“Is killing her once good enough?” Ye Xiu asked.

Chen Guo hesitated. After thinking for a bit, she asked: “Will she come back?”

“Tsk tsk, what poisonous thoughts!” Ye Xiu sighed.

“What did you say!” Chen Guo was both angry and ashamed.

“Don’t worry. It’s no pressure. You’re a friend. I won’t judge you.” Ye Xiu said.

“…..”

“But……”

“But what?”

“But if the people knows that I was the one to kill them, do you think they might feel proud?” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was speechless, but she had to admit that it was a real possibility.

Chapter 477 – Gap

After discovering Lord Grim’s traces, everyone in the guild began getting excited. Lord Grim was their priority. Deception was just a side gift.

The three guild leaders were also very excited. They had the map of Wilderness Town opened up on their screens. After asking for his coordinates, they immediately pinpointed his location and began making arrangements.

“Don’t rush. Form a steady encirclement and slowly shrink the circle. He won’t be able to run.” Changing Spring said. Golden Fragrance’s team was from Excellent Dynasty. The ones chasing behind Deception were from Herb Garden. Blue Brook Guild’s troops weren’t directly involved yet, so Changing Spring could see the field in a calmer manner.

“Right, it looks like he doesn’t plan on logging off, so we’ll just accompany him until he does.” Arisaema added.

“Why did he jump out all of a sudden?” Changing Spring asked.

“I heard he took down Excellent Dynasty’s Golden Fragrance.” Arisaema said. He really wanted to see Chen Yehui’s expression. Was Lord Grim attacking Excellent Dynasty? Before, when he broke through the encirclement, he had killed off a Launcher, who was also one of Excellent Dynasty’s. This time, he killed off another Launcher and a core member of Excellent Dynasty at that……

Thinking of this, Arisaema and Changing Spring opened up a private chat between the two of them.

“Ye Qiu seems to be aiming at Excellent Dynasty.” Arisaema said.

“K”

Now that they were conversing in messages, Changing Spring spoke in a simple manner. He was even too lazy to type out punctuation. Seeing this reply, Arisaema turned furious. Their Herb Garden and Blue Brook Guild were originally enemies. He also hated Changing Spring’s bad habit. Right now, he didn’t want to deal with this guy, but then he quickly realized that he didn’t need to deal with him! As long as his guild benefited from this, why would he need to talk to Changing Spring? Thinking of this, Arisaema closed the chat window. He was calculating whether or not there would be an opportunity to sit on the mountains and watch the tigers fight below. In any case, Lord Grim had to be killed. Whether or not they or Excellent Dynasty killed him didn’t matter. He really didn’t mind if Lord Grim could take a few bites out of Excellent Dynasty in the process.

“Make sure there aren’t any gaps. Don’t be too excited. Make sure you figure out Lord Grim’s intents.” Arisaema quickly ordered.

On the streets, Lord Grim and Deception were both running madly. The pursuers behind them were chasing after them. Anyone who was in range to attack them wouldn’t hesitate to attack them.

But these didn’t matter too much. As Lord Grim ran, Ye Xiu was talking to Chen Guo. Deception was focused on listening to see if he could figure out anything from eavesdropping.

But after hearing Ye Xiu say “do you think they might feel proud?” Deception couldn’t stop himself from coldly making a “hmph.”

“Who do you think you are?” Deception actually said this to Ye Xiu.

“I’m someone who almost got surrounded and died.” Ye Xiu said.

“……” Deception was annoyed.

“Twice.” Ye Xiu even added.

“I’m going my own way!” Deception decided. There just happened to be another intersection ahead. Deception turned right, but Lord Grim also followed along.

“Don’t follow me.” Deception said.

“You really are a genius. There are three possible directions which we can go. Two of those directions have people. You moved in the third direction, telling me not to go with you. Why didn’t you go in the direction where there are people?” Ye Xiu said.

“…..”

“Make a left turn up ahead.” Ye Xiu said.

Deception ignored him and continued forward. Ye Xiu didn’t care and his Lord Grim turned left. But it hadn’t even been three seconds, when Deception rushed back over.

“Don’t follow me.” Ye Xiu coldly said.

Deception wanted to cry, but no tears came out. It wasn’t that he wanted to follow him, it was just that he didn’t want to die. He was having a hard time bearing Ye Xiu retaliating tooth for tooth. Deception halted and turned his head.

“Wow, young people these days sure have attitudes.” Ye Xiu said, but he also had his Lord Grim turn back.

“Why are you following me!” Deception countered.

“I’m a realist.” Ye Xiu said.

“What?” Deception didn’t understand.

“There’s more people that way……” Ye Xiu explained.

Deception wanted to cough blood. He couldn’t describe how he was feeling right now.

There were five players blocking their path forward. They seemed to know the two were strong. Seeing the two of them rush at them, they didn’t rush forward to meet them. Instead, they immediately stood still in position and prepared to face them head on.

Deception saw an empty building up ahead and ran towards the entrance.

“What are you planning on doing?” Ye Xiu asked.

Deception didn’t explain and continued into the building. Ye Xiu didn’t have Lord Grim go in. He stood outside the building and laughed grimly.

He counted one two three, but there were still no movements.

If you don’t come out, are you planning on dying?” Ye Xiu lazily asked.

Deception slowly walked out embarrassedly.

“How did you know there were no windows in that building?” Deception asked.

“Look at the map, genius.” Ye Xiu remarked.

“There are labels on the map?” Deception was puzzled.

“An online map from outside the game, are you a noob or an expert?” Ye Xiu said.

“Expert!” Deception replied with confidence.

“Get ready to fight, expert.”

The two may be talking, but their characters weren’t moving slowly. In a short amount of time, they entered the five enemies’ attack range. The two didn’t make the first move. They were waiting for an opening first. If the opponents didn’t move, then that would be great. They could just run passed them.

From this, it could be seen that Deception wasn’t a noob. He clearly had a lot of experience at running away.

The blockers wouldn’t just let them pass. As the two got closer and closer, two of the Blade Masters in the team moved. Blade lights flashed and both of them slashed with a Sword Draw. The blade lights intersected and flew towards them.

They were both from the same guild and the same team, so their coordination was quite good. Even though their coordination wasn’t as good as pro teams, everyone learned from them, so even if it wasn’t amazing, it was at least decent.

The Blade Master’s duet was one form of strategy for two Blade Masters. As one of Glory’s most popular classes, whether it was in-game or in the pro scene, it was a common sight.

But when the blade lights fell, they only destroyed a clone. Deception had jumped back and used a Shadow Clone Technique. His hands were quick and the skill came out on time. They hadn’t even realized that he had left his clone behind, while the real one had passed them.

Deception turned around and saw Lord Grim, who was a bit slower than him, but it looked like he was just strolling idly in a park. Deception didn’t think he used any skills. Could he have just strolled past them like that?

Deception didn’t want to believe it, but it was the truth.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had ran over in this way. The two Blade Masters had thought that their blade lights had connected with Lord Grim. Who knew how but he went right through their blade light and then ran past them.

Shock!

It was because of shock that they reacted slowly. If not, they would have reacted to Deception’s Shadow Clone Technique.

But Lord Grim just went right through the blade light and went past them. They hadn’t even thought that was even possible.

“How did you get past them?” Deception was curious.

“I ran.” Ye Xiu replied.

“How did you run?”

“Like this.” Lord Grim ran a few steps to show Deception.

Others might think Lord Grim was just playing around with him, but Deception immediately saw through it.

It was rhythm!

It was a simple movement, but it had a rhythm to it. By utilizing the different in rhythm, he deceived the enemies. The enemies thought their attacks had hit, but there was actually a minute difference between the attacks. By using the difference in rhythm, he dodged the attack. The theory was this simple.

The theory might be simple, but actually doing it was a completely different beast.

It wasn’t just simply having a good grasp of one’s own rhythm. The opponent’s rhythm had to be completely grasped too. This was decided by the stats, equipment, skill level, and the player’s actions. Seeing through this in an instant wasn’t simple.

Was it by luck?

Deception couldn’t believe there was such an expert.

The danger hadn’t passed yet though. He didn’t have time to think about it more carefully. The two could chat like this, but it would be too easy to get distracted if he thought too deeply. If he got distracted, it would be likely a mistake would occur. Bumping into a tree while walking wasn’t something that only happened in real life.

After breaking through the five players’ blockade, there might not be anyone blocking them in front anymore, but it just meant that there were more pursuers behind them.

“Let this brother give you a few lessons. I’ll teach you what to do in this type of situation.” Ye Xiu said.

“I’ve gone scrap picking countless times. What haven’t I experienced before?” Deception wasn’t modest at all.

“You’ve definitely never experienced our current situation.” Ye Xiu said.

“And you’ve experienced it before?” Deception said.

“Brother, in the tenth server……”

“You don’t feel any shame talking about which server you’re from?” Deception interrupted him in disdain.

“Brother, in those days…….”

“Who doesn’t know how to talk about that past?” Deception continued to look down on him.

Brother, have you ever entered the Heavenly Domain at Level 50!”

Deception couldn’t reply back. He wasn’t able to make a comeback. Entering the Heavenly Domain at Level 50 was something he had never thought about, but the person in front of him had done it. He was running with him at Level 52 and had caused such a ruckus. In reality, when Ye Xiu said the tenth server, Deception believed him. Someone who could create such a storm at Level 52 in the Heavenly Domain would certainly bring disaster wherever he went. Deception was just saying that.

As soon as the guilds saw Lord Grim, they immediately pounced on him, ignoring the great and famous scrap picking king. It had made a deep impression on him. He had always thought he was someone who could immediately make the guilds go from calm to angry, but now it looked like, that was just the surface. The guilds may have been scared of him and guarded against him, but they had never made such a large movement in order to kill him. To make an entire leveling area turn into such a mess, was this guy some sort of f*cking boss who only spawned once a year?

I have to observe him carefully and see where the gap between us is! Deception thought.

Chapter 478 – A Good Lesson

“Let me give you a good lesson.”

Deception was planning on figuring the gap between them himself, but hearing the other side speak, it seemed like he was going to directly tell him where it was. Deception suddenly felt unwilling now. He recognized that Lord Grim might be more skilled than him, but it didn’t mean he was willing to take his advice. Even more so, this guy was acting as if that was the way it should be. There wasn’t the slightest bit of modesty in his words.

If this wasn’t the only direction he could go, Deception would have split up with him a long time ago.

“No matter the circumstance, carefully observe the situation. Gathering valuable information should be the first thing you do.” Ye Xiu said.

“No sh*t.” Deception wasn’t going to take his advice.

“You already know this?”

“Hmph……” Deception felt like this question was too stupid. He was too lazy to reply. How could he not know this? Whenever he went scrap picking, the first thing he would do was understand the situation clearly before moving. He wasn’t like other scrap pickers, who just blindly charged in without any plan.

“No. You don’t know this. You don’t even know which buildings have windows.” Ye Xiu said.

“That…..” Deception stared dumbly. He didn’t think he would go there. There was nothing he could say either. He really hadn’t known about it.

“Isn’t it very useful to know which buildings have windows?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Yes…….”

“But you don’t know.”

“……”

“Information is very important!” Ye Xiu instructed.

“Everything was all very sudden. I didn’t have time to prepare.” Deception made an excuse.

“You just have to open up a map on the internet. If you don’t how to even do this, then it means that you’re not regarding information as important enough.”

“I’m used to playing on full screen……” Deception himself didn’t think this was a good reason.

“Ha ha.” Ye Xiu laughed, but didn’t say anything. Deception’s ninja blade slid out slightly from its sheath, but Deception was able to stop himself.

“Right now, we need to escape from these guys.” Ye Xiu said.

“No really?” Deception had calmed down a lot. This time, these two words were just said as a sarcastic reply to the statement. There wasn’t any energy behind it.

“The first thing we need to do is escape from their line of sight.” Ye Xiu said.

“Obviously.”

“Do you know why we have to do this?” Ye Xiu asked.

“So they can’t see us.” Deception said.

“Are you an elementary school kid? Can’t your answer have a little more depth to it?” Ye Xiu said.

“And your question has so much depth to it.” Deception remarked sarcastically.

“Our goal is to not let them find us. Not letting them see us is simply to create a space which we can use to accomplish this.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha ha, how deep.” Deception sneered.

“Then do you know where we can find such a space in our situation?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Uh?” This question was a bit sudden. Deception had no idea.

“The answer is intersections!” Ye Xiu answered.

“F*ck!” Deception felt like he had been tricked. Once they turned around the corner, their pursuers wouldn’t be able to see them. It was such a simple matter, but he just had to make the question so unnecessarily complicated, saying stuff like space……

“It sounds like you don’t understand what I mean.” Ye Xiu sighed, “What I mean is at the intersection, when our pursuers lose sight of us, they’ll scatter. At a two way intersection, they’ll split into two. If it’s a three way intersection, they’ll split into three. By doing this, we peel away our pursuers layer by layer.”

“Oh?” Deception stared blankly. By finding more intersections and making more turns, it would be easier to shed off pursuers. Deception knew about this concept, but he had never thought of why it made it easier to escape. It wasn’t a difficult concept to understand, but only after understanding it was it possible to deduce many things from just this.

The intersections was just an example of space.The point of space was to make their pursuers lose sight of them in order to force them into having several options.

“Understand this. You have to plan when you’re escaping too. You have to make it your goal to shed off pursuers. Do you have a plan?” Ye Xiu continued.

“I do……”

“Tell me your plan.” Ye Xiu said.

“Head north and jump into the river.” Deception said with difficulty. His plan was just a general direction. It wasn’t the type of detailed plan Ye Xiu was talking about. But he had to prove that he had a plan!

“Your plan isn’t bad.” Ye Xiu replied in a dull tone.

“Okay, from this intersection onwards, follow me closely!” Ye Xiu said as he made a left turn at the intersection ahead.

Deception didn’t say anything. The guy talked about a bunch of theory, but would it even work? If the people behind them were their only pursuers, then Deception wouldn’t need to know this theory. He would just run around in circles a few times and completely escape from them. The problem was that the people behind them were not their only pursuers. There were others elsewhere. After the pursuers behind them told them of their location, more people would gather around to their location. They might shed off a few pursuers, but more would come to fill up the gap endlessly. This was why Deception hadn’t been able to break through the encirclement.

Right now he wouldn’t say anything. He was going to see if this guy’s theory would actually work in practice.

Left turn?

There wasn’t anything special about that. He knew how to make a left turn too.

Deception followed along and made a left turn.

“Go in.”

Right after making a left, Lord Grim immediately went into a building on the side.

This building had windows. They went through the window and out onto another street.

Deception admitted he didn’t know there was a window there, but the other side was relying on an online map to know this. If he had an online map opened up, he could make the same decision too.

After going through the window, they flipped onto a tall wall.

Wilderness Town wasn’t just a town with proper streets everywhere. There were small alleyways too. And with the word town in its name, it was obviously not as elaborate as a big city. In reality, most of this leveling area was in the wilderness. The town was just a small corner of the map. It was because of this that the three guilds were focused on this place. As time went on, more and more backup would arrive and escaping would become even more difficult.

Deception just followed behind Lord Grim and didn’t talk, quietly experiencing their route.

It wasn’t over a wide area, but there were a lot of twists to it. In addition, they weren’t running their fastest the entire time. In some places, Lord Grim would stop and wait.

The other side didn’t say anything, so Deception wouldn’t ask. But he was already able to tell that Lord Grim wasn’t simply running around in circles to hide from their pursuers behind them. He was hiding from every single one of their pursuers. It was as if he knew where their enemies were.

Is that even possible? Deception was amazed.

It wasn’t that Lord Grim never encountered any enemies. However, they had never fallen into a trip like Deception had fell into several times before. During these three minutes, they hadn’t fought with anyone. As soon as the enemy saw them, they would immediately choose a different route, flipping over walls, going through windows, running through alleys. Their seemingly random route had goals to it. There were always options to choose from whenever an unexpected event occurred.

The concept of space wasn’t just to create choices for the enemies. It was also leave choices for themselves.

Deception was beginning to understand.

However, in order to do this, having a good grasp of the terrain was crucial. This was information Deception hadn’t thought was important before.

“What do you think?” Ye Xiu suddenly spoke.

“Meh.” Deception was still very stiff with his words.

“But you’re at least safe now.” Ye Xiu said.

“Is that a joke? We still haven’t escaped our enemy’s encirclement. We’re still in it.” Deception said.

“Oh? You’ve been paying attention to our pathing?” Ye Xiu asked.

“……”

“Have you already noticed that you’re already out of combat?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Ah?” Deception was surprised. He just realized that he was out of combat. He could simply log off and he’d be safe.

“You can log off now.” Ye Xiu said.

“And you?”

“Me? I haven’t thought of leaving! I still need to continue scrap picking!” Ye Xiu said.

“……”

“You’re still not going to log off?” Ye Xiu glanced at Deception, “Are you perhaps interested in scrap picking too?”

“That’s my strength!” This was something Deception was confident in. If he said he was the number two scrap picker, no one would dare call themselves number one.

“You’re still green.” Ye Xiu disapproved.

“……”

“It looks like I need to give you another lesson.” Ye Xiu said.

Deception was about to explode from anger. Someone actually dared to give him a lesson in scrap picking. He thought it was too hilarious.

“That’s not called scrap picking. What you’re doing is called PKing.” Deception corrected Ye Xiu.

“Ha ha, in reality, it’s hard to avoid thinking of PKing to get items as a scrap picker. It just depends on if you have the ability to or not, which is why you can only sit and wait for an opportunity, am I right?” Ye Xiu said.

“Of course you’re not right! To put it simply, scrap picking is a way to obtain lots of equipment quickly. If you go PKing one by one, how could that be more rewarding than scrap picking?” Deception said.

“Not as rewarding as scrap picking? If I go to a leveling area and kill whoever I see. In one day, do you think I’ll get more equipment from PKing or do you think you would get more equipment from scrap picking?” Ye Xiu asked.

“You…… PKing all day, you’re a demon!” Deception said. He realized that with his comparison, scrap picking wasn’t as rewarding as PKing. Scrap picking required waiting for an opportunity to appear. For PKing, you create your own opportunities. It was very easy to create one too. You just had to attack a person…….

“Scrap picking isn’t any better. PKing requires some skill at least.” Ye Xiu said.

“No, that’s not right…….” Deception argued, but he couldn’t say what was wrong.

“What’s wrong? Scrap picking is probably even more immoral than PKing. If nothing else, it’s because scrap picking is more passive. But in reality, from a wishful thinking perspective, your scrap picking is also a type of active playing, no? Your end goal is equipment, so what’s the difference with PKing to get it?” Ye Xiu said, “Rather than being a dirty scrap picker, it’s better to just jump out and kill everyone.”

Chapter 479 – Self Defense Counter-attack, Start!

“No, that’s not right……” Deception felt like Lord Grim’s reasoning was completely skewed, but he couldn’t find any holes at the moment, so he could only mutter weakly.

“Of course it’s not right. Whether or not you’re PKing for items or scrap picking, none of them should be encouraged.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then what was the point in saying all that?” Deception stared.

“I was helping you understand that occasionally scrap picking isn’t too shameful, but scrap picking professionally is just as shameful as PKing for items. Plus, the efficiency between scrap picking and PKing is completely different, so not only is crap picking shameful, it’s second-rate. If you treasure your time and your life, I suggest using the time you use to pick up scraps to PK for items.” Ye Xiu said.

Deception really was about to cough up blood. Where did he get treasure your life from?

“Then why are you scrap picking here?” Deception didn’t let up.

“That’s just something I said.”

“Then what are you going to do?”

“Didn’t you see me defend myself?” Ye Xiu said.

“Self-defense? You can log off right now, so why aren’t you logging off? What self-defense!” Deception remarked.

“Why should I log off? I have to defend myself. If they kill me, I kill them back. I’m a man! There’s no need to explain!” Ye Xiu said.

Deception was just about to log off, but he stopped himself. This f*cker. Isn’t he saying that if I log off, I’m not a man? I’m a man! Most definitely!

“Why aren’t you logging off?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I’m a man! There’s no need to explain!” Deception said.

Ye Xiu laughed, but didn’t say anything more. Lord Grim stuck out his neck from behind a wall to look around and then quickly retracted it.

“There seems to be a lot of people in this team!” Ye Xiu said.

“What team doesn’t have a lot of people…….” Deception glanced and saw ten or so people together, a very normal team.

“Five or less is easier to deal with.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?”

“Because I’ve done more research on this number.” Ye Xiu said.

“Research what?” Deception asked.

“How to kill them.”

“Demon…….” Deception was dumbstruck. Someone who studied how to kill a team of five all day, if he wasn’t a beast, what was he?

“Jump up and see if there’s anyone above.” Ye Xiu directed.

Deception acted quickly. In addition, he didn’t need need Ye Xiu to tell him to be secretive. After jumping up, he stabbed his ninja blade on the wall and used it to quickly take a look above.

“No one.” Deception said.

“That means there are only these ten people. How do we get them to split up……” Ye Xiu muttered to himself.

“Rush out. I go left and you go right. They’ll have to split up to chase us. You’re familiar with this map. Plan out a route. After escaping from them, we’ll meet up and attack back!” Deception wasn’t someone with no suggestions.

“It’s not good.” Ye Xiu denied it.

“Why?”

“What if they don’t split up?” Ye Xiu asked.

“How could they not……..” Deception didn’t completely say the word “not” when he suddenly stopped. He recalled how the others had immediately ignored him after seeing that Lord Grim was there. It was very likely they wouldn’t split up……

“Should we go on the roof first?” Deception suggested.

“It’s not a good option. If we have options, it’s best not to go up on the roof. It’s an open area making it easy for them to see us.” Ye Xiu said, “Let’s go here first.”

Deception turned around. Deception followed. A few steps later, they went into another building.

“No window!” Deception discovered.

“Go to the second floor.” Ye Xiu said. It was a two storied building.

The second floor had a window. Lord Grim went to it and only exposed half his body, while telling Deception to hide.

From this window, he could see the street below. The team of ten people stopped at the intersection for a bit. After looking around, they split into two teams. One team went forward, while the other two headed towards them.

One step, another step. The five player team walked outside of the second floor door and stopped.

“Go in and take a look.” One person in the team said. Two people entered the room to look.

Deception understood what the other side meant by giving them more options. Even an entrance to a room could be used, not just an intersection. It was just that they didn’t seem to have any choices right now. Apart from the window in front of them, they had no way to escape. If they went out through the window, they would land in front of the other three people.

“Now we can only go on the roof right?” Deception said.

“Why run? This is a good opportunity to attack back.” Ye Xiu said.

The footsteps below could be heard. Soon, the two players were walking up the stairs.

“Focus on one.” Ye Xiu didn’t speak. He switched to using messages. While they were running, the two had created a party.

Deception quietly took out his ninja blade. As the footsteps grew nearer and nearer, the heads of the two players could be seen sticking out from the stairway.

“The one on the right!” Ye Xiu typed. Lord Grim had already thrown a grenade over. Deception wasn’t slow either. When he saw the message, he immediately used a “Storm Sword”. This was a sword buff. Only Ninjas could learn this skill.

The spinning blades spun in circles as they flew towards the player on the right. Deception also followed after it.

Smoke and flames exploded. Lord Grim’s grenade had set off. The air from the explosion split the two players apart from each other. One of them was sent up, while the other was sent down.

The player on the right was then hit by the Storm Sword. Deception closed in and stepped on his shoulder. He jumped up and while landing, he swung the rope back to use a Neck Binding Technique, forcing the player onto the second floor.

Everything happened in an instant. When Deception dragged the player onto the second floor, the one on the left hadn’t even finished rolling down the stairs. Seeing one go up and the other go down, Deception started thinking.

Was that intentional? Was it even possible to time a grenade that precisely? The grenade just happened to be between the two players.

A low-leveled skill with many uses.

The air of a great expert!

Deception thought, but his attacks didn’t stop. He turned his head and saw that Lord Grim wasn’t helping him. He was standing at the window, watching the scenery.

“What are you doing!” Deception was angry. It’s a hard to come by opportunity, so why aren’t you taking it? And you call yourself a killing specialist?

Lord Grim immediately turned around and fired twice. Then, he turned back to watch the scenery again. The two shots seemed like a half-hearted response to Deception’s shouts. Deception was furious, but these two shots were very accurate. His movements had been extremely quick, yet the two shots didn’t miss.

“Are you done looking!” Deception attacked quickly. Even though it was only a one on one, that player didn’t have any way of fighting back. The player was pushed to the window, almost getting knocked outside.

“Woah, be careful. Don’t push him out.” Lord Grim used a Knee Strike to send the player back.

“Hurry up and attack!” Deception was worried. The other side didn’t only have one person. The other side had five and the four could come and assist him at any moment!

“Okay!” This time, he finally got the response he wanted. Lord Grim had finally come out. Even though the damage he did as a Level 52 was very limited, it was still faster than not doing anything. With the two working together, the player quickly died.

“Pa!”

An equipment dropped onto the ground. Deception was just about to pick it up, when he saw that Lord Grim was still looking out the window as if he didn’t care about the equipment. Deception suddenly also stopped.

“What are you looking at?” Deception was curious. What was there to look at!

“The stratagems once said: If the enemy’s power is not revealed, then there might be traps. Therefore, one should not take the enemy lightly. One should try to figure out as much as possible about the adversary. To do so, one can fake some attacks to force the enemy to reveal their cards, just like baiting a snake out of its nest. Do you understand?” Ye Xiu said.

I’m going to stab you! Is that okay?”

“Dodge!” Ye Xiu yelled as he jumped out the window as well.

“F*ck!” It was a bit sudden. Deception hadn’t thought of doing this and followed after him.

There was quite a lot to see out the window. There were many people moving about, heading towards this direction.

Lord Grim pointed his gun downwards and fired Anti-Tank Missiles. Three missiles shot out. Deception watched as the bullets as they flew through the air. How accurate! The three Anti-Tank Missiles headed towards that building’s entrance. The team of four were still through the entrance to the building.

Lord Grim used the recoil from this attack to stay in the air longer. The roof across the street was lower than the second floor’s window. By using Aerial Fire, he was able to directly go across the entire street.

Deception’s Ninja couldn’t do this, but after blasting the four players below with Anti-Tank Missiles and gunshots, they were in complete chaos. Deception landed without any problems. It was just that when he looked around, he could see many running in this direction. Deception didn’t dare delay. He climbed up onto the roof. Lord Grim was already ahead of him by a bit.

“Faster.” Hearing Lord Grim urge him to hurry, Deception increased his speed.

Their running was very frantic. Going up and down, many of the places required a certain level of skill to reach. Deception didn’t have time to look at their route and didn’t have any time to ask any questions either. It wasn’t easy keeping up. He couldn’t help but think of the difficult trials from the Heavenly Domain Challenge.

At first, Deception heard a lot of “Kill him!” or “Over here!” But soon afterwards, the voices gradually quieted down. Then, they went out of combat again and escaped once again.

“How unfortunate. We could only kill one!”

It was only until this moment when Deception caught up to Lord Grim did he heard him sigh.

Even though Deception wasn’t running in real life, but he felt his arms and legs weaken after doing this. One reason was because he had been nervous. Another reason was because he had to put in a lot of inputs while running about. He seemed to understand that the instant the two began fighting, the other side immediately called for backup. That guy had been standing at the window side looking below from up above to see where the enemy backup was coming from. After gathering the information necessary, he was able to create a route to break past the pursuers. It was terrifying and dangerous. In any case, if it was him, he would have definitely gotten trapped. Deception didn’t doubt this.

“Our self-defense counterattack, officially begins!” Deception had just thought he would be able to relax for a bit, when he heard the guy make a declaration.

Chapter 480 – One Minute of Retaliation

“Retaliate now? Where to?” Deception was struggling to keep up.

“We have a pretty good chance now. Follow me!” As Ye Xiu spoke, Lord Grim charged out of the dark, narrow alleyway.

“What! He escaped again!!!”

After receiving reports from their subordinates, the three guild leaders were outraged. They all used “he” instead of “they” in their sentences. Clearly, Deception was of no importance to them.

“After wasting so much time, he’s only killed one person. Now he’s disappeared again. He’s not even logging off. What does he want?” Changing Spring complained.

“Does he want to wear us down like this? Shouldn’t he know better? This method might work in regular servers by slowing our leveling speed and affecting our progress in pioneering, but it would never work in the Heavenly Domain.” Arisaema analyzed the situation.

Chen Yehui said nothing. His eyes darted back and forth in front of the computer screen. He had no idea what Ye Qiu’s intentions were at all. Ye Qiu was perfectly capable of just walking away and leaving this entire mess behind. However, he stayed and was now playing hide and seek with them. Was this some sort of entertainment to him? He shouldn’t be so immature… A top tier God, looking for this kind of childish amusement?

“Deception also hasn’t run away yet. They’re back together again. What are they plotting?” Changing Spring asked. Deception had become a person again.

“If they’re not planning on leaving, then we don’t need to spend so much effort on defense. Let everyone join the pursuit.” Arisaema suggested. To prevent the targets from escaping the area, the guild leaders used a large amount of manpower in the east and north of Wilderness Town. Now, since the targets showed no intention of leaving, they didn’t need to waste their time waiting there.

Just after Changing Spring and Arisaema finished talking and were about to give orders, Chen Yehui suddenly received a new update, “They’ve appeared again!”

“Where?!!” Changing Spring and Arisaema yelled out together.

In an alley someplace, three players from Excellent Era were on their way to check another alley, when they suddenly saw a shadow move. In a flash, Lord Grim appeared in front of them.

“AH!” The three cried out in surprise. They didn’t attack immediately and sent out a message instead.

Lord Grim didn’t try to run away. Instead, he attacked.

Sky Strike!

The strike landed on all three of them, who were standing in a row, side by side.

The one on the right didn’t react fast enough and was thrown straight into the air. The other two jumped back hurriedly to dodge the strike, but the Sky Strike’s animation had already ended.

Falling Flower Palm!

The airborne player was immediately blown away by the palm.

Ninja Arts – Hundred Streams!

Countless water streams rushed out the small alleyway like vipers. Before the poor player could land, the water streams all rose and twisted into a water prison that incapacitated the player. The gray shadow of Deception dashed out right away. Three shurikens shot out with a swing of his hand. The two other players tried to dodge, but Lord Grim pulled a prank on them. The battle spear tapped once left and right, forcing the two others to stop. With two swooshes, each player ended with a shuriken in their characters.

Ninja Arts – Flame Cut!

Ninja Arts – Cicada Shell Double Slash!

Ninja Arts – Shadow Dance!

The shurikens temporarily paralyzed their targets. Deception seized this opportunity and dumped three skills on them at once. Every skill was released with extraordinary speed. With the flames of the Flame Cut still ablaze, the Double Slash’s silver flashes already sliced through both enemy players. The casting of Shadow Dance started amid the metallic flashes. With shadows dancing across the screen, all the attacks were concentrated on these two.

The two players were unable to defend themselves whatsoever. The continuous combos even knocked the two into the air.

This was all from Deception alone. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim wasn’t slacking off either. Lord Grim attacked and contributed his portion of damage within the storm whipped up by Deception. He matched Deception’s attack patterns perfectly.

Deception, on the other hand, did not really put the two in his mind. He was more interested in competing with Lord Grim. Upon noticing Lord Grim cooperating with him, he constantly switched up his rhythm. It was as if he had to trip Lord Grim up to feel happy.

Despite this, Lord Grim even found time to send a smiley face, which popped out above his head. He had clearly detected Deception’s efforts to throw him off, but he kept up with ease no matter how chaotic the rhythm was. His attacks stayed steady from start to finish.

The player who was trapped by the Hundred Streams had no way of escaping. All he could do was keep sending out messages. The dancing shadows that filled the screen terrified him. His two buddies were no match for such offensive power. However, among the dizzying silhouettes, Lord Grim’s existence stood out unexpectedly clear. Every move and every skill was pellucid.

The screen full of silhouettes melted back into one as Shadow Dance ended. Instead of running away, Deception didn’t take a single step back. The final move appeared just like the case of Golden Fragrance: Deception manifested himself directly above the two players and crushed the two underneath with a Bird Fall. His attacks were far from over!

Too strong!

The two attacked players could not even begin to express their bitterness in words. As members of one of the big guilds, they’d never suffered so much at the hand of another player. If this had happened in the arena, then it’d undoubtedly be a complete victory for the opponent.

A Neck Bind technique followed the Bird Fall. Deception’s bread and butter combos and swift performance eliminated any chance the two might have had for a come back. From start to finish, the two didn’t even have a chance to show what class they were, because they didn’t have a single chance to attack.

Until now!

Neck Bind Technique could only be use on one person at a time. By using it here, one of the players gained an opportunity to catch his breath. His face was buried in the dirt due the Bird Fall though. He scrambled to get up, but was quickly smashed back into the ground. When Deception threw the other down, he had thrown the other right on top of him.

The two couldn’t even understand what was happening, when a grenade rolled into their field of vision. With a thunderous boom, smoke filled their screens. The two players had no idea where they were flying to. All they knew was that their HP bars were still dropping at incredible speeds. The opponent’s offensive was still continuing.

“We’re done for….”

The two had nothing but despair left in their hearts. They had given up on putting up any type of resistance. Unless there was some kind of outside help, they felt there was nothing they could do anymore!

30 seconds!

During the entire half minute, the two players had been kicked around, unable to put up a fight. In that moment, Hundred Streams’ time was finally up. The player, who was trapped, was finally released. The offensive that unfolded on his two friends was truly terrifying, but he could not bring himself to just abandon his friends.

“Screw this!”

Just as the thought emerged in the Berserker’s head, before he could even raise his broadsword, he heard a sudden bang and he was frozen to the ground.

Spitfire skill: Stun Bullet.

As the name implied, the target would be stunned after being shot. On top of that, to be able to have the word stun in its name, the stun state it caused was nowhere as short as the stun from Dragon Tooth and other related skills. This bullet stunned the target for a full two seconds.

Two seconds of stun was quite a long time. A single Stun Bullet could very well be the turning point in a battle.

A stun could interrupt any attack.

A stun was also the best chance for retaliation.

For any Gunner class, no matter if one was a Spitfire or not, Stun Bullet was a skill that everyone learned. For a short while, some people even thought it was a bug in the game.

As a highly valued skill, it was analyzed thoroughly and received high precaution. If Stun Bullet really was untraceable, then it would really be a bug. Actually, even if it was as easily traced as normal bullets, it would have still been suspected to be a bug.

In reality, Stun Bullet was slower than normal bullets. Additionally, it made quite a unique sound when it left the barrel. The bullet was also bigger than regular ones. Players caught up with the special characteristics of Stun Bullet quickly. With enough precaution, everyone learned to be wary of this skill.

In high skilled battles, like pro matches, Stun Bullet couldn’t even be considered a direct attack move. There had to be a set-up beforehand in order to land this skill. From the early days of PvP to now, Stun Bullet had become a support type skill.

The poor Berserker had clearly been careless. Although they all knew that Lord Grim was unspecialized, none of them were attentive enough to figure out what skills and tricks he might have up his sleeve.

Moreover, Ye Xiu’s strike was very well covered.

He used the surrounding chaos to cover up the strike. The sound of the bullet was drowned out by the surrounding noise and the fire that spit out of the barrel was hidden by the flashy display of skills. He had even calculated the duration of Hundred Streams’ prison.

Even the Berserker who was trapped hadn’t counted. He simply waited for the water prison to dissipate. He never thought he would be attacked while he was still inside the prison. This was because any damage to the water prison, even if it was from the person who released the skill, would shorten the duration of the water prison’s bind effect.

This unexpected and precise shot was calculated to the extreme.

The water prison hadn’t even disappeared yet when the bullet left the barrel.

When the bullet arrived, the water prison had just disappeared. When the Berserker said “Screw it!”, he might have even seen the bullet. However, he would have had no time to react at all.

With an additional two seconds of stun, unable to do anything, he watched helplessly as the real Lord Grim teleported in front of him with the Shadow Clone Technique.

His demise was about to begin…

After receiving the discovery of Lord Grim’s location for about a minute, Chen Yehui received another message: three man team, wiped out.

Changing Spring and Arisaema had no idea about this news. They were still organizing people to raid the place.

Chapter 481 – Another Encounter with Golden Fragrance

The entire battle took about a minute.

When the teams received the news, it took them some time to figure out how to get to the location. By the time they arrived at the place, they couldn’t even find the corpses.

The poor players had already been killed.

This was the news that Changing Spring and Arisaema got. Their people arrived at the location and found no traces whatsoever.

“What’s going on?!” The two shouted out at the exact same time. They were asking Chen Yehui because the information had come from Chen Yehui.

“They already escaped…” Chen Yehui replied.

“What about your men?”

“Dead….” Chen Yehui said.

“Dead?” A hint of schadenfreude could be heard in their voices.

“Cough, sorry about your losses…” Arisaema tried to hide his joy with a slight cough.

He truly is targeting Excellent Era! Arisaema couldn’t have been happier. He had no idea what was happening on Changing Spring’s end, but he planned on releasing the news later. He wanted Excellent Era to suffer, but he did not expect this would cause them to lose track of Lord Grim altogether. It had only been a minute! Ye Xiu was indeed powerful, but how strong could a level 52 character be? Even a Silver class weapon had to follow the level rules. Maybe… That guy’s Silver weapon had a special attribute that lowered the required level?

For example, a level 50 weapon with an attribute that lowered the required level by 5 meant that a level 45 character could use that weapon. Similarly, if the required level was lowered by 10, then a level 50 weapon could be equipped by a level 40 character. This type of equipment was undoubtedly worthless to a max level character, but it was pretty useful for a character who was still in the process of leveling up.

Arisaema guessed. He checked and found Lord Grim hadn’t logged off yet. With the target missing, he could only ask his men to continue searching the area.

“Slow, too slow! Do you have any decent equipment? What kind of trash are you wearing? With this kind of lame attack power, aren’t you ashamed of yourself?” The two ran along the streets. Deception was feeling very good about himself from the previous battle. Initially, he was a bit bitter about Lord Grim, so he tried to mess him up. After having enjoyed the benefit of teamwork, he started to cooperate with Lord Grim. The high efficiency of killing three players within a minute made him extremely proud of himself. In the end, he got scolded solemnly by Ye Xiu during their escape.

“How do you still have the shame to laugh at my equipments?” Deception was surprised by the sudden outburst. Is this guy seriously mocking me with his ridiculous rainbow set of equipment? It was true that he didn’t wear his best set this time, but at least everything he was wearing was from the Heavenly Domain!

“Which level am I? Does the Heavenly Domain have anything that I can use?” Ye Xiu retorted.

“…” Deception didn’t know what to say. Heaven’s Realm was released when the max level in the game was still 55. As a result, the lowest leveling area and lowest equipment level were both level 55.

“I…”

“Quiet!” Ye Xiu abruptly interrupted Deception. Lord Grim, who had been walking in front, came to a sudden halt. Clearly, there were enemies up front.

“I am going to lure them out. Get ready to use the Underground Tunneling Technique. Wait for my signal.” Ye Xiu explained as Lord Grim charged out.

“LORD GRIM!!!”

A female shouted from outside. The voice sounded a bit familiar to Deception.

“Woah!” Lord Grim also cried out in surprise and scurried back.

“Shameless!” Deception looked down on Lord Grim’s acts, but he still used the Underground Tunneling Technique. His character dove into the ground and stayed underground. This skill allowed the character to stay underground for awhile. The only requirement was the use of a ninjato. The sheath on the ninjato could be used as a straw to draw air in for breathing.

While underground because of the Underground Tunneling Technique, the player would only be able to see a small area above his head. The player could adjust his view, but not by alot.

Just after Deception dove under, a rainbow figure ran across his screen. No one other than Lord Grim would wear such a disgusting combination of equipment.

Lord Grim took a sharp turn into the narrow alley and then jumped up onto the roof immediately. The chaotic footsteps told Deception that a huge crowd of people had rushed into the alley after Lord Grim. There was at least half of a patrol of them.

Deception was shocked by the crowd. Then a message popped up in the chat, “The same Launcher as before! Attack her! Then destroy her!”

Deception looked through the small view and spotted the Launcher immediately. The ID above her head: Golden Fragrance.

He still says he has nothing against Launchers?

With such targeting, Deception seriously doubted Lord Grim’s intentions. Right now, attacking anyone was the same, so I’m going to deliberately attack someone else. Deception thought happily and was about to attack when he heard the Launcher yell,“Where is he?! And also that Deception! I’m going to tear him to pieces along with the other one!”

Tear me to pieces? You’re the one who’s going to get torn to pieces! Upon hearing her threats, Deception redirected his attack towards Golden Fragrance right away. Underground Tunneling Technique’s attack didn’t attack a set point, but a place in his visible range, so it could be used as an underground teleportation type skill. Deception set his sights on Golden Fragrance. He shot out from underground and went directly towards her the moment she entered his attack range.

Golden Fragrance was launched into the air by the sudden attack. Deception followed Ye Xiu’s advice for the moment. His character flipped, his head down and feet up, as he delivered a kick straight to Golden Fragrance’s chin with a Broken Flash.

The airborne Golden Fragrance flew even higher than before. While the surrounding players were still reacting to the sudden ambush, a battle spear shot down from the roof top. Its tip embedded itself into Golden Fragrance. With a fluid arc, the Circle Swing smashed the girl onto the rooftop. Lord Grim then swung out his hand, and a grenade leisurely fell into the crowd.

The crowd screamed for cover. The shock wave of the explosion had a blow away effect. Unless one went into a super armor, there was no way for one to deal with the effect.

On the other hand, the shock wave has no effect on Deception because he was on the same team as Lord Grim. He jumped up and stabbed his ninjato into the wall. Due to the low walls, he was on the rooftops within a second. Lord Grim already started to bash Golden Fragrance. Still annoyed by her earlier statements, Deception joined in without any hesitation, turing the situation into a group fight.

“You two are seeking death!” Golden Fragrance shouted.

The two continued attacking without replying.

“Our Excellent Dynasty won’t let you off easily!” Golden Fragrance continued.

“Humph, Excellent Dynasty Era? What’s that?” Deception didn’t even put these big guilds in his mind. He always stole these big guilds’ kills, so he was never scared of them anyways.

“Sister, are you a new to this? Do you even understand what the situation is right now? Do you know who I am?” Ye Xiu was also puzzled. He found this girl’s arrogance to be extremely childish.

“She’s the Golden Princess. She doesn’t care who you are.” Chen Guo cut in. Upon seeing Golden Fragrance, Chen Guo was excited. This time, she jumped right into the mood without any doubts. Her only regret in that moment was that her Chasing Haze couldn’t teleport to their location and join in on the fun.

“I know who you are, but with only yourself, what can you do?” Golden Fragrance was actually looking down on Ye Xiu, but it was Deception who got annoyed.

Only myself? These people don’t even see me in their eyes! Am I not a person???

This time, Deception completely misunderstood the conversation between Golden Fragrance and Ye Xiu. The two of them were talking from a different angle. Golden Fragrance wasn’t ignoring Deception at all. Deception had made a huge mockery out of her earlier by stealing her equipment with Ye Xiu earlier. Those actions had ensured a solid enmity between her and Deception.

“GO DIE!!” Deception roared and attacked even more furiously. This confused Ye Xiu even more. Are we on such a good terms already? She was talking about me, so why are you so angry? Ye Xiu didn’t realize that Deception had misunderstood the conversation.

“You take over?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I got it!” Deception replied without any hesitation.

“Faster.” Ye Xiu said and then took out a Gatling Gun. Bullets rained down in a downpour, washing down all the players who were trying to scale the wall.

Spells, grenades, missiles…

Ye Xiu threw down all of his long-distance skills to sweep the players away. The total damage couldn’t be considered to be fatal in any way. However, their attempts at reaching the rooftop were thoroughly crushed.

This time, Golden Fragrance was in a ten-person team. After she was knocked up, the other nine players tried their best at jumping up to rescue her, but all of their attempts were fruitless. Lord Grim defended the roof ferociously with all kinds of attacks. He wasn’t aiming to deal damage. All he wanted was keep the enemies at bay and make them fall back down.

Lord Grim glanced down from up high. There were other teams rushing over. After their whereabouts had been reported, the enemies had clearly called for reinforcements.

“How much longer?” Ye Xiu asked Deception.

“These garbage equips really suck!” Deception even cursed at himself. The attack power of the set he had for kill stealing was way too low for his liking. It didn’t help him vent his anger at all.

“Tell her to hand over her weapon, then we’ll spare her.” Ye Xiu continued.

“What kind of nonsense is this?” Deception didn’t understand Ye Xiu.

“Take it at face value.” Ye Xiu jumped out sideways while talking. With a Collapsing Mountain, he smashed another player, who was trying to jump up, back down into the alley.

“DIE!!!!” Deception roared. Ye Xiu turned around and found Golden Fragrance flying away with blood spilling from her mouth. He had no idea what skill Deception used to do that.

“F*ck! What a waste of time!!” Ye Xiu immediately abandoned the edge of the roof. Lord Grim jumped after her.

“She’s already dead!” Deception yelled.

“Equipment!” Ye Xiu yelled. With an agile leap, Lord Grim secured another piece of Golden Fragrance’s equipment that flew out from her corpse.

Deception was puzzled. I don’t understand him at all!

The three we killed before dropped equipments too, why didn’t he go after them with the same crazed excitement?

Could it be…… another Orange equip!!!

This time Deception had fun killing Golden Fragrance. He didn’t really care what equipment dropped. The corpse of the girl flying away was nothing more than a corpse in his eyes. He didn’t even bother looking at it. As of now, the equipment dropped was already in Lord Grim’s pocket. Was it another Orange equip? Is he one of those high level scrap pickers who only look for Orange equips to steal?

Chapter 482 – Armor-piercing Cannon

“Hurry up and run!” Ye Xiu shouted as he dashed along the rooftop.

“What about the others?” Deception was still a bit hesitant.

“They’ve all been killed by me.” Ye Xiu said.

“What??!!” Deception turned pale.

“As if that’s possible.” Ye Xiu sighed.

“......” Deception was speechless. He looked around and saw reinforcements pouring in. There was no way he could keep fighting, so he hastily followed after Lord Grim.

Golden Fragrance was dead. She didn’t choose to revive though. Her ghost stayed floating in the air. Seeing the two leave just like that, she wanted revenge.

As a core member of one of the top guilds, Golden Fragrance had experienced many things before, but today’s situation was still a first. They had talked for a bit, but it was while fighting. The two quickly killed her, threw her corpse to the side, and then ran. What were her teammates doing? Why hadn’t she seen any of them from beginning to end? What was going on?

Golden Fragrance didn’t choose to revive because in the Heavenly Domain, Level 70 Clerics had a revive skill. Revived characters would revive with low health and mana, but the character wouldn’t be in a critically ill state. By reviving at the same spot, she wouldn’t have to waste time running back here. More importantly, she wouldn’t lose ⅓ of her experience. However, the only thing she could prevent was losing experience. The money and equipment that had been lost couldn’t be returned. This was because the money and equipment were still there. It was just that they were on the ground.

Golden Fragrance gritted her teeth. An option on-screen appeared, asking whether or not she would like to be revived.

After accepting it, the color returned to her world of gray. Golden Fragrance stood up. On the ground nearby was a small money bag that had dropped when she died. The amount of money was a percentage of her total wealth. Golden Fragrance picked up the coins and saw her nine teammates standing in a circle, staring at her and not saying a word. As for the two who had run off, none of them had gone to chase after them. They were all waiting for Golden Fragrance’s orders.

“What are you staring at?! Chase them down!” Golden Fragrance shouted.

The team immediately rushed out. Golden Fragrance followed after, while checking her inventory in grief. She had been so sad that she had even forgotten to do this. Seeing the money on the ground around her, Golden Fragrance felt like it was a good sign. She even thought she hadn’t dropped any equipment, but when she checked her inventory to look, her weapon slot was empty. Her world turned dark.

“MY WEAPON!!” Golden Fragrance cried.

The nine teammates jumped up in fright. They turned around to look at her.

“Where’s my weapon? Did it drop? How come I didn’t see it!!!” Lord Grim had been too quick. He had picked it up so quickly that Golden Fragrance hadn’t even seen it drop.

The nine others were silent. All of them knew how precious Golden Fragrance’s weapon was.

Orange weapon, Armor-piercing Cannon. Level 70, 715 Attack Power, +55 Strength. It also had an additional effect. When attacking, there was a 5% chance to ignore armor for six seconds.

This ignore armor effect was targeted. The armor would only break at a certain spot. For example, if your attack triggered the ignore armor effect on the body equipment. The body equipment would be ignored. The stats from the ignored equipment would be wiped clean as if it didn’t exist. The durability would also decrease by 300% the normal rate during these six seconds.

In Glory, when an equipment’s durability reached zero, it couldn't be fixed, so if an equipment broke due to loss of durability, it would always be painful for the player. If they weren’t careful, the equipment would be destroyed once the durability hit zero. There was no equipment in Glory that could directly reduce durability. Usually, the effects would make the durability drop 10% or 20% faster. This Armor-piercing Cannon was one of those type of equipments. Even though it only had a percentage chance to proc, a 300% increase effect was far greater than normal weapons.

However, rapidly decreasing durability might be annoying for the enemy, but in a real battle, the ignore armor effect was much more useful. Erasing the stats provided by a piece of equipment would greatly weaken the target’s defense.

In short, the Armor-piercing Cannon not only had Orange level stats, its effects were useful whether it was in PvE or PvP. It was an extremely valuable weapon. Just hearing that it had dropped made the others feel hurt.

“Hurry up and chase them! Get it back for me!!!” Golden Fragrance shouted in anger. The nine others immediately began chasing. Golden Fragrance had already entered a berserk state. In the guild chat, she yelled out, calling for friends. It was originally a guild related battle, but now, it had become a personal battle.

Chen Yehui saw this, but he didn’t block it. In fact, he was actually delighted.

This was one very important reason why Golden Fragrance was able to become a core member in the guild.

Club guilds may operate like a business, but the absolute majority of the guild members didn’t have a professional, business-like attitude. They had gathered under the guild because of their love for the team and to support their favorite athletes.

Doing work for the guild was the same as supporting the team, which was why many players were happy to do it. Clubs relied on this in order to gather a large number of troops. While Clubs may have a strict system of organization, to the majority of guild members, the guild leader couldn’t just order them however he wanted. After all, the players were there to play the game. Supporting the team was secondary. In their eyes, the guild leader wasn’t that important. As a result, the tasks given by guilds were mostly voluntary. The guilds didn’t dare force orders onto the players that weren’t willing to do them.

As for Golden Fragrance, although some people might not like her, the majority liked to circle around her. This type of person could rely on her personal connections to bring out a lot of players. Club guilds needed these type of people. The people Golden Fragrance called for may be her private friends, but Chen Yehui didn’t mind.

This was because these private people would listen to her and Golden Fragrance listened to Chen Yehui. Once a player became a core member, he or she would no longer be a regular player. The player would have to have a professional attitude. The Clubs didn’t let them do whatever they wanted all day. Core members could be managed and ordered around more easily.

“What’s wrong Golden Fragrance?” Not only did Chen Yehui not stop her, he even tried to spur her on.

“My Armor-piercing Cannon dropped!” Golden Fragrance was furious.

“Ah?” This news made even Chen Yehui’s heart hurt. Even for top guilds, this type of Orange equipment wasn’t easy to get.

“They’re still here! Hurry up and get it back!” Chen Yehui used the opportunity to urge Golden Fragrance on. He wasn’t just saying it as an act. He truly wanted Golden Fragrance to get back the weapon. Core members were also the main force for dungeons and bosses. The Armor-piercing Cannon was very useful. Golden Fragrance wasn’t the only player in Excellent Dynasty who had one, but one fewer, meant one less powerful player.

“I know!” Golden Fragrance cried and sent an angry face. When others saw her crying in the guild chat, a whole bunch of players asked her what was wrong.

After Golden Fragrance got promoted to a core member, she automatically became big sis Golden Fragrance.

As soon as they heard her equipment had been stolen, quite a few of her supporters rallied up, telling her they would get revenge. Chen Yehui didn’t say anything. These people should be sent out by Golden Fragrance, not him.

“They escaped again? What’s going on!” Arisaema received the news. Lord Grim and Deception had appeared again, but had escaped.

‘I heard there were ten people in that team over there, but they still couldn’t stop them?” Arisaema asked Chen Yehui. He was starting to doubt whether or not Chen Yehui had let them go on purpose in order to avoid any further casualties. This wasn’t like the past, where there were only three people per team. No one questioned Lord Grim’s skill, but as a level 52 character, his DPS wouldn’t be high. Ten players should at least be able to stall for a good amount of time right? However, they failed once again and could only continue chasing.

No one had any confidence in chasing them down because Lord Grim hadn’t escaped without a trace just once.

“What do you mean?” Chen Yehui had lost an Orange weapon! How could he be pleased?!

“If even ten people couldn’t stop them, there’s no way we can kill them. Most teams are split into either three or five player teams. They have no chance, no?” Arisaema said.

“It’s not like anyone of us ever thought a single team could kill them, right? It’s simply to widen our area of control. Once we find our target, we will surround them in one go.” Chen Yehui said.

“Then we have to hurry and surround them!” Arisaema said.

“Yes, surround them. Who didn’t do it?” Chen Yehui said.

Arisaema was surprised. Could he have figured out that their Herb Garden’s movements were a bit slow?

The two were still fighting a word battle, when new information came. They had disappeared once again.

“F*ck!” Changing Spring shouted.

“What do you think? Armor-piercing Cannon. Are you satisfied?” Ye Xiu asked Chen Guo.

“Not bad, not bad.” Chen Guo nodded her head. The equipment was very good. It used to be Golden Fragrance’s, after all. The expression on her face was probably very good too. Who knew how long it would have taken her to get this weapon if she had stayed in Excellent Dynasty.

“You also want a hairband right, but I don’t think I saw Golden Fragrance with a hairband!” Ye Xiu said.

“Mm, I don’t want hers.” Chen Guo said with disgust.

Equipment on the body affected the character’s appearance more than a weapon, so she cared a lot about it. Chen Guo had chosen to wear a hairband to match her in-game appearance with her real life appearance. As for Golden Fragrance, she used a flower hair clip. Chen Guo didn’t like it at all, no matter how good the stats on it were.

“Who has a good hairband?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Ah, it’s fine. This weapon is more than good enough.” Chen Guo said. This was the truth. An Orange weapon was definitely much rarer than a Purple weapon. Finding one that could be used was extremely hard to come by. Many players were happy just to have an Orange weapon, let alone one that suited them.

“You should go level up.” Chen Guo reminded Ye Xiu.

“It’s no problem. It’s just a day.” Ye Xiu looked like he was a bit hesitant though. On the other hand, Deception was more enthusiastic: “Where do we go next??”

Chapter 483 – Is There Space Here?

“Now what??” The guild leaders had a terrible headache.

They had originally thought that this was a once in a lifetime opportunity, but after stationing themselves in Wilderness Town for some time, not only had they failed to achieve their goal, their opponents had killed off several of their men.

A few deaths wasn’t a big loss, but more importantly, they couldn’t see any ray of hope.

The two ran and ran. They would suddenly appear and then disappear. The three guilds had so many people pursuing them, but they weren’t able to do anything except die. What were they supposed to do?

“Target found!”

Another one of these messages came.

“Kill! Kill them for me!! Hurry up and kill them!!!” The three guild leaders ordered.

A minute later, another message arrived: we got wiped.

It was another assembly of three players. These three clearly weren’t opponents for those two. They couldn’t even last a minute.

What did it mean to be able to kill three players in one minute? It meant that it wasn’t a battle. It was a one-sided massacre. Lord Grim was only Level 52, so his DPS was limited. Deception was max leveled, but his equipment was lacking. On the other hand, everyone in the three guilds had a full set of equipment with good stats, yet they couldn’t even last a minute before dying. If they had been sandbags with the same stats, the sandbags would have probably been defeated in the same amount of time.

Their enemies had used the same trick twice. The Ninja would imprison one with Hundred Streams and then focus on killing the other two. Once those two died, they would come back and kill the one trapped in the water prison.

It was a very simple tactic which relied on brute force. There wasn’t anything special about it.

“The enemies are stronger. Let’s have every team be made of at least five people. The backup from outside the encirclement have basically all arrived. We should hurry up and have them join.”

The three guild leaders hastily made adjustments to their plan.

After the two wiped out the three-man team, they quickly vanished. They disappeared so thoroughly, that they didn’t leave any traces behind. The guilds couldn’t even figure out their general location. Their only choice was to scour the streets. Time passed. Apart from knowing their targets were still online, they had no other information on them. Some people were even beginning to doubt the two were still in Wilderness Town.

Just when the three guild leaders were wondering if this was true, a message arrived. The two had appeared again.

“Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry!” The three guild leaders immediately ordered. Now, every team was made up of at least five players. If it was five against two, they should be able to stall for some time, right?

Sure enough, five was greater than three. They were at least able to stall until backup arrived. However, the two didn’t linger around with the five players. The two also ran away earlier. Everyone coughed blood as they chased with a terrible premonition in their hearts. Their premonition turned real and the two disappeared again without a trace.

The team of five didn’t wipe out, but two of them had still died. The Cleric was hurried over to revive and heal them, but their money and equipment had already been procured cleanly.

“I thought you only wanted Orange equips?”

In the previous two fights, Lord Grim had picked up all the equipment that dropped. This made Deception confused again. He thought Lord Grim was someone who only cared about Orange equipment.

“Yeah, I don’t really want to pick them up, but if I don’t, then they’ll take it back. It’d be better if I had it rather than them.” Ye Xiu said.

“How unfortunate. We can’t kill them all.” Deception and Ye Xiu had completely swapped places. One of them wanted to kill other players, while the other one wanted to pick up scraps.

“Our damage isn’t good enough.” Ye Xiu said.

“We don’t have enough time.” There was nothing Deception could do either. As soon as they engaged with the enemies, the enemies would immediately send out a report to the others. Soon afterwards, a huge crowd of players would come over to attempt to catch them. They could only stop fighting and escape.

Many of the players in the three guilds were exhausted, although there was still one group that was still full of fighting spirit.

“Sis’ Golden Fragrance, where are they!” Someone in the team cried.

This group wasn’t fighting under the guild’s banner, but rather under Golden Fragrance’s name. Most of them were from Excellent Dynasty, but there were also a few non-Excellent Dynasty players. All of them were Golden Fragrance’s personal friends.

“Lord Grim. There are even rumors going around saying he’s Ye Qiu!” One person said.

“It doesn’t matter who he is! No one can bully Golden Fragrance. We have so many people here. We’re not afraid of anyone!”

‘Thank you everyone for coming here. Besides Lord Grim, there’s also that guy called Deception. I think everyone has heard of him before?” Golden Fragrance said.

“Deception? I know him! He’s that scrap picker!”

Deception was still quite infamous.

“Yes, those two. My Armor-piercing Cannon was stolen by them. They haven’t left yet. The weapon is still with them. Please help me get it back.” Golden Fragrance asked.

“Don’t worry! Even if we have to go to hell and back, we’ll help you get your equipment back!”

All sorts of people were trying to win her favor.

“Good. Let’s move out. I just received a message. Our targets have appeared, but they’ve escaped. We’ll head over there.” Golden Fragrance said.

As a result, a team of twenty players headed towards the last reported location Ye Xiu and Deception had been seen at. This team had gathered solely for Golden Fragrance. Even Chen Yehui wouldn’t be able to order them around. He saw this, but didn’t say anything about it.

The players participating in this activity headed towards the location. As they moved towards it, they saw quite a few teams running around. The more they saw this, the more wary they became.

“How many people from the three guilds have come?” Someone asked.

“So far I’ve seen enough people to make up several groups.” One of them was astonished.

Each group could hold 100 players each. It was considered a very large unit of measurement in the game. No matter how difficult a boss was, there was no such boss that a group couldn’t take down. Yet against these two players, the three guilds had dispatched enough troops for several groups.

“There’s nothing we can do. These two guys are extremely cunning. They’re constantly hiding and running. If it was a direct confrontation, we wouldn’t need so many people.” Golden Fragrance explained.

“Then how are we supposed to find them?” The two asked.

“Right now, we’re shrinking the amount of space they have to move around in. Once we’ve shrunken it down to a small enough space, they’ll have to come out.” Golden Fragrance said.

“If the others kill him, then won’t our trip have been wasted?” Another person asked.

“Right, that’s why we have to move faster. There are Herb Garden and Blue Brook Guild players here too. If they kill him and my Armor-piercing Cannon drops, I doubt they’ll give it back.” Golden Fragrance said.

Ye Xiu and Deception were running around. They saw a few individual teams while moving about, but they didn’t attack them. Deception was starting to get impatient.

“Why aren’t we killing them?” After passing by another team, Deception finally asked.

“Look over there.” Ye Xiu pointed in a certain direction.

Deception turned his head to look and saw another team come from around the corner of a street.

“The enemies are gathering together. The amount of space we have to move around in is being compressed. It isn’t a good time to attack. The past few times we had a certain amount of time to finish them off, but this type of opportunity isn’t going to be easy to find anymore. They’re tightening the space between them.” Ye Xiu said.

“What do we do?” Deception asked.

“We’re going to have to move around in a large area. We have to go this way. They don’t have complete control over this area yet.” Ye Xiu led Deception down a different route.

“How do you know?” Deception didn’t understand.

“Remember the enemy teams and observe their positions. Translate it onto the map and predict their movements.” Ye Xiu said.

“......” Deception was sweating just from hearing his explanation.

“Golden Fragrance.” At this moment, Golden Fragrance received Chen Yehui’s message.

“Hm?”

“We’ve shrunken their area of movement on this side. I purposefully left a space open. They’re probably going to be heading in that direction. You have enough troops. Finish them! If Herb Garden and Blue Brook Guild surround them, they’ll probably take their items away.” Chen Yehui said.

“Thank you guild leader!” Golden Fragrance was overjoyed when she heard this.

“Besides your Armor-piercing Cannon, take note of Lord Grim’s weapon. If it drops, you have to get it no matter the cost.” Chen Yehui added.

“Okay, I understand.” Golden Fragrance replied.

“Someone will provide you with accurate information.”

“Okay.”

Golden Fragrance was delighted. She turned around and told the good news to everyone. Everyone cracked their knuckles. Their only regret was that just killing these two wouldn’t be enough.

After a short moment, Golden Fragrance received a message. It was from a player in Excellent Dynasty, reporting their location.

“Good!” Golden Fragrance checked the map and after studying it, she led everyone to lay in wait for an ambush.

Ye Xiu and Deception weren’t having an easy time running either. From time to time, they had to hide from small teams. It made Deception feel like the enemies really were gathering in one area, but as they moved, fewer and fewer teams appeared, letting Deception know that they were gradually breaking through the enemy’s encirclement. Afterwards, for a long while, the two didn’t even try hiding because no one was there.

“Did we break through the encirclement?” Deception was surprised. Thinking of before, they hadn’t even started shrinking the encirclement yet and he had already had a difficult time running away. Now that he was with Lord Grim, they ran and stopped, neither slowly, nor quickly, and were able to escape from the encirclement with ease.

“Like I said, they’ve gotten a bit careless with their formation on this side.” Ye Xiu smiled.

“Really?”

Deception didn’t have enough time to say anything more, when someone interrupted him. In an instant, many people jumped down from the roofs and buildings. It wasn’t just five or ten people. Deception looked around. There were too many to count.

When Deception saw this, he smirked: “They’ve gotten a bit careless with their formation on this side?”

“Uh, you see, this formation doesn’t count as a part of the previous formation.” Ye Xiu said.

“Now what?” Deception asked.

“Kill them all.” Ye Xiu said.

“What?” Deception thought he heard wrong.

“Look how arrogant and confident they are. This time, they probably won’t ask for backup!” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s not necessarily true.” Deception said.

“More importantly, look who is over there.” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s that girl.”

“Yeah, she lost her weapon, so she wants to personally take it back. If others got it, who would return it to her?” Ye Xiu said.

“So you’re saying, they’re going to just stand there and let themselves be killed?”

“Don’t be afraid. I have a plan.” Ye Xiu said.

“How could I be afraid!” Deception charged directly towards Golden Fragrance.

Chapter 484 – Formation

Golden Fragrance had suffered under Deception’s hands twice already. There was no way she wouldn’t be prepared this time. Launchers were a pure long-ranged class. They shouldn’t even be letting their opponents get near. The previous two incidences had been because she was careless. Se wouldn’t make the same mistake again. When Golden Fragrance saw Deception moving towards her, she used Aerial Fire in order to fly backwards.The two players next to her had charged forward ferociously to meet him in battle. One was a Battle Mage, while the other was a Berserker. A spear and a greatsword shot towards Deception.

Deception leapt up and landed with a Bird Fall. His movements were so quick that the other two weren’t able to react in time and were stepped on.

Deception didn’t follow up though. With around twenty enemies around them, the melee classes had already started surrounding them and the long-ranged classes had begun firing at them. There was no time to stay in one spot for too long. After stepping on their shoulders, he flipped into the air towards the back. Even so, he was still hit by several bullets in the air. There were just too many enemies. The enemies were ready for ambushes too and their attacks were focused.

It had only been a single exchange, but Deception was already in a fluster. Deception really didn’t have any confidence in this sort of situation. He only had one more trick in his arsenal.

As soon as he landed, he quickly formed a hand seal. Several shadows flew out from him and began wildly attacking.

In this sort of situation, the skill was used defensively. The shadows scattered around. The enemies couldn’t accurately grasp which ones were which, but at the same time, they didn’t need to care about Deception’s attacks. They threw out all sorts of skills. If the attack hit, then it hit. If it didn’t, then it didn’t. It didn’t really matter.

As for Ye Xiu, there were also players attacking him. He wasn’t as panicked as Deception was though. Using another player as a weapon, he easily swatted away the two incoming enemies. Following afterwards, he followed up with a Gatling Gun. He swept his gun across the field, interrupting several skills from long-ranged classes in the distance.

The mages had their magic staffs pointed at him, but no magic came out. Their pose made them look incredibly stupid.

“He really is powerful!”

Such control over the battlefield was more than enough to astonish these Heavenly Domain veterans.

The rumor that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu had spread far and wide. Though for them to be willing to stand with Golden Fragrance, none of them were loyal fans of Ye Qiu. They were still interested in the God’s skill though. Being able to fight with a God in the game was certainly brag-worthy.

As a result, after seeing Ye Xiu’s beautiful movements, the enemies only grew more excited and attacked more ferociously.

Ye Xiu hastily had Lord Grim roll backwards a few times, dodging the incoming attacks. Some looked as if they were going to hit, but Deception’s shadows suddenly appeared to block them.

A coincidence?

Did he dodge in this way on purpose?

Did Deception really intentionally block it for him?

No one had time to carefully ponder over it. In any case, it had all happened in an instant. Two of Deception’s shadows had died. The fewer the shadows, the clearer the field became. The enemies’ attacks had a focus to them.

Deception glanced around while switching between his shadows. He saw Lord Grim rolling around, dodging the barrage of attacks. This didn’t look like someone who was going to “kill them all”.

“Who has my Armor-piercing Cannon?” Golden Fragrance was excited. She stood out, acting as if she had control over the entire battle.

“Are you going to let us go if we hand over the cannon?” Ye Xiu joked.

“Hmph, if you give it to me, I’ll let one of you go.” Golden Fragrance said.

“So it’s like that. Then it looks like only I can go. He can’t give you what you’re looking for, ha ha ha.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Demon!!!” Deception’s Shadow Dance had ended. He heard what Ye Xiu said and glared at him in disdain.

Golden Fragrance didn’t know how to reply.

At this moment, shouldn’t he be standing out like a hero and sacrificing himself for his friend? If this happened, she would get her Armor-piercing Cannon back. Deception would get to leave, while Lord Grim would die. She would be able to keep her promise, as well as complete her objective. Her image would be safe and sound too.

But this guy was too shameless. He was actually prepared to sacrifice his friend. Lord Grim would be let go, but she would have her weapon back.

Golden Fragrance hesitated for a moment. After all, even if she killed the target, whether or not her Armor-piercing Cannon dropped or not depended on luck. After he revived, he could transfer the Cannon away. This meant she only had one chance. However, there was a very low chance that the Armor-piercing Cannon would actually drop. Right now, she had a 100% chance to get it back. Should she sacrifice a bit of her status in the guild to let Lord Grim go?

If she went back on her word and killed them both after taking her weapon back…… with so many of her friends watching, Golden Fragrance felt too ashamed to do such a thing.

In the end, she didn’t need to feel ashamed. Her friends supported her.

“Golden Fragrance, this is a really good opportunity. First, take your weapon back and then kill him.” Someone suggested.

“That’s no good!” Golden Fragrance was elated. If someone was willing to offer her bad advice, then she wouldn’t let the opportunity go.

“Don’t worry. We’ll kill him, but let Deception go. We can just say that we never let them choose who could go. Isn’t that perfect?” Another person added.

“Oh, that works!” Golden Fragrance agreed.

Thus, she immediately shouted: “Hand me the cannon!”

“You’ll let me go?” Ye Xiu needed confirmation.

She lost the word battle. Golden Fragrance was stuck. However, her other friends had an idea: “Return the cannon to Golden Fragrance and we’ll let you go.”

“Who do I mean when I say “you”? I’m talking about Deception, ha ha ha ha!” This person explained.

How low……. Even she couldn’t help but look down on him.

“So the deal is set?” Ye Xiu said.

“Yes!”

“You won’t go back on your word?” Ye Xiu said.

“I won’t.”

“Hm, let me think about it. I feel like it’s a bit embarrassing for me to accept it.” Ye Xiu said.

“You!” Golden Fragrance obviously understood that she had been played. During this time, their attacks had stopped and the two had time to rest.

“I’m not letting a single one of you leave alive!!!” Golden Fragrance shouted.

“Agreed!” Ye Xiu replied.

Right when Ye Xiu said this, raging flames suddenly roared up from the ground. However, the flames didn’t target Deception or Lord Grim, but rather the players.

All of them stared blankly in surprise. Fire Storm was a Level 60 Elementalist skill. An unspecialized couldn’t learn it, so who had used it?

They still hadn’t figured it out yet! Boom! The sounds of raging flames and violent winds burned their bodies.

“WHO IS IT!!!!” Everyone was astonished. Someone was clearly attacking them.

A shadow suddenly flickered on the ground. They looked up and saw a Berserker lifting a greatsword above his head. The Berserker leapt down from a nearby rooftop and smashed the ground with an Earthsplitting Slash.

There were many skills in Glory which began from high above to down below. The damage and effects depended on the height difference. Earthsplitting Slash was one such skill. By jumping down from the rooftop, the player could take advantage of the extra height between the roof and ground.. This was common knowledge.

How big would the area of effect for the Earthsplitting Slash be?

The noobs in the normal servers might not know, but the Heavenly Domain veterans had an idea. No one dared to face it head on. Everyone immediately spread out.

Another two shadows appeared, but neither of them arrived on stage in as domination of a fashion as the Berserker. Of the two shadows, one of them held a battle spear, while the other had nothing in his hands. One was a Battle Mage, while the other was a Grappler. These two figures took the rear. An Elementalist was standing on another rooftop. His staff was pointed towards where the Fire Storm was blazing. Clearly, he was the one who had executed the sneak attack.

“Who are these people?” Everyone cried out in astonishment. Rumble! The Earthsplitting Slash crashed into the ground and the ground shook. From where the sword hit, a shockwave spread out. A faint sword energy could be seen resonating within the shockwave. This was an effect of the Earthsplitting Slash. If a target was hit, there was a chance the target would turn Dizzy.

Fortunately, they had prepared themselves and spread out. No one was hit by the Earthsplitting Slash, but immediately afterwards, a red glow emanated from his body and he entered a Berserk state.Two scarlet eyes stared in their direction. He crouched down and his greatsword was placed behind him. A bright light shone from the tip of the sword and a bloody mist formed above the ground.

“Crimson Storm!!!”

They immediately recognized this skill. It was the Berserker Level 70 skill, Crimson Storm!

“Interrupt him!!” Someone shouted.

Crimson Storm was extremely powerful, but it had a very slow startup animation. Without any setup, it was unlikely to come out.

However, Crimson Storm wasn’t a skill that was cast like Elementalist skills. As a result, the skill couldn’t be interrupted with a simple attack. There were two ways to interrupt it. One was to use a Grab skill. This could interrupt any skill. The other way is to do enough damage, which was set by the system, to forcefully stop the attack.

At this moment, this Berserker had used an Earthsplitting Slash in order to scatter the enemies. He had done a bit of setting up. It was a bit too late to grab him, but long-ranged classes could still attack.

Long cast time skills couldn’t be used, but they could still send out a few quick attacks.

Bullets and magic flew towards the Berserker. However, Lord Grim suddenly rolled forward and with a “hua!”, his Thousand Chance Umbrella opened up, blocking the incoming attacks.

This was enough. Crimson Storm activated and the Berserker’s greatsword was transformed into a humongous, blood-colored sword. The sword descended towards the ground. The instant the sword hit the ground, it exploded and a bloody mist spread out all around.

“F*ck!” They weren’t able to interrupt his skill and hastily tried to escape, but several of them weren’t able to escape in time. Fortunately, no one had been directly cut by the blood sword. It was undoubtedly a huge portion of the skill’s damage.

The Battle Mage and Grappler had finally arrived. The Battle Mage lifted up his spear and a huge dragon roared towards the enemies. The Grappler closed in on a player, lifted him up, and swept around in a circle.

Grappler skill: Spinning Throw.

Chapter 485 – Attack Like Fire

Each of them displayed skills with incredible effects. In an instant, a Fire Storm turned the streets into a sea of fire. A Crimson Storm covered the ground with pools of blood. A Dragon paved a path through the blood. A Spinning Throw created a single spot of blank space. None of Golden Fragrance’s people had died, but they were instantly forced to be on the defensive against these attacks.

“Don’t let them run!!!”

Golden Fragrance was a Launcher, so she stood farther away from the carnage. None of the attacks had reached her, but when she saw the encirclement split apart, she hastily let out a shout.

“Relax, none of us will run!” Ye Xiu replied. After Lord Grim covered for the Berserker, he rushed through the pools of blood created by the Crimson Storm. It was a bit of a dirty move, but it was certainly effective.

The Cleric on the rooftop cast a heal and a white light surrounded Lord Grim’s body.

A Shield could only reduce damage. If it were possible to avoid the attack, then it would be best to avoid it instead of blocking it. Lord Grim was only Level 52. By protecting the Berserker from all the incoming attacks, his health had dropped drastically.

Deception threw out a shuriken and his character followed behind Lord Grim. He wasn’t surprised by this. Before these people had joined the battle, they were already in the party. He had known that there were helpers coming. He and Lord Grim were simply stalling for them to arrive!

“Who are these guys!” The players on Golden Fragrance’s side were shouting furiously, but they didn’t recognize any of the names of these players. None of them had a guild tag either. Where had they come from?

These four players broke into the crowd of confused enemies. They followed along the path that Lord Grim took and attacked the players forced away by the Crimson Storm.

When these character focused on one target, their strength was incredibly ferocious. In the blink of an eye, one of the players was beaten up and killed.

“Ice Wall, left side!” As soon as Ye Xiu shouted this, the Cleric immediately cast an Ice Wall. Ping! Ping! Ping! Walls of ice formed, blocking the path of the incoming enemies. These enemies didn’t go around them. Instead, they attacked the Ice Walls and broke through them, but in just this brief moment, another one of their allies had fallen.

“What are you doing, Cleric?!”

Two allies had died instantly without any chance for them to be rescued. Golden Fragrance furiously pointed her finger at the Cleric on her team.

“Fast…… too fast…….” The Cleric could only tell the truth. Everything had happened too quickly. Lord Grim’s team had six people. They would surround one person and then attack like fire. Lord Grim’s team was blocking the view and the visual effects also covered the name. The Cleric couldn’t even tell who they were attacking!

He could jump up and see who was being attacked or look at the team list in order to see who was being attacked. However, these methods were way too slow!

By the time he jumped up to see the name and landed to cast the heal, or if by the time he figured out whose health bar was dropping rapidly, the health bar would be empty and he wouldn’t be able to heal them anyway.

This was how two of them had died already. It wasn’t an instant kill, but it was close. For these Clerics, their skill level wasn’t good enough to keep up with the pace.

The Ice Walls shattered and the group of players rushed forward. Then, they saw Lord Grim flick his sleeves and a Shadow Cloak flung out.

Shadow Cloak was a Grab skill. It didn’t do much damage, but it had a fairly wide area of effect. When the Shadow Cloak came out, the group of players wanted to dodge, but because they were clumped together, blocking each other’s paths, many of them weren’t able to avoid it.

The several that had been wrapped up in the Shadow Cloak were squeezed together into a tight space.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

Thunder Apocalypse!

Whirlwind Strike!

Flame Cut!

Earthquake!

Lord Grim and the other five in his team attacked at practically the same time. Their timing was slightly off, but the Shadow Cloak had bound several players together, making them unable to escape.

Shadow Cloak didn’t do much damage. It was mostly used to interrupt an opponent’s attack, which was why Grab skills were so useful. In addition, it was good at gathering monsters.

Of course, in this case, the Shadow Cloak wasn’t gathering monsters, but players instead.

The following five attacks might not have been their class’s strongest skills, but they were most definitely the most suitable at this moment.

Magic rippled. Thunder roared. A tornado whirled. Fire blazed. An earthquake shook the ground. The caught players were blasted into the air. Not a single one of them came back down.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had followed up with a Collapsing Mountain after using the Shadow Cloak. Lord Grim’s attack power was weaker than everyone else’s, but it was still something. If he didn’t seize these type of openings, he didn’t deserve to be called a God.

As soon as this wave finished, everyone immediately unleashed another wave of attacks. Everything happened extremely quickly and, in an instant, five players had already died.

This sort of strategy was often employed against monsters, especially low-leveled ones. The strategy was to gather the monsters and then kill them all in one go. However, now it was being used in a PvP scenario. In just two waves of attacks, five players had been wiped out.

Golden Fragrance was still trying to get the troops back in order! Even though the sudden entrance had caused their formation to go into disarray, when she saw that it was just four people, Golden Fragrance didn’t think too much of it. Her side still had the advantage in numbers, so what if another five came? Her side would still have three times the number of players that they had.

Who would have thought that these five would be able to kill off seven of her allies in just 30 seconds?

Golden Fragrance wasn’t even able to finish repositioning her troops. She was still figuring out where everyone was supposed to go. By the time she checked the team list and prepared to arrange them appropriately, seven names had already turned gray.

Golden Fragrance was shocked!

After the shock came helplessness. Her opponent’s offense was as swift as the wind and as fierce as fire. And her? Her mind was completely blank. She had never seen such a ferocious assault before. Her knowledge wasn’t able to keep up. Her experience wasn’t able to keep up. She had no idea what to do in this situation.

In addition, the people on her side were sloppy. Their strategy was simply to take advantage of their numbers to bully the opponents. Tactics? Coordination? They hadn’t thought this far. Even though a few of them inside were friends or had played with each other often, it was useless. Against the opponent’s ferocious assault, everyone was like Golden Fragrance. They didn’t know what to do. They couldn’t figure out any way to break their opponent’s strategy, apart from a few ----- the few being attacked. When the blade sliced down from above them, they would instinctively defend.

But what could this type of defense do?

The players who were able to dodge the Shadow Cloak could only watch as their captured comrades fell and then their opponents immediately switched over to them.

In the blink of an eye, another two died. So far, apart from hitting Lord Grim’s umbrella shield once and breaking an ice wall, they hadn’t been able to do anything else.

The group who had been trying to break through the ice wall only had three players left. They were the ones with a disadvantage in numbers now.

The remaining three were so scared that they had even forgotten there were others in their team. After seeing two more players die, they immediately headed towards the alleyway. All three of them had a similar single thought resonating in their minds: run!

Running was their only option.

Running was the only thing they could do.

What other choice did they have? The three didn’t know and didn’t have the time to know. They were trying their hardest to run, but…….

A shadow flickered and appeared in front of them. Another shadow came from above.

Sword Draw!

Ninjutsu - Bird Fall!

Lord Grim and Deception had used the Shadow Clone Technique to instantly move there. The three had only thought of running and nothing else, so they hadn’t thought of this possibility.

A sword light flew towards them and two feet stomped down. The three players flew backwards. Behind them was the Grappler, who grabbed one with his left hand and the other with his right. He suddenly leapt into the air and his two legs caught the last one.

The Grappler grabbed all three of them.

He had used two Grappler skills simultaneously: Flying Hands and Aerial Twist! It was possible to perform both at the same time.

With the two legs twisting and two hands flying, the Grappler threw all three into a ball and then landed on the ground.

The Berserker, Battle Mage, and Elementalist were already prepared and immediately attacked. Lord Grim and Deception followed up with their offense. After a single wave of attacks, the three players turned into three more corpses.

Twelve players!

As of now, nearly half of Golden Fragrance’s team had died. It had only been a minute since the fight had begun.

It wasn’t like Golden Fragrance had no sense of tactics. She focused on the Cleric on the roof and had her subordinates target that Cleric.

This wasn’t a wrong choice. In a team battle, if the enemy’s Cleric was killed, then the battle could be won much faster.

However, common tactics were naturally used during normal situations.

Kill the Cleric first? Truthfully, Golden Fragrance had felt that she had been too careful in her preparation for it. It wasn’t a normal situation. Her side had such a large numbers advantage. Did she really need to make a plan?

Sure enough, it really wasn’t a normal situation.

Cleric? Was the Cleric even useful in this battle? Golden Fragrance was doubtful. While twelve of her allies died, the enemy Cleric hadn’t done any healing.

Quick! Too quick!

Killing twelve players in one minute. This was how fast a one wave strategy was. However, a one wave strategy was generally only used when one side had a clear numbers advantage and a levels advantage. According to normal theory, her side should be the one doing this. Why had it flipped? Why was their side being the one being crushed?

“Too strong! Let’s retreat!”

None of them were noobs. If they weren’t able to figure out the huge difference between their strengths, then that would be a noob.

“Let’s retreat. I’ll call for backup!” Golden Fragrance hastily called.

“You’re going to run? You’re making this difficult for us…… I keep my promises. If I say no one escapes, then no one escapes!” Ye Xiu’s voice rang out.

Chapter 486 – No One Escapes

Golden Fragrance had originally never intended to call for help. Firstly, because she believed there were enough people, and secondly, because if her equipment dropped, she didn’t want it falling into someone else’s hands. Despite being in the same guild, when faced with good equipment, the trust between one another was almost obsolete.

Chen Yehui had obviously thought about this, which was why he arranged it in such a way. He even hoped people from Herb Garden and Blue Brook Guild to be far away from them, let alone calling for assistance. The path he left would already be considered fairly out of the way.

As a result, Chen Yehui was shocked when Golden Fragrance called for help.

Even if it's Ye Qiu! Even if Deception was also very strong! They had over 20 people! Wouldn't calling for more assistance be over the top?

Chen Yehui could tolerate if the two escaped again, but he found it hard to believe that the two couldn't be defeated?

“What happened?” Chen Yehui wanted to find out what was going on, but the news Golden Fragrance sent didn't say much. She merely sent her marked location, calling for help.

　

How could Golden Fragrance possibly have time to explain? The group of people’s quick AOE attacks struck them dumb with astonishment.

Twelve people annihilated in under a minute, which meant a person was killed every five seconds on average. How long would sending this message take? By the time the message was sent, she would long be dead.

Golden Fragrance saw Chen Yehui’s questioning message, but she also saw the people rushing towards her like the wind. It was definite that replying to the message would cost her her life, so Golden Fragrance ignored the message to turned tail and run without hesitation.

Run!

Purely running away.

She didn't have any routes of escape or acts of resistance, she just turned around and pressed the key to scurry straight forward.　

Before, the three great guilds had pursued Lord Grim and Deception restlessly, but right at this moment, in a certain way, events had taken a great turn.

When escaping, Ye Xiu was rich in experience, so he was very skilful; now that it's his turn to pursue, his ability was by no means weaker. In addition, Golden Fragrance and her group were only aiming to go forward and forward and forward. They didn't even observe their pursuers’ action. They chose a running style that required the least amount of skill.

Stun Bullet!

Hundred Streams!

Ye Xiu and Deception each used a skill.

Lord Grim’s bullet caught a player while Deception’s water streams surged closely behind. The streams instantly formed into a water prison, which incapacitated the player.

The imprisoned player was dazed. Although the water prison had caught him, in a way, it protected him as well. As long as the prison was up, he couldn't receive any damage.

　　

Before he could understand any of it, the people behind Lord Grim and Deception were already charging forward. They attacked while they ran, so it didn't take long before the water prison was destroyed. The second wave of attacks thrusted him into the ground. After that, the mob only needed to throw out some random attacks to finish him off.

The ghost floated in midair while its player watched with a stunned expression as the mob rushed over his corpse. It was as if his consciousness was still lingering in confusion back at the water prison. The time the had passed only felt like the blink of an eye before he was sent off to float into the sky. Yet, the opponents’ footsteps didn't slow down a fraction. As they stomped over his corpse, they managed to shorten the distance between themselves and the escaping players ahead.

A lot of offensive skills had a slight displacement effect and these effects were faster than plain running. The pursuers skilfully utilised these skills, so while they killed the previous player, they weren't delayed at all.

Another died!　

Golden Fragrance and her group didn't even dare to look back, they discovered the losses through the darkened names on their team list. They didn't have time to check who it was, they even hoped that the player sacrificed could perhaps help them earn a bit of time to escape.

In a bright flash, a person’s silhouette was instantly formed, right in the center of Golden Fragrance’s group.

Teleportation!

An actual teleportation, which was an electric type Elementalist skill.

An Elementalist teleporting into a group of people would usually be considered an act of suicide.

However, Golden Fragrance and her group were desperate to escape, so all they thought was: D*mn it, they have caught up!

　

As they thought, the Elementalist’s teleportation wasn't an act of suicide!

The staff lifted as it made cracking sounds. A few sheets of ice walls immediately formed behind the elementalist.

The people trapped within the ice walls panicked, they threw whatever skills they could afford towards the ice walls. Unfortunately, the delay was enough for the people behind them to catch up.

Shadow Cloak!

Double Flying Hands!

This time, Ye Xiu coordinated himself with the Grappler. The six people whom were stopped by the ice wall were instantly gathered together by the skills of Ye Xiu and the Grappler. Under the blast of AOE skills, it was without a doubt another textbook type of AOE combat style. There was little to no time difference from when the first, fifth or last person fell down.

In addition, the remaining energy waves from the attacks happened to break the ice walls in time. After finishing off the six people, they continued their pursuit. The ice walls didn’t bring them any inconvenience.

We’ve lost another six!　

There were only six people remaining in Golden Fragrance’s group. From that moment on, even the number of people’s advantage was overturned. Lord Grim’s group have seven people in total, besting their group by one person. Although the Cleric from before didn’t have much use after healing Lord Grim.

“Everyone, run in separate directions!!” Golden Fragrance yelled. 　　

The six people’s sacrifice finally helped them gain a bit of time. A crossroad appeared before them, even though someone would be doomed after splitting up, at least it was a good plan to prevent a team wipe. The six people’s avatars on the team list darkened simultaneously, evident that they were wiped out through the use of AOE skills. Golden Fragrance and her group were already very deeply afraid of Lord Grim’s mob of AOE techniques.

One step, two steps, three steps…...

　

Why aren’t we at the intersection yet!

The intersection that no one cared about before now seemed impossible to reach in their eyes. In their hearts, everyone in the group resented that they didn’t have wings.

Nearly there!

Finally, they reached the intersection. The three forked roads glowed with hope. They didn’t have time to distribute themselves into groups, so everyone choose a random fork in the road.

The remaining six people prepared to run towards the hope in their hearts. However, they caught a flash of shadow. The two silhouettes which brought them fear and annoyance instantly appeared before them.

Lord Grim, Deception…...　

The cause of what had happened. 　　

The beginning of all nightmares. 　

At such a crucial time, the two became their obstacles.

Deception made a seal and a Shadow Dance started again. Instantly, the shadow who blocked the road split into who knows how many? The shadow clones, which flew out of Shadow Dance, attacked the six people and restricted their movements. Lord Grim was on the side making matters worse for the six people. Those who didn’t get restricted enough would immediately receive their lesson.

The berserker’s helpers arrived soon after. Since they had been faced with the final six people, they didn't use the AOE method again. Everyone had one opponent to fight.

Miss Golden Fragrance managed to survive till now, as long as she used her Aerial Cannon without error, she still had quite an advantage in running away. Unfortunately, her advantage was nonexistent now because the opponent she had to face was Lord Grim.

Normally, Golden Fragrance would be happy to tease a Level 52 player and feel all high and mighty. However, now that she knew of her opponent’s identity, Golden Fragrance didn't have a teasing mood or attitude.

“What sort of good equipment do you have?” Ye Xiu asked, as if he were a hijacker.

Golden Fragrance had died twice today and dropped two pieces of equipments, both of which were orange. Even if she was one of the guild’s core members, she felt pained over the loss of her equipment. Core members of guilds were still far from a pro-gamer’s situation, where orange equipment was regarded as basic gear.

Now that the bandit who targeted her equipment was blocking her once more, Golden Fragrance truly wanted to cry. Not only was she not going to get her equipment back, but now she would lose another piece of hers.

Golden Fragrance looked left and right, and saw that her other five teammates had battled into a mess. At this point, she had to fight with all she had, because no matter how one looked at it, they were the ones being surrounded.

“The great god Ye Qiu bullies me, a girl? Is it meaningful??” Golden Fragrance asked.

“Hehe, sorry about that.” Ye Xiu replied.

Golden Fragrance was about to say something else, but Ye Xiu had already sent a smiling emoji along with: “I will be more aware next time.”

　

After Lord Grim sent this sentence, he rushed forward.

Golden Fragrance was surrounded in the center, so she had nowhere to escape to. In addition, with someone as skilled as Ye Xiu, she was caught before she even took two or three steps. Golden Fragrance’s struggle merely proved her existence, to let people know that her character was under her control and not a block of wood.

Golden Fragrance was depressed. Why was this god picking on her so much? If it was someone other than him or Deception who was intervening her escape, she could have had a chance to escape…...

Golden Fragrance wasn't the only one with this thought. The players who didn't encounter the two strong players had a spark of anticipation in their hearts.

The anticipation quickly became hope. After fighting with Lord Grim’s helpers, they realized that although they were strong, it was not to the point where they have no hope.

　

The four people became energized and began to oppose fiercely.

In order to hold them up, Lord Grim’s four helpers fought head on. They even received damage they could have been avoided.

　

Golden Fragrance’s group observed. At this rate, they had a chance! Not only might they escape, they could also turn the other group into corpses.

　

Little did they know that at this moment, a ray of white light would shower onto the Elementalist.

Soon afterwards, the white light flashed towards the other players.

The people coughed up blood, as they looked around, they realised that the opposing team’s Cleric had just arrived. Only now did they remember that they also had a Cleric. As for their own team, they no longer had a Cleric. Their Cleric had already been killed by the opposing side.

No wonder Lord Grim’s group blocked them with such hardness. Under the assistance of a Cleric, they had no reason to hold back. This was a very logical and sensible tactics choice.

As the group had feared, they had no hope. The mob was in complete despair. At this very moment, a band of players appeared on a crossing that led off from the road ahead.

Chapter 487 – What’s the Situation

Chen Yehui was a veteran with many years of experience in battles. Even though he wanted to know the details from Golden Fragrance, seeing how he didn’t receive any response, he immediately knew that the situation wasn’t looking good. The situation had already deteriorated to the point that she didn’t even have time to reply.

How had Ye Qiu and Deception forced the team into such a position?

Chen Yehui was astonished, but he couldn’t slip up. The very first thing he did was tell this information to Arisaema and Changing Spring.

“What? How’d they get there?”

The two guild leaders were very surprised. They hadn’t known that Chen Yehui had intentionally let them slip through the encirclement. According to their original plan of shrinking the encirclement, their two targets may have escaped, but they shouldn’t have been able to escape without anyone noticing.

Following this logic, because the two guild leaders hadn’t received any news, the two guild leaders thought that Lord Grim and Deception were still trapped inside their circle!

Their encirclement had shrunk and shrunk. Their two targets would have to appear soon. The two guild leaders couldn’t help but begin to feel excited, until Chen Yehui told them the news. They looked at the map and the coordinates were a good distance away from their encirclement.

“Who knows how they got out?! More importantly, one of my teams is currently fighting with them. Do any of you have troops nearby?” Chen Yehui was extremely cunning. As soon as he realized the situation wasn’t good, while not knowing the details, he wasn’t going to run in blindly. First, he was going to have these two guilds probe the situation.

Chen Yehui completely tricked the other two guild leaders. Neither of them thought too much of it.

“Let me see.” The two replied and immediately called out to their respective guilds.

“I have one team here!” Arisaema quickly said.

“Have your players hurry and assist them. Our backup will be there soon.” Chen Yehui said.

“We have to create another encirclement. How troublesome.” Arisaema was still confused as to what was going on. He thought Lord Grim and Deception were still using hit and run guerrilla warfare tactics. As for Golden Fragrance, her side was in a tragic situation. Chen Yehui hadn’t received any confirmation, but he was certain of it. However, he didn’t tell the two of them.

Sure enough, Ye Qiu was out for revenge against Excellent Dynasty! Excellent Dynasty really is trash though. We’re not going to be able to catch them here like this. Arisaema thought. He was happy to see Excellent Dynasty’s players being attacked, but he was starting to get impatient.

Street intersection.

Golden Fragrance and her five allies weren’t able to hold on any longer. However, this time, they weren’t gathered together and swept away in one wave like the others. As a result, it took some time for the situation to worsen. As their first ally fell, a group of players appeared at the intersection.

That group of players saw the commotion going on here and hastily ran over. Golden Fragrance and her allies were at first happy, but soon, they realized that the support was only made up of half a teams worth of players. Their hopes immediately dwindled.

Let alone half a team, a whole team wouldn’t be enough in front of them!

But these new arrivals weren’t aware of this. They charged forward aggressively. As they got closer, they were able to see that they were members of Herb Garden.

Most of the teams participating in this activity were made up of five players. This team wasn’t an exception. After receiving personal orders from their guild leader, they quickly arrived at the designated location. They hadn’t reached the location yet, but when they saw the huge commotion at the intersection. This desolate Level 55 leveling area shouldn’t have anyone inside, so what else could a commotion mean?

This was why the five players didn’t wait to see what the situation was before rushing forward. When they got closer, they noticed Lord Grim’s and Deception’s names. Apart from them, there were ten others! It was clear who had the advantage in numbers!

The five players excitedly came over, but as they got nearer, they suddenly realized that something wasn’t quite right. The ten other players didn’t seem to be surrounding Lord Grim and Deception and fighting them. There seemed to be two teams fighting.

“What’s going on?” The captain of this five-man team shouted in surprise. Soon afterwards, he saw the Excellent Dynasty players fall and the ones who killed them didn’t have a guild tag next to their names.

These killers picked the dead clean. Next, they headed towards this five-man team.

One, two, three, four, five, six, seven…..

The captain counted the number of people heading towards them. They had seven people, two more than their group. Plus, with Lord Grim and Deception, two exceptional experts, how were they supposed to win? Hurry and run!

The five players had been a bit slow at first, but this time, they acted nimbly. Without even asking or trying, they turned tail and ran. The captain hastily sent his guild leader a message: “They have a lot of people. Seven!”

This message was sent out at the cost of his life.

It had only been seven words, but it was enough time for the enemies to arrive and surround him.

Editor Note: Ten words is correct because in Chinese, including punctuation, it’s ten characters total.

“You guys go ahead!!!”

The captain was very heroic. As soon as he saw that there was no chance for him to escape, he let out a line straight from a drama and then died as a sacrifice for his teammates.

He died.

After making his final cry, he didn’t do anything else.

The captain felt like he was a piece of straw and the enemies were like a swarm of locusts. The locusts swept over him. He was merely a lone piece of straw. Soon, they ate him clean.

“F*CK! WHAT’S GOING ON!!!” The captain’s ghost flew up into the air and then looked down. The seven wolves pounced onto his other teammates.

Why are they doing this? Why are they so enthusiastic?

The captain was planning on waiting for a Cleric to arrive and revive him, but because of this, he had to watch a tragedy unfold.

His other four teammates weren’t able to actually escape like in the movies just because he said “you guys go ahead.” The locust-like mob of seven chased after them and used their instant movement skills to block their path.

And then there was a fight.

A fight between blades and words.

The four poor teammates weren’t able to do anything but curse. They quickly fell under their opponent’s hands and then became four corpses on the ground. Their ghosts floated into the air. Ghosts weren’t able to see each other though, but because their corpses were still there, it meant their ghosts were there too.

“What? Seven????”

Chen Yehui and Arisaema received the news at nearly the same time.

Golden Fragrance had been killed off, so she now had time to report to Chen Yehui. As for that captain, he died soon after she did.

“Seven people? What’s going on?” Arisaema asked Chen Yehui. Chen Yehui wasn’t going to reveal anything.

“I only just got the information too.” Chen Yehui replied, “The previous reports didn’t say this. They only asked for help.”

Arisaema didn’t say anything further. It wasn’t the time to bicker.

“Apart from Lord Grim and Deception, who else could there be?” The two guild leaders asked the same question.

“I don’t recognize them. I didn’t recognize the other five of them. They have no guild tags and I’ve never seen their names before either.”

Their responses were the same.

Chen Yehui suddenly shivered in fear because he suddenly remembered that Ye Qiu had gathered a group of incredible experts around him. All of them were at the pro level and were likely to be a part of his pro team.

Golden Fragrance’s detailed description of their opponents’ strength only helped to confirm Chen Yehui’s suspicions.

To be able to completely suppress the top guilds through their explosive strength indicated that even if they weren’t at a pro level, they weren’t far from it! A lightning like offense required exceptional levels of coordination, the sort of cohesion seen at a pro level. This was the only way such a display of strength could be made.

Could their troops block these types of players?

12 players killed in one minute. This meant that against their current strategy using small teams to stop them would only be crushed through their opponent’s brute force.

Three players against Lord Grim and Deception resulted in a team wipe.

Five players against Lord Grim and Deception resulted in two deaths and their escape.

Now that they were against seven players, how many troops did they need to send out? Even 25 players wouldn’t be their opponent.

If they couldn’t kill them, then they couldn’t stop them. Stall for time? One or two people could stall for time because one or two people had a limited amount of killing power. However, against seven people, if they attacked twice, focusing on one target, they would be able to kill the target. In addition, with their mobbing strategy, stalling for time and dying was basically the same thing.

What should we do? What should we do…...

Chen Yehui felt a headache coming, but Arisaema and Changing Spring didn’t know that the opposing side had only killed half a team of players. It wasn’t any surprise five player stood no chance against seven! The other side had Lord Grim and Deception, two exceptional experts and had a numbers advantage. Of course, it would be a one sided battle.

“Small teams combine and form full teams as individual units. Hurry!” The two guild leaders ordered.

A full team was ten players. Before, it had been five players as a unit. Now, they were going to increase the unit size to ten in order to fight back.

“They might be thinking they can kill us off one at a time. We have to hurry and gather our troops together. Don’t have them reveal themselves. Wait for the enemies to enter our attack range and wipe them out in one swoop!” Arisaema and Changing Spring discussed.

“Mm, sounds good!” Chen Yehui was the one to agree. He already knew how strong the enemy team was, so he hoped for Arisaema and Changing Spring to experience it for themselves. In reality, despite having a pro team above them, the guilds rarely had a chance to experience their team’s strength for themselves. Sometimes, their guild would have a spar with the pro players, but that was just for fun. No one took it seriously.

“East West 3rd Street, heading west!” A report informed.

“Don’t rush in rashly. Wait for them to move deeper into our range. Good, they’re going into our previously formed circle. Our encirclement hasn’t been completely broken up yet!” Arisaema ordered delightedly.

“Yeah, yeah!” Chen Yehui agreed, while sending out a message to his teams. His orders consisted of only half of Arisaema’s: “Don’t rush in rashly. Wait for my orders.”

Chapter 488 – Lure the Enemy in Deep

East West 3rd Street

The system couldn’t generate a name for every street and alleyway in every town and city, so online maps outside of Glory often used this sort of naming method to mark out unnamed locations.

From a direction and distance perspective, this naming method was more intuitive than coordinates. When an experienced Glory player heard these name, he’d know the general location. By using this information along with the coordinates received, finding the exact location became easier and faster to find.

At this moment, on East West 3rd Street in a narrow alley going from north to south, a team of Herb Garden players began to retreat.

This was a full team of ten players. The captain was called Orobanche, the name of an herb. Herb and plant names were commonly seen in Herb Garden, especially among the senior guild members. Nowadays though, because of Herb Garden’s fame and strength, Herb Garden wasn’t going to refuse a fan for not having an herb name. Many Herb Garden players had herbs as names, but not all of them did.

Orobanche sent a message to Arisaema telling him that their team had retreated.

“We’re not going to attack, captain?” One of the team members asked.

“The guild leader told us to wait. Once they get closer, we’ll surround them.” Orobanche explained.

“Okay.” No one objected. Their opponents had seven people on their team, while they had ten. Even though they had a slight advantage in number, their opponent’s team had Lord Grim and Deception, both exceptional experts. Whether or not they could win was a completely different matter. All of them were veterans and very well knew their own limits, so none of them arrogantly declared they would take their opponents down for sure. It would be better to wait until more backup arrived before surrounding them together. There was a limit to skill. Even if your opponents were pro players with godly skill and amazing equipment, if you had a lot more people on your side, you’d eventually win. A numbers advantage would always be a reliable advantage in the game.

The team of ten sat in the alley quietly.

“Captain, you said……”

Suddenly, the light seemed to have dimmed all of a sudden. The team lifted their heads up. Two people were standing outside of the alley, blocking the sunlight from coming into the alley.

“See, I told you there would be people here!” The person on the left spoke. The ID above his head spelled out Lord Grim.

“If these people had been equipment, I definitely would have seen them!” The person on the right denied his inability. The ID above his head spelled out Deception.

“You can see equipment on the ground, but you can’t see equipment on someone’s body. What’s up with that?” Lord Grim lifted up one of his hands.

“Shut up!” Deception drew his blade.

A grenade rolled over, and a wave of fire blasted towards them.

Hand Grenade!

Flame Cut!

They had just passed the street, but then quickly came back. The team, which had been quietly sitting in the alleyway, wasn’t prepared at all. Ye Xiu and Deception chatted and moved quickly, immediately covering the alley in smoke and light. Captain Orobanche had been closest to the entrance of the alleyway and took severe damage.

Collapsing Mountain!

Lord Grim and Deception suddenly crouched. A Berserker flew over their heads with his huge sword held high above his head. The sword crashed down with a might that could split mountains.

Ice Wall!

Several ice walls shot up in the alleyway. The alleyway was very narrow. It wasn’t easy to get two people to stand shoulder to shoulder with each other. A single ice wall would be enough to block the alleyway, but instead there were four. This wasn’t like dominoes. If one fell, the other walls weren’t going to fall down too. They would have to break each wall one at a time. How long would that take?!

There were also seven enemies! They were blocking the alley entrance. Plus, they could throw whatever skills they wanted at them. With such little space to move around in, where were they supposed to run? It was impossible to escape.

Orobanche’s team was like a stuck monster. They could struggle all they wanted to, but they wouldn’t be able to find a way out. They tried to squeeze their way out, but Lord Grim simply repelled them with a Falling Flower Palm. Magic spells rained down on them from above and they didn’t even know where the enemy Elementalist was.

After a short moment, there were three shattered ice walls and ten corpses lying in the alley.

Whether they waited for someone to revive them or whether they revived back at the city wasn’t something Ye Xiu’s team cared about. They picked up the dropped items and gold before heading north through the alley.

“What? What did you say? Why didn’t you hide better?” Arisaema received the news.

Orobanche felt wronged. Hide better? Our original orders were to actively look for Lord Grim. Then, after discovering that Lord Grim had a team, you told us to not to make any rash movements and to await further instructions.

“Where are they heading?” Arisaema asked.

“Towards the north. Coordinates XXX, XXX.” Orobanche replied. This alleyway was so small, the outside maps didn’t even have a name for it.

“Those near coordinates XXX, XXX. Pay attention to the north side. If you see Lord Grim’s team, lure them in deep!” Arisaema ordered and told the information to Changing Spring and Chen Yehui.

The guild teams were still looking at the map after studying these coordinates, when Ye Xiu’s team rushed out from the small alleyway. When Ye Xiu’s team looked around, they didn’t see anyone around.

“This way.” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim led the way.

Not long after heading left, another alleyway heading north appeared. Lord Grim and the other six went in.

This time, after going through the narrow alleyway, they saw a team of ten players. This team was from Blue Brook Guild.

Did the guild matter though?

Clearly not. The seven players charged forward and attacked. This team of ten was still digesting the orders given to them. Who would have thought their mission would suddenly land on top of their heads? They hadn’t even figured out how they were going to position everyone, when Lord Grim bound them together with a Shadow Cloak and threw them onto the streets.

“F*CK!!”

The team cried. If they were going to be so violent, where was the need to fake it? They turned their heads and immediately began running. They were truly luring their enemies in deep. Who would dare call them out for acting fake? They truly were putting everything they had into running for their lives.

Unfortunately, they weren’t able to escape. Six of them tried to head inwards to hide, but were quickly caught and killed.

Ye Xiu saw the direction these six were heading towards and was forewarned. He took his team in the opposite direction, while figuring out how to head north and break out of the trap.

“I lost a team too!” Changing Spring shared the same losses as everyone else.

“Where did they head?” Arisaema quickly asked.

After hearing this, they saw the map and became silent. Looking at their direction, they were heading in the opposite direction from their encirclement. If they kept heading north, they would break out of their range and escape!

“Hurry! Hurry up and pull back! Pincer them from both sides.” Arisaema shouted, while ordering his subordinates.

Changing Spring was more calm: “Didn’t these two teams die a bit too quickly?”

Only now did Arisaema realize that he had ignored this issue.

How had a full team of ten players die so fast?

“Who are those five people?” Arisaema and Changing Spring both had a team die to them. Now they were at the same level of understanding as Chen Yehui. These five weren’t just random players.

“No guild. We don’t recognize their names either……” The twenty players who had died didn’t know.

“What were their classes then?” Changing Spring asked.

It would be easier to figure out who these experts were after narrowing down their options. Their intelligence network was spread far and wide. They had information on all of the experts in the Heavenly Domain.

Chen Yehui hadn’t asked this question because he already had a feeling that he knew their identities. Did their classes really matter? Anyone at the pro level could play any class far better than ordinary players. Pro players wouldn’t only know how to play their own classes. You had to know yourself and know your enemies thoroughly in order to win. If you didn’t know your opponent’s class well, how were you going to win?

“Berserker, Cleric, Elementalist, Battle Mage, Grappler…….” Arisaema and Changing Spring got a list of their classes. By narrowing the options, they could figure out the origin of this class composition.

The report quickly came back: Heavenly Justice’s five experts played these five classes.

“Heavenly Justice!” The first to receive the information was Changing Spring.

“Ah? You’ve figured it out?” Arisaema said.

“Heavenly Justice??” Chen Yehui was very surprised when he heard this answer.

“Wasn’t Heavenly Justice planning on entering the pro scene?” Changing Spring said.

“I’ve talked with them before. Their skill isn’t ordinary. I tried to pull them in before, but I wasn’t successful. Now I know the reason why.” Arisaema said.

“I haven’t seen them in action for a long time though, so I don’t know how strong they really are.” Changing Spring continued. He had tried to do the same thing as Arisaema before.

“But if they dare to enter the pro scene, they can’t be bad, no?” Chen Yehui said, while thinking. He connected Heavenly Justice’s experts with the hidden experts inside the Internet Cafe across the street from them.

“To think Heavenly Justice would act against us first.” Arisaema said.

“Heavenly Justice? Do you have proof? These are open accounts.” Changing Spring said.

They went silent. Open accounts were used so that no one would be able to recognize the person using it. This was why top guilds had so many of them!

“Against such a team, ten people isn’t going to be enough! Hurry up and call everyone together.” Arisaema hastily said.

“Already done.” Changing Spring replied.

On the streets, a team of seven was running around.

“What are we going to do next?” The Berserker spoke in a much more respectful tone to Lord Grim compared to how Deception spoke to him.

“They have an encirclement set up. Right now, we have to hurry and run along the perimeter and break through. We’re not going to attack them face to face, so they won’t be able to make use of their number advantage.”

Chapter 489 – The Enemy Closes In, While We Back Out

“Oh, like that huh……” The Berserker heard Ye Xiu’s reply and felt like he had a certain level of understanding now.

“How did you figure out their formation?” The Berserker asked again.

“It took me a lot of observation and analysis. Afterwards, I made a judgement based off of their teams’ distances, movement direction, and the empty spaces on the map.” Ye Xiu said.

“You can even do that?” The Berserker was surprised.

Deception had heard all of this before. In the beginning, he hadn’t believed it either, but after running around with Lord Grim for a while, he slowly realized that Lord Grim truly did have an understanding of the enemy’s positions based on how the players moved. Lord Grim didn’t know everything, of course, but it wasn’t something Deception could do.

“We have to learn from him well!” The Berserker told his comrades.

Changing Spring’s deduction was correct. These five players were indeed from Heavenly Justice. The Berserker was Loulan Slash. The Battle Mage was Little Bei. The Grappler was Night Tide. The Elementalist was Ocean Ahead. The Cleric was Thousand Falling Leaves. Ye Xiu had told them to come over to practice.

Loulan Slash’s group was planning on joining the pro scene. Practice was a must. The equipment issue could be solved some other way. Ye Xiu didn’t ask about this. He reckoned Loulan Slash wouldn’t be so confident that he would think the Heavenly Domain equipment he had equipped would be good enough for the pro scene. Loulan Slash didn’t tell him what they were going to do about it, so Ye Xiu wasn’t even going to ask.

In any case, an individual’s skill and the coordination between a team could always be improved. Especially after fighting with Ye Xiu, Huang Shaotian, and Wang Jiexi, Loulan Slash’s group had already completely dispelled their initial overambitious thoughts. Their goal the first year in the pro scene had changed to defending their spot in the Alliance.

Defending their spot meant not falling into the bottom two places, which would be auto-relegated.

A team joining the pro scene and then dropping out after their first year wasn’t anything new. Loulan Slash’s group felt scared just thinking about it. If they hadn’t met Ye Xiu, with their initial confidence, thinking they could immediately become the Champions, they would probably fall to last place and be relegated.

Improve!

Loulan Slash’s group only had this thought in their heads now. They weren’t there to have fun in the pro scene. They weren’t fans like Chen Guo, who would just be happy to have the experience. They were there to make a name for themselves.

After learning that Ye Xiu was actually God Ye Qiu, Loulan Slash’s group obviously wanted to learn from him. As a result, Ye Xiu called them over to come when he saw such a big scene unfolding.

Although this scene wasn’t something that would ever be seen in pro matches, it was still a good opportunity to practice team coordination. Having the chance to spar with other pro players wasn’t something that could just be asked for.

When they arrived at the scene, the lightning fast offense led by Ye Xiu shocked not just Golden Fragrance and their enemies, but them too.

They already felt like they had learned a lot so far.

Who didn’t know how to group up monsters and kill them in one burst? But to do this to such an extent wasn’t something anyone could do.

So this was a pro!

Loulan Slash thought. This also made them realize that if they wanted to survive in the pro scene, they would need such a level of strength. However, if Ye Xiu wasn’t there to lead them like this, Loulan Slash wasn’t confident that he could do the same.

They were quite proficient with their own classes, but their knowledge on the synergy, skill combinations, and skill usages between the different classes couldn’t compare to Ye Xiu’s.

“Record it! Record it all!” Loulan Slash whispered privately to his team members.

“Of course. I’ve been recording this entire time.” Ocean Ahead replied.

“We’ll need to study this when we’re done and then we’ll go practice.” Loulan Slash said.

While talking, the seven player team encountered a Blue Brook Guild team. When the team of ten guild players saw these seven players, they immediately turned pale and turned tail.

This time, it was real. They weren’t trying to lure the enemy in deep or anything. This was because, they already had orders that any team with 30 or fewer players was to immediately escape.

These seven players were regarded as having the strength of 30 guild players by the guild leaders. Even with this, they weren’t sure. They were striving for a group of one hundred players before engaging in battle.

Slowly, the three guild leaders had already forgotten about hunting them. To their understanding, this was a confrontation between two equal powers. They would organize their strength and face their opponents.

Knowing the difference between their skill levels, the ten player team turned tail and ran for their lives. The seven players had no way of blocking them.

“Are we going to chase them?” Loulan Slash asked.

“Follow them.” Ye Xiu said.

The seven players chased after the ten runners.

“Pay attention to my pacing while moving.” Ye Xiu said.

Everyone began paying attention to Lord Grim’s movements.

The ten player team only had thoughts of widening the distance as much as possible and didn’t hold anything back. Seeing the seven players shrinking in the distance, their hearts calmed down a little bit, but not long afterwards, the seven players appeared behind them again, hanging around neither too far nor close to them. The ten player team tried to sprint away again, but they realized they didn’t have enough stamina. Without stamina, they couldn’t sprint and their running speed would drop. Starting from here, the seven players drew nearer and nearer.

“THEY’RE COMING!!!!” The ten player team cried for their lives and spammed their coordinates in the guild chat.

“Hang on!” The guild players could only reply. It would still take them time to arrive and help them.

“THEY’RE GETTING CLOSER! EVEN CLOSER!!” The ten player team was in complete chaos. The enemies were getting closer and closer in front of their eyes and there was nothing they could do but await their pitiful demise. It was a feeling even more terrifying than death.

“No good. Our support won’t arrive in time!” The captain of the ten player team looked around left and right. Apart from the seven enemies clawing closer and closer to them, there was no one else in sight.

“What do we do?” One of the members mourned.

“Log off!” The captain decided.

“Ah?” One of the team members gasped.

“If not, we’ll die for nothing! Our other team wasn’t weak either, but they didn’t even last a minute.” The captain hastily explained.

“Then let’s hurry up and log off! They’re about to get in range!” Another team member shouted.

Following afterwards, the ten players disappeared. They had logged off beautifully.

“No way??” The seven were completely stunned, even Ye Xiu. None of them expected their opponents to log off.

“Head east!” At this moment, Ye Xiu didn’t delay and immediately shouted out an order. The team switched directions from heading north to east.

“Why?” As long as there was a chance, Loulan Slash would always ask why so he could grasp Ye Xiu’s way of thinking.

“Our opponents have probably figured out our battle strength, so they’re probably gathering together. If we continue to go down that path, we’ll probably encounter a huge team. It’s better to turn back for now!” Ye Xiu explained.

The seven player team headed east. At the same time, the three guilds completely lost track of their position.

By gathering their troops together, they would obviously lose control over the area. If the previous team had died, their ghosts would still be able to monitor them for a bit. However, because this team logged off, they now had no idea which direction the seven had run off in.

A short moment later, the three guilds gathered all of their troops together and then stood there stupidly. Where was Lord Grim? No idea. Where was that team? No idea.

“F*CK! That’s too cunning!” Arisaema was pissed. After learning that their opponents had Heavenly Justice’s five experts too, the prey had become the hunter and their guilds became the targets. This was why they had hastily changed plans, but once their opponents got close to them, they suddenly turned passive again and hid. Now what were they going to do?

It wasn’t going to be possible for them to scatter around the map again. If they did, they would all become meat buns. The animals eating weren’t dogs either, but were really wolves.

Should they continue maintaining these huge teams? They had too few units and too little control over the area. Their opponents would be able to escape easily.

The three guilds were in a difficult predicament. It seemed like there was only one option in front of them: to give up on the operation.

They weren’t willing to! They had put so much effort and manpower and it was just going to end like this? The three guild leaders had this type of remorse. They felt like they were in the tenth server once again, where they were helpless under Lord Grim’s hands. The Heavenly Domain was supposed to be completely different, but in reality…… was it just the same?

“The other guilds……” Chen Yehui suddenly thought.

“They’re probably sitting there eating popcorn…..” Arisaema sighed.

With a good opportunity to kill Lord Grim, they hadn’t hidden the information away and actively shared it. However, the three guilds had been the first to arrive at the scene and after seeing such a commotion, the other guilds sat back to watch the show instead of joining. The three guild leaders definitely understood this. They would have done the same too. Killing Lord Grim would benefit everyone, so there was no need to compete to do it. As a result, everyone was very nice about it.

“I refuse to have it end like this!” Changing Spring roared, but what could they do? Keep adding troops? Changing Spring thought.

Chen Yehui took off his headphones and then picked up the cellphone on his desk.

“Ye Qiu is currently in the game. He’s leading those Heavenly Justice guys who are claiming they’ll be joining the pro scene next season. They’re showing off their strength.” Liu Hao had taken the call and then turned his head to explain the situation.

“Hmph, them? They’re nothing special.” Sun Xiang coldly said.

“However, the guild players aren’t enough.” Liu Hao said, “I heard they only have a total of seven players on their team, but they were easily able to kill off a full team.”

“I can kill off a team of normal players on my own.” Sun Xiang sneered.

“Ha ha, of course.” Liu Hao said, “I happen to have a few accounts on hand. Let’s give them a little surprise.”

“Oh?” Sun Xiang’s eyes suddenly lit up, “That sounds fun!”

Chapter 490 – Team Excellent Era

“Here’s a Battle Mage account card.” A trace of treachery flashed across Liu Hao’s face as he handed an account card to Sun Xiang.

In fact, before Sun Xiang even came to Excellent Era, he hadn’t used a Battle Mage. However, his Battle Mage was also very good. After obtaining One Autumn Leaf, some people speculated that Sun Xiang had planned on succeeding Ye Qiu long beforehand. Why else would he put in so much effort to train his Battle Mage? If he really planned on snatching the name of Battle God, then Sun Xiang was truly an ambitious fellow.

Right now, they were using open accounts, so even if Liu Hao had given Sun Xiang his original class, Sun Xiang would still be able to perform at a high level as well. However, Liu Hao still gave him a Battle Mage account, a class Sun Xiang had only officially taken out halfway through his first season. It could be said that Liu Hao had a good grasp of Sun Xiang’s personality.

If he gave Sun Xiang his original class, Sun Xiang might be able to perform well, but with his arrogant and confident personality, he definitely wouldn’t take it well and might even become angry. It would be implying that he didn’t have confidence in Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage. Making such an action might rub him the wrong way.

Sun Xiang was impatient in proving his Battle Mage could succeed Ye Qiu’s. In the All Star Competition, he challenged Excellent Era’s sworn enemy and Ye Qiu’s long-time rival Han Wenqing. However, it resulted in a loss by the slightest of margins. However, for him, the result was completely humiliating, especially after Han Wenqing declared in front of everyone how he couldn’t even compare to Ye Qiu…...

Sun Xiang had lost, so he couldn’t refute it. He hadn’t lost his poise in front of the public at that time either. Only his teammates knew just how furious Sun Xiang was after the match. His mentality had been affected for several days in a row. Those who tried to console him only seemed to make it worse by striking the nail in deeper. Now, it motivated him to try even harder to prove his strength and directly make Ye Qiu and Han Wenqing concede.

Ye Qiu was now playing in game.

It was just in the game. With Sun Xiang’s arrogant personality, he normally wouldn’t put it in his eyes. However, in the previous spectacle, he had been there too. At that time, he had wanted to fight Ye Qiu. Unfortunately, Ye Qiu never gave anyone the chance to. After beating Huang Shaotian, he ran off, making Sun Xiang extremely upset.

Liu Hao had seen all of this and immediately used this to his advantage today.

When he handed over the Battle Mage account card to Sun Xiang, Liu Hao called a few others together. Half of Team Excellent Era was headed by him.

“Do we need this many people?” Sun Xiang heard Liu Hao call others to come and coldly scoffed.

“Ha ha, this is for fun. Everyone should have some fun together.” Liu Hao didn’t dare be careless with his words, especially with Sun Xiang. If not, Sun Xiang wouldn’t want anyone to help, which would completely mess up his plans.

After hearing Liu Hao say this, Sun Xiang didn’t say anything further.

Once everyone got together, they logged on. Their accounts were all max-level open accounts and were naturally in the Heavenly Domain. Liu Hao and Chen Yehui contacted each other and immediately organized this team.

Their characters were close to each other in the beginning, so they quickly found each other.

Battle Mage, Spellblade, Elementalist, Striker, Cleric.

This was their team’s class composition. When Liu Hao heard the opposing team had a Cleric, he didn’t dare to be careless. Along with himself, the team had Sun Xiang, He Ming, Shen Jian, and Zhang Jiaxin.

Among them, He Ming had a position somewhere in between the main team and the substitute players. He was often the team’s sixth player. The other four members were Excellent Era’s main force. If Su Mucheng could be called in to help, they would have made the team that they used in official matches.

Su Mucheng was obviously out of question. Plus, calling too many people would make it seem like he was scared of Ye Qiu. Even though Liu Hao didn’t mind being too careful, with Sun Xiang there, he was afraid Sun Xiang would be unhappy with it. Five players was the standard for a team in competitive play anyways. He didn’t think Sun Xiang would object to that.

Everything went as Liu Hao expected. Sun Xiang coldly humphed, but didn’t say anything else towards the team.

“Which way?” Sun Xiang wanted to hurry up and fight.

“Wilderness Town. I’m still trying to get an exact location.” Liu Hao said, while telling Chen Yehui to use everything he had to find Ye Qiu’s position.

Chen Yehui obviously complied. Ye Qiu had already gathered an incredibly strong team together with him. For their guild, if they sent too few players to fight them, they wouldn’t be opponents. If they sent too many, they wouldn’t be able to maneuver around and would be stuck in place. Chen Yehui felt gratified for Liu Hao coming to help so readily. As a result, he quickly assembled a ready-to-die team and told them to do everything in their power to figure out Ye Qiu’s location.

A ready-to-die team was essentially a suicide squad. Chen Yehui’s suicide squad consisted of individual units. If they saw Ye Qiu’s team, they would certainly die. In any case, they were to try and run. Once they died and became corpses, they were to stay there and monitor them. In short, they would constantly update Chen Yehui with Ye Qiu’s position.

By being made up of individual units, their scouting range would be enormous. Chen Yehui was willing to sacrifice his troops to achieve this. After organizing them together, he told them to hand over any important equipment they possessed to someone else for safekeeping. His message told them that the probability of dying was extremely high.

This team was aware of this and after receiving their orders, they immediately spread out.

This method was truly effective. One of the players heading east quickly made a report. He had found the seven players, who were running quickly. However, he didn’t know their goal.

Goal?

Chen Yehui didn’t care about their goal because the guild wasn’t going to be the one to fight them. His objective was very simple: to find their position and report to Liu Hao.

The first player to find the target was also quite lucky. He hadn’t been discovered, but this also meant he would have to continue watching them until he died.

This brother wouldn’t be so stupid as to get too close. He watched from far away, but as a result, he couldn’t see their IDs clearly. In the end, after seeing them make a turn, he ran over, but had already lost them. With his method of tailing, he would certainly lose them after a while.

But by finding their general location, Chen Yehui organized the others to narrow their search to that area. Soon, a second player caught sight of them again. However, this brother wasn’t as lucky and was discovered. After making a report, he valiantly sacrificed himself.

“Didn’t you say they gathered all of their troops together? Why are we still bumping into random players out here then? They’re alone too.” Loulan Slash asked after cutting this player down.

“They couldn’t pinpoint our positions, so they probably sent out a ready-to-die team to find out our positions at the cost of their lives.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then we’ve been exposed already.” Loulan Slash said.

“For now, yes, but it’s not like we’re just going to stand there stupidly and do nothing, no?” Ye Xiu said.

The seven players continued moving ahead. Chen Yehui continuously received reports of their location from the sacrificed players. These seven players just seemed to be wandering around randomly. He couldn’t figure out their next step.

Chen Yehui sent Clerics over to revive them and then had them continue scouting.

Whenever Chen Yehui received a set of coordinates, he would send them over to Liu Hao. Liu Hao and the other pro players quickly arrived in Wilderness Town. The randomly changing coordinates made them helpless too. They could only run towards the coordinates sent to them.

Arisaema and Changing Spring hadn’t given up yet and had their huge army walk around through Wilderness Town and see if they could bump into them. The two would sometimes let out sighs. Chen Yehui didn’t have the energy to deal with these two. He had five seniors from the team calling for him!

After not seeing any results for a while, Chen Yehui was starting to get anxious, so he secretly sent more players to scout around. This time, two scouts found the opposing team simultaneously. With more scouts, the reports began coming in faster and Liu Hao’s side now had a sense of direction to head in.

“Have you guys noticed something? Everyone we’ve killed so far has been from Excellent Dynasty.” Little Bei suddenly spoke up.

“Really?” Ocean Ahead replied lazily. It had always been one target at a time and the targets never showed any resistance either. They would run as soon as they were discovered. It felt so pointless now. In the beginning, it had been fun, annihilating team after team, but now it felt like the big feast was over and dessert was being given a tiny nibble at a time.

“Be careful, they’ve upped their scouting.” Ye Xiu said, “Reinforcements must have come, so they have more players at their disposal.”

“Yeah, don’t get careless!” Loulan Slash was their Heavenly Justice’s leader and was calmer than the others.

“Yo yo, there’s a team over there!” Little Bei suddenly realized.

“Hm?” Ocean Ahead heard this and grew excited. His character moved around in a circle, trying to find the enemy team.

“It’s only five players……” But after seeing the team, Ocean Ahead couldn’t hide his disappointment.

“It’s still better than a single person.” Little Bei shrugged.

“A simple matter nonetheless.” Ocean Ahead commented.

“Be careful.” Ye Xiu’s voice was solemn though

“Is it some sort of trap?” Loulan Slash asked.

“Be careful when facing them.” Ye Xiu didn’t give a direct reply.

The five players at the end of the street also saw the seven players and immediately charged at them. Seeing this, the seven players immediately felt like something wasn’t right because their enemies had always ran for their lives as soon as they were discovered, even if they were a team of ten players. However, it was just a five player team now, yet they were actually rushing forward instead of retreating. The enemy should have a grasp of their strength, but they still dared to do this…...

“They can’t be weak.” Loulan Slash concluded.

“Even if they’re strong, how strong could they be?” Ocean Ahead asked.

“Could there be some sort of ambush lying in wait?” The Cleric, Thousand Falling Leaves, wondered.

“There shouldn’t be any. The enemy has been trying to find our location this entire time, so they wouldn’t have had enough time to set up an ambush.” Ye Xiu said.

“Which means they must be experts!” Loulan Slash turned serious.

“Good!” Ocean Ahead grew excited. This Battle Mage loved to fight.

Chapter 491 – Strong Enemies!

“Brothers, forward!” Ocean Ahead shouted and led the charge. This clearly wasn’t an action an Elementalist should be doing. Elementalists might have powerful spells, but they usually hid behind others for protection.

“Slow down!” Loulan Slash hastily caught up to him and used his body to force him back. Ye Qiu told them to be careful because their opponents were strong. Ocean Ahead not only didn’t listen to the warning, but he became even more excited. Loulan Slash understood his personality well, so despite being upset, he couldn’t do anything about it.

“Let them come to us. We’ll wait here and save our stamina.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Little Bei, Night Tide.” Loulan Slash called out. These two characters stepped forward. All three of them were melee classes, so they usually fought up front.

Ocean Ahead could only move backwards obediently. The staff in his hand never stopped waving around though. Ye Xiu watched all of this and knew that he was impatiently waiting, ready to attack at any time.

Ye Xiu chuckled. Even though he was playing the role of a gunner on this team with long-ranged attacks, seeing how excited Ocean Ahead was, he decided to let him make the first move. Ye Xiu feared that if he made the first move, Ocean Ahead would recklessly waste skills or charge forward.

“Heavenly Lightning! Little Bei, jump!” Ye Xiu suddenly yelled.

“They’re coming!!” Ocean Ahead shouted as he lifted up his staff. If a noob saw this, the noob might think that it was too early to cast a spell. However, Ocean Ahead was a great expert and knew that when Ye Xiu made this command, he had considered the enemy’s movement speed as well as his cast time. Casting the spell at this moment was perfect.

“Jump?” Little Bei hesitated, but he still jumped without wasting any time.

“To block his staff.” Ye Xiu smiled.

“D*mn…..” Little Bei thought it would be for this reason. He was positioned right in front of Ocean Ahead. When an Elementalist casted a spell, the staff would point towards a certain location, indicating where the spell would land. An experienced opponent could determine the spell’s target by observing the staff’s movement. Ye Xiu had Little Bei jump up in order to block the enemy’s view of the staff, stopping them from figuring out the spell’s target. He might be able to block the enemy’s view of the Elementalist too, so they wouldn’t even know that the Elementalist was casting a spell.

Bang!!

Thunder boomed from the skies and gray clouds billowed forth as lightning flashed down. The ground below glowed red and it seemed as if the land had turned transparent. Bang! Bang! Bang! The red earth cracked open and flames rushed out.

Level 70 Elementalist skill, Heavenly Thunder Earthen Fire, a damaging attack with both lightning and fire properties.

Lines of lightning and fire intertwined with each other like a network along the street. The scene looked like the coming of an apocalypse. If the people inside didn’t die, then it wouldn’t match the fiery visual effects.

Ye Xiu didn’t give out any orders as he watched the area in which the skill targeted. The figures inside the crackling fire and lightning were difficult to see. However, they were still moving forward at high speeds.

“They’re looking to die!” Ocean Ahead was astonished.

Heavenly Thunder Earthen Fire was a persistent effect skill. Lightning and fire erupted randomly within the skill’s area of effect. Each bolt of lightning or flare of fire dealt damage. If a player stood still inside the area and didn’t move, he might take less damage than moving about. Experienced players would usually stand still and wait for the spell to end. However, the enemies were unexpectedly charging through it. Ocean Ahead was naturally surprised at their actions.

In the blink of an eye, a figure broke through the circle of fire and lightning. This person didn’t have any burn marks on him. Ocean Ahead stared with his mouth wide open. Similar to how there would be blood if a character was hit by a blade or bullet, spells also had some sort of visual indication if a character had been struck by one, but this person had absolutely no marks on him, which meant he hadn’t been hit by any of the lightning or fire.

“How is that possible?” Ocean Ahead gaped. This enemy had clearly been inside the Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire and Battle Mages didn’t have any instant movement skills. At best, Battle Mages had the movement speed buff from Neutral Chasers.

The Battle Mage in front of them had a full set of equipment. White, red, yellow, blue, and purple magic undulations circled around his feet, arms, hands, spear tip, and spear handle. These magic undulations were five types of Chasers buffing his character. He was the first person to break through the Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire and his battle spirit wasn’t any weaker than Ocean Ahead’s.

“For Heavenly Lightning Earthen Blaze, you need to be able to practice until you can manually control it.” Ye Xiu wasn’t surprised by the Battle Mage like everyone else had been. Instead, he took this opportunity to give Ocean Ahead a lesson.

“Ah?” Ocean Ahead stared blankly. After casting the spell, the targeting for the lightning and fire could be manually controlled. However, the skill was strong enough already with just the system’s automatic targeting, so oftentimes, Elementalists would use this chance to send out other spells for extra poke damage. Ocean Ahead also felt like this made sense and it didn’t seem like very many players in the pro scene controlled it manually either.

In this short amount of time, the Battle Mage had already closed in. A Battle Mage with Neutral Chasers had astonishingly high movement speed.

Loulan Slash, Little Bei, and Night Tide jumped forward to intercept him. Loulan Slash swung his sword, using Colliding Stab to see if he could knock the enemy Battle Mage back into the Heavenly Lightning. Such a simple move would never hit an expert under normal circumstances. However, Loulan Slash wasn’t alone. To the left, Little Bei’s Battle Mage threw out a Falling Flower Palm. To the right, Night Tide’s Grappler slammed the ground to create a shockwave.

The combined attacks of the three covered a huge range. The enemy Battle Mage didn’t move away and met Loulan Slash’s Colliding Stab head on. Just before the attack was about to hit, the enemy Battle Mage suddenly jumped.

This jump allowed the enemy to dodge the shock wave, but Colliding Stab was a flexible move. As soon as Loulan Slash saw the enemy leap up, he swung his mouse and his Swordpoint swung upwards towards the Battle Mage.

“Roll back!!!” Ye Xiu shouted.

“What?” The three up front felt unsure who he was talking to.

“Could he be talking about me?” After all, Loulan Slash was the person directly facing the opponent, so he reckoned Ye Qiu was warning him. He didn’t have any doubts about Ye Qiu, so he hastily rolled backwards, but because of this slight moment of hesitation, he had done it slightly too slow.

The enemy’s spear stabbed forward like a viper. Even though Loulan Slash’s Swordpoint had swung upwards, it had missed the enemy by just a tiny bit. The enemy’s spear had a longer range, so the spear stabbed straight through his body.

Like a gale, the spear tossed him up into the air and then slammed him back into the ground in a circular arc. Circle Swing was a move that forcefully knocked the target onto the ground and couldn’t be teched out of with a Quick Recover.

When Loulan Slash crashed into the ground, the enemy Battle Mage also landed. He retracted his spear and stepped forward. Then, he suddenly turned around and stabbed twice. Two cold lights flew to his left and right.

“F*ck!!!” Little Bei gaped. He was a Battle Mage too and could tell this move was the low level skill Double Stab. However, this enemy Battle Mage had actually been able to split the two stabs, one for each person. This required extremely high mechanical skill to achieve, especially since Little Bei and Night Tide weren’t next to each other! Little Bei had never imagined Double Stab could be mastered to such a level.

Pu! Pu! The attack had been too sudden. Neither of them had been able to react in time. Double Stab had a small knockback effect. The attack had been split into two, so the effects were halved, but the two were both pushed back half a body’s length. The enemy Battle Mage had already turned around, so he was facing forward. He no longer had his four allies nearby to cover for him. His Battle Mage pushed his palms out with a Falling Flower Palm.

Deception reacted quickly and shot towards him. His body turned around in midair and kicked out using Bird Fall.

This skill was very fast. The direction of the attack could be controlled by the user. When Deception used this on other players, it always connected.

“Bang!”

Falling Flower Palm shot out.

At the same time, Deception stepped on the enemy Battle Mage’s shoulder. His Bird Fall had hit the opponent, but it hadn’t been able to interrupt the Falling Flower Palm. Fortunately, the Bird Fall had been able to delay the palm, giving Ocean Ahead enough time to jump back and dodge the attack.

Deception was about to slide down the Battle Mage’s back after stepping on his shoulder. At the same time, he flung the rope on his ninjato out in preparation to activate a Body Bind Technique.

“Dodge!” Deception heard Lord Grim shout, but was puzzled by the warning. Suddenly, the tip of a spear flashed and his body was launched into the air. Following afterwards, a flurry of magic chasers barraged him.

Boom boom boom boom boom!!!!!

Magic chasers continued to chain into each other as Deception tumbled higher and higher into the air.

At this moment, lightning and fire crossed over each other in front again. The enemy’s Elementalist had also cast a Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire. Loulan Slash, Little Bei, and Night Tide were instantly enveloped by the spell. Several figures broke through Ocean Ahead’s Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire and entered their own.

The lightning and fire made everything a blur. The thunder’s booms covered up the sounds of attacks. Soon afterwards, three figures flew out from the storm. Loulan Slash, Little Bei, and Night Tide had been pushed out from the spell.

Loulan Slash and Night Tide crouched on the ground after using a Quick Recover. Little Bei fell face first into the dirt and slid to Lord Grim’s feet. The opponents had used an untechable skill.

A ball of lightning formed and floated in the air as it crackled. The three saw this and grew alarmed.

Spellblade skill: Electric Wave Formation!

Chapter 492 – Sun Xiang’s Dragon Raising Its Head

In the confrontation between the two teams, Ocean Ahead might have been the first to make an attack, but it resulted in his own team being swept away.

Loulan Slash, Little Bei, and Night Tide were thrown into the enemy’s Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire and then knocked back out.

Deception may have hit his intended target with Bird Fall, but it wasn’t because his opponent couldn’t dodge it. Rather, his opponent didn’t feel the need to dodge it. Following afterwards, his opponent’s rapid attacks quickly broke through Deception’s own follow-up attacks. The magic chasers exploded, sending him tumbling through the air and into a wall.

Ocean Ahead had been blown back by the Falling Flower Palm. Neither him nor the Cleric had yet to take damage, but they no longer had any protection from the frontline. The enemy Battle Mage had completely exposed the backline and he posed a heavy threat to them.

In this brief exchange, the other four enemies hadn’t even arrived in front of them yet and their formation had already been destroyed.

Now, an Electric Wave Formation had been placed.

The crackling electric ball was storing up energy. The Spellblade was casting this spell. As soon as he finished channelling, the electric ball would expand, creating a circular sphere, where enemy players inside would take electric damage over time. The spell couldn’t be dodged, whether one went into the air or underground. The only way to escape from the attack was to get out of the Electric Wave Formation’s effective range.

A max skilled Electric Wave Formation had a radius of 15 body units. With the team in complete disarray and the enemy Battle Mage completely controlling the situation, it would be very difficult for them to escape this attack.

At this moment, Ye Xiu finally acted.

He leaped into the air and his Thousand Chance Umbrella opened up. Ta ta ta ta! A stream of bullets shot into the Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire.

A faint curse could be heard amidst the loud thunder. The electric ball suddenly shook. Everyone’s hearts tightened, but the electricity didn’t burst out. Zi! Like a power outage, the electric ball blinked and dispersed.

The veterans obviously knew this was because the Spellblade’s attack had been interrupted. The Spellblade had been hiding inside the Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire, but Lord Grim had still been able to hit him.

Meanwhile, Ocean Ahead and Thousand Falling Leaves were frantically running. They had seen how terrifying this Battle Mage was. This Battle Mage had broken through the Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire completely unharmed. What did this mean? It meant that he had dodged the random attacks from the Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire with inhuman reactions and hand speed. Then, he leaped into the midst of their entire team, sent four of them flying, and even sent Ocean Ahead a palm. Ocean Ahead and Thousand Falling Leaves had no close combat capabilities. Why would they dare to stay still and fight?

But this Battle Mage didn’t even glance at the two of them. He stepped forward with his spear pointing directly at Lord Grim. With the distance between them, this spear was way too far away to hit him, but at the same time, magic waves emanated out from the spear, forming a dragon --- Battle Mage Level 70 skill, Rising Dragon Soars the Sky.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim dodged to the side. Even though this Rising Dragon Soars the Sky had a long attack range, if it didn’t have the proper set-up for it, with such a large distance between the target, it would only be able to hit in theory. However, there was more than enough time for the target to dodge. Lord Grim didn’t seem flustered at all and leisurely headed towards the side.

Who would have thought that the magically formed dragon would suddenly shake its head to the side and bite down on Lord Grim. All of the magic waves poured into Lord Grim and with a dazzling explosion, Lord Grim was blasted flying away.

“Are you kidding me!!!!” Little Bei had just gotten up from the ground and his eyes almost popped out seeing this scene.

Dragon Raises Its Head!!!

Not just Little Bei, but everyone else recognized it too. When this Rising Dragon Soars the Sky flew out, the dragon clearly twisted its head. It was reputed that only Ye Qiu alone could perform this variation of the move, Dragon Raises Its Head!

Lord Grim was only a Level 52 character and his equipment was lacking too. The damage he took certainly wouldn’t be light after being hit directly by a Level 70 skill. He used a Quick Recover and landed on the ground steadily.

“Who are you?” Little Bei shouted.

To be able to perform such a mighty Dragon Raises Its Head, could this Battle Mage be the real Ye Qiu? Could this Lord Grim actually be a fake? Little Bei wondered.

“Sun Xiang.” Sun Xiang’s tone was filled with arrogance. He was very satisfied with how this Dragon Raises Its Head had turned out, especially with it being able to hit Ye Qiu. This was a scene he had dreamed of countless times and the dream had turned into a reality. Unfortunately, the scene took place in a random street in game. There weren’t any spectators watching. If this had taken place in the All Star Competition, how great would that have been?

As soon as this name came out, Loulan Slash and the others immediately stood there stupidly. A God! What an amazing practice today turned out to be. After taking down the little thieves, the boss came out?

“Who’s that? Is he good?”

At this moment, Deception came down from the wall and asked.

“Bro, seriously? Did you buy this your account?” Loulan Slash asked incredulously. Deception was very infamous. As players in the game, they obviously knew who he was. They had never interacted with him before though. Today, because of Ye Xiu, they were fighting together as allies, but they hadn’t talked to him much, b. But Deception actually didn’t know who Sun Xiang was, which made everyone very astonished. They wanted to doubt him, but then again, he showed the skill to back up his name. They had seen Deception’s capabilities while fighting alongside him. He wasn’t any weaker than them.

“You really don’t know?” Ye Xiu was also surprised. Deception didn’t know about him, so he probably didn’t pay much attention to the news nor any drama floating around. He didn’t have any friends either, so it would make sense if he didn’t know about him, but to not even know the name of a God like Sun Xiang? That was strange for an expert like him. Could he actually be someone who only cared about himself and didn’t care about anyone else?

“Why should I know?” Deception asked in return.

“You’re just pretending.” Sun Xiang laughed coldly. Deception had been the only one to hit him, so his skill obviously wasn’t bad. Sun Xiang doubted such an expert didn’t know a God like him.

“How’d you like the taste of my Dragon Raises Its Head? It’s not bad, right?” Sun Xiang ignored the pretending guy. He only had Ye Qiu in his eyes. He thought he could easily succeed him, but his ghost always seemed to be haunting him.

“Mm, not bad.” Ye Xiu seemed to be as calm as ever. Beside him though, a girl had cried out loudly. This girl was Chen Guo, of course. She wasn’t happy at all about Sun Xiang’s Dragon Raises its Head. She had originally been indifferent towards Sun Xiang, but after knowing about the details about Ye Xiu’s release from Excellent Era, she now hated him. And now, Sun Xiang was actually able to perform Dragon Raises Its Head. Chen Guo didn’t feel comfortable knowing this.

“How talented. You couldn’t do it in the All Star Competition yet, no?” Ye Xiu continued.

“You’re right, but now I can do it even better than you.” Sun Xiang said. After returning from the All Star Competition, he had gone through intense practice and research before mastering Dragon Raises Its Head. In addition, after comparing it to Ye Qiu’s previous uses of the move, Sun Xiang was certain his Dragon Raises Its Head had an even greater range than Ye Qiu’s.

“So what?” Ye Xiu said.

“......” Sun Xiang was stumped. He had done something even Ye Qiu couldn’t do and felt extremely happy about it. However, Ye Qiu himself didn’t seem to think much of it. It was like punching cotton, not satisfactory at all!

“So what? Ha ha, this means you’re already of the past. Did you really think your little show off of Dragon Raises Its Head in the All Star Competition would be enough to make others not forget about you? But now, you’ve already been completely replaced. What else can you do to prove yourself?” The Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire faded away and four characters walked out. The one who replied to Ye Xiu was the Spellblade, Liu Hao.

Lord Grim turned around slightly. Ye Xiu glanced at them, but simply repeated himself: “So what?”

“Hmph! You’re pretending!” Liu Hao also choked slightly at Ye Xiu’s response and then used Sun Xiang’s line.

“I really hope to see how long you’ll be able to keep on lying to yourself like that.” Liu Hao continued. Liu Hao’s skill in provoking others was at a higher level than Sun Xiang’s.

“He Ming? Shen Jian? Zhang Jiaxing?” Ye Xiu looked at the enemy’s classes and guessed their identities.

Loulan Slash and the others sucked in a cold breath. This was Excellent Era’s main team! That Spellblade was probably Excellent Era’s vice captain, Liu Hao. This was the pro team’s main roster! Their equipment was just slightly lacking.

“Sorry, Ye. Today, we’re going to have to play as pigs and eat the tiger.” He Ming said.

“Play as pigs and eat the tiger?” Ye Xiu laughed, “It won’t be that easy! Do you know what it means to play as pigs and eat the tiger?”

“Ye, your actions in the tenth server can be considered as playing as a pig and eating the tiger.” He Ming calmly answered.

“It looks like you don’t understand it well enough.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh? Then, please give us a lesson.” He Ming said.

“To play as a pig and eat the tiger, the tiger has to do his part too. If a pig plays as a pig, then the pig can’t even try to eat the tiger.” Ye Xiu said.

“You……”

“It’s just an analogy. You don’t need to assign roles to it.” Ye Xiu smiled.

“Ignore him. He’s good at this sort of trash talk.” Liu Hao said in a low voice. He didn’t care about Ye Xiu’s mocking.

“Who’s the pig? Who’s the tiger? We’re about to find out.” Sun Xiang said.

“Are you guys really pro players? We have the absolute advantage. Do you guys actually not see that?” Ye Xiu said.

“What?” Let alone Excellent Era’s players, even Loulan Slash’s group stared stupidly at these words.

“We have more people.” Ye Xiu said.

TL:To play as a pig and eat the tiger comes from a story. A hunter is tasked by a village with killing a tiger. The hunter is unable to do so with force, so he learns to how to oink like a pig. The tiger hears the oinking and thinks there is prey nearby. The hunter lures the tiger over in this way and then launches a sneak attack, when the tiger least expects it. The tiger may not have immediately died, but it is gravely injured. The hunter finishes off the wounded tiger and brings the dead tiger back to the village.

Chapter 493 – Valuable Reverse Teaching

“We have more people on our side……”

Excellent Era’s side had a standard five player team. Ye Xiu’s side had a total of seven players which included Deception, Lord Grim, and Loulan Slash’s team. From a numbers perspective, Ye Xiu’s side had the advantage.

However, playing Glory was never as simple as counting numbers. Having a numbers advantage didn’t guarantee a victory. Just before, seven players had easily annihilated twenty five players. It would be too embarrassing to think about things in this way. Apart from Ye Xiu himself, everyone else was dumbstruck by Ye Xiu’s words, even Chen Guo.

“Ha ha ha ha.” Sun Xiang was the first to recover from the shock and let out a few loud laughs. However, his laugh seemed somewhat forced. Then, he continued: “Don’t blame me for being too blunt, but with just these guys, what can you do?”

Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage turned around in a circle and looked down at the few players around him.

If this was before Loulan Slash’s group had met Ye Xiu, they would have certainly been furious, but after getting to know Ye Xiu, in nicer words, they recognized the skill gap between them and their future opponents. In harsher words, the skill gap was far greater than they had expected. They had somewhat lost their confidence. Sun Xiang was looking down on them right now, but none of them said in anything in response because they recognized their inferiority…...

“So what!”

Someone retorted though. Deception. After being smashed into a wall, Deception rushed forward and threw shurikens in a V formation towards Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage. The theory was the same as the Launcher’s triangular formation of Anti-Tank Missiles.

Sun Xiang humphed coldly. This sort of little technique wasn’t anything in his eyes. This guy pretended to not know him and was now shouting back at him? He would give him a good look at reality. After seeing the three shurikens, he tapped his keyboard and moved his mouse. His Battle Mage swung his spear in a V shape.

“V Sky Strike!” Little Bei cried out in astonishment. This was an extremely advanced Battle Mage technique, which he had yet to master. After Sun Xiang created a Z with his spear, the spear tip hit all three shurikens in an instant and knocked them on the ground. Sun Xiang had clearly mastered this technique. No matter how much Little Bei detested him, he had to admit his loss here.

But with his current circumstances, this technique was completely excessive.

Excessive movements would expose openings. Deception wouldn’t let this go. His figure shook and left behind a Shadow Clone. His real body instantly travelled to Sun Xiang’s side and a blade slashed against his throat ---- the Assassin skill, Cut Throat.

In terms of speed, Assassins were the king compared to the rest of the classes. However, this skill actually missed. Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage had rolled forward, dodging the blade. Before even getting up, the spear in his hand stabbed backwards.

Attacking behind oneself was possible in Glory. It wasn’t difficult to do, but more importantly, the player had no vision behind him, so the player had to completely rely on his own judgement of where the opponent was positioned.

Sun Xiang perfectly predicted Deception’s position as if he had an eye on the back of his head.

However, Deception didn’t react slowly either. When the spear stabbed towards him, he suddenly disappeared.

Underground Tunneling Technique!

As soon as Deception dug into the ground, he immediately tunneled out. Just as his character broke out through the ground, Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage leapt up high into the air and swung his spear. It was a very simple Dragon Tooth, but Deception had no way to dodge it. After the Dragon Tooth hit, Deception was stunned and could no longer move. His Underground Tunneling Technique was interrupted and half his body was stuck underground. Sun Xiang followed up with a Circle Swing and threw Deception out from the earth to the side.

“Bang!” The sound of a gunshot.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim shot out a Stun Bullet.

However, Sun Xiang clearly hadn’t been entirely focused on his battle with Deception. He only had one goal. Whether it was Deception or Loulan Slash, both of them were simply weeds on the side of the road, not worth looking at.

Thus, he immediately knew Ye Xiu had made an attack.

It was a good opportunity to use a Stun Bullet. A normal player would have most likely gotten hit by the bullet mid Circle Swing. However, Sun Xiang was nowhere near a normal player and this sort of opportunity wouldn’t be enough.

Sun Xiang forcefully cancelled his Circle Swing and stepped slightly to the side to dodge the bullet, but because he cancelled his Circle Swing, the effects wouldn’t be complete. Deception was tossed out from the earth, but he wasn’t slammed back into the ground. He quickly Quick Recovered and landed in a crouching position.

Ye Xiu’s follow ups arrived. After the Stun Bullet came Anti-Tank Missiles. The three Anti-Tank Missiles covered a huge area.

However, no matter how huge of an area it covered, they were only Anti-Tank Missiles. Against an expert like Sun Xiang, it wouldn’t be enough. His Battle Mage leapt up like a fish and squeezed his way out from a crack between the missiles, but a Grenade was already flying towards his face. Ye Xiu had linked together two Gunner skills.

Sun Xiang swung his spear at the grenade and sent it flying away as if it were a baseball.

This was absolutely terrifying.

Grenades could be blocked in this manner, but they would usually explode on contact. Sun Xiang had hit it away, but it hadn’t exploded, which meant the moment his spear made contact with the grenade, he decreased his strength. To be able to do this meant his microing had reached an incomprehensible degree.

“This guy really has some skill……” Even Chen Guo had to respect his skill.

“What’s up?” Tang Rou had been called over by Chen Guo to watch.

After Chen Guo gave her an explanation, Tang Rou asked: “Is that necessary?”

“Ha ha ha ha!” This time, Ye Xiu laughed out loud. His laugh wasn’t as fake as Sun Xiang’s. It was real laughter. Then, he continued: “You’re right. It wasn’t necessary at all. Too many excessive movements will leave too many openings.”

“Really? You just seem to be watching these openings pass by then!” Sun Xiang replied.

“Sorry, I wasn’t talking to you. However, I have to express my thanks. You’re extremely valuable as teaching material! Keep up the good work!” Ye Xiu honestly admitted.

Sun Xiang was so furious that his face went green. Liu Hao couldn’t do anything either. He really did want to tell Sun Xiang that he should just fight. For something like trash talking, a rooke like him, with only two years under his belt, couldn’t compare to an experienced veteran like Ye Qiu.

The grenade that Sun Xiang had sent flying exploded who knows where. Lord Grim finally stopped shooting from far away and charged forward to clash with Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage.

Liu Hao and the others watched from the side, but didn’t interfere. Loulan Slash’s group didn’t move either. They wouldn’t interfere either, but hoped that Ye Xiu would win. After their brief exchange with Excellent Era’s pros, their momentum had been completely diminished. Seeing Sun Xiang’s brilliant performance, their hearts turned heavier and heavier.

Collapsing Mountain!

Ye Xiu initiated with this skill. Lord Grim leaped into the air and swung downwards. Even though it didn’t do much damage as a low-leveled skill, the effects were quite impressive. The momentum from the Collapsing Mountain wouldn’t lose to anyone else’s.

Sun Xiang stepped once diagonally. He was still being cautious.

Collapsing Mountain didn’t have to attack along a straight path. Experts could use their mouse to cause their blade to turn in mid-air and force the path onto a diagonal path. Sun Xiang negated this option with his step forward. Afterwards, he leaped out and stabbed at Lord Grim.

The jump was to dodge Collapsing Mountain’s shockwave. Collapsing Mountain could also be considered a small AoE attack. Normal players would usually jump out of its range, but experts would jump over the shockwave and counterattack.

Ye Xiu had predicted this would happen. He had started the Collapsing Mountain very low, so he landed quickly. Before the spear came at him, he had already landed and rolled to the side, while slashing out with a Sword Draw.

Sun Xiang immediately stabbed again with his spear. Two cold glints shot out ---- Double Stab.

“Dong!”

Sun Xiang had used Double Stab to block the Sword Draw. Sword Draw was an extremely quick skill. Blocking the attack in this way required exceptional judgement of the sword light’s pathing. Sun Xiang had actually been able to hit it with a Double Stab. This wasn't something that could be done purely through quick decision-making or mechanics. It required an understanding of the opponent’s attack speed too.

“You’ve done your research!” Ye Xiu grinned. Sun Xiang must have studied his recordings.

“Unfortunately, it’s an unnecessary activity. You’re still good teaching material!” Ye Xiu lamented. He wasn’t in the pro scene anymore, so he had no competitive relationship with Sun Xiang. If Sun Xiang’s efforts in research him weren’t superfluous, then what were they?

“Shut up!” Sun Xiang continued with his arrogance and followed up with an attack. Ye Xiu had started with a Collapsing Mountain and then a Sword Draw. Sun Xiang’s Double Stab attacked twice. The first stab blocked the Sword Draw. The second stab was still an attack and it instantly became a priority move.

“The ground!” At this moment, Liu Hao suddenly shouted.

Sun Xiang heard the warning and was just about to retreat, when he saw countless streams of water swarm around him. His retreat path had been cut off by the water streams too. He had unexpectedly been captured by the Ninja’s Hundred Streams.

“DESPICABLE!!” Sun Xiang was furious. Even though the attack hadn’t hurt him, being sneak attacked like this wasn’t something he could bear.

“You aren’t the only one playing Glory! How many times have I told you guys this? It looks like you guys still don’t understand! It looks like I have no choice. Even though I’m no longer your captain, I’ll give you guys a lesson for free! You people over there, where’d your spirit go! This isn’t an arena competition. This is a team competition!” Ye Xiu shouted. The latter words were for Loulan Slash’s group to hear.

Chapter 494 – Sneak Attack Cover Up

As Loulan Slash listened to Ye Xiu, he couldn’t help but be doubtful. Even though he had heard the battle of words between Ye Xiu and Sun Xiang, he would soon be joining the pro scene, so he had a certain understanding of the meaning of these words. These words could be considered as a type of psychological battle. As a result, trash talk usually wasn’t treated as truth.

However, Ye Xiu’s tone of voice sounded as if it really was the truth. Did he really think they could beat an actual pro team with just themselves?

Even though Excellent Era didn’t have a good record this season, a lean camel was still bigger than a horse. No pro team dared to think that Excellent Era would be a free win. Now, a God and the previous captain of Excellent Era said these words.

“Ha ha ha ha, really……”

Bang bang bang bang!

The sounds of repeated gunfire.

Liu Hao also wanted to say a few words, but how could he know Ye Xiu would just immediately start firing after speaking. Liu Hao couldn’t just stand there talking, while taking bullets. Ye Xiu didn’t stop there. Lord Grim held the Thousand Chance Umbrella in a straight line and continued to shoot. The Thousand Chance Umbrella’s gun form was a rifle. In Glory, rifles weren’t automatic and their firerate couldn’t even be compared to handguns. Every wave only consisted of two bullets, but each bullet had a more range and a stronger force than handguns.

Just like this, Lord Grim’s repeated firing forced Liu Hao to swallow what he was about to say. Everyone stared dumbly at the scene. A moment later, someone said: “So we’re starting?”

“Hurry up and get me out of here!” Sun Xiang impatiently shouted. No matter how much of a God he was, it wasn’t like he could break the game’s rules. The water prison created by Hundred Streams couldn’t be broken from the inside.

Excellent Era’s side responded. He Ming’s Elementalist lifted up his staff, when Lord Grim suddenly switched targets from Liu Hao’s Spellblade to him. He Ming was also a pro player, so he saw it and immediately dodged the bullet. However, his channeling had been interrupted. Liu Hao wasn’t a weakling either though. Seeing an opening appear, he raised his sword as fire began to swirl around his body ---- Spellblade skill: Firewave Sword.

There were four elements in Glory: Fire, Ice, Light, and Dark. Battle Mage chasers, Elementalist spells, Ghostblade formations, Spellblade wave swords, and wave formations were all elemental skills. Apart from these, some skills were non-elemental. Elemental skills had an extra effect to them compared to non-elemental skills. By using equipment and other skills, the elemental damage could be increased. However, at the same time, there was also equipment with elemental resistance. Thus, elemental skills aren’t necessarily better than non-elemental skills. It depended on the circumstance.

The four elements were also connected. Fire and ice were a pair. Light and dark were the other. Opposing elements did additional damage. Similar elements did decreased damage.

For example, fire versus ice or ice versus fire would do increased damage to each other. Fire versus fire or ice versus ice did less damage to each other. The actual numbers depends on the elemental buffs and resistances between the two opposing sides.

Liu Hao’s Firewave Sword was a high damage skill. The fire spiralled towards the water prison. Even though the water prison was made of water, it was still categorized as an Ice elemental skill. As a result, the fire attack would do increased damage to it. This attack wouldn’t be enough to instantly destroy the water prison, but Liu Hao followed the attack with another wave sword.

Excellent Era’s other two players weren’t just standing by idly. Shen Jian’s Striker had no long ranged capabilities, so he charged forward towards Deception. As for Zhang Jiaxin, his Cleric was a support class. The battle had just begun though, so his team hadn’t taken much damage yet. His opponents didn’t have any buffs on them either, so there was no point trying to dispel them. He would be useless and alone for now.

As for Ye Xiu’s side, as soon as their Cleric Falling Thousand Leaves saw the battle start, she also began to get busy despite being unconfident in herself. Her side had people with tons of injuries. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had just eaten a full Rising Dragon Soars the Sky not long before and had lost a large chunk of his health.

“What are you all waiting for? When you begin a pro match and you see the enemy coming, you’re not just going to stand there, are you?” Ye Xiu saw that his words didn’t seem to have much of an effect on them and gave them a scolding.

This time, Loulan Slash and the others finally woke up and felt ashamed at how little confidence they had. They might not be able to compete with their opponents, but they couldn’t lose their spirit because of this. How would they be able to survive in the pro scene with such weak mentality?

“Heavenly Lightning!” Ye Xiu began to lead the team.

“Where?” Ocean Ahead was a bit slow. This was a common issue in new teams. If the leader’s calls couldn’t be understood quickly and had to be explained in detail, then the opportunity might be lost. When someone joined a team, people would talk about adjusting to the team. What did they mean by adjusting? Solving this issue.

Ye Xiu was currently an outsider in Loulan Slash’s team, but his words held power. RIght now, he was the team’s shotcaller. It was easy to bully weaker opponents because the calls were simple and easy to understand. However, in a high level battle with skilled opponents who had more practiced tactics, Ocean Ahead clearly didn’t know the purpose of using Heavenly Lightning Earthen Blaze. He had finished casting it, but he didn’t know where to throw it towards.

“Wherever there’s people……” Ye Xiu didn’t have time to say too much. It didn’t take much to say it, but the battle was constantly shifting. This wasn’t a single-player game where he could press pause and explain.

With these words, Ocean Ahead threw out his Heavenly Lightning towards a location with many enemies. At the same time, Ye Xiu reflected on his shotcalling. He couldn’t be too blunt and direct with them!

“If you were able to control your Heavenly Lightning Earthen Blaze, you would be able to maintain that water prison for a while longer.” Ye Xiu said and gave Ocean Ahead a pointer.

The Heavenly Lightning Earthen Blaze enveloped the water prison. Liu Hao had to dodge the attacks from the spell, so he couldn’t attack the water prison directly. However, the lightning and fire from the spell hit the water prison and assisted in breaking it. The water prison could be broken by anyone’s attacks, even those on the same team as the caster.

As soon as Sun Xiang broke free from the prison, his first thought was to find Deception, but under the cover of the Heavenly Lightning, he wasn’t able to see everything clearly. Sun Xiang decided to exit the range of the Heavenly Lightning first. He quickly reacted to the lightning and fire to dodge them. Right when he was about to break out of the area, a ray of light suddenly flashed in front of him. The light definitely wasn’t an effect of the Heavenly Lightning Earthen Blaze.

Loulan Slash’s Berserker was guarding this spot. This ray of light wasn’t actually a ray of light, but a bloody mist. It was the Berserker skill, Crimson Storm.

At this moment, the move had reached its peak. The huge blood blade was already just about to cut apart Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage. No matter how fast Sun Xiang was, he wouldn’t be able to break through it, so he hastily rolled back. Because of this, he wasn’t able to break out from the Heavenly Lightning and even took a few hits. However, the damage from it was much negligible compared to how much he would have taken if the Crimson Storm had hit him.

The blood blade crashed towards the ground and burst apart, mixing together with the Heavenly Lightning Earthen Blaze. Sun Xiang didn’t care about this though. He had just dodged the Blood Blade, when he saw a cold light fly towards him and felt a sense of imminent danger.

Sun Xiang was more than familiar with this effect.

This was the Battle Mage skill, Dragon Breaks the Ranks. The skill had actually been waiting for him to come.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks shot forward in a straight line. Battle Mages were a class with both physical and magic skills at their disposal. Although this skill didn’t do any magic damage, it had a magic effect. The shining light at the tip of the spear expanded into a wide circle, similar to how Falling Flower Palm hit opponents near the palm as well.

It was too late to dodge. Dragon Breaks the Ranks attacked all around and with this distance, there was nowhere to run to.

At this moment, Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage hastily raised up his spear too. Someone with good eyes could tell amidst the blurry surroundings from the Heavenly Lightning that the tip of his spear began to emit a faint light. However, the light instantly disappeared because Little Bei’s Dragon Breaks the Ranks had arrived and enveloped the area.

Boom! The sound of a huge explosion.

Little Bei thought his Dragon Breaks the Ranks had hit the opponent, but he discovered that he was the one flying backwards.

How was that possible!

Little Bei was astonished. For him to have been hit flying away, what had his opponent done?

Little Bei adjusted his view and soon saw that Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage was also flying away in the other direction. Even his posture was the same as his.

This was…….

Little Bei instantly understood. In that instant, Sun Xiang had also completed a Dragon Breaks the Ranks. The two sides had both used the same skill, so the results were the same.

Incredible…….

Little Bei respected the play. He conceded that he didn’t have the skill to complete such a move in that situation. With this, Sun Xiang still took damage, but he didn’t let Little Bei get free damage off.

“How unfortunate.” Ye Xiu said, “If your coordination had been slightly tighter, he wouldn’t have had the opportunity to do that.”

Not only was Sun Xiang unable to break out of the Heavenly Lightning Earthen Blaze, he had even taken damage and had been pushed back. These chains of attacks were a result of Ye Xiu’s commands.

Heavenly Lightning Earthen Blaze wasn’t a damage skill at this moment. It was a cover. By utilizing it to obstruct the opponent’s view, they were able to successfully inflict heavy damage onto Sun Xiang. And the ones to do it were Loulan Slash and Little Bei, two players that Sun Xiang had considered weeds on the side of the road.

Chapter 495 – Ambush

The attacks from the Heavenly Lightning Earthen Blaze weren’t endless and finally ended at this moment. In Glory, visual effects caused by skills hitting the terrain could be seen. The small street was filled with fresh holes. This was the third time the skill Heavenly Lightning Earthen Blaze had been used in this fight. The place looked similar to the aftermath of a war zone, especially since the third Heavenly Lightning had been activated where the second Heavenly Lightning had been.

Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage was crouching down in this charred landscape.

Although his in-game character didn’t show any expression, Sun Xiang was sitting in front of his computer pale-faced. Not only did his attempt to rush out of the Heavenly Lighting fail, he was also forced into a difficult situation by his opponents. In that previous confrontation, the only damage received by Little Bei was from his Dragon Breaks the Ranks and nothing else. Sun Xiang wasn’t so fortunate. He was unable to avoid the damage from the Heavenly Lightning as he was sent flying. One could tell that Sun Xiang’s character had taken damage just by looking at the smoke emitting from his equipment.

Zhang Jiaxing now had something to do as he quickly healed Sun Xiang. The Heavenly Lightning had crashed down right when Shen Jian’s Striker went after Deception. He had to constantly dodge the attacks from the Heavenly Lightning. At the same time, his line of sight had been blocked. All he could see was a vague silhouette of Deception. Before he could get into range, a bolt of lightning cut through the silhouette, making him realize that something wasn’t right. The effects from Heavenly Lightning stopped and Deception was still standing in his team’s formation without harm. The silhouette struck by the Heavenly Lightning had been his shadow clone.

No decisive conclusion could be made from this exchange. However, from the looks of the situation, Ye Xiu’s team held the upper hand.

The morale of Loulan Slash and Little Bei were especially high after forcing Sun Xiang to back off. In their eyes, if they chased after their opponents, they would take the victory, but before they could act, Lord Grim typed, “Retreat!”

“We’re running?” Loulan Slash hesitated.

“We’re not running, it’s a tactical retreat!”

As he typed, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim retreat. The other six followed suit.

“Trying to run?” Sun Xiang was stomping his feet in impatience and wanted to chase after the group.

Liu Hao wanted to warn Sun Xiang, but he held himself back. Their young captain wasn’t someone who listened to other’s advices. If Sun Xiang made a decision, Liu Hao doubted he would be able to dissuade him and might even annoy him. Thus, Liu Hao refrained from restraining Sun Xiang.

“Everyone, be careful.” Liu Hao chose not to address Sun Xiang directly, and used the more general term of “everyone” instead. Deep in his heart, he knew that Ye Xiu had not shown his true capabilities. If the others were from Heavenly Justice, then the hidden experts from the cyber cafe might be with them too. With their sudden retreat, Liu Hao was reminded of the possibility of an ambush ahead.

We have more people on our side!

Ye Xiu’s words reverberated deep in Liu Hao’s mind. He doubted that Ye Qiu would be dumb enough to think that just those seven would be enough of an advantage to beat them. Now that he was thinking about it, could there have been a hidden meaning in his words? What if the experts following Ye Qiu logged into the game undetected and came over as reinforcements?

Liu Hao didn’t dare to irritate Sun Xiang, but he warned He Ming and Shen Jian in private. Those two were in the same boat as him. There weren’t any secrets between them. They clearly remembered what happened before and understood the situation immediately. They surrounded Sun Xiang to protect him from any ambush aimed against him.

Sun Xiang didn’t pay attention to any of this as he continued to chase at full speed. These little weeds had made him suffer losses time after time. He was going to turn each and every one of those weeds into ashes.

“Into the building!”

The seven of them rushed out from the streets. With the movement buff from the Neutral Chasers, Sun Xiang was rapidly closing the gap between them with incredible speed. Liu Hao was starting to get worried. They couldn’t keep up with Sun Xiang. He would be the first to arrive at the intersection, which would be the perfect spot for an ambush.

“Watch out for any ambushes!” shouted Liu Hao. At this point, he didn’t care about annoying Sun Xiang.

“Hmph!” Sun Xiang responded coldly. As Liu Hao expected, Sun Xiang paid no heed to him at all.

“He Ming.” Desperate, Liu Hao turned to He Ming for help.

“Got it.” He Ming nodded his head and used the Elementalist’s Teleportation to catch up. Teleportation was an Elementalist’s life saver, but at this moment, he was using it to protect Sun Xiang’s life.

Ice Wall!

He Ming rushed forward and threw a spell at the intersection to his right just in case of an ambush. The spell would serve as a buffer against potential enemies to buy time for Sun Xiang to react.

“What are you doing?” Sun Xiang was puzzled by He Ming’s action.

“Be careful. They may have set up an ambush.” He Ming didn’t dare to be careless. He focused his attention on the street to the left, ready to release spells at any time.

“What ambush?” Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage had already moved past the intersection. There hadn’t been anyone around. Their seven opponents hadn’t made any turns either and headed straight for a building at the intersection.

“The ambush is in that room!” Liu Hao felt uneasy. He didn’t care about anything else and shouted, “Wait!”

But Sun Xiang totally ignored his warning and made a beeline for the entrance. Sun Xiang was prepared though when he entered the room and swung his spear around.

He Ming’s Elementalist turned around and shrugged at his three teammates as he entered the building.

Liu Hao was filled with anger at this point. In Sun Xiang’s eyes, Loulan Slash and his team weren’t the only weeds. Liu Hao and the other pros were also included in this group of weeds. The pain of having to babysit somebody as proud and arrogant as Sun Xiang gnawed at Liu Hao. He even secretly hoped that Sun Xiang would be burnt to ashes.

In the end, nothing happened. Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage swung his battle lance freely and entered the room. They watched from the outside, but didn’t see any battles taking place.

“They’ve all run away...what the f*ck are you guys waiting for!” Sun Xiang shouted with rage, extremely dissatisfied about the fact that Liu Hao told him to “wait” earlier on.

Liu Hao responded absent-mindedly: “They ran away?”

At this moment, He Ming entered the building and noticed a window on the wall. The house was already empty. Sun Xiang had jumped straight out through the window.

“He Ming, follow him!” Liu Hao felt puzzled at the situation. He didn’t know whether or not their opponents had actually run off and he wasn’t yet in position to confirm it. However, with Sun Xiang focused on chasing after the enemies, the distance between him and their team was growing farther apart. Even if the enemies hadn’t actually run off, if this continued, it would be the same as if they had. Alone, Sun Xiang could easily be picked off by Ye Qiu and his team. After all, those guys weren’t bad players. They really weren’t like those weeds that could be found all over the game.

At this moment, He Ming was crouching beside the window. He spotted Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage chasing after a person and then disappearing after making a turn. He Ming, of course, shared the same dissatisfaction and worries as Liu Hao. Just as he was about to follow after him out the window, he saw the earth beneath the window rise and a silhouette burst out.

“Sh*t!” He Ming cursed. A mage in mid-air could only do so much. He couldn’t avoid it. The only possible skill that could be used in this situation, Teleportation, had been cast moments before and was still on cooldown.

The silhouette that appeared, of course, was Deception. He broke through the ground with the Underground Tunneling Technique. He Ming, with half of his body outside the window, was pushed into the window frame. Deception landed, strapped a noose around the neck of He Ming’s Elementalist, and dragged him out with a Body Bind Technique.

He Ming, knowing that he had been tricked, knew that the enemy’s attack would not stop there. He requested for help immediately. At the same time, he saw several silhouettes descend from the rooftop and attack him. An Earth-Shattering Slash from the Berserker sent him up into the air. Right when he was about to use a Quick Recover, the Grappler wrapped his legs around his neck, and dropped onto the ground after spinning in mid-air, slamming He Ming into the ground.

Three shots followed right after, along with a pillar of flame. All of these attacks were directed at He Ming who was on the ground. He Ming immediately understood. After going through the window, only one of the opposing members ran towards the intersection while the Ninja dug into the ground under the window with his Underground Tunneling Technique and the rest jumped onto the rooftop.

Sun Xiang would be the first to arrive. The opposition could tell judging by how fast he was moving compared to the rest. He Ming would be the second because he had cast Teleportation to catch up.

The enemy drew Sun Xiang away and then acted against the second target…

He Ming was an Elementalist, so he didn’t have much health. Add to the fact that he was using an open account, his equipment was no different than the ones used by common guild members. Ye Xiu and his team could defeat guild members within moments. His Elementalist would be killed quickly as well.

He Ming attempted to struggle, but as Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim landed blow after blow on him, He Ming knew that he would die here. Lord Grim’s level wasn’t high, but in this situation, damage wasn’t necessary. It was already enough just by attacking him. A surrounded Elementalist trying to escape without Teleportation didn’t abide to the rules of Glory.

With his Teleportation on cooldown, He Ming could only wait for reinforcements. The moment he heard Liu Hao’s voice, his heart was filled with joy. He still had some hit points left, and if his teammates got there in time…

“Heavenly Lightning.”

At the same time, he heard another voice.

Heavenly Lighting Earthen Blaze, the most popular spell in today’s battle, was cast for the fourth time, and it was placed in the room through the window.

With the lighting and flames, the interior of the house erupted in chaos, the position of the window could no longer be found. Heading to the window would probably be slower than going over the rooftop.

At this moment, He Ming knew, that he was beyond rescue.

Chapter 496 – Bullying

Liu Hao and the others saw He Ming’s Elementalist’s health rapidly drop. They didn’t need He Ming to shout for help in order to know that the situation wasn’t looking good. Even though their team had a Cleric, He Ming’s Elementalist wasn’t in spell range, so the Cleric couldn’t do anything.

In order to cast the spell, not only did the Cleric need to be close enough to the target, the target also had to be in the Cleric’s line of sight. Right now, He Ming’s Elementalist were separated by the wall and couldn’t be seen by them. Zhang Jiaxin stared with wide eyes, but couldn’t think of a possible solution. Listening to Liu Hao’s orders, the three exited the building as quickly as they could. Just as they reached the roof, Liu Hao’s icon turned gray, indicated his character’s death.

“F*CK!!” Liu Hao cursed. The dead He Ming quickly reported what had happened. The three pro players didn’t dare to make any rash movements. If they leaped down from the roof back onto the streets, they would be vulnerable as they fell, which would give the enemies a good opportunity to attack them.

Liu Hao could only shout fiercely at Sun Xiang in the team chat, but didn’t receive a response.

He Ming’s Elementalist had already died. Sun Xiang should have been able to see it too. However, Liu Hao reckoned that not only would Sun Xiang not be worried, he might even be thinking of how trash He Ming was to actually die in the hands of these weeds.

“What now?” Shen Jian asked Liu Hao.

Meanwhile, Zhang Jiaxin’s Cleric cautiously climbed towards the eaves of the roof to see if there was anything below. As soon as his head poked out, he heard a bang! Zhang Jiaxin immediately shrunk back. The eaves of the roof shattered into bits in front of his face.

“Let me!” Liu Hao had his Spellblade move carefully to the eaves of the roof. He raised his sword and cast a spell. An electric ball formed below. He was going to use an Electric Wave Formation to clear out a safe space for them to land.

However, as soon as he began to cast the Electric Wave Formation, the skill’s visual effects appeared, exposing his plan. This was one big weakness of using this sort of skill. When the electric ball appeared, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim suddenly jumped up.

“Ha ha, too late.” Liu Hao laughed. He obviously knew about the huge weakness of the Electric Wave Formation. However, neither side knew where the other was located. By the time Lord Grim located him and shot at him, even if the bullet landed, he would have finished casting the spell. Liu Hao had calculated all of this before carrying out his plan.

Who would have thought that when Lord Grim jumped up, he didn’t shoot at him. Instead, Lord Grim had his back facing them and shot at the ground. He was going to use an Aerial Fire to fly up onto the roof!

Liu Hao was puzzled, but at this moment, a leg suddenly appeared beneath him. It was the Ninja skill, Annihilation…….

Liu Hao had been so focused on the Lord Grim in the air that he hadn’t thought someone would be hiding beneath the eaves of the roof. Only now did he realize that their opponents had a Ninja. By using the Disappearing Body Technique, setting up and ambushing from below the eaves of the roof was completely possible.

Unfortunately, in the time it took for him to figure this out, Liu Hao’s Spellblade had already been thrown into the air. Deception flipped onto the roof. He lifted up two shurikens and threw them at Xiao Jian and Zhang Jiaxin.

As for Lord Grim, after Aerial Firing his way onto the roof, he lobbed a grenade towards Liu Hao’s Spellblade.

The grenade exploded. Deception was also here, but he wouldn’t take any damage from it. However, Liu Hao was sent crashing towards the streets from the shockwave.

Zhang Jiaxin was a Cleric and didn’t have much combat ability. Their current situation was the same as the previous one. No one had lost much health, so there wasn’t much for him to do. This time, Zhang Jiaxin didn’t stand idly. He lifted his staff and cast a Sacred Fire at Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu used a Shadow Clone Technique to dodge it before pouncing towards Zhang Jiaxin’s Cleric.

A Cleric in close range needed protection. Xiao Jian’s Striker rushed over almost instinctively. At the same time, they heard several thumps. Behind them, Loulan Slash, Ocean Ahead, Night Tide, and Thousand Falling Leaves had jumped onto the roof.

Thousand Falling Leaves waved her staff and also used a Sacred Fire to force Xiao Jian’s Striker to retreat. Xiao Jian hastily leapt back to dodge it. Lord Grim had unexpectedly swapped off the Cleric and rushed towards him instead. Lord Grim stabbed forward with his umbrella spear. Xiao Jian was still in the air and couldn’t dodge, so he attempted to use an Empty-handed Blade Block. However, his hand failed to grab anything. Lord Grim’s spear stopped midway and didn’t follow all the way through with the stab. When his hand missed, the spear suddenly shot forward again.

Xiao Jian’s Striker landed on the ground, but the attack was now too close and too quick for him to dodge in time. The spear pierced into his body.

“You’re looking down on me too much. You should know just how much experience I have against Strikers!” Ye Xiu grinned and then swung his spear in a circle, slamming Xiao Jian’s Striker into the ground once more.

Xiao Jain was depressed! He obviously knew what Ye Xiu had meant by this. Ye Xiu had been rivals with God Han Wenqing for so many years, so, of course, he had tons of experience against Strikers. His little technical skills couldn’t compare to a fraction of Han Wenqing’s. However, in that instant, how could he have thought about all of that? He had done this out of instinct. Even if he had considered this point, he couldn’t have done much else.

Circle Swing forcefully knocked him down, so Xiao Jiao couldn’t do anything in return. When he turned his camera around, he saw Deception swing his blade. Countless water streams headed towards him.

Xiao Jian suddenly paled in alarm. What could he do? The Circle Swing had thrown him right into the water prison’s path.

Sure enough, the water prison formed the moment Xiao Jian’s Striker hit the ground. XIao Jian couldn’t do anything, but watch as the prison formed around him. He turned his camera to look to the side and saw the Berserker, Grappler, and Elementalist beating down Zhang Jiaxin’s Cleric.

No matter how good Zhang Jiaxin was, there was only so much a Cleric could do. No matter how amazing his mechanics were, they couldn’t be used to attack. At this moment, he could only dodge about and try to hang on. Fight back? Zhang Jiaxin only had a few skills that he could use to attack, but with the enemy’s Cleric still standing, attacking back would be a waste of mana. Furthermore, Loulan Slash and the others weren’t so weak that they couldn’t even take down a Cleric by themselves.

Meanwhile, after imprisoning Xiao Jian’s Striker, Lord Grim and Deception also rushed forward. With five players attacking together, Zhang Jiaxin’s situation became similar to He Ming’s.

Xiao Jian couldn’t do anything to help. Zhang Jiaxin wanted to cry, but no tears came out. Liu Hao’s Spellblade had finally made his way back onto the roof, but before he could even land on the roof, Lord Grim tossed another grenade at him.

Liu Hao was still a pro player. He swung his sword and knocked the grenade aside. However, he wasn’t as flashy as Sun Xiang and didn’t send the grenade back. Using the grenade’s explosion as a cover, three Anti-Tank Missiles sped away. Xiao Jian and Zhang Jiaxin saw what was happening, but it was too late to warn Liu Hao. Liu Hao’s Spellblade made his way out of the smoke, but ate three Anti-Tank Missiles instead. The missiles exploded and sent him flying from the roof.

They were all pro players, so they had the ability to judge the situation. The battle was over. Among their team of five, He Ming was already a corpse. Sun Xiang had disappeared to who knows where after chasing after one of the enemies. Liu Hao was unable to come up. Xiao Jian had been CC’d in a water prison and couldn’t break out. Zhang Jiaxian was being surrounded and beat down…...

“It’s over……” Xiao Jian closed his eyes. Zhang Jiaxin wouldn’t be able to hang on for much longer. When Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim joined the bullying, he pushed him into Falling Thousand Leave’s Sacred Fire. Sacred Fire silence enemies that it struck, making it impossible to use skills for three seconds. During these three seconds, the five enemies barraged him with attacks. After the three second silence had ended, he used an instant heal on himself, but it would only allow him to survive for a fraction longer.

Liu Hao didn’t dare to get onto the roof directly anymore, so he hastily took a roundabout way. However, by the time he arrived, Zhang Jiaxin’s Cleric had already fallen and Xiao Jian’s Striker was still stuck in prison.

Liu Hao could obviously tell how terrible the situation was. After eliminating Zhang Jiaxin’s Cleric, they smashed open the water prison surrounding Xiao Jian’s Striker and went to bully him next.

Xiao Jian struggled and resisted, but his opponents had a huge numbers advantage…… In addition, the enemy Cleric still standing, so they wouldn’t care about his pathetic struggles to fight back.

This was a perfect example of safety in numbers. They didn’t even need skill! They just attacked him with whatever they had until he died. Xiao Jian had planned on running away as soon as the water prison broke, but the enemies had surrounded him too tightly. Plus, with Ye Xiu controlling the situation, he had no way of escaping the encirclement and could only watch as his health fell to zero.

And Liu Hao? Liu Hao quietly watched the scene, but didn’t dare to move.

He felt like their loss was already guaranteed. Even if he went out and helped Xiao Jian escape, with just the two of them, how were they going to beat six players including a Cleric?

A loss! Another loss!

He had called Sun Xiang over. Excellent Era’s main team had come out to enter the fray, but they actually lost! Moreover, the amount of time it took…… was probably shorter than a normal pro match! Could these guys actually be better than a pro team?

Liu Hao was embarrassed and at a complete loss.

He wasn’t afraid of dying. As a pro player, how could he care about the equipment and experience loss of an open account? What made him the most depressed and hurt was their defeat. It should have been an easy victory. Why had he lost again? Why?

“Is there something you want to say?” Ye Xiu had Lord Grim turn around and look at the frozen Liu Hao.

“Where did you all run off to?! COME OUT!” At this moment, Sun Xiang suddenly shouted in frustration.

Chapter 497 – Many Bullying the Few

“What took you so long?” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim stood atop the roof. Loulan Slash, Deception, and the others lined up beside him, looking down below.

As for Liu Hao? Hearing Sun Xiang’s voice, he didn’t feel happy at all. When he saw the six players standing together, especially with Lord Grim in the middle, Liu Hao could only feel a sense of loss.

Whoosh!

A shadow flew out. Deception threw a shuriken towards Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage.

“Little bug.” Sun Xiang didn’t feel any fear facing these six players. After sneering, he didn’t even attempt to dodge the shuriken. His Battle Mage pulled his spear back and swung through the air. A cold light flashed. Battle Mages added magic to their martial skills, so even though many of their skills were close ranged, they had an extraordinarily long range for melee attacks.

For example, the assault from Dragon Breaks the Ranks extended past the tip of the spear.

Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart had an attack range of up to five body units.

This attack knocked away the shuriken and continued forward without losing any speed. Deception was still in the air and couldn’t dodge it. The cold light struck through his chest, sending him crashing down. The other five followed Deception down. After all, Sun Xiang had just used a high level skill, which had a long ending lag, so he wouldn’t be able to throw out any other moves against them. The five players landed on the ground safely. Deception had taken some damage, but a white healing light quickly brought him back to a healthy state.

“Hmph…..” Sun Xiang had thought of something just now. Loulan Slash moved his hands and unsheathed his sword with a Sword Draw. Before the sword light had even dissipated, he immediately followed up with a Collapsing Mountain. Both skills were low-leveled skills and had little lag. These two moves alone covered the spaces above, below, left, right, in front of, and behind his character.

However, Sun Xiang wasn’t any ordinary player. His character dashed diagonally and brushed past the Sword Draw. He raised his spear in an attempt to knock Loulan Slash out of the air. His decision was brimming with self-confidence. If he failed to knock down Loulan Slash, the Collapsing Mountain’s aftershock would definitely hit his target.

Sun Xiang’s arrogance wasn’t just for show. Sure enough, he successfully knocked Loulan Slash out of the air. He stabbed through Loulan Slash and tossed him into the ground, but before Loulan Slash hit the ground, a ring of fire rose from beneath Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage. However, Sun Xiang noticed it in time. He cancelled his Circle Swing and leapt backwards.

The column of Raging Flames had just barely been dodged, but before he could do anything else, two legs pincered him while in the air.

Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage swung his spear in an attempt to land another Sky Strike behind him without looking. Sun Xiang always completed these difficult and flashy moves perfectly though. Night Tide’s Aerial Twist failed to follow through on the target and his character was hit by the Sky Strike. Right when Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage was about to land on the ground, the earth shook and a person flew out.

Deception! Underground Tunneling Technique!

This time, Sun Xiang had no way of dodging this move. Deception broke through the earth and slashed his blade across the neck of Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage. A streak of blood blossomed out. Deception didn’t stop there and followed up with an Annihilation.

Both attacks had been extremely quick. Sun Xiang had almost been able to react to the second attack, but he was still a bit too late and was kicked flying.

Sun Xiang was extremely furious. This little weed had somehow given him so much trouble. While flying backwards through the air, he calculated how he would kill off Deception. Then, he suddenly heard a gunshot. Lord Grim’s gun was pointed at him.

It was extremely difficult to dodge in the air. Apart from a few classes which could move through in the air using their skills, it wasn’t possible to make any large movements. Twisting the body was the best one could do, but it wouldn’t help too much. Hearing the gunshot, Sun Xiang slashed with his spear and was able to hit two out of three Anti-Tank Missiles. The third missiles avoided his attack and the explosion consumed his body.

The explosion blasted Sun Xiang in another direction. At this moment, Sun Xiang wanted to hurry and land on the ground, but Loulan Slash had prepared for him. He slashed out with a Gore Cross in the air, which hit Sun Xiang’s body and kept him suspended in the air. Night Tide’s Grappler followed up and slammed Sun Xiang into the ground, creating a small crater.

Grab skills couldn’t be teched out of, so Sun Xiang was stuck in the ground and could only curse furiously in his heart as his opponents continued to attack. Ocean Ahead’s Elementalist cast a Thunder Apocalypse. Thunder roared and lightning descended towards Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage. How was he supposed to dodge?

After the lightning passed, his Battle Mage’s hair stood erect, like a porcupine’s quills. He immediately rolled and got into a crouched position.

“Very good. Nice coordination. Continue!” Ye Xiu said and had Lord Grim make a clapping motion.

Sun Xiang swept his surroundings to look at the situation. However, as soon as he turned a little bit, he saw some movement behind him. These guys were too evil! They were always moving around behind him outside of his line of sight. It was true that Sun Xiang was quite good at fighting against enemies behind him, but attacking behind him relied completely on judgement. In any case, the probability of missing when attacking behind oneself blindly would be much greater than the probability of missing when attacking an enemy in front. Fighting an entire battle in this way wouldn’t work.

Hearing the movement from behind him, Sun Xiang hastily turned around just in time to see a Berserker’s Earth-Shattering Slash striking his face.

If Sun Xiang wanted to dodge, he still had enough time. He knew that as long as there was an attack towards him, there would be others attacking from behind as well. His opponents clearly wanted to keep chaining attacks one after the other.

As a result, he chose to dodge and hastily hopped to the side, finding a location outside of Earth-Shattering Slash’s range. At the same time, he closed in on Ocean Ahead’s Elementalist and prepared to attack him. Before he could make a move, Deception suddenly appeared in front of him with a Shadow Clone Technique and attacked.

“YOU AGAIN!!!” Sun Xiang roared. He was about to explode in anger at having this little weed thwart his plans again and again. Using enough force to break a keyboard, he slammed a button on his keyboard and slashed at Deception. Deception didn’t move slowly. In reality, if he had fought Sun Xiang directly, he would have ended up losing, but it wouldn’t have been without any resistance. Making a few exchanges was still possible for him. Deception didn’t dodge Sun Xiang’s attack. He actually held his ground and attacked back. Sun Xiang saw this and became even angrier. This weed actually dared to fight him face to face? Just when he was about to go all out and let this weed know his place in the dirt, his body was suddenly pulled back and lifted into the air.

Elemental Power!

Sun Xiang immediately recognized the move.

This was the Elementalist’s knock-up skill! Every class had at least one type of low-leveled and basic skill, each with their own unique aspects. Elemental Power was the slowest knock-up skill. It had quite a lengthy cast time to it.

However, Elemental Power also had the greatest range. It could even be considered an AoE move. Under Deception’s distraction, Ocean Ahead had secretly cast an Elemental Power. Sun Xiang had been tunneled in on teaching Deception a lesson and hadn’t noticed it. Of course, by the time Elemental Power had begun sucking him into the air, it was already too late.

Behind him, an ethereal ball of energy gathered in the air. It didn’t look as domineering as the Spellblade’s electric ball visual effect from an Electric Wave Formation though. Just like this, Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage was lifted into the air and then the Elemental Power disappeared into nothingness.

How would Deception miss this obvious of an opening??

Of course he wouldn’t! He directly used a high-leveled skill: Shadow Dance!

Shadows flew across the sky. All of them pounced towards Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage, who was only able to block a few of the attacks. However, Deception wasn’t the only one who seized this opening. Ocean Ahead prepared to cast another spell. Loulan Slash’s Berserker charged forward. Night Tide’s Grappler predicted where Sun Xiang would land and prepared to grab him. As for Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim? He waved the Thousand Chance Umbrella in his hands and healed them with Cleric skills. The actual Cleric, Thousand Falling Leaves, went to who knows where.

Sun Xiang was raging. These trivial weeds were about to beat him into submission?

Sun Xiang turned his camera around and happened to catch Liu Hao’s Spellblade staring stupidly at the fight from the roof.

“Liu Hao, what are you doing?” Sun Xiang roared.

“Oh? You need help?” Ye Xiu responded for Liu Hao.

Sun Xiang’s face turned ashen and suddenly went silent. Asking for help was something he felt too ashamed to say.

“Don’t worry so much! Just ask for help! We’re bullying you few with so many, so you don’t need to feel bad calling for assistance.” Ye Xiu said.

Sun Xiang grinded his teeth, but didn’t say a thing. He didn’t even look at Liu Hao and focused on defending against their attacks.

Liu Hao was also very conflicted. He could have helped him long before this point, but he wasn’t conflicted about this!

From the looks of it, today’s assault was already a failure. Even Sun Xiang was being bullied into a mess by them. Would his additional help even be able to turn the tides? Impossible! If he went down there, he would just be throwing himself into the fire too!

He had come in order to step on Ye Qiu and see him in a sorry state. He hadn’t thought he would be the one to be stepped on in the end. They had clearly lost this battle. Why would he set himself up to be stepped on even further?

However, if he didn’t go up, Sun Xiang would see that he wasn’t helping him. Sun Xiang would certainly be very unhappy with him and that wouldn’t be good either.

Liu Hao hadn’t thought that calling for Sun Xiang would put him into such an impossible scenario.

Chapter 498 – Useless Skill

If I go up and fight, I’ll be stepped on by Ye Qiu.

If I don’t go up and fight, I’ll probably be stepped on by Sun Xiang in the future.

Who would I rather get stepped on by? That was the question at hand.

Could there be a better option? Liu Hao watched the situation unfolding below as he racked his brain. Below, Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage was surrounded by several enemies. The enemies didn’t attack together as one, but rather separately one after the other. As a pro player, Liu Hao knew that this was the only way to pull off a true unbreakable combo.

He was very familiar with this method.

Liu Hao couldn’t help but have this thought. However, he immediately ground his teeth after thinking about it. How could he not be familiar with this method? When Ye Qiu was still Excellent Era’s captain, he had often said these words to them. Now, Sun Xiang was truly helpless against the team’s combo. Fortunately, the enemy team wasn’t well coordinated and Sun Xiang sometimes found small openings in their attacks and managed to survive for a bit longer. However, if Sun Xiang didn’t have such incredible mechanics, a normal player would have died several times already. Moreover, the best Sun Xiang could do was survive for a bit longer. He couldn’t find any opportunities to counterattack.

If I go down there, I might not be able to reverse the tides of the battle, but maybe I can work together with Sun Xiang and break out of the encirclement?

Liu Hao thought to himself, but he also couldn’t help but worry. With Sun Xiang’s pride, would he be willing to stoop so low as to run away? Especially to these people, who he considered weeds.

Running away was shameful, but dying was even more so. He should know that shouldn’t he?

Liu Hao favored one choice over the other. He attached importance to his relationship with his captain. After all, this relationship would still exist in the future. In reality, after causing his team to lose due to his poor mental state from failing to set the dungeon record, he had already made up his mind. Dealing with Ye Qiu would be something he did in his spare time. His work time couldn’t be spent on Ye Qiu. It was just that with the possibility of Ye Qiu turning into their future competitor, taking down Ye Qiu became a public-private joint ventureship. This was why he began interfering with in-game affairs again. If not, he could have simply tossed the task to Chen Yehui to deal with like he had done so in the tenth server.

After quickly weighing the pros and cons of his choices, Liu Hao decided he would have to take the risk. Even if he were stepped on, he would be stepped on together with Sun Xiang. Both of them would share the bitterness and form companionship through this hardship. Being stepped on also had its value. If he had to sacrifice himself in order to break through the encirclement, then that could be another valuable option!

The more Liu Hao thought about it, the calmer he became. Slowly, he saw the benefits of being stepped on.

There was no need to hesitate anymore. Liu Hao immediately began to move. He brandished his sword and started to cast a wave formation. However, a gunshot came out almost the moment he drew his sword. His cast was instantly interrupted. Below, smoke drifted from the tip of Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella.

Sun Xiang was used as a training dummy for the others to practice on, so Ye Xiu hadn’t participated in this team-building activity. He directed their tempo, healed them from time to time, and also paid attention to Liu Hao’s movement. As soon as he saw him move, he immediately shot at him.

Liu Hao knew he wouldn’t get any further trying the same move again, so he ran to the other side of the roof and jumped down. He rushed into the empty building and planned on letting out a wave formation from the window, but when he ran to the window side, he couldn’t attack anyone from this angle. The other side seemed to have predicted this might happen and pulled the battle to the side. Attacking from the window wasn’t possible.

Helpless, Liu Hao jumped through the window. Sure enough, as soon as he came out, he could see the battle!

Liu Hao hastily had his Spellblade rush forward and cast an Ice Wave Slash. Ice crystals formed on the surface of the ground. Not long afterwards, the ice crystals began to creep up Loulan Slash’s back.

Liu Hao didn’t think too much about who he would attack. In any case, if he disrupted up one of the enemy’s tempo, there would be an opportunity to break out of the encirclement.

Sure enough, when the Ice Wave Slash flew out, Loulan Slash had to dodge. Because of this sudden movement, their formation was interrupted. Sun Xiang saw the opportunity and immediately swung out a Sky Strike.

“Retreat!”

Ye Xiu’s warning came out faster than the attack. Deception and Night Tide had already leapt out of the way. As for Ocean Ahead, Elementalists wouldn’t attack be in range in the first place.

The amount of space to maneuver around had widened. Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage dashed out. He chased after Deception and stabbed with a Dragon Tooth.

Liu Hao saw this and it had panned out as he expected. Sun Xiang had no plan on running away. Pro players didn’t care about experience or equipment, only victory. Running away or dying was the same as losing.

Liu Hao already had a plan in mind to resolve this issue. He bravely entered the battle and pushed Loulan Slash’s Berserker away with an Earthquake Sword, while saying: “We were careless this time. Let’s retreat for now. Regroup and then return!”

These words didn’t seem like anything special, but they held subtle implications.

First, it pointed out their carelessness, giving Sun Xiang a proper excuse to leave.

Secondly, retreat, regroup, and return indicated that this fight hadn’t ended yet. The winner had yet to be decided yet.

However, Sun Xiang coldly humphed in response. He took the opportunity Liu Hao had created and pursued Deception incessantly.

“Let’s hurry up and run! I’ll protect you!” Liu Hao knew Sun Xiang would back off, so he continued with his plan by showing off his righteousness.

“Hmph, no need!” Sun Xiang refused and attacked even more ferociously. His attacks were no longer just aimed at Deception, but also Loulan Slash and Night Tide. Ocean Ahead’s Elementalist was somewhat far away. Liu Hao wouldn’t just stand there, so he ran over to block Ocean Ahead’s attacks.

Sun Xiang had previously been surrounded and most of his inputs had been for dodging and defending. The magic chasers surrounding his bodies had faded away long ago. After seizing the opportunity Liu Hao had created, his following waves of attacks replenished the chasers on his body. At the same time, a faint golden aura emanated from his body. His attacks suddenly became faster and more ferocious.

“This is…..” Liu Hao saw this and was startled.

“Ha ha ha, you guys probably didn’t think about this, did you?” Sun Xiang was delighted. His incessant attacks struck Deception, Night Tide, and Loulan Slash, continuing to rack up combos. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was busy healing them.

“Battle Spirit!” Liu Hao shouted.

Deception was puzzled though. Battle Spirit was the Battle Mage’s Awakening skill. Every Battle Mage had it. What was there to be so surprised for?

Deception’s confusion was because of his unfamiliarity with the pro scene.

The instant Battle Spirit appeared, Ye Xiu and Liu Hao immediately understood why Sun Xiang was suddenly so confident and delighted. As for Loulan Slash’s group, even though they weren’t yet pro players, because they planned on becoming pros, they obviously had a wealth of knowledge when it came to the pro scene, especially with Little Bei maining Battle Mage. Their reactions had been somewhat slower, but they also realized why Sun Xiang suddenly became excited.

This was because Battle Spirit was considered a useless skill in the pro scene nowadays.

This was because Battle Spirit required a certain number of consecutive hits in a combo to activate. The seventh stage for Battle Spirit may be terrifyingly strong, but it required 120 consecutive hits in a combo to fully activate. In the pro scene, let alone 120 consecutive hits, just 10 consecutive hits for the lowest tier wasn’t easy to achieve.

In a one vs one duel, it might be easier. In a team competition, it was near impossible.

In a high paced competitive match, getting Battle Spirit to activate in order to win used to be a viable strategy in the early days, but now, this strategy was way too inflexible and too easy to break. As a result, in the pro scene, Battle Spirit was considered a completely useless. The vast majority of pro Battle Mages only had one point in the skill, which was automatically added by the system after awakening. Afterwards, they didn’t even glance at it.

It was different in the game though. The game had PvE. Against a mob of monsters, it was very easy to reach the max stage of Battle Spirit. By relying on this skill, Battle Mages were easily one of the strongest DPS classes in PvE. As a result, for in-game players, maxing Battle Spirit was a must.

The open accounts raised by guilds were for multiple uses. They weren’t like pro characters, who only focused on PvP, so Battle Spirit was often maxed on open accounts. Thus, the Battle Mage that Sun Xiang was using had a max skilled Battle Spirit.

This is what Sun Xiang had meant when he said “you guys probably didn’t think about this did you?”

His skill was clearly superior to Loulan Slash’s group, so getting to a higher stage Battle Spirit was completely possible.

After the faint golden aura of Battle Spirit appeared on his body, he quickly used the three nearby targets to push Battle Spirit to the second stage.

His attacks didn’t stop and he continued to rack up combos. Attacking three less skilled targets wasn’t too difficult for him.

Stage three!

The golden aura from Battle Spirit grew brighter and brighter. Sun Xiang’s attack speed, movement speed, and attack power continued to increase. Deception, Loulan Slash, and Night Tide began having a harder and harder time keeping up. Ye Xiu only had low leveled Cleric skills, so he couldn’t nullify the damage with his healing.

“Ha ha ha ha, Battle Spirit is still a very nice skill! It’s too bad it’s too difficult to use in real battles. Luckily, I’ve met you weeds.” Sun Xiang shouted in glee. Battle Spirit was now in the fourth tier. He was no longer at a disadvantage in this 1v3 situation and the damage racked up from his combos wasn’t light. Ocean Ahead was struggling against Liu Hao. If it wasn’t for Ye Xiu’s support, they would have probably been defeated already.

Liu Hao was overjoyed. From the looks of it, could they actually turn the tides and obtain victory.

Chapter 499 – Opportunity Knocks But Once

“Be careful of your consumption.” Liu Hao shouted.

Sun Xiang and Liu Hao were fighting against many with just two players, so their mana consumption would naturally be higher. Of course, for pro players, endurance was a fundamental skill. Moreover, in game, there was no limit to the amount of potions that could be carried, so they didn’t need to be worried about running out.

When Liu Hao saw how fiercely Sun Xiang was fighting, he became worried about him getting over his head and forgetting something basic like this.

“Who needs you to remind me?”

Sun Xiang replied in disdain. Liu Hao wasn’t happy, but he endured because he had foreseen this might happen. If Sun Xiang had really forgotten, he probably wouldn’t reply back. If he hadn’t forgotten, he would obviously look down on Liu Hao. As a pro player, this type of reminder was very childish.

“Should we back off for a bit?” Loulan Slash finally couldn’t bear it anymore and made a suggestion.

Battle Spirit. If the combo stopped, it would stop at that stage. Afterwards, if another attack came out, it would start over from there. As a result, Battle Spirit was also a very troublesome skill for the user because it was very easy to lose your stacks. This was the reason why the pro scene considered it a useless skill.

Loulan Slash, Night Tide, and Deception had become combo fodder. Every time they tried to surround him, Sun Xiang would always find someone he could attack. If they backed off for a bit and dodged attacks, they would be able to stop Battle Spirit’s stacks from rising any further. Battle Spirit was an easy move to break out of. It was just that their shotcaller, Ye Xiu, hadn’t said anything, so they just continued to persist. By now, Sun Xiang had pushed Battle Spirit into the fifth stage. He now had an additional 2 Attack Speed, a 10% increase in movement speed, and 110 additional Strength. On paper, it doesn’t seem that incredible, but Sun Xiang was far more skilled than any of them in the first place.

The three didn’t even need to look at the density of the gold aura around him because when Battle Spirit reached such a stage, they could clearly feel their opponent getting stronger. Even the slightest advantage became magnified under a pro player’s hands.

“Back off? Ha ha ha, do you think I’ll allow you to back off? Do you know why you three are still alive? It’s because you haven’t backed off yet. If you backed off, I can just choose one of you as my target and instantly kill you.” Sun Xiang said with glee.

Loulan Slash shivered and understood that what Sun Xiang had said was the truth. Battle Mages had Neutral Chasers, which buffed their movement speed. Along with Battle Spirit, no matter how the three went about retreating, one of them would easily get caught. In a one on one, not only would his combo not break, he could also focus his attacks onto a single target. If they went to rescue him, wouldn’t it just turn back into a 1v3 like before? What was the difference?

“Oh? It looks like you actually have a bit of a brain for strategy.” Ye Xiu replied.

Loulan Slash immediately knew that God Ye Qiu had understood this, which was why he hadn’t told them to retreat. He clearly knew that for the three of them, retreating was not the solution to their problem. Right now, he was trying to limit the advantage the other side could gain from this situation. Even though Loulan Slash didn’t know when the turning point would occur, he could only continue to believe in God’s judgement and shotcalling.

Loulan Slash thought as he stole a glance at Ocean Ahead’s side.

Elementalists only had a slight advantage in terms of attack range over Spellblades. If the two sides were of unequal skill, Elementalists could kite Spellblades simply through the Teleport skill. However, in this case, Ocean Ahead was far less skilled than Liu Hao. Kiting wasn’t an option. If it wasn’t for Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim supporting him by attacking from time to time, Ocean Ahead would probably have died long ago.

Loulan Slash’s slight loss of focus actually became an opening for Sun Xiang. Sun Xiang’s attack suddenly fell onto his head.

“Hmph……”

Loulan Slash heard his humph and reckoned it was a response to Ye Xiu’s words.

“However, it really is just a bit!” Ye Xiu emphasized “a bit”, “If not, someone should have attacked by now! Could no one have noticed that I’m the backbone of this team?”

“There’s no need. I can break your formation just like this. You don’t need to be so impatient to die.” Sun Xiang said.

“Tsk tsk tsk, young people! Opportunity knocks but once!” Ye Xiu said

“Do you really think there’ll be any more opportunities?” Sun Xiang asked.

“We have more people. That’s our advantage. Our opportunity will come from this.” Ye Xiu said.

“Really? How come I can’t see it yet?” Sun Xiang said.

“Because you only have a bit of a brain and that’s about it.” Ye Xiu emphasized “a bit” again and didn’t even put in the “for strategy” part.

Liu Hao was getting worried! He really wanted to tell Sun Xiang not to talk with him, but this young guy loved showing off and liked to provoke others, but if you keep on provoking others, are you sure you’re going to come out victorious? Did the fight with Han Wenqing at the All Star Competition not teach you well enough?

Sun Xiang couldn’t care less about Ye Xiu’s words. On the other hand, Liu Hao couldn’t help but carefully ponder over it.

The advantage in numbers…...

Liu Hao looked around and suddenly realized: the other side was missing a person. Where’s the Cleric? Where’d the Cleric go? There’s a Cleric on the other team!

“Okay, if you want to die sooner, then I’ll give it my all for you!” Sun Xiang didn’t leave any room for discussion and used his actions to express his words.

At this moment, the golden aura around his body looked dazzling to the eye. Battle Spirit had reached the sixth stage. The seventh stage would multiply the buffs, but also required Sun Xiang to reach a much higher combo. Sun Xiang lost his patience. Against these weeds, current stage was more than enough.

Falling Flower Palm!

Sky Strike!

Two skills in a row. In order to continue the combo, Sun Xiang used low leveled skills more often. Low leveled skills had short cooldowns, so they would be used the most often in combos.

Falling Flower Palm shot out. Loulan Slash and Night Tide both dodged it, but the following Sky Strike landed on Night Tide and launched him into the air.

Dragon Tooth

Night Tide ate another attack. Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage stepped out from the encirclement and charged towards Lord Grim. He planned on keeping Night Tide in the air, attacking him as he advanced towards Lord Grim.

Lord Grim was a Level 52 character. A Level 70 Battle Mage buffed with every chasers, as well as a sixth stage Battle Spirit, wasn’t something he could take a hit from.

Loulan Slash and Deception hastily tried to rescue him. However, the sixth stage Battle Spirit seemed to have opened up a completely new realm for Sun Xiang. The strength Sun Xiang displayed leapt by a huge step. If before, every time Battle Spirit went up a stage, their pressure increased, then this was the point where the straw broke the camel’s back. They had no way of resisting anymore.

Strong beyond belief.

Fast movement speed, fast attack speed, along with Sun Xiang’s mechanics, trying to rescue Lord Grim from this situation was impossible for Deception and Loulan Slash. By the time they saw him move, they would be sent flying away before they could even try to defend.

Night Tide was still Sun Xiang’s combo fodder. He attacked Night Tide, while heading towards Lord Grim.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

The final attack would hit both Night Tide, as well as Lord Grim. Sun Xiang had calculated it very precisely. Lord Grim might be able to dodge the attack, but Night Tide die regardless. Lord Grim’s low-leveled Cleric heals wouldn’t be enough to save Night Tide. This last attack would be a fatal blow!

“Bang!”

A sound of metal colliding, but also the sounds of magic colliding rang out. Sun Xiang only knew that his character had shot back out of his control.

What happened?

This was something completely outside of Sun Xiang’s expectations. He immediately turned his camera to look around. He saw a character flying backwards in the same posture as him. Why did this scene seem familiar?

“IT’S YOU!” Sun Xiang saw the name of the character flying backwards. At the same time, he saw a white light envelop the Grappler’s body. The warm, overflowing white light was completely different from Lord Grim’s faint white healing. These were true Holy Words from a Cleric.

“Yeah, it’s him?” Ye Xiu lazily said, “Clerics can revive players! Don’t tell me you didn’t know that!”

“F*ck, too despicable!!!”

Liu Hao stamped his feet in anger.

Where did the other side’s Cleric go? He finally knew. Their Cleric went to revive the other dead player. The Battle Mage had been the one of lure Sun Xian away. In the end, he had easily been caught and killed. However, by luring away Sun Xiang, his team had been able to kill three of the five players from Sun Xiang’s side. At this moment, they sent their Cleric out to revive the dead Battle Mage.

Liu Hao wasn’t grieved over the fact that their enemies had one less casualty now. He was grieved that the other side had gain reinforcements quickly and shifted the tides of the battle.

Four players was clearly the limit of weeds that Sun Xiang could handle simultaneously.

He could make a combo out of three players and rack up stacks of Battle Spirit. However, four players became a situation like before where he was unable to fight back.

Sure enough, opportunity knocks but once!

Liu Hao was upset and regretful. He should have attacked Lord Grim. Why did he have to follow Sun Xiang’s intent and attack the Elementalist? They wasted such a good opportunity because of it.

Sun Xiang failed to tech out of the fall. Loulan Slash and Deception caught him. Little Bei’s Battle Mage and Night Tide’s Grappler went up to attack him as well. Four versus one. Another four versus one.

Liu Hao wanted to go over and assist him, but a figure suddenly moved in front of him. Lord Grim was blocking his path.

“Opportunity knocks but once. Didn’t I already say this?” Ye Xiu calmly said.

Chapter 500 – Glory Doesn’t Suit You

With the Cleric arriving on the scene and with Sun Xiang in a situation where he was facing four enemies at once, protecting himself was hard enough already, let alone attacking back. Thousand Falling Leaves was clearly enough to do this. Ye Xiu seized this opportunity to personally intercept Liu Hao.

“Ocean, you take care of the other side.” Ye Xiu said to Ocean Ahead. He didn’t know Ocean Ahead’s real name, so he used his ID instead.

“You want to fight me alone!” Liu Hao’s expression became serious. If he couldn’t defeat Ye Xiu with an 18 level advantage, it would tarnish the name of pro-players, but because the opponent was an unspecialised character that knew him well, Liu Hao didn’t dare to let his guard down.

“Have Little Bei come over.” Ye Xiu had more to say before replying to Liu Hao, “I’m racing against time, so I don’t have the time to fight you one on one.”

Liu Hao nearly coughed up blood…. Two against one. One of them was Ye Qiu, who he already had no confidence in defeating in a one on one. Now, there was also a Cleric on the enemy team. Liu Hao stood no chance.

Liu Hao had steeled himself for this, but Sun Xiang’s sudden activation of Battle Spirit had rekindled his hope. He had even fantasized how tantalizing it would be to step on Ye Qiu, but life is full of uncertainties, and his moment of happiness barely lasted for a short while before the tables were turned once again.

Liu Hao no longer had any expectations of his teammates coming back to reverse the tides of battle. The other side’s Battle Mage had died nearby, so he had been able to return to battle immediately. However, their side had died and respawned in the city. There was no way to know how long it would take for them to rejoin the battle.

As for seeking help from Chen Yehui, it was meaningless to Liu Hao. What he wanted was to reverse the situation, not to be rescued. Even if Chen Yehui sent an entire army to their aid, it would be completely meaningless. It only meant that Liu How would lose face in front of even more people, despite them not knowing his real identity.

Ye Xiu didn’t even talk much and sprang into the action right away. After battling him for a few seconds, he had even adjusted his character’s view, observing the battle raging on the other side while fighting against Liu Hao,while directing his four companions in a loud voice, a classic example of multi-tasking.

Liu Hao was so angry that he almost coughed up blood, but he was helpless. He wished that he could kill Lord Grim instantly with one hit, but the problem was that he couldn’t!

Let alone defeating Lord Grim, he wasn’t faring any better than Sun Xiang. Ever since the opponent’s Battle Mage had shifted his attention towards him and joined forces with Lord Grim, Liu Hao was completely at the mercy of his opponents.

He had no experience in fighting an unspecialized character. Although he was familiar with the Battle Mage class, the fear in his heart was quite large as he had been brought up being thrashed by this class. If the Battle Mage’s ID had been One Autumn Leaf, with such an advantage on the opponent’s side, Liu Hao would already have ran away long ago.

In a situation where both of them were beaten badly by the enemy, Liu Hao could not find an excuse even if he wanted to.

Sun Xiang, however, excelled in provoking the enemy instead, but in his current situation, what could he do? Besides, his provocations never bore any good result.

“Watch your positioning. Loulan, don’t give him an opening!”

“If you want to use Fling, face the wall!”

“Ocean go further to the front, there’s no danger!”

“Deception your damage output is weak…..”

Ye Xiu was constantly giving instructions to the other four while fighting against Liu Hao, and he didn’t forget about Little Bei who was beside him once he was done, “Don’t only think about using your high-leveled skills! He’s not so bad that he’d give you a chance to do that so fight properly!”

“You can even notice that!” Little Bei was surprised.

“Don’t you know? The technique you’re using was created by me.” Ye Xiu said.

“What technique?” asked Little Bei.

“You’ve made some changes, but the principle is still the same…… “ Ye Xiu gave Little Bei a lesson about Battle Mage technique.

“Look at this, Sky Strike can be used like this.” Ye Xiu even gave him a demonstration.

“He dodged it.” Little Bei pointed out.

“Bro, I’m level 52.” replied Ye Xiu.

“Not bad. Why haven’t you taught me that yet?” Tang Rou, who was watching, interjected.

“Really? I could’ve sworn I told you about it before?”

“No!”

“I definitely did, you must’ve forgotten about it.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Nope!”

“If that’s the case, then do you want me to show it to you right now?” Ye Xiu replied.

“Sure!”

“Watch closely!” Ye Xiu replied, and made the same move with a sudden strike.

“It landed!” Little Bei was surprised, “Why did he not dodge it?” and he imitated Ye Xiu’s movements.

“Hey, I landed a hit too!!” Little Bei grew more excited.

“Huh?” Ye Xiu felt that something was off. He didn’t follow up on the knocked up Spellblade. On the other hand, Little Bei kept attacking hit after hit on his opponent.

“Hey, when did I turn so amazing?” Little Bei was extremely surprised. Had his skill level reached another realm after being instructed by God Ye Xiu? The person in front of him was the vice captain of Excellent Era, as well as a famous pro-player, but he still managed to land a lot of combos on him in the air.

“Hold it, stop attacking.” said Ye Xiu.

“Huh?” Despite being puzzled, Little Bei stopped his attack. Liu Hao’s Spellblade landed on the ground.

“Pro player?” asked Tang Rou. A pro-player that fell without using a Quick Recover, what kind of nonsense was that?

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim walked up to him without attacking, and stepped on his character while shouting, “Are you there? Are you there?”

There was no reply.

“Are you serious? He disconnected?” Little Bei finally found out that something wasn’t right.

Disconnection was a thing from the past, but there were still valid reasons that could cause it, such as a power outage, or maybe the cable got chewed of by rats. It could also be that the computer itself exploded. These were reasons that were severe enough to cause a disconnection.

“He can’t be faking it right?” Ye Xiu was more acquainted to Liu Hao’s craftiness, and Lord Grim poked the Spellblade on the ground again.

But he was wrong about Liu Hao this time. Liu Hao had actually disconnected from the game. Angry that he was being used as a punching bag, he accidentally kicked the power source of the computer. Such a technical error was not his first time.

“What do we do?” Little Bei asked.

“Keep it up! The system will force logout if he was disconnected from the game! Hurry up and kill him.” Ye Xiu increased the strength of Lord Grim’s attacks.

A character that was disconnected in battle was more helpless than a character that was weak. Ye Xiu, being a God of the game, bullied him effortlessly and with Little Bei’s help, reduced Liu Hao’s Spellblade to a corpse in an instant.

As he turned around, Sun Xiang was still holding his ground.

“It not over!” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim walked over.

“Almost there, almost there.” replied the other four.

“Ye Qiu, fight with me one on one if you have the balls!” Sun Xiang was still hanging on to dear life!

“Are you not embarrassed? I’m only level 52.” Ye Xiu responded with confidence.

Distracted, Sun Xiang took a hit from Loulan Slash. After such a long time of combat, their Cleric was already dead, and the only reason he survived thus far was by drinking potions nonstop. Sun Xiang didn’t want to give up, so he had been counting the potions that he consumed, sustaining his hitpoints and mana to the maximum.

“Sigh, I feel sorry for him.” Ye Xiu said, “Come Little Bei, pick up the pace and take him out!”

With Ye Xiu entering the fight, the situation instantly changed. He was playing more of a support role than a comboer. If a hit didn’t strike at the right time, he would immediately make up for it. With this, the hits landing on Sun Xiang intensified and with fewer openings to defend himself, his health rapidly fell.

Noticing that he had little health left, Sun Xiang became increasingly tenacious, ignoring the damage he received and going all out towards Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu was too lazy to dodge the attacks though. He had Lord Grim open up the Thousand Chance Umbrella, turning it into a shield and resisting the attacks.

“Let me be frank with you,” Ye Xiu said, “With your poor attitude, don’t play Glory, Super Mario or Galaxian might suit you better.”

“You….” Sun Xiang felt insulted. He watched on as Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella transformed into a rifle and fired right into his chest. Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage flew backwards and slammed against the wall. He didn’t stand up again. He didn’t revive his character either.

“Dead?” Night Tide could not believe it He walked up to Sun Xiang, hovered his cursor over his HP bar. It really had hit zero.

“They’re all dead?” Loulan Slash’s tone was the same, he adjusted his vision, stopping at all the spots where their enemies lay slain.

“We’re….. Too awesome.” Ocean Ahead said. He didn’t shout out in celebration after winning the battle. He let out a sigh of relief too.

Little Bei and Thousand Falling leaves were silent, but their emotions were similar to their companions. They had annihilated the main force of Excellent Era, which was an unbelievable feat even if they hadn’t been using their professional accounts.

Deception kept quiet as well and after confirming that Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage and Liu Hao’s Spellblade did not revive. He circled their corpses and silently picked up the equipments dropped by those two.

“Hahaha… Why are you so mean? Super Mario? Sun Xiang will be furious.” Chen Guo was more excited than anybody else.

“I was speaking the truth.” mused Ye Xiu, “even Contra wouldn’t be suitable for him. That game even comes with a 2-player mode!”

“You….” Chen Guo noticed that Ye Xiu’s expression was odd even after achieving victory. Happiness? None at all. He even seemed a little sad…..

Sad? Chen Guo shook her head. She must be seeing things, how could he be sad? As she was about to say something, Ye Xiu stood up abruptly, “I’m going out for a smoke.”

“You account is still online!” Chen Guo didn’t forget that the three guilds were still going after them and the appearance of Excellent Era was just an interlude.

“Just help me log out!” replied Ye Xiu.

“Not going to kill them anymore?”

“No more.” Ye Xiu replied.

Chapter 501 – Self Sacrifice

Upon seeing Ye Xiu leave so abruptly, Chen Guo locked gazes with Tang Rou for a brief moment and stood up.

“Log him out, please.” Chen Guo told Tang Rou before following Ye Xiu out of the room hurriedly.

“Okay.” Tang Rou answered while watching the two leaving the room hastily.

Chen Guo stepped out of the room and found Ye Xiu right away. Instead of going anywhere, Ye Xiu was smoking, facing across the street. She slowed down, carefully composing her words in her head, but just as she walked up to him, Ye Xiu crushed the cigarette, which still had a good deal left, on the windowsill.

It angered Chen Guo immediately, but she stopped herself before the words fell out. Considering Ye Xiu’s feelings, she thought to forgive him just this once.

“You…”Chen Guo only spoke one word before Ye Xiu’s soft sigh interrupted her. Staring out of the window, he spoke quietly, “This is the end of Excellent Era.”

“Hmmm?” leaving a confused Chen Guo, Ye Xiu turned around and walked away quietly. Chen Guo followed his gaze to out of the window. On Excellent Era’s headquarter, the team emblem still glowed radiantly.

However, what about the actual team?

Chen Gou’s heart ached all of a sudden. Nonetheless, she did invest a lot of emotion and energy into the team for years. She didn’t only enjoy Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng’s performance..

That was her, then what about Ye Xiu?

He never said much about retirement. Facing the various powers and in the game, he was not particularly nice to anyone due to his attachments. However, this didn’t mean that Ye Xiu didn’t care about Excellent Era.

Sun Xiang’s addition was the hope for many Excellent Era’s support. It filled them with expectation.

Wouldn’t Ye Xiu have the same expectations?

Chen Guo suddenly thought that Ye Xiu leaving Excellent Era already made many uncomfortable. When he was still a part of the team, Excellent Era had been failing. To save the team, Ye Xiu chose to leave. Did he know that his departure would have been an effective way to save Excellent Era?

Unfortunately, Excellent Era was simply too heartless. To get rid of what they labeled as a useless burden, they used everything they had. They would probably never know that their team leader, for a chance to improve the team, had already decided to leave on his own.

For the growth of the team’s next generation prodigy, Wang Jiexi faked his loss and sacrificed his own reputation. However, this was a competition, after all. No one could keep a perfect record forever. A single defeat didn’t spell the end of the world. On top of that, his sacrifice would be understood and appreciated.

What about Ye Xiu?

Was there anyone who would understand his departure? Would anyone think of the efforts and troubles he had gone through? Excellent Era might have even believed that it was their trick that forced him to leave. They probably even took pride in it. They would not know that this could have been resolved peacefully. They never had to chose between the team and Ye Xiu, because their team leader was perfectly content with making sacrifices, even himself...

Him leaving had brought in Sun Xiang, a shining rookie from the pro scene. He was also a prodigy.

Ye Xiu was just like all the other fans of Excellent Era, filled with anticipation for Excellent Era’s future.

However, as of now, he was full of disappointment.

Sun Xiang was one one factor. After all, there was only so much you could ask of one person. The cause of his despair was probably Excellent Era’s entire team for their inability to guide one single member. His disappointment was never targeted towards any particular member of Excellent Era, but rather towards the entire team and the whole club. The difference in ideologies was the spark of the conflict between Ye Xiu and the club.

Finally, after all the self-sacrifices, he was remunerated by nothing but regrets and disappointment. These kinds of emotions never showed even when Excellent Era abandoned and mistreated him, but it surfaced when Excellent Era continued to decline.

Chen Guo watched Ye Xiu walk back to the room in silence. She found herself on the verge of tears and in a turmoil of emotions.

“You’re back?” In the room, Tang Rou was sitting on Ye Xiu’s seat, controlling Lord Grim when she saw Ye Xiu walk back in. She was telling the others that she was logging out.

“How long does it take to smoke a single cigarette?” Ye Xiu smiled.

“Oh, do you still want me to logout?” Tang Rou asked.

“Log me out.” Ye Xiu consented with a wave of his hand. If he didn't log out, the big guilds would definitely coming back to cause more trouble. He had enough troubles for awhile now. Running around took too much time. It was much more convenient to just logout.

“Okay.” Tang Rou nodded, told those around Lord Grim in the game, and logged out of the game. Then, she left the seat and gave it back to Ye Xiu.

“How’s the tenth server?” Ye Xiu asked half-mindedly upon seeing Tang Rou going back to her game.

“It’s the same as always: dungeons, leveling…” Tang Rou replied.

“You are already tackling the Heavenly Domain Challenge, aren’t you?” Ye Xiu asked again with a laughter.

“Yep! I’m trying.” Tang Rou answered.

“Didn’t you finish the challenge for boss once already? Why are you trying so hard?” Ye Xiu shook his head.

“I am just trying to find our difference in skill!” Tang Rou answered with a smile and looked at the door questioningly, “Where’s Guo Guo?”

“She’s still outside.” Ye Xiu spoke.

“Didn’t she go looking to talk to you?”

“When she walked over, I was crushing the cigarette on the windowsill. She caught me red-handed, so I ran away as fast as I could. Awkward!” Ye Xiu explained.

Tang Rou’s head poked out from behind the screen, and she peered at Ye Xiu, who sat across her to the side. In the end, only a sentence slipped out nonchalantly, ”So that’s it.”

“Hurry and level up. The Heavenly Domain is much more fun than regular servers.” Ye Xiu spoke.

“I can see that.” Tang Rou agreed with a nod.

No one spoke another word after. Everyone was minding their own business on their computers. Tang Rou was still in the game, tapping out a string of clicks on the mouse and keyboard. Ye Xiu left the game to the side. No one knew what he was doing.

After a few moments, Chen Guo came back into the room and settled herself in the seat directly across from Ye Xiu’s. Likewise, she didn’t say a word and dived straight into the game.

However, in the game, after Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim left, Loulan Slash and the others were still indulging in the joy of their victory. They couldn’t believe that they had actually defeated Excellent Era’s starting line up. They didn’t even notice that Deception had vanished.

Until another group of people appeared at the opening of the alley.

“Perfect! My ambitions are still burning right now!” Ocean Ahead yelled out in the front.

“Hahaha! Let’s go!” Loulan Slash didn’t stop anyone. All five of them were using alternates, so they weren’t afraid of being accused of being unfair. The guilds were all rivals, so no matter what you did, there was always someone who used unfair tricks. What’s important was that you couldn’t leave a handle on the surface for someone else to accuse you with. This was the rule for survival for the guilds. Loulan Slash and the others had been preparing for a long time, so they understood this rule pretty well.

“Let’s use them to practice our teamwork!” With a swing of Loulan Slash’s sword, the five charged ferociously at the group with the same amount of momentum as before.

The group at the end of the alley was a normal ten-people team. Uponing seeing the five rushing at them, the group immediately turned tail, just as like they had been ordered to do.

“D*mn! They’re no fun!” Ocean Ahead cursed, running ahead of the group.

“Should we chase them?” Homeward Bound asked.

“Yes! We have nothing to do anyways!” Loulan Slash yelled back.

The five ran after the group. They enjoyed the chase and the chaos that followed greatly. They still needed improvement before they could be compared to the pros, but in comparison with the regular players, their skills were unmatched. With the professional league as their goal, their teamwork was above most guild teams. Five versus ten posed no problem for them at all.

The guild masters had just received news and were hastily reorganizing troops. They were rushing over to supervise the battles by themselves.

Loulan Slash had no intention of playing guerrilla warfare. Instead, they wanted to see just how powerful the five of them could be as a team.

The five were brimming with pride after they crushed the starting team of Excellent Era. Despite the fact that they had seven people before and their victory was largely due to brilliant command of a God, their victory couldn’t have been possible without their teamwork and efforts. Their crushed confidence was re-ignited.

Compared to professionals, we are not all that great, but professional teams weren’t unbeatable.

All five of them had such realization in their hearts. At the same time, their performance was vicious as well. They slipped in and out of the chaos with surprising orderliness.

“Great! It feels so good!” Ocean Ahead was a total battle enthusiast. Stepping over the piles of dead bodies, he roared as spells exploded all around him. It was as if his battle cries were setting the rhythm of his spell releases.

“I say that you guys should at least pay some attention! Some dropped pretty useful equipment. Don’t forget to pick them up!” The Cleric, Thousand Falling Leaves, reminded his teammates while pocketing a light saber from a swordsman himself.

“True. Look at Deception. He even picked up Sun Xiang and Liu Hao’s equipments.” Loulan Slash commented.

“Of course, he’s a professional scrap picker. Things like that are instinct for him.” Night Tide agreed.

“Speaking about him, his skills are pretty good too. Should we try to recruit him?” Ocean Ahead stopped his shouting and began to talk business.

“That guy, so many guilds had their eyes on him, but none of them succeeded. Look at him, he doesn’t even know who Sun Xiang is. I don’t think he feigned ignorance. Who knows where that NEET came from.” Loulan Slash exclaimed.

“No matter how much of a NEET he is, he still plays Glory. To know utterly nothing about the pros, isn’t that a bit too extreme?” Ocean Ahead spoke.

“This huge world is filled with exceptions!” Loulan Slash exclaimed.

“Hey! Can you guys stop chatting now?! I can’t hold them off anymore!” Homeward Bound cried out at that moment. As more and more people gathered, the group was starting to have a difficult time holding on.

“Kill! Kill until we die!” Loulan Slash shouted, rushing over to help Homeward Bound.

The guild masters of the three guilds were present at the battlefield already. They were on the verge of tear of joy over the fact that they were actually able to surround their enemies this time. In the end, with a closer look, they only found five people… Why was it only five? Where were the other two?

After a thorough investigation, they still didn't know if the missing two were dead or just escaped their radar. Then they checked again, only to find that both of them had logged out.

‘F*ck!” The three guild masters were scratching the walls in frustration. Without their main targets, what was the point of attacking the five random characters from Heavenly Justice. What was the point?!

Chapter 502 – Bounty

Changing Spring and Arisaema were scratching their heads. Chen Yehui was also scratching his head, while asking for outside help. He had thought that once Liu Hao’s side moved out, their targets would be eliminated for sure. When he received the message that Liu Hao’s side had surrounded their target, he stopped caring about the situation.

He knew which open accounts he had given to Liu Hao and had them all added as friends. Among the ones previously online, one of them had been a Battle Mage. Chen Yehui was aware that this time, even Sun Xiang had come. When he looked at the other open accounts given, he saw that the players were Excellent Era’s starting roster. How could that team lose?

Chen Yehui didn’t think it would even be possible and he even thought he would need to call his troops to retreat soon. When he suddenly received the news, he woke up from his daydream and realized that Sun Xiang’s Battle Mage and Liu Hao’s Spellblade were offline. The other three were offline too.

Chen Yehui felt that something wasn’t right. When he gathered everyone to surround them, he discovered that Lord Grim and Deception were offline too.

What exactly had happened?

Changing Spring and Arisaema had no way of knowing. Chen Yehui knew a little bit of what had happened though. Could the five pros have logged off after killing those two?

However, those seven were together. If they fought, shouldn’t they have killed the other five too? Why were they still alive?

Puzzled, Chen Yehui picked up the phone and called Liu Hao. However, no one picked up.

“Could something have happened?” Chen Yehui felt certain that something bad had happened. Afterwards, he heard Changing Spring and Arisaema order their troops to kill the five players and he followed suit in order to vent his frustrations.

Loulan Slash’s group had never thought of staying alive. They were prepared to fight until their deaths. Because they had been prepared, when they died, they didn’t feel worried at all. After dying, they immediately revived. They had lost a bit of equipment from dying, but it couldn’t be compared to the three great guild’s losses today.

Today’s mess had finally come to an end. The players of the three guilds looked at each other in puzzlement.

In the end, they had only killed off the five mysterious invaders, but what about their original two targets? Where did they go?

Even though the guild leaders were racking their brains over this, they didn’t lose hope so quickly. They knew that this battle wasn’t something that could be resolved in one or two days.

With their targets offline, it wasn’t possible to fight them anymore, so the two guild leaders tasked players with spreading the word through the forums.

Lord Grim was now a public figure. Anyone who killed him would have their name spread far and wide. It hadn’t been an easy opportunity to come by, so they needed to hurry up and seize it.

Quickly, videos of Lord Grim and Deception fighting shoulder to shoulder appeared all over the Glory forums. The guild members cried about how these two guys had killed them to steal their items.

For the guilds, this was enough. They didn’t need to make Lord Grim look like an evil street thug. They just needed to let everyone know that they had good reason to kill Lord Grim.

The Club guilds only needed to provide a pretext to cause trouble.

Lord Grim and Deception had killed their players and stolen their items, which was why they had chased after them. It was a valid reason. Deception’s infamous name only made the story more legitimate. Many people would now see Lord Grim in a bad light. The guilds didn’t need to look at the results. They knew that they didn’t need to care about Lord Grim’s current fame anymore.

After completing the surface work, the three guilds gathered the other guilds together to make a joint declaration, denouncing scrap picking. Then, they announced their plan to pursue and kill Lord Grim and Deception to elaborate on their denunciation. Loulan Slash’s group of open accounts were also hung up on the blacklist.

All seven of them had a bounty placed on them. This time, the bounty reward wasn’t virtual rewards, but real money! Lord Grim and Deception were valued at five hundred yuan. If someone found Lord Grim or Deception and called the guilds over, as long as the target was found and successfully killed, the finder would receive five hundred yuan! Loulan Slash’s group was worth less money. Every person was only worth one hundred yuan.

Compared to the surface talk from before, this bounty was certainly much more eye-catching. In games like this with trade, everyone knew that the most valuable item in game was real money.

This wasn’t the first time a bounty like this had appeared, but if some random person put it up, you would need to convince people to believe you! No matter how much of a money warrior you were, money and trust were unrelated. You needed to build up trust in the people in order to do this type of transaction.

However, the bounty was being put up by the Club guilds! These guilds were certainly trustworthy. If they promised a reward, they would definitely pay out.

As long as you encountered someone with a bounty and called the guilds, you could earn real money. This money was too easy to get!

As for the Club guilds? On the surface, they simply used scrap picking as their pretense. This bounty was only the first wave. First, they would utilize Deception’s infamous name. Afterwards, they would decide the next step depending on the circumstances.

This was the first time the Club guilds had allied together for this type of activity. The online world immediately exploded and all sorts of discussions were created

The guilds in the tenth servers had been waiting for this day to come. Lord Grim! He had made them grind their teeth in anger for so long. Now was the time for his retribution. They wondered whether or not they should dig out the tenth server’s Guild Happy since Lord Grim had gone to the Heavenly Domain.

However, none of the guilds would agree to this suggestion.

Their reason for allying together and killing Lord Grim was because of the threat Lord Grim’s real identity and goals posed to the Clubs. As long as they could stop him from progressing, it would be enough. After all, Guild Happy was only a guild made up of normal players. Dragging all of Guild Happy’s members into this conflict wouldn’t look good for the Club guilds. Their image was still very important to them.

“Shameless, too shameless!!” The Club guilds’ announcement appeared as the headlines for all the Glory sites and forums. After Chen Guo saw it, she immediately became angry.

“Hm? Why?” Ye Xiu looked over and asked.

“Look!” Chen Guo gave Ye Xiu a link to the announcement.

“Okay okay……” Ye Xiu clicked on it and looked. After reading it, he asked Chen Guo: “What’s so shameless about it?”

“This this this….. How is this not shameless!?” Chen Guo pointed at the screen.

“Apart from saying that Deception and I are partners, everything else they said is true!” Ye Xiu said.

“What?” Chen Guo stared dumbly. Then, she looked again and thought about it.

Scrap picking? Ye Xiu had picked up scraps... Killed players? He really had killed quite a few players... Steal items? He had definitely stolen equipment for her Chasing Haze…… it really was the truth…..

“They’re using this to cover up their true motives.” Chen Guo shouted.

“Yeah, that sounds about right.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“Five hundred yuan each time! Tsk tsk tsk!” Tang Rou saw it and sighed.

“Sigh, I wonder if it counts if I go undercover! 500 yuan each time! If no Cleric came to revive me, every five deaths would mean I lose one level. That’s 2500 yuan. We won a total of 24 accounts from that other Internet Cafe. If all of them were killed until they hit zero experience, how much money would that be?” Ye Xiu began to calculate it in his mind.

“4.2 million!” Tang Rou helped Ye Xiu calculate it.

“I really want that money. Hmm, let me think……” Ye Xiu began to think seriously.

“Don’t even think about it!” Chen Guo almost flipped the table over.

“It probably doesn’t count if I go undercover. I’d have to use my real self……. Let me check Taobao.” Ye Xiu said.

“Taobao?”

“I wonder if they’re still selling unspecialized accounts. If they are, then I’ll just let them kill Lord Grim, but it’s been so many years. Do you think they’ll still have any unspecialized accounts?” Ye Xiu began to look. Not long afterwards, he got his answer, “Sigh, they really don’t have any! There aren’t any unspecialized accounts to buy.”

“You you you……”

“There might not be any unspecialized, but what about Ninjas! If we send Deception in to die, his account can earn us 170,000 right?” Ye Xiu calculated.

“175,000.” Tang Rou corrected.

‘NOOO!” Ye Xiu slammed his keyboard.

“What’s wrong?” Chen Guo hastily asked.

“I don’t think I added him as a friend. I wonder if I can still find a way to contact him.” Ye Xiu said in a sad voice.

Chen Guo rolled her eyes. She didn’t know what to say in response.

“Hm? Right, there’s also Loulan Slash’s five accounts. It’s just five open accounts. It doesn’t matter if they die. Free money!” Ye Xiu said.

“But they’ll be the ones earning the money. It’s not like they’ll give me any.” Ye Xiu said with a sigh.

“Do you really think they’ll stoop as low as you?” Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu with disdain.

“So you’re saying, they won’t even consider it?” Ye Xiu said.

“Of course!” Chen Guo didn’t think a famous money warrior like Loulan Slash would think about it.

“If that’s the case, then because we’re very close now, I’ll trade those five accounts for five of ours. Give them the same classes.” Ye Xiu said, while pulling out a drawer and looking over the 24 account cards. From these, he pulled out the five classes.

“Hey, you’re not actually going to do it right?” Chen Guo saw Ye Xiu’s actions and discovered that he was actually thinking about it.

“It’ll be money for my return to the pro scene! I didn’t think it’d be so easy to get though. Back then, getting money in game wasn’t so easy!” Ye Xiu said as he thought back to the old days.

Chen Guo’s head fell to the table. She just couldn’t see how this person was the same person who would sacrifice himself for his team.

It looked like she wasn’t looking at things the right way! Her insights had been completely wrong…...

Chapter 503 – Collaborator

Chen Guo couldn’t believe what was happening. She tapped her keyboard, got up from her seat, and then walked towards Ye Xiu.

When she looked over…..

It was real. It was actually happening. This guy was already on QQ chatting with Loulan Slash.

“You really have no shame!” Chen Guo cried.

“Did you see the declaration the top guilds made today?” Ye Xiu greeted Loulan Slash with a question.

“I saw it. Ha ha ha ha! We’re only worth 100 yuan. All of us together are only worth one of you. How depressing.” Loulan Slash replied. He was someone who knew how to find fun in things. He was conflicted about his bounty’s value!

“We’re all foils. Look at that declaration. Deception is the main focus.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha ha, naturally. He’s a scrap picker. Of course, he should stand out, but their emphasis is still mostly on you. They don’t want everyone to forget about you, so they also placed a 500 yuan bounty on you.” Loulan Slash understood the guilds’ intent.

“I came looking for you to discuss this.” Ye Xiu said.

“Mm, it really is troublesome. Our characters were just open accounts. We can just not use them, but it’s a lot tougher for you!” Loulan Slash sighed.

“That’s not it. My meaning is I wish to take that money.” Ye Xiu said.

The other side didn’t reply for a long time. Loulan Slash clearly knew what Ye Xiu’s intentions were.

Ye Xiu saw that the other side suddenly stopped talking and moved his QQ window around.

“God, are you serious……” Loulan Slash could only use ellipses to express his thoughts. He felt too embarrassed to say anything negative, but couldn’t think of anything positive to say.

“I can’t change my main account. Right now, I just don’t know if you’re interested or not. If you’re interested, then it’s fine. If you’re not, then I can exchange five of my open accounts for those five open accounts.” Ye Xiu said.

“There’s no need to trade. You can just have them.” After a short moment of silence, Loulan Slash gave a blunt answer.

“Wow! How nice of you! Do you want a share of the pot?”

“No need! No need!”

“You’re an investor too, so your share won’t be small!” Ye Xiu replied politely.

“No need. Really, there’s no need!” Loulan Slash refused.

“You’re too nice.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha ha ha, this small amount of money isn’t much to me. Really, believe me!” Loulan Slash didn’t want to be involved in this, so he spoke as if he were filthy rich.

“Okay, okay. If you don’t want to, I won’t force you.” Ye Xiu said.

“Uh, but speaking of this, even though the bounty is out, we might just be something said for appearances. That bounty says the target has to die for the reward to be paid. If they don’t kill the target, you won’t get the money.” Loulan Slash shifted to a different topic and dug into the issue with the guilds’ statement.

“Mm, I thought of this too, but if I’m controlling it myself, why do I have to let them kill me? I’ll kill myself off, record the death, and send it to them.” Ye Xiu said.

“But if you keep doing it over and over again, won’t it seem too fake?” Loulan Slash asked, “You can kill yourself in the game, but there’s only so many ways to do it, no?”

“That’s true, so I need a few collaborators. How about it?” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh no, my mom called me to come eat dinner. I’ve got to go. Give me an address and I’ll send those five accounts over to you. That’s all for now then. Bye!” Loulan Slash quickly logged off.

“Shameless! Too shameless!” Chen Guo muttered.

“Who would be less suspicious to collaborate with?” Ye Xiu pondered.

Chen Guo saw Ye Xiu’s and Loulan Slash’s chat exchange, looking down on him, while also beginning to think too.

Contact her friends to help? Chen Guo originally had this thought, but when she thought about it, no matter how many friends she had, it wouldn’t be enough! In order to kill all 5 characters until they dropped to level one would require 1750 deaths. Even if each friend could kill one character ten times, she would still need at least 175 friends. Ten times for one character was already very suspicious too.

The Heavenly Domain was the final destination for all ten servers. In order to accommodate all these players, the world was enormous. Finding a single person within that sea of players was like finding a needle in a haystack. Why else would the Club guilds place a bounty on them? The Club guilds were already considered extremely powerful forces in the game.

Chen Guo wasn’t able to think of a good solution. When she looked at Ye Xiu, his computer screen had the webpage for a game studio.

“Are you going to look for a studio?” Chen Guo asked.

“Aren’t studios very fair?” Ye Xiu said.

CHen Guo thought about it for a moment and agreed. For this type of buying and selling that required effort to complete, let alone one character being able to kill for a bounty ten times, killing the bounty a few more times wouldn’t be a problem, especially if they recorded it themselves. This was something a studio could easily do.

“Illusion Studio is a pretty good option.” Chen Guo sat to the side. She saw Ye Xiu skim over information on studios and recommended one of them as she saw him skim past.

“Really?” Ye Xiu opened up the description for Illusion Studio, but then closed it after reading it.

“What do you think?” Chen Guo was puzzled. Illusion Studio was a trustworthy, in-game, studio. They had many options and had good ratings. Chen Guo didn’t understand why Ye Xiu was unsatisfied with it.

“I’m going to keep looking.” Ye Xiu continued to search.

“Future is pretty good too.” Chen Guo recommended again. Experienced players usually had some understanding of studios, so they knew the more popular ones.

However, Ye Xiu looked at it and then rejected it too.

“What are you looking for?” Chen Guo didn’t know what he wanted.

“One that I’m familiar with.” Ye Xiu said.

“You….. you’re familiar with some of them?” Chen Guo was astonished.

“I’ve played this game for ten years. I have all sorts of connections.” Ye Xiu didn’t think much of it.

As he said this, he finally clicked on a studio that he was looking at. Chen Guo looked at it. This studio had a pretty low rating and the customer reviews were very mediocre. Most players would consider it a scam and wouldn’t do business with them. However, Ye Xiu didn’t look at these reviews and immediately clicked on the contact info. He really was looking for someone he recognized, and not a famous one.

“Mo Qiang, not a well known one…….” Ye Xiu muttered, while asking Chen Guo if he borrow her cellphone.

Chen Guo handed over her handphone and saw Ye Xiu quickly punch in the phone number listed for “Mo Qiang Studio”.

“Hello, old Mo?”

“Who is it?”

“Can’t you tell from my voice?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I can’t tell. This is a work phone. If you have business, say it.”

“Is your QQ XXX?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Yeah!” The other side was a bit suspicious.

“Let’s talk on QQ.” Ye Xiu hung up.

“If you know his QQ, why did you call him?” Chen Guo was puzzled.

“How could I know he’s doing this now? Shouldn’t I confirm it by phone first?” Ye Xiu said. He looked for the QQ username and messaged him.

“!!!!!” The other side replied with five exclamation marks.

“You were the one who called?” The other side followed.

“Yes, it was me.”

“You’re still alive!”

“Of course…..”

“If you’re alive, then why’d you retire????”

“......”

“Let’s chat later. First, let’s talk business.” Mo Qiang said.

“Did you see the bounty offered by the guilds?” Ye Xiu replied.

“Of course. Oh! You’re Lord Grim?”

“Yeah, that’s me!”

“D*mn! Are you planning on sacrificing your own account to give this bro some nice money to spend? Let me think about it. Each death is 500. One level five times. Level 70 to Level 1 means 175,000 yuan. We can also get a Cleric to revive you, so you double that and that’s 350,000! Since that’s just the Heavenly Domain. You can pretend to run back to the normal servers. If we go to the normal servers to kill you, then double it again for 700,000! Holy sh*t! You’re going to send your bro 700,000! You really are a God. You’re too enlightened!” Mo Qiang said.

“Did you finish calculating it?” Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. Chen Guo was frozen. He really was a f*cking professional! He maximized the amount of profit that could be earned. Ye Xiu and Tang Rou had calculated 175,000 yuan, but this figure was way too weak compared to the 700,000 that had just been mentioned.

“I obviously know you’re not here to give it to me for free. What are your conditions?” Mo Qiang asked.

“When did I say I was going to allow you to get Lord Grim killed?” Ye Xiu was speechless.

“Then what are you here for?” Mo Qiang was puzzled. It sounded like Ye Xiu wasn’t looking for him to do this.

“I have to use Lord Grim, but I can provide you the other five accounts who are on the hitlist.” Ye Xiu said.

“Which five accounts? Are you talking about the ones worth 100 each?” Mo Qiang said.

“Yes……”

“Those five. Isn’t that a bit too small? The net profit is only only worth one Lord Grim for all five…… What about Deception? Can you get that one?” Mo Qiang asked.

“I can’t……”

“How regretful.” Mo Qiang expressed.

“Can you do it?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I can. Of course, I can! However, you’re going to need to give me the details. I have to do some analysis to see how I should go about this.” Mo Qiang asked.

Ye Xiu gave him a general explanation. Mo Qiang listened and expressed some of his disappointment: “So it’s like that….. Those accounts are clearly just for appearance. With how crafty those guys are, if you only provide them with information, they won’t give you the money. Even if we do it like you say, at a certain point, they’ll remove the bounty and you won’t get the maximum theoretical profit possible.”

“True.” Ye Xiu wasn’t too surprised. He had clearly thought about this too.

“If we just directly kill you until they stop giving the bounty, then it’ll be very fake…… but then again, this amount of money isn’t much to them anyways. Plus, it’s all of the Clubs combined. With their work ethic, I doubt they’d go back on their word.” Mo Qiang asked.

“They shouldn’t.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then we’ll do it like that then! We won’t revive with a Cleric either. If we do it too excessively, they won’t be happy with us getting so greedy. We have to leave them some face.” Mo Qiang suggested after thinking about it some more.

“Then it’s set?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Bullsh*t. What’s my share?” Mo Qiang asked.

“I’ll give you half.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay okay okay. God is still a God. How daring. Then I’ll go arrange it.” Mo Qiang said.

“Okay.”

“Alright, let’s chat then. Why did you retire?” Mo Qiang asked.

Chapter 504 – Unending News

Even though Ye Xiu didn’t have a cellphone, he still frequently used QQ as a communication tool. When he had retired, many people had messaged him, but he ignored all of them. Back then, Mo Qiang had asked him about it too and, now that he had been contacted, he used this opportunity to chat.

“It’s quite a long story. Let’s talk about it when I’m less busy!” Ye Xiu avoided the subject.

“Are you really planning on creating your own team?” Mo Qiang asked.

“I have thought about doing so.” Ye Xiu said.

“So this is to help raise money for it?” Mo Qiang asked.

“Not entirely.” Ye Xiu replied.

“It looks like you’re not having an easy time. This bro won’t take half then. I’ll just take profit from two of the accounts.” Mo Qiang said.

“Thanks!” Ye Xiu didn’t refuse.

“I say we just have those five accounts party up and then kill them together.” Mo Qiang clearly wasn’t very insistent on chatting and quickly returned back to discussing business.

“I’ll leave it up to you then!”

“Alright! Just wait for the money to arrive!”

With the deal completed, Ye Xiu turned his head. Chen Guo was still beside him and had a complicated expression on her face.

“Hey, it isn’t easy starting from scratch.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was startled. She felt as if her heart had been pricked again. Ye Xiu took out a cigarette and told her he was going out for a smoke.

Chen Guo went back to her game. Right now, quite a few people were talking about the news. Some people just randomly sent out coordinates, saying Lord Grim was here or that Lord Grim was there. They were making fun of the guilds. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim wasn’t even online.

Not just Lord Grim, but Deception and Loulan Slash’s five open accounts weren’t there either. The players could only shout loudly. If their targets weren’t online, what could they do?

The guilds were obviously paying close attention to them. Them not being online was a success for them in a way. After all, their goal was to stop Ye Qiu from levelling.

Ye Xiu finished smoking his cigarette and returned. He logged into the game. On a different computer, Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze received a notification indicating a friend had logged on.

“You’re still going to keep playing?” Chen Guo was astonished.

“Why not?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Be careful!” Chen Guo said.

“Yeah, I know, but I’m only going to leveling areas without many people. I’ll take a look at the circumstances and see whether or not there’ll be people wandering around hoping to catch sight of me.” Ye Xiu said.

“I imagine there’ll be quite a few people doing that.” Chen Guo said. She understood a player’s mind. Five hundred yuan wasn’t much, but it wasn’t a small amount either. One of the main purposes of the game was to strengthen one’s character. If the five hundred yuan was spent on a piece of equipment or an item, it would definitely be able to purchase a top quality item. There would be players who would try to test their luck.

“Mm, if it doesn’t look good, I’ll run.” Ye Xiu said.

“If you really need an unspecialized account, you can just look for someone to level it up for you. It wouldn’t take very long.” Chen Guo said. She understood that Lord Grim himself wasn’t worth much. It was mostly the Silver weapon that was valuable to them. Apart from a few bored players or collectors, there probably wouldn’t be any other unspecialized characters out there. However, a studio wouldn’t care. As long as you needed one, they would level one for you. It was just a matter of how much you paid. All he had to do was transfer the Silver weapon to the new account and character. If he did that, wouldn’t he be able to avoid all of the hunting and grinding? Lord Grim could also be used to earn some money too. This was what Chen Guo was thinking.

“Ha ha, I’ll do it if I don’t have any other options!” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo heard this and knew he had already thought about it before, so she didn’t say anymore.

“Where are you?” Chen Guo asked. After Ye Xiu told her his location, Chen Guo immediately had Chasing Haze head over.

As she moved towards his location, Chen Guo discovered a few players moving in a similar direction as her. It seemed like quite a few had noticed that Lord Grim had come online. Everyone knew Lord Grim’s level too. He could only move about in the Level 55 leveling area, so they immediately headed towards it.

“It looks like quite a few players are heading towards the Level 55 leveling area.” Chen Guo said to Ye Xiu.

“Ha ha, the leveling area is so large. They won’t be able to find me so easily.” Ye Xiu said as he continued to level up. He was still in Wilderness Town, a Level 55 area.

As he killed monsters, Ye Xiu looked for a place convenient for observing the surroundings. He didn’t move around randomly either. If he didn’t see anyone around, he would stay there. If he moved around randomly, it was more likely that he would bump into someone.

Even so, he wasn’t able to kill monsters peacefully the entire time. After a period of time, Lord Grim finally noticed a player heading towards him. With his current situation, it didn’t matter if the player was in a guild or not. Now that a bounty had been place on his head, it really was as if he had become a street rat. He wasn’t just any street rat, but a street rat worth five hundred yuan.

Chen Guo was concerned about Ye Xiu’s situation and switched to a computer next to Ye Xiu to play. She constantly glanced at Ye Xiu’s screen. She saw how unsafe Ye Xiu’s leveling was and would turn her attention to his screen from time to time. Fortunately, Ye Xiu had lots of experience and an incredible amount of skill. Whenever he saw a player, he immediately hid. With the distance between them, the other side wouldn’t be able to see Lord Grim’s ID clearly, so Ye Xiu hadn’t been in any danger yet.

“Are you sure someone isn’t following you?”

Chen Guo was worried that someone might be following Ye Xiu. However, it was Ye Xiu who reminded her of something.

Chen Guo stared blankly. She turned her Chasing Haze around and immediately saw a bunch of players following her. She couldn’t hide her surprise after turning around.

Chen Guo suddenly understood. Some of them might have known about her relationship with Lord Grim, so they tried to see if they could get their five hundred yuan through her. Thinking of this, Chen Guo began to sweat. She really had been looking for Lord Grim. If Ye Xiu hadn’t reminded her, she would have guided a whole bunch of players over to his location. She had been concerned about Ye Xiu’s situation and nearly caused a disaster.

“You don’t need to worry. Nothing will happen. People will watch you closely if you’re online and might look for you if they need something. How about you go play in the tenth server for now? You can help manage the guild while you’re over there.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo looked at the crowd of people behind her. There was nothing she could do about it, so she accepted Ye Xiu’s suggestion. At the tenth server, she had an account which was in Guild Happy too. Her position there wasn’t low either. Her character’s level might be low, but the guild knew that her main account was a Heavenly Domain character.

As a result, Chen Guo began managing the tenth server guild. Ye Xiu was having a difficult time in the Heavenly Domain. Even though he hadn’t been killed yet, his leveling speed had been greatly affected. Chen Guo had been very anxious at first, but when she saw that Ye Xiu didn’t seem to care at all, she became more at ease.

On Saturday, an unexpected result appeared in the Pro Alliance. In the match between Excellent Era and Thunderclap, Excellent Era had been completely crushed.

Ye Qiu had retired and Sun Xiang had taken his place. After a period of ups and downs, Excellent Era seemed to have returned to their best shape. Even though there wasn’t any hope of making it to the playoffs this season, with their recent results, Excellent Era had once again become a strong competitor for next year’s championship.

But in this match, everyone in Excellent Era showed a terrible performance. The end result was 1:9. Throughout the entire competition, they had only won a single point from the individual competition. The rest of the competition was plagued with mistakes. Excellent Era’s players looked as if they had something else on their minds.

Especially during the team competition. Xiao Shiqin’s Team Thunderclap was relatively weak in the individual competition and group knockout competitions, but with a Master Tactician leading their team, no one would ever underestimate them in team competitions. In the team competition, Excellent Era lost magnificently.

The media was stunned. Excellent Era fans were also stunned. Even the victorious Team Thunderclap was stunned. In the post-match interviews, when Thunderclap’s Captain Xiao Shiqin was asked about Excellent Era’s loss, he couldn’t find anything good to say because there simply wasn’t anything Excellent Era had done well during that battle. In the end, he lied saying “their performance wasn’t bad, but luck just wasn’t with them today.”

Happy Internet Cafe didn’t stream Excellent Era’s matches like usual, so there weren’t as large of an audience. However, there were still quite a few players who watched the match on their own. That day, Happy Internet Cafe was also in an uproar. Excellent Era’s disgusting performance made many jump out and praise Chen Guo for not streaming their match. It was their one bit of salvation from the disaster.

The customers, who had watched the match, all looked as if they had eaten a fly. They ran out the door and began throwing rocks at the nearby Club Excellent Era. This match had even taken place in Excellent Era’s home stadium. Those who had watched the match live had gathered around, refusing to leave and shouted angrily at Excellent Era.

Excellent Era wasn’t a stranger to this scene though. Their performance in the first half of the year had been very bad. Fans had done this before.

However, no matter how poorly they had performed, the hate they got had never been this bad. Today’s performance could be described with two words: unprecedented brutality.

Just when everyone’s hopes had been rekindled, Team Excellent Era dumped a bucket of cold water over it. The disappointed fans gathered around in the winter cold and refused to leave for a long time. Excellent Era could only look at the scene in shame. The spokesperson, manager, and team members all went out to apologize as well as promise that they would do better in the future.

However, were they actually sincere in their promises?

Sun Xiang, Liu Hao…… Excellent Era’s main team all had dead expressions on their faces.

Chapter 505 – To Relegations

The web game had its own liveliness, while the pro league had its own news.

Excellent Era had always been the center of attention. After all, they were a seasoned and well-known team in the Alliance. Before this season, they had always been contenders for the champion spot. However, this season, the characters being paid attention to were different. From the beginning of the season, Excellent Era was very unstable. Their captain and ace player changed halfway through the season and the team seemed to be on the rise again. However, a few weeks earlier, vice captain Liu Hao had a disastrous performance and the team was in complete disarray. Their last two performances were so bad that their defeats would go down in the history books.

The press and newspaper once again used the headlines that they had been using throughout the season: What Happened to Excellent Era???

This time, they added additional words in their headlines: What Is Actually Going on with Excellent Era???

Excellent Era’s public relation team appeared helpless in the face of this historical disaster. Their fans were tired of their empty promises and wanted results instead of empty talk. Before it happened, they would never stop making their dissatisfaction known.

In Excellent Era’s inter-team meeting, the manager could sense that something wasn’t right.

Despite his shouting, his only response to it were the dead expressions on the team. Sun Xiang, Liu Hao, Shen Jian… All of the main players appeared to be out of it.

The worried looks on their faces were not for the team, but for their own futures. Right now, Excellent Era was a sinking ship and the people that were supposed to be the fixers of the ships were thinking about matters after the ship had sunk.

The sight that played out before him frightened the manager. The poor performance during the first half of the season could be brushed aside as a period of transitioning, but what about now? He didn’t know how the situation had gone out of hand so quickly and he had no solution to it…

Pacing back and forth unsure of what to do, the manager decided to conclude the meeting. He hadn’t achieved the outcome that he had hoped would happen through this meeting. The only thing he obtained through the meeting was knowledge on how grave the situation looked. He had no choice but to pull out his phone, “Boss….”

Although in-game players paid attention to the pro scene, the game wouldn’t be directly affected by news from the pro scene. Dungeons, missions, and PK’s between players continued regardless. The disastrous performance of Excellent Era, however, was a disgrace in the eyes of their fans as well as a subject of ridicule for their opponents.

Chen Yehui managed the in-game guild. The pro team’s poor performances had nothing to do with him. However, as a core member of the club, he could clearly feel the heavy atmosphere within the club.

What happened to Liu Hao and his companions last time? Chen Yehui couldn't muster the courage to ask. He came across Liu Hao several times since then, but Liu Hao always seemed to have something else in his mind and walked past him without noticing him.

He Ming, Shen Jian, Zhang Jiaxing...

Everyone he encountered looked like they were troubled. As for Sun Xiang, according to the information that Chen Yehui had gathered, it was said that he had isolated himself in his room and only came out for training and meal times.

With the situation being so serious, Chen Yehui didn’t dare to do anything rash. He came to the conclusion that going back to the game and completing his responsibilities was the safest way to go.

Progress in the game remained the same as before. The bounties placed on Lord Grim and Deception didn’t seem to affect them.

The leaders of the big guilds understood that even though there were a lot of names on their wanted list, 6 out of 7 of them were just dummies. Lord Grim. Their only target was Lord Grim. This was precisely the reason that they reacted to news regarding Lord Grim while ignoring the rest.

But what about Lord Grim? They had received a lot of information about him in these past few days, but they still hadn’t managed to catch a glimpse of him. They weren’t even sure if the information that they received were real or just to pull their legs. Later, the guilds required reports to confirm the target and keep the target in sight until they arrived. But when they thought about it, who was it they were supposed to keep in sight? Ye Qiu! Three guilds had allied together and sent out over a hundred players to lock down Wilderness Town. Even so, Ye Qiu had still been able to escape from their eyes. How could a single player keep him in sight for so long? It would only possible if Ye Qiu didn’t care and intentionally let someone pursue him.

Would Ye Qiu be so careless with his current circumstances? Clearly not. For the past few days, Lord Grim was nowhere to be seen despite being online. The intelligence received by the big guilds decreased by the day. After the initial hype, not many were actually willing to try their luck in low level zones.

Was this another wasted effort? Each club-backed guild was puzzled. Why couldn’t they defeat Lord Grim even when such a strong weapon, the renminbi, was employed.

One week passed in the blink of an eye and a new round of the weekly pro matches began. Other than the Glory fans that cared about the top 8, the number of fans that were concerned that their teams would be disqualified increased as well.

In terms of the long-term competition system of the professional league, doing horribly in a game or two wouldn’t decide the overall situation. The two teams that usually got relegated were usually teams that that had been at the back of the pack due to their lack of actual strength. But for the first half of the current season, Excellent Era had dropped low because of their continuous bad performances. A few good matches came after switching ace players, but the collapse that followed right after made many feel that Excellent Era had returned to the bottom. A contender for relegations was back!

If Excellent Era actually got relegated, it would not be a small matter.

With only 8 seasons, the development of Glory’s competitive scene was still considered quite short. The rise and fall of a powerhouse hadn’t occurred in history yet, but in this season, Excellent Era might just fulfill that role. Could the champions who once led to the creation of the first empire in the history of Glory be trying to change the history of Glory again, but this time in the completely opposite direction?

Reports from the mass media were full of such sarcasm. Even though they were no longer as invincible as back in their days as reigning champions for three years, Excellent Era was still a strong competitor. However, they had suddenly plunged into the possibility of relegation without any warning as if to surprise the masses.

Excellent Era’s rivals took pleasure in their misfortune, while their supporters were ridden with anxiety. Their next match began with much attention to it. Excellent Era would be the away team facing against Samsara.

Samsara had been the host of the All Star Weekend, but unfortunately, their team didn’t show anything very outstanding. Despite that, their morale were exceptionally high after the All Star Weekend. Excellent Era was demoralized after their disastrous last match and was unlucky to face such a team with high spirits, but it was also a chance for them.

If they were going to defeat Samsara, they would need to pay tremendous effort to do so. Btut if they managed to defeat them, it would be very strong evidence that their strength hadn’t faded.

Could Excellent Era make it? The fans of Excellent Era weren’t the only ones paying attention to this match. Even Happy Internet Cafe was broadcasting this match. Chen Guo’s current policy was to stream important matches, so she didn’t avoid Excellent Era on purpose. This match would without a doubt be one of the the most important matches of the season.

Happy Internet Cafe was once again full of customers, but the atmosphere was very heavy. There might be neutral fans watching the match elsewhere, but at this specific location, almost all of the audience members were Excellent Era supporters who were watching with sweat covering their palms. There were no cheers when the match started, no shouts of approval for their favorite players. Everyone was silently and anxiously paying attention to the match.

Su Mucheng won the first individual match, bringing everyone’s spirits up.

In the second match, vice captain Liu Hao managed to win too and the atmosphere in Happy Internet Cafe suddenly livened up.

Even Chen Guo let out a breath that she had been holding in. Her wish to see Excellent Era fail miserably faded after seeing Ye Xiu’s dejected expression. She suddenly began to hope that Excellent Era could make a comeback.

Without a doubt, Chen Guo was a typical fangirl. Su Mucheng was still a member of Excellent Era! If Excellent Era fell into disarray, wouldn’t Su Mucheng be affected as well? Just imagining this made Chen Guo hope that Excellent Era would deliver.

Chen Guo stole a glance at Ye Xiu, who was smoking at the doorway. The guy was expressionless, as if the 2 wins were nothing to him.

Excellent Era lost the third round. The Internet Cafe was filled with sighs of regret, but the atmosphere was way better than it had been when the match first started. At least the place was getting more lively.

The group arena competition that followed was like a heavy rain, drenching the audience’s morale heavily. There was only one player that took part in the team knockout tournament from Samsara’s side, Zhou Zekai.

1v3!

Zhou Zekai scoring a 1v3 in the team knockout tournament with his stylish Sharpshooter may have been dazzling, but nobody was in the mood to appreciate his magnificent skills. Most of them wanted to eat Zhou Zekai alive.

At this grave moment, a cheer emanated from amongst the crowd, “Awesome!”

The cheer could only be towards Zhou Zekai. The crowd looked for the source of the voice with fury in their eyes. The owner of the voice was luckily a beautiful girl. If it were a guy, the emergency services would be needing to take a field trip to Happy Internet Cafe.

The atmosphere of the internet cafe regressed immediately to a state similar to when the game had first started. The team competition started with great anxiety amongst the audience. Lasting for 30 minutes, the match was just of moderate length, but it caused Excellent Era fans to wince with pain.

Defeated. Once again, they had suffered defeat.

2 : 8 was the final score, with only a difference of one point compared to their last match. Although not as disgusting as their last match, Excellent Era’s team remained in low spirits, retaining their horrible performance. This was made obvious by the team competition.

“F*ck!” The air in Happy Internet Cafe was filled with strings of curses.

Chapter 506 – Xiaoqiang Productions

Curses filled the air. Quite a few audience members stood up and kicked away their chairs, just like the ending of a movie in the cinemas. In their agitated state, there was no order when the audience left the place. Individuals at the front of the crowd were cursed at whenever they slowed down. The chaos didn’t subside even after a long time. Most of them went across the street, throwing bricks, vandalizing the walls, but how could Excellent Era’s guards have the courage to stop them?

They watched or at least saw the results of the match. The moment the saw that Excellent Era had lost again, they knew it would be a disaster. At that moment, the only thing they could do was shut the main entrance. The best they could do was to stop the crowd from entering their headquarters and wrecking it from within.

Chen Guo was stunned by the result of the stampede. A lot of her customers didn’t intend to destroy her Internet Cafe intentionally, but in their moment of rage, much destruction was wrought upon the facilities. Chen Guo realized that her previous decision had been a blessing in disguise. The popularity and income of the Internet Cafe suffered drastically from her action of cancelling the broadcast of Excellent Era’s match, but with the team’s current performance, she was lucky that she stopped the broadcast. With their disgusting performance, her Internet Cafe would be the audience’s first place to release their rage. If the situation continued, her Internet Cafe would’ve been dismantled.

While directing her staff to clean up the place, Chen Guo glanced at the doorway, Ye Xiu was already gone. She shifted her view and saw that a huge crowd had formed outside Excellent Era’s entrance. It wasn’t as bad as last time though. They knew that it was an away match and that not many of the staffs members were around.

Excellent Era had lost to Samsara, who were at the peak of their performance, so the media gave them a bit of leeway and didn’t show too much disappointment towards Excellent Era’s performance.

However, having scored only a meager three points total from their last two matches, Excellent Era’s ranking plunged. Their score this season wasn’t high to begin with and they had only barely increased their ranking with their previously stable performances the last few games. The blunder that they’d made caused their ranking to drop, and they were headed straight towards disqualification.

“If this continues, will Excellent Era be eliminated?” Chen Guo went upstairs and was surprised that Ye Xiu had not logged into the game yet and was in the living room instead.

“I don’t know…….” Ye Xiu replied as he looked out through the window.

That night, Ye Xiu didn’t spend any time on the game, but the next morning, he headed straight to the computer.

He continued levelling his character, but not long after logging into the game, he received a message from Mo Qiang on QQ.

“God d*mn, after working on this for a week, I’ve finally finished it!” said Mo Qiang.

“It’s done?” After Ye Xiu’s discussion with Mo Qiang last time, he gave Mo Qiang’s address to Loulan Slash and the five accounts were sent straight to him, giving him full access to the accounts.

“It’s done. Let me send a short clip to you!” Mo Qiang sent Ye Xiu a video file.

After receiving the file, Ye Xiu clicked into it and the words “Xiaoqiang Productions” appeared on screen in a comical fashion.

“Your introduction…” Ye Xiu hesitated.

“Brand consciousness is a must!” replied Mo Qiang.

“You’re overdoing it... your deal with the Clubs is like ripping hair out of their heads. They’re going to hate you for doing this and you actually made an intro to deepen their impression of you?” Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry.

“Ayy! You’re right about that. It’s not like I’m going to have any more business relationships with these Clubs, so I’m going to gross them out.” said Mo Qiang.

“If you push them too far, they might not pay you for this!” said Ye Xiu.

“Oh they can’t.” Mo Qiang sent a sly smile emoticon, “I’ve already made preparations, they will pay me no matter what, unless they don’t care about their reputation anymore.”

Ye Xiu kept quiet. He guessed that Mo Qiang would be doing this deal in the open, where it could be seen by all the players. Under these circumstances, the clubs wouldn’t be able to go back on their words. Even if they knew that Mo Qiang was tricking them, they could only suffer in silence.

But with so many guilds offering the bounty, the expense would be shared between them. With the sum divided amongst themselves, it wouldn’t be considered much. Just as Mo Qiang said, even if it did not affect them financially, it was more important that they gross them out.

Ye Xiu didn’t comment on Mo Qiang’s mischievous joke because he knew that Mo Qiang didn’t have a good view of these Clubs.

“Do what you want! I only care for the money.” Ye Xiu replied with an “Emotionless” emoticon.

“Keep watching my video, I’ve been working on it for a week and the only thing you’ve watched is the introduction? How could you!” Mo Qiang grumbled.

“I’m watching, I’m watching…” Ye Xiu continued watching the video helplessly.

The main theme of the video appeared right after the introduction, starting with a chaotic battle. Mo Qiang grouped the 5 accounts together, creating a scenario where the party was annihilated in battle. The footage was shaky, hinting that the person recording the video was also a part of the battle. The video ended with 5 corpses on the ground, with the shot stopping at each ID.

“The party was annihilated, but they don’t revive themselves and they just lay there so you can get a clean shot on them? Isn’t this too take? You really intend to disgust them to death!” said Ye Xiu.

“Hahaha, keep watching!” Mo Qiang continued.

Ye Xiu continued to watch the video. The footage zoomed out as if the character were backing off and looking around, while paying close attention to the corpses lying on the ground. Not long afterwards, a Cleric appeared on camera. Ye Xiu immediately understood his intention.

It was scripted. Everything was scripted to giving the chance for his opponents to be rescued by their Cleric and then ambushing them.

“......” Even Ye Xiu was speechless.

“Haha, if the characters respawn, we still need to control them. I was a little lazy. By doing this, even if they counted these two occasions as one, it’s still quite convenient!” said Mo Qiang.

“You often use this method. It’s too disgusting.” said Ye Xiu.

“Yeah yeah, that was why I made it look like they saw through it after a few times and then stopped doing it. We want to decrease our workload, but we can make it look realistic at the same time! For the viewing pleasure of the higher ups of the clubs, it can’t be done too crudely, right?”

“With these five accounts moving around so frequently, won’t people notice them?” said Ye Xiu.

“Who would notice them faster than our own guys? I notified the big guilds every time, saying how I found these five player’s whereabouts. But these guilds are really sly. These five characters had a bounty placed on them to fool the public. They don’t even care about them. I’ve never seen any one of their men come over. I’m guessing the others that gave them intelligence on these five were also ignored. I was lucky that I had a trick up my sleeve. Xiaoqiang’s product, home made. I feel good earning this money.” Mo Qiang prattled on.

“In the end they’re all bald?” asked Ye Xiu. Being “bald” meant that all the experience points on the characters were gone. Even though their levels were still at 70, if you opened up their character info pages and looked at their stats, you would break into tears.

“Sigh, speaking of which, we made a mistake in our calculations. The minimum level a character can have in Glory is level 1, there is no level 0, so to make these Level 70 characters go bald, there are only 69 levels. With 500 yuan per level and 5 times 69 levels, we’ll only get a grand total of 172,500. The sum that we came up with, 175,000, was incorrect!” Mo Qiang continued!

“So how much are you going to get in the end..…” said Ye Xiu.

“I didn’t finish off all of their levels. It would be too unrealistic, so I got a total of 150,000.” said Mo Qiang.

“This isn’t realistic either.” said Ye Xiu.

“Isn’t 150,000 easier to divide? We’re aiming to decrease our workload.” said Mo Qiang.

“Sure, sure. I’ve finished watching the video, do what you have to do!” said Ye Xiu.

“I intend to leave it there for a few more days, but I’m afraid that they’d suddenly cancel the bounty. I heard that even after so many days, they still couldn’t get ahold of you right? Why don’t you give them some hope? Dying once or twice. Isn’t there’s a huge pile of money waiting for you after that? Make some sacrifices. Huh? Come on!” Mo Qiang continued earnestly.

“Stop spewing nonsense, if you’re afraid that the bounty will be canceled, do it faster.” said Ye Xiu.

“But there is also a possibility that they will increase the bounty. Raising yours to a thousand, and if these accounts’ got increased by about 200 yuan, it would still be a very big profit!” said Mo Qiang.

“Don’t be too greedy. If the amount is too big, aren’t you afraid that they’d rather lose face than to pay the bounty? Everything has a limit!” said Ye Xiu.

“Yes yes yes, you are right. Fine! I’ll cash in on the bounty, give me your account number, I’ll send the money later.” said Mo Qiang.

“Slow down, I have a list of things here that I need, so help me acquire those.” said Ye Xiu.

“What do you need?” asked Mo Qiang.

When the shoplist was received by Mo Qiang, he immediately understood Ye Xiu’s attention after a glance, “You’re going to upgrade that Silver Equipment of yours!”

“Yes!”

“You’re upgrading it to level 50, am I right?” Mo Qiang continued. Each equipment and materials had their own levels. The level of the materials used to forge a piece of silver equipment wasn’t limited, but it was still based on the level of the end product. Guessing the level of the equipment was simple just by looking at the list of materials.

“Yes.”

“I don’t have all the things you need. How could this be a single weapon? This is enough for an entire set!” Mo Qiang was amazed.

“I know you have your ways of getting it done. The money is with you, just help me out here. Is it enough?” said Ye Xiu.

“It’s hard to say, Orange Equipment is easy to get, but you need three materials that are only dropped by wild bosses, which are mostly owned by the big guilds. It’s tough luck for the studios. Even if others have them, if we try getting it, they will certainly raise the price unreasonably, you know that.” said Mo Qiang.

“Yes, I know.” Ye Xiu nodded. There was no market price for such rare materials. They were so rare that they couldn’t even form a market out of it. Such items could accurately be described by “rare commodity”. If any workshops got their hands on them, they would only sell them when the time is right.

“Then, leave it to me!” said Mo Qiang.

Chapter 507 – Leave It Alone

Three of the materials required to upgrade the Thousand Chance Umbrella to its Level 50 form only came from wild BOSSes. No other upgrades had required such luxurious materials thus far.

This was because the upgrade process from Level 5 to 45 could be considered relatively easy to accomplish, but from Level 45 to 50, the capabilities of the Thousand Chance Umbrella would be completely branch out. When the Thousand Chance Umbrella had been designed, Level 50 had been its final form. Leaving the extremely precious materials until the final form was done in order to save materials needed for the previous upgrades. Most Silver equipment followed this train of thought. If materials could be saved from previous upgrades, then it was best to save them.

However, the current Silver equipment had their final upgrades from Level 65 to 70, while the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s final upgrade was still stuck at Level 45 to 50.

The current tenth server might not even be able to gather together enough materials needed for this upgrade. However, Ye Xiu was already in the Heavenly Domain and he could acquire these materials through others from older servers. Items could go forward, but not backwards in the Heavenly Domain and normal servers. In other words, items from normal servers could be brought into the Heavenly Domain, but items from the Heavenly Domain couldn’t be brought back to normal servers, unless the item originally came from the normal server. If a player had any sort of item from the Heavenly Domain, the player would have to store it in the Heavenly Domain before going back to the normal server.

After finishing his deal with Mo Qiang, Ye Xiu continued to level up. He played cautiously every day, not allowing anyone find his tracks. Even though this slowed down his leveling speed, he slowly wore away at the patience of bounty hunters. Ye Xiu had predicted this would happen. At first, everyone would be filled with excitement, but after awhile, most people would give up on trying their luck and would stop wasting their time.

Chen Guo saw how the situation had turned for the better, so she logged into her Chasing Haze and began to help him level. Helpers would increase his leveling speed, so Ye Xiu didn’t refuse her assistance.

They killed monsters for the entire morning. After eating lunch, everyone took a short break. Chen Guo took this time to browse the internet. She checked the forums and saw a post created by Mo Qiang. Seeing this, she hastily called for Ye Xiu to come over and see.

Ye Xiu went over and looked. Sure enough, Mo Qiang had posted videos of him killing those five open accounts. It wasn’t all of it though. There would be too many videos and file size would have been too big. He only posted the videos that he had sent Ye Xiu to take a look at. It was only a small portion of all of them. The main content of the post was the text. Mo Qiang told everyone of how hard he had been working for the whole week. This cunning fellow didn’t even mention that the amount he had killed was worth 150,000 yuan. Killing them that many times in the span of a single week would clearly be too fake. Were those five fake? If those five knew that they would be pursued every day, why would they stay online and letting their experience drop?

Just from these videos and this text, it seemed like Mo Qiang had truly gone through great difficulties just to kill these five a few times, which was why he went on the forums to express his joy.

“F*ck these Clubs!”

Ye Xiu was reading through these posts, when he received a message from Mo Qiang.

“What?” Ye Xiu was surprised. Would the Clubs really not reward him for cashing in the bounty? Ye Xiu hadn’t thought that this would happen, but Ye Xiu also needed this money. Getting the materials he needed just through in-game methods would be extremely difficult! Ye Xiu didn’t mind using real life money in this case. The more time he could save, the better.

“They said today is Sunday. Wait until Monday!” Mo Qiang typed furiously.

“Oh…… then just wait!” Ye Xiu saw his reply and broke out into a laugh. It was a very normal response. No one would be willing to work on the weekend or work overtime for something so trivial.

“Do you think they’re going to try to keep on delaying it?” Mo Qiang clearly didn’t have a good image of the Clubs.

“For something like this? Just wait. There’s more to come!” Ye Xiu calmly said.

“What?”

“Do you think you’re talking to a real person? The Club is still a company. No matter how they run, it’s going to take them awhile to process it. If you get it by next week, then that would already be considered quite quick.” Ye Xiu said.

“I’m just afraid that long delays will cause trouble!” Mo Qian said, “If I knew there would be a delay, I wouldn’t have posted it today. What happens if I rustle the grass and scare a snake?”

“You can always delete posts you know…..” Ye Xiu said.

“Right right right, I’ll delete it first.” Mo Qiang immediately went to do it. Fortunately, he had just posted it, so it hadn’t gotten much attention yet. After deleting it, he repeatedly searched the post on Baidu and let out a sigh of relief after seeing no one had reproduced it.

Chen Guo saw the treacherous dealings going on between these two, but didn’t have the energy to scold them.

That day, at Club Excellent Era, a huge number of fans had gathered at its entrance again to protest. It was Sunday, and they clearly didn’t have much else to do.

Despite protesting, it still showed the fans’ passion. With Excellent Era’s recent performances, they couldn’t just turn a blind eye towards the fans, so they sent some people out to calm them down and provided them with food and drinks. Later, it was said that they invited a few representatives of the fans to go inside and have a chat…..

A chaotic day passed by just like that.

The next day was a business day, so Mo Qiang did the same thing that he had done yesterday. He made a post and contacted the Clubs for the rewards.

“Oh? You killed them? And you have video proof??”

The person who replied today was someone who managed this type of work, not an answering machine.

“Yeah, should I send over the videos?” Mo Qiang asked.

“Sure, go ahead!” The manager clearly didn’t care.

“Okay.” Mo Qiang replied. He sent the files and the other side received them. Afterwards, he commented: “This is for 104 kills.”

“How many?” The manager rubbed his eyes as if he had read the message incorrectly. He felt like it would only be a few times at most for a few hundred yuan. How could he have imagined that the other side would say 104 times. The amount of money to be paid out for that amount already broke the ten thousand range.

“104 times. If you don’t believe me, you can count. My recordings should be quite clear.” Mo Qiang replied and then sent another file over.

“Why did you send it again?” The manager was confused.

“It’s another file. 112 times.” Mo Qiang said.

“There’s more!” The manager cried.

“Of course.” Mo Qiang said.

The manager received it, while feeling astonished. This was already within the twenty thousand yuan range.

And then a third, a fourth, a fifth…...

“How many do you have?” The manager couldn’t believe his eyes.

“10 files for a total of 1500 times.” Mo Qiang replied.

“1500 times……. 150,000……” The manager was completely stunned. He stared at the files sent and didn’t know what to say.

“I’ll keep working hard!” Mo Qiang said.

“Uh…… wait. We’ll have to look over all of your videos before talking again.” The manager replied. 1500 times, 150,000 yuan, the number was so ridiculous that they seemed fake. The manager felt like he had encountered a scammer, so he had to verify it. As a result, he hastily called over people to watch the videos and confirm the number count.

Ten videos. Fifteen hundred kills. Even though he killed them five times in some of the videos, it wouldn’t be easy to look through them, especially since they had to check if he was hacking.

After working busily for the entire day, the specialists came to a conclusion: there were no problems with any of the videos.

“Are you joking!” The videos weren’t fake. Moreover, the manager had counted the number of kills, exactly 1500.

However, killing them that many times in an entire week only existed in theory. Anyone who understood anything about the game would know that something wasn’t right.

Even the video specialists expressed how even though the videos were clean, the content themselves………

The responsibility had exceeded this manager’s power. It was clearly a fraud, but there was no proof…...

1500 times meant that each player had died 300 times. 5 deaths 1 level, so 60 levels lost.

For five players to have lost 60 levels in one week……. If the five weren’t killing themselves on purpose, then only an idiot would believe it.

“This has to be fake!” The manager felt. Something so ridiculous didn’t need proof. However, he knew the other side must have understood this too, yet he still spoke so frankly. Why was he not afraid?

The manager felt like this issue was a bit complicated and he couldn’t make a rash decision. Moreover, he was just acting on behalf of others. This was something created by all of the Clubs, who had allied together. How could he represent all of the Clubs?

As a result, he decided to ask his boss for help. Anyone would immediately understand something so obvious! No one cared about the stuff on the surface. After all of the Clubs received this news, they pondered over whether there was something more to this.

They could already figure it out easily enough.

Because as everyone already knew, these five accounts were Heavenly Justice’s open accounts.

What were open accounts? Open accounts were accounts with no identity and could be sacrificed at any time. And now, these five accounts had been killed in such a way. Trying to level them back up would be nearly the same as leveling them from scratch. They could already be considered as trashed. However, the sacrifice was worth it! Five accounts, 150,000…...

Heavenly Justice had done it!

All of the guilds now thought that they were the perpetrators. Who would have thought that such a famous guild would do something so dirty.

The Clubs now had an even worse impression of Heavenly Justice. None of them had a good feeling about them ever since their eye-catching step onto the professional stage.

However, in the end……

“Give it to him!” The Clubs decided despite their anger. They weren’t angry towards the money, but rather this incident. They had been scammed.

However, when they thought of Heavenly Justice, everyone still felt cautious. If they prodded at them any further, who knew if they would do something in return. Heavenly Justice couldn’t be underestimated.

Give them the money. Leave it alone.

At the same time, they began to ponder whether Lord Grim or Deception would do the same. If they also let themselves die, then that would be even more disgusting.